Chapter 214: Young Miss

Stunned, Quinn John dropped his pen. He looked up at Laura and said, “Did Evan really say that? Did he really agree to this?”

Laura nodded and said, “Yes, Grand Duke Evan has agreed to it. He stated right at the beginning that he will help me manage the stores. When I looked at his expression and saw that he was earnest, I knew he didn’t wish to seize our stores. That was when I proposed to a 4:6 split, which he agreed to.”

Quinn John thought about it for a while, then nodded. “This is amazing, but you should have clearly explained the entire situation to Grand Duke Evan. Since the managers of our stores are our trusted subordinates, if we need them in the future then he must let them go.”

Laura understood what Quinn John meant. With regards to merchants, the need for talented individuals was very important. Since they needed to leave the Purcell Duchy and Aksu Empire and head to another country, they would need to continue to do business in order to live. Doing business with untrusted subordinates wouldn’t be good. This was Quinn John’s meaning.

Nodding, Laura said, “Please don’t worry, Grandpa Quinn John, I will tell him that later. As matters stand right now, however, we will need to change the contents of the letters.

Quinn John nodded. “Then let us have them come to Casa City all at once. Once they are here, we can explain the situation to them and let them make their preparations. I will send Searle to clean out the treasury and bring anything we need to pack up. Fortunately, Mister had sent us several of those Spatial Bags, else we wouldn’t be able to take much with us.”

Laura smiled wryly and turned to Quinn John. “How about my father?”

Quinn John forced a smile and said, “In his eyes, is there anything more important than his darlings? He’s going to pack up his darlings[1].”

Laura couldn’t help herself and smiled bitterly. She knew what Quinn John meant. Those ‘darlings’ Quinn John referred to were the magic array books Karen had collected throughout the years, along with several of his experimental notes and testing tools. These were all more important to Karen than anything else.

She looked at Quinn John as asked, “Quinn John, have you thought about where we will be going? Are we going to directly leave the Purcell Duchy?”

Quinn John placed his pen down and thought for a while, then said, “Leaving directly wouldn’t be good right now. We currently have two options. First is to move to the Beastfolk Prairies where we have several businesses set up. If we go to the Beastfolk Prairie now, then no matter if it’s the Markey Dell clan or Boric, neither are strong enough to directly contend with the Beastfolk Prairie’s strength. If we go there, then they wouldn’t dare to send out experts to deal with us. We should be safe there.”

Laura nodded. “There isn’t any problem with going to the Beastfolk Prairie, but we cannot stay there forever. We can also go to other places on the continent through the Beastfolk Prairie. There are three roads with the first being the Purcell Duchy. The second road leads to the Elven Forest[2], and the third is the sea route. Going back to the Purcell Duchy is definitely impossible, so that only leaves us with the Elven Forest and the sea route.

“The Elven Forest is the domain of the elves. With regards to them, they aren’t friendly with the other races. We don’t have much time on our hands, so we cannot prolong our actions, thus going through that route is not feasible. The last route, the sea route, is a dangerous one. Although the other countries can send trade fleets towards the Beastfolk Prairie, their trade fleets are easily exposed to pirate attacks. This also isn’t a feasible option. Is there any other way?”

Quinn John looked at Laura and smiled faintly. “There is another, more simpler way, and that is Zhao Hai. The matters this time won’t allow Zhao Hai to stay in the Purcell Duchy. Their identity would be exposed otherwise. I had heard, in the past, that the Buda clan’s misfortunes all stem from Boric. If they allow Boric to know they are here, then they will be in danger. Therefore, they will most certainly leave. Zhao Hai has a treasure that can be used to easily transport things, otherwise he wouldn’t have been able to so easily deliver food to the Purcell clan in their time of need. This time, we can go and find him. For sure, he will be able to take us to safety. However, that treasure may be an important clan treasure, so if he does use it for us, then there will be conditions attached.”

Laura couldn’t help but blush when she heard what Quinn John said. She remembered what ‘condition’ Zhao Hai had proposed to her before. If she wanted to know the true secret of the Buda clan, then she must marry Zhao Hai. With this thought, Laura couldn’t help but turn a deeper shade of red[3].

Quinn John smiled when he saw Laura’s reaction. For the condition Zhao Hai had told Laura, Quinn John knew of it. Laura’s many contacts with Zhao Hai had been something Quinn John had paid attention to. After all, for these past years, Zhao Hai had been the only real man Laura set her eye on. Therefore, every time Laura came back after visiting Zhao Hai, Quinn John would find the opportunity to ask Nier about what Zhao Hai said. As such, the condition Zhao Hai had stated to Laura was naturally passed to Quinn John.

When Laura saw Quinn John looking at her, she became even more red. She saw his expression and knew that Quinn John understood what she was thinking. It could only be Nier that told him.

She couldn’t blame Nier for telling Quinn John about this matter. Laura was just a bit shy about it. She was still a girl, after all. Furthermore, she really did have some interest in Zhao Hai. Yet, she was slightly afraid of meeting Quinn John’s eyes.

In the end, Laura clenched her teeth and said, “Alright, let’s go to Brother Hai so that we can leave with him. Furthermore, we can discuss the future whereabouts of Brother Hai. Later on, we will need to cooperate with him.”

After hearing what Laura said, Quinn John’s eyes shone brightly. He understood what she meant. It seemed Laura really did have feelings for Zhao Hai, since saying such things was equal to accepting Zhao Hai’s condition.

Actually, Quinn John quite liked Zhao Hai. Since he knew Zhao Hai possessed a mysterious Divergent Technique, his future was limitless. Moreover, since Laura would be with him, this made Quinn John very happy.

Laura looked up at Quinn John who smiled faintly and said, “Alright, we’ll finish packing up here and then go to Zhao Hai. Young Lady, it’s better to send a letter to Zhao Hai first and not just go directly.”

Nodding, Laura looked up at the sky and said, “I’ll write a letter and send it tomorrow. It’s quite late now, and we have to rest early. Oh, by the way. Grandpa Quinn John, we’ve forgotten something.”

“Forgotten what?” asked Quinn John.

Laura’s eyes flashed coldly. “We’ve forgotten about Alodia.”

Quinn John was stunned after he heard what Laura had said. His face sank as he said, “Yes, we’ve forgotten about his group, but I would still like to keep them. Contact Zhao Hai since he’s a Divergent Warlock. Although I don’t know what his Divergent Technique is, looking at all his undead, he possibly knows how to turn people into undead. If we can truly use these fellows by letting Zhao Hai turn them into undead, then that’ll be good.”

Laura didn’t oppose it since she had a mutual hatred against Carlo now. Incidentally, they also hated Alodia, so she naturally didn’t go against Quinn John’s words.

They discussed several more matters before finishing and going off to rest. None of them could afford to be flustered right now and instead should act normally. Otherwise, flaws might be discovered.

*    *    *    *    *

The next morning, Zhao Hai and the others got up early. After eating their breakfast, Zhao Hai led Green, Meg, and Shue of Ten-thousand Shadows towards Casa City.

When they arrived at Casa City, the city gates had just been opened. Zhao Hai immediately entered the city and went straight towards Faith Mansion. Since events were happening quickly, they didn’t want to lose much time.

Zhao Hai going towards Faith Mansion was something Laura had just found out. She was prepared to write a letter, but didn’t know Zhao Hai would arrive this early.

They welcomed Zhao Hai and his group into the study. Laura looked puzzledly at Shue of Ten-thousand Shadows and asked, “Brother Hai, this is?”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and said, “This is Shue of Ten-thousand Shadows. He was previously invited by Carlo to move against me, but has currently taken a blood oath to serve me. Miss Laura needn’t be worried.”

Laura was surprised for a moment, but immediately recovered and greeted Shue of Ten-thousand Shadows, who then hurriedly greeted her in return. Afterward, he moved back to his previous position behind Zhao Hai.

Zhao Hai turned his head towards Laura and said, “I came today to ask after your preparations. Also, have you told Evan about the situation clearly, and do you have any plans?”

Laura and Quinn John looked at one another, then Laura said, “I have already explained the matter to Grand Duke Evan. The Grand Duke said he cannot participate in this matter, but can keep our stores intact. We can keep the stores open and he’ll look after their management. I have reached an agreement with the Grand Duke to split the income, 4:6 — I will get 4 parts, he will get 6. I do hope, however, that Brother Hai won’t break off the Taoyuan supply.”

“That’s fine,” Zhao Hai replied. “There will be no problem in the supply of Taoyuan products. What’s more, you can retain your stores, which is for the best. I was really worried about this matter.”

Laura relaxed after hearing Zhao Hai’s reply. Her complexion couldn’t help but give off a happy glow as she said, “This time, we are prepared to leave the Aksu Empire. We must ask, however, if Brother Hai will be able to help us in delivering us to a safe place. What is Brother Hai’s intent?”

After hearing her words, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but be surprised for a moment. He looked at Laura’s blushing face and understood what she meant. Zhao Hai couldn’t help but tease her as he grinned and said, “There’s no problem in taking you to someplace safe, but Laura, do you agree to my conditions?”

As Zhao Hai spoke those words, Green and the others stared closely at Laura. They were waiting for her reply, which made her face even more red. She finally gathered herself up and gravely looked at Zhao Hai, saying, “Please, Brother Hai. Help me.”

After he heard what Laura said, Green couldn’t help it anymore and laughed. “Good, great! It seems like we’ll have to change what we call Miss Laura and instead call her Young Miss[4].”

Laura’s face became redder, and Zhao Hai also blushed. He didn’t think Laura would actually comply, so he felt a bit awkward. Behind that awkwardness, however, was a bit of excitement. Even if Laura wouldn’t have complied, he’d still have told her his secret. Now, however, since she did agree, it made things a lot better.

* * *

Footnotes:

[1]宝贝 – Bǎobèi. 宝 is treasure or jewels. 贝 is shells/seashells/valuables. 宝贝 can mean Babies, Treasure, Darling.

[2]精灵森林 – Jīnglíng sēnlín. Elven Forest.

[3]Now, while I’m all for Zhao Hai finally winning a person’s heart (loyalty/love, whatever) without having to use the space… he has so many red marks that I can’t drum up the support. Still hoping Cai’er can go ahead and take over… Bringing the Farm to Live in Another World, with the “Another World” being the Devil World now… Dun Dun DUUUUN.

[4]少夫人 – Shǎo fū rén. Shao is Young or Small. Furen is Husband’s person, or Madam, Mrs., Spouse, Partner, Lady. You get it. The options were Young Mistress, which is basically a woman in control, but Mistress has somehow been sullied to mean a woman in an extramarital affair with a married man. Madam sounds really old… I don’t wanna call Laura, Madam. Miss works. Lady has already been used. Mrs. is weird. Partner and Spouse aren’t things you say as a title.

Chapter 215: Do You Hate Me?

Quinn John sighed. Although he knew this day would come, it still made his heart uncomfortable. After all, he’d watched Laura as she grew up. Now, suddenly, she said she agreed to Zhao Hai’s condition to marry him. It was like saying she would leave him forever. It was a very uncomfortable feeling.

After a while, Zhao Hai calmed down. He looked at Laura and asked, “What else do you need to prepare? If you have anything you need to carry off, tell me and I’ll help you do so.”

When she heard what Zhao Hai said, Laura relaxed and said, “We’re almost finished tidying things up here. It’s really fortunate Mister gave us several of those Spatial Bags as they’re really helpful. Still, we’ll need a few more carriages in order to take away everything. Moreover, we need to explain several matters to the rest of our clan here, and that will take several days.”

Zhao Hai thought for a while before saying, “Alright then, we’ll stay here for a few days. Please arrange a room for us. When you finish whatever you have to do, we can leave together.”

Laura froze for a moment, then nodded and said, “Okay. The mansion has a guest room. You can stay there for the next few days.”

Nodding, Zhao Hai said, “You should speak to Evan. After we leave, he can send people to Stony Mountain every five days to get the commodities. Once they are at Stony Mountain, they just need to knock on the ground three times. We will arrive the next day and they can pick up the commodities from a warehouse. If they don’t knock, however, then they can’t get the products.”

Laura nodded. “Alright, I’ll tell him that. Also, I have some of Carlo’s subordinates held captive. I wish for them to pay for their crimes. What do you think?”

After thinking for a while, Zhao Hai said, “That’s fine. How do you want me to deal with them? Do you wish them to be silenced?”

Laura looked at Zhao Hai and sighed. “I don’t really want to silence them, but we can’t control them. The threat they represent is too large. While Alodia and his team have been obedient these past few days, we already have some sense of them. As such, I don’t trust them.”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “Alright, I understand. Hand them over to me and I’ll deal with them.”

Laura nodded. She turned to Nier and said, “Nier, take Brother Hai to his room to rest. Tend to whatever needs Brother Hai has.”

Nier complied and stepped up to Zhao Hai.

Zhao Hai stood and said to Laura, “This matter needs to be solved as soon as possible since Boric and the Markey Dell clan both have their eyes set on us. We will need to leave immediately.”

Laura nodded and Zhao Hai followed Nier.

After waiting for Zhao Hai to walk out, Laura turned her head towards Quinn John and said, “Grandpa Quinn John, we need to finish taking care of our issues as soon as possible. When the store managers arrive, we’ll tell them about everything and then we will need to leave immediately. What Brother Hai said about us not being safe now is correct.”

Quinn John nodded and said, “Relax, the matter of cleaning up here has already been assigned to Kiel[1] and the other trusted subordinates. Furthermore, they are determined to come with us, so rest assured. Oh, right. We forgot to ask Zhao Hai how many people we can take along. If he can take many people, then everything will be fine.”

Laura frowned. “I forgot to ask. Let’s talk about it at when it’s time to eat. Anyway, he’ll  be staying for the next few days, so there’s no need to worry.”

Quinn John nodded and gave a faint smile. “I noticed that Zhao Hai is very concerned about you. In fact, he’d probably take you in even if you didn’t accept his request.”

Laura paled as she glanced at Quinn John. Sighing, she said, “To be honest, I have a very good impression of Brother Hai. We’ve met with great misfortune at this time, and only Brother Hai could and would help us. Moreover, from our previous meetings he didn’t say much. He didn’t try to coax a girl with his words. The condition he put forward was actually a proposal in disguise. With his disposition, doing such a thing was already being forward. Why wouldn’t I comply?”

She relaxed. In all honesty, with her business running all year round, as well as the people she dealt with, Laura’s disposition was a great deal more open than Zhao Hai’s which was a bit nerdy. In terms of love, she was braver than Zhao Hai and dared to say what she liked and what she hated. Therefore, she accepted Zhao Hai’s condition.

Quinn John smile faintly. “I’m afraid you can’t see the point. Although Zhao Hai is good to you, he really isn’t good to others. He also isn’t very consistent with the rumors, the one where he’s said to be a dandy, yet now he isn’t. If you marry him, he’ll certainly be good to you. At least he’s stronger when compared to those other dandies, so I’ll feel more relieved.”

Laura snorted. “I’d rather find an honest man than a dandy if I could. Zhao Hai looks honest and capable, so I’ll choose him.”

Quinn John laughed and said, “Ah, you’re not a shy little girl anymore. You actually said those words.”

Laura had finally calmed down by now and chuckled. “This is what we call seizing the opportunity. If I miss this chance, then it would be an injustice. You might not have noticed, but that Meg has been covetously eyeing him at the same time.”

Quinn John and Laura smiled, and the depressing mood seemed to have dissipated from their hearts.

For the past few days, Laura had felt depressed. She had worked hard these last few years to lay down the foundations for her business, yet now they were forced to leave their homes. With the current situation, how could anyone describe the depression she felt.

Due to her mood influencing her, Laura had complied with Zhao Hai’s condition, a marriage proposal in disguise, in return for him rescuing her. She’d said words of compliance, and was now smiling. She had been suppressing the mood in her heart, most of which had already disappeared. Right now, she was thinking about Zhao Hai’s conditions. Since she complied with it, there didn’t seem to be anything harmful within it.

There was silence for a time, then Quinn John turned and looked at Laura. “Little Laura, you agreed to Zhao Hai’s condition, but you should be clear about some matters. Zhao Hai is the only successor to the Buda clan. As such, Green will certainly make Zhao Hai find other wives in order to increase the clan’s fertility. This will allow the Buda clan to grow branches and leaves and thrive. In the future, you will need to keep up with many women ready to rob your husband away.”

Laura sighed. “I know that, but there are few men who only have a single wife in their lifetime, especially aristocratic men. I like Brother Hai, and he also likes me. If, one day, he doesn’t like me anymore, then I’ll still earn my living. In any case, even if I don’t have any man in my life, it’ll still be the same since I can live without one.”

Quinn John sighed. This was a woman’s intolerance. On the Ark Continent, although women have the right to inherit and had standings similar to men, when you really looked back, women have a weaker status than men[2]. There wasn’t any law that could solve this matter.

After chatting for a bit, the store managers from Laura’s shops arrived in Casa City. Yesterday, Laura had sent letters to the store managers, telling them to come to Casa City because she had an important matter to discuss with them.

To the large merchant firms, they already knew Casa City was in a turbulent period. It was like some important matter was about to happen. Because of that, they didn’t feel it was strange when they saw Laura’s actions.

These store managers were the genuine aides trusted by Laura as she had personally trained them. They had obligations towards Laura and were therefore dead set on following her. Since Laura had called for them, they knew that an important matter had recently popped up.

After she called for them, they quickly arrived at Casa City. Those who came from afar rode wind chasing horses since late last night. They had tied several horses in order to lessen the need to make a stop and swap. Noon the following day, all store managers had arrived.

Laura didn’t immediately meet with the store managers. Instead, she first let them eat and rest till later in the day. At noon, she invited Zhao Hai to eat in the dining room.

The food served by Laura was quite different from what Stony Mountain had. They ate the best veal with other delicious dishes and also had very fine wine.

Zhao Hai, however, wasn’t used to eating such things and only ate the veal steak.

After their meal, Laura led Zhao Hai to the parlor room. Once they all sat down, Laura asked Zhao Hai, “Brother Hai, how many people can you help me take away? How many items? It’ll be easier for me to prepare if I know.”

Smiling, Zhao Hai said, “Relax. No matter how many items you wish to bring, you can bring them. The same goes for people. There is one thing you need to ensure, however. Those people must be completely trustworthy.”

When she heard Zhao Hai’s reply, Laura’s expression turned joyful. “Rest assured, they are all naturally trustworthy. Otherwise, exposing the Buda clan’s secret would be troublesome.”

Meg smiled and said, “Miss Laura hasn’t gotten married. Have you already started planning for the Buda clan? Isn’t the Young Miss getting anxious about this marriage?”

When they heard those words, Green and Quinn John both smiled.

Laura’s face reddened. She stared at Meg and said, “Hmph, you’re talking nonsense. I won’t let Brother Hai marry you.”

Meg’s face also reddened. She hadn’t thought Laura would unexpectedly see through her thoughts. Zhao Hai also didn’t think Laura would tease Meg like that and it made him embarrassed. He glanced at Green and said, “Grandpa Green, Grandpa Quinn John, everyone can leave first. I wish to talk to Laura alone.”

Green and Quinn John looked at each other simultaneously and both saw a happy expression on the other’s face as they turned and left. Zhao Hai and Laura were thus left alone in the room.

This was the first time Laura was alone with Zhao Hai. She was somewhat anxious as she looked at Zhao Hai; she didn’t know what Zhao Hai wanted to say.

Zhao Hai had an infatuated expression as he looked at Laura, which made her heart beat faster. After some time, Zhao Hai said, “Laura, do you hate me?”

Laura was surprised. She didn’t understand what Zhao Hai meant. They were now engaged, so how could he suddenly speak about hate?”

When he saw Laura’s puzzled look, Zhao Hai sighed and said, “If I didn’t appear, these matters wouldn’t have happened. You won’t be compelled to leave Casa City, to leave the Aksu Empire. You wouldn’t need to give up everything. Are you not angry?

“Earlier, you were right when you said I’d marry Meg in the future. We grew up together and she was beside me, taking care of me during the toughest time of my life. I won’t deny I have passionate feelings for Meg, but I also love you. Making me give up either of you is something I cannot do. Am I too greedy?”

* * *

Footnotes:

[1]基尔 – Jī ěr. Supposedly new? I couldn’t find him in the last 70 chapters we did… so meh.

[2]If I had to make a conclusion, then it should be because which gender would allow a clan to thrive? If the Buda clan only had a female who could inherit, then unlike Zhao Hai, she wouldn’t be able to marry a bunch of guys and give birth to a bunch of kids. At least, she can’t rival a male MC. Female bodies just don’t work like that. Honestly though, this is just dumb justification to make a harem.

Chapter 216: This Moment

Laura stared blankly at Zhao Hai. She didn’t think he would say that, which surprised her. All the same, she was moved by those words.

On the Ark Continent, there wasn’t a law that dealt with monogamy. If Zhao Hai wanted, he could definitely marry any woman he fancied. Laura accepted this idea completely as it was natural on the continent.

In Laura’s view, Zhao Hai’s words meant he truly liked her. Because he liked her, even loved her. Thinking that another person was in his heart felt as though he was betraying Laura. This had made him feel guilty, and that moved Laura the most.

Laura stood up and walked before Zhao Hai. She looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Brother Hai, I’m not blaming you for all of this. To be honest, I was afraid you wouldn’t accept me. After all, Meg has been with you since childhood. You know a great deal more about her. Furthermore, you are the Buda clan’s patriarch. As the only successor of the Buda clan, it’s impossible for you to marry only me if you take the clan’s future into consideration. I won’t oppose you marrying Meg. To be honest, Meg also likes you. I had seen this and prepared myself already. You don’t need to worry.”

Zhao Hai stared at Laura. He told Laura about these matters because he couldn’t cross that ridge in his heart all by himself. His world view had been formed from almost three decades of living on Earth. Don’t say he could just change his view, Zhao Hai truly felt affection for Laura and that had caused him to feel sorry towards her.

Now that he heard Laura’s feelings, Zhao Hai felt a bit better. He looked at Laura and pulled her into his arms. Laura was surprised, but didn’t resist. Instead, she gently leaned her head onto Zhao Hai’s chest. They didn’t speak, but during that moment, they both felt the other’s warmth.

After some time, Zhao Hai said to Laura, “Laura, I’m sorry for making you lose your business after you did everything you could to painstakingly take care of it. If it wasn’t for me, you wouldn’t have fallen to such a state today.”

Laura sat down and leaned against Zhao Hai’s arms. She looked at him and said, “Brother Hai, don’t say such things. I could have such success because of you. If not for you, it would have been impossible for me to achieve all I have today. Just as I said before, I am now your fiancee. If you’re going to be so polite towards me, I’ll be angry.”

Zhao Hai watched Laura’s expression and saw that she was only pretending to be angry. His heart was filled with warmth as he looked at her. Laura’s beauty, intelligence, and compassion all attributed to the warmth Zhao Hai felt. He was moved.

He couldn’t help but cling tightly to Laura, as if to crush her against his body. Laura felt his stirred emotions and smiled sweetly as she was held tight. At this moment, their hearts were tied together and couldn’t be separated.

With Zhao Hai’s intent, Laura and he moved and appeared inside the Spatial Villa. Laura suddenly felt her surroundings shift, as though she wasn’t in her study anymore. When she took a more curious look around, she truly did see that she wasn’t in her study.

Laura whispered uneasily to Zhao Hai, “Brother Hai, we’re in a strange place.”

Zhao Hai loosened his embrace of Laura and smiled faintly. “This isn’t a strange place[1]. It’s our Buda clan’s greatest secret. This is my domain.”

Surprise, Laura looked around puzzledly. Zhao Hai smiled and pulled Laura up. They then went out of the villa and looked at the prairie outside.

As Laura looked around, she found many fruit trees, bamboo rice plants, radishes, and other crops. Most importantly, she saw fire fishes within a hot spring.

Upon seeing these, the intelligent Laura immediately understood. This was where the Taoyuan products came from. But, she didn’t know where exactly they were.

Zhao Hai looked at Laura and smiled. “Do you now know why I said only through marriage would I tell you my greatest secret? It’s because of this place. This is the Divergent Technique I obtained. This entire Space is mine, and I am god here. When I plant crops here, such as fruit oil trees, they will mature in only a few days. Bamboo rice can mature several times a day. Furthermore, the water and soil from this Space can make the lands of the Black Waste arable enough to plant crops there. Lastly, placing undead in here will make them my summonable creatures. This is a world of infinite possibilities.”

Laura was confused as she looked around. While she could understand the explanation Zhao Hai gave, she couldn’t clearly process the whole of what he said. Some things were still unclear.

Seeing Laura’s expression, Zhao Hai smiled. “Simply put, this Space is like a Spatial Bag. This Space has its own separate and independent laws, but is also not a subspace. This Space instead coexists with the outside. Neither the outside nor the Space will affect one another[2]. In this Space, however, I am god.”

Laura stared emotionally at Zhao Hai. She now understood what he meant. This pleasant surprise was truly too large for her and she couldn’t believe it.

Zhao Hai looked at her and smiled. “Don’t be so surprised. This Space is the place where I produce the Taoyuan products. Others won’t be able to enter this place unless I allow them. This is our Buda clan’s greatest secret. If it is exposed, then there wouldn’t be a place for us on the Ark Continent.”

She nodded in agreement. “If this place is known, then you really wouldn’t be able to stay on the continent. Rest assured that I won’t say a word about this.”

Zhao Hai looked at Laura and smiled. “Even if you wanted to let this be known, it’s already too late. Remember, you’re now my fiancee. Haha.” He hugged Laura as he spoke those words.

Laura glanced snappily at Zhao Hai but didn’t say anything. She instead smiled as she knew Zhao Hai had already accepted her.

Zhao Hai led Laura around in order to help her familiarize herself with the situation of the Space. After a look at the ranch, they left the Space.

When they came back to Laura’s study, they called for Green and the others to come back. As they arrived, Green and the others saw that the two had a different air around them. A sort of understanding passed between them and they smiled. None of them asked the couple anything as it was a secret between the two of them.

Now that Laura knew of Zhao Hai’s ability, she had more confidence. After the noon meal, she immediately met with her people, the store managers. So long as she clearly explained the situation to them, the Higanbana stores would continue their normal operations.

In fact, this matter was rather simple. She simply told them that if any issues were to arise in the future, they could go to Grand Duke Evan and directly ask him for help. In order to keep a convenient mode of contact, Laura also told them of the Eagle Virtuous Phantasms. If Laura had any issues herself, she could send the Eagle Virtuous Phantasms to look for them. If the store managers needed Laura, they could just go to Stony Mountain.

After explaining the current situation to them, she moved on to the people of Faith Mansion. Not all of them would be going with her. Aside from Quinn John, Karen, Nier, and Kiel, they only allowed their most loyal servants come along. As for the others, if they wanted to become commoners, then they would receive severance pay. If they wanted to stay and work in the Higanbana stores, Laura could tell Evan of it.

They finished packing their things up as, later on, they wouldn’t be living in Faith Mansion anymore. These past couple of years, Laura had accumulated a great many good things. Since this was the case, she couldn’t let others take care of them for her. As such, she’d take them all away.

After eating dinner, Zhao Hai called for Karen, Quinn John, and Nier and had them gather in the study. He then led them into the Space. In any case, since they would be following Zhao Hai from now on, Zhao Hai wasn’t afraid to let them know his secret.

Karen was shocked when he arrived in the Space. This place had a very good environment. The first thing that came into his mind upon seeing his surroundings was that it would be a good place for his experiments. He immediately fell in love with the place and, without hesitating, occupied the basement of the Spatial Villa and set it up as his experiment room.

Zhao Hai had no way to make Karen’s account for the matter. To be honest, Zhao Hai really did admire Karen. Although in the eyes of everyone else, Karen’s research was useless, Zhao Hai saw that Karen’s value couldn’t be compared to others.

The Ark Continent was currently in the initial periods of magic and machine school of learning. Zhao Hai thought that the unfolding future would be dependent upon people like Karen. As such, Karen’s approached to matters was something Zhao Hai allowed without regret.

Zhao Hai also brought Quinn John and the others to Fort Iron Mountain. This was, after all, their rear base. As such, he must let Quinn John and the others know of it.

He then led them back into the Spatial Villa to continue their discussion on what to take with them. Laura proposed a major move, which Zhao Hai and the others weren’t opposed to.

If it wasn’t for Zhao Hai’s Space, then Laura wouldn’t be able to take away so many things. Since Zhao Hai did have the Space, however, Laura was confident that she wouldn’t need to lose anything. After she moved the things out of Faith Mansion, she only left a few things there and didn’t remove them. She them began to purchase a great deal of basic necessities.

Naturally, it was impossible to leave with a lot of things from the Higanbana stores. Laura’s intent was to slowly move things one after another to Faith Mansion, then move them into Zhao Hai’s Space.

As a result, there was a great deal to prepare, so they had to push the time allotted to them before they could leave. Fortunately, Laura had given the Higanbana stores to the Purcell clan. Since the Higanbana stores were now completely handled by the Purcell clan, many of the things she took away would be deducted from her part of the store income.

Laura took these things away for not only her use, but for trading within the Beastfolk Prairie. Zhao Hai had asked Laura about her plans earlier and she said she’d already established a business there. The issue Zhao Hai wanted to discuss was the matter of trading inside the Beastfolk Prairie, so he told Laura about it. She naturally agreed and this was the reason they’d bought a lot of commodities.

* * *

Footnotes:

[1]It is. It’s where you kidnap people and brainwash them to serve you.

[2]Simplified. Both this Space and outside space exist at the same time. Unlike a subspace which is cut from the space outside, the Space here wasn’t made from the outside space. Neither space will affect one another easily, so most likely he means that unless he—or Cai’er—wills it, no attack can damage it.

Chapter 217: Poison

Ten days. For an entire ten days, the people of Casa City watched as various commodities streamed towards Faith Mansion. The whole of Faith Mansion seemed like a giant beast that ate and ate without worry about being full. It just kept devouring things and never let any of it out.

Although the people of Casa City felt it was strange, they didn’t say anything. Laura, on the other hand, selected those items with a great deal of discretion. Aside from the belongings taken from Faith Mansion, there were commodities that would be of use within the Beastfolk Prairie.

One must know that there were many commodities within Casa City that weren’t suitable for trade within the Beastfolk Prairie. This was due to the fact that the needs of the beastfolk were different from the needs of Casa City commoners.

It was because of this that Laura’s actions didn’t cause much change in the prices of the Purcell Duchy’s daily necessities market. Furthermore, those firms were more than willing to sell their wares to Laura.

The hands of those large firms weren’t necessarily clean. When they did business with the beastfolk, they resorted to smuggling. This matter was something they always did, so when they saw the items Laura had bought, they understood Laura’s intentions. They didn’t stop her. Although they wouldn’t earn much by selling to her, it was still an instant transaction. These were also goods that could be quickly transported from the back, so there wasn’t anything strange about it.

On the tenth day after Zhao Hai’s arrival in Casa City, Zhao Hai, Laura, Quinn John, and Green had all gone to Laura’s study.

Laura received a report about their current situation. With that in her hands, she faced the others and said, “I just received a report with regards to the situation in the Purcell Duchy. Today, a few mercenaries entered the Purcell Duchy from the back. They’re moving towards Casa City and have unknown intentions.”

Quinn John snorted coldly. “It’s nothing unclear. They’re here to deal with us. Since they definitely know Zhao Hai is also in Casa City, they want to deal with all of us in one go.”

Green nodded. “I also think this is the case. Let them come. We’ll tidy them up before withdrawing immediately. I want to see what they can give us.”

Laura turned towards Zhao Hai and said, “Brother Hai, what about resolving Alodia’s matter? Why haven’t we moved on them these last few days?”

Zhao Hai nodded. “I need to resolve them. These past few days, they found out too much. I wasn’t resolved to killing them since I didn’t want to kill those who don’t have the power to fight back, but I have no choice now.”

When Zhao Hai said this, Laura and the others understood. Zhao Hai needed to find an excuse for himself, an excuse that allowed him to kill them.

This behaviour might seem ridiculous and self-deceiving. On the other hand, this behaviour also had some good points. At least it would allow them to feel a bit better.

*    *    *    *    *

After eating their evening meal, Alodia and the others returned to their rooms. All of their weapons had been taken away. Through their observations these last few days, Alodia understood that Laura had the determination to kill them.

Unfortunately, Alodia couldn’t do anything. They didn’t have any weapons and were surrounded by all those undead. No one could escape from such a thing.

All they could do was stay in their room honestly. If Laura really wanted to kill them, then all they could do was go all out against her.

Sadness. Alodia felt unprecedented sadness. He was thinking about how high-spirited he had been before. No matter where he went within the Aksu Empire, so long as he revealed his identity as Carlo’s subordinate, no one would dare to undermine him. Now, however, he had fallen into a situation where he could only wait for his death. It was like he were a blue-eyed rabbit taken to the slaughterhouse, waiting as they readied their knives. This was a very unpleasant feeling.

He was thinking of resisting, but it would be of no use. No matter how restless they became, the undead could easily contain them. So long as they approached the undead, they would immediately be attacked. They wouldn’t even attack to kill, instead, they’ll be disabling them twice before tossing them back into the courtyard. It was as simple as that.

If they were dealing with humans, then Alodia could have tried to communicate with them. He could have tried to take advantage of them and have them spare his life. Right now, however, they were not dealing with humans, but undead. He wouldn’t even waste his breath with them—undead couldn’t be bought. Even if he had all kinds of schemes, they wouldn’t be tricked.

These last few days, Alodia looked aged as his spirit was constantly tormented. He didn’t expect such a day would come. What’s more, he never would have thought Laura would be the one to hold them. She could easily kill them at any time.

Alodia, however, still held some faith within him. For the past several days, he firmly believed that Carlo would send people to rescue him. As Carlo’s most trusted aide, Alodia was clear about some matters. Behind Carlo wasn’t only the Markey Dell clan, but also Southern King Boric. At this crucial moment, Carlo would certainly ask Boric to move. This was what Alodia’s spirit was hanging onto.

For the last few days, Alodia had been diligently gathering information about Laura. This was possible to do so long as they didn’t leave the front gate of the yard—they could still move around inside Faith Mansion freely. Alodia wanted to collect information about Laura that could be of some use in the future.

Laura’s actions these last few days were clear to Alodia since he could see her movements. This had boosted his confidence to go on living. What Laura had shown clearly stated that they were going somewhere else, that they had to run. There was only one explanation for this: enemies had come.

He knew Laura had one enemy, and that was Carlo. Since he saw this, his determination to live was strengthened.

At the same time, Alodia noted several warehouses in the rear yard of Faith Mansion. Seemingly, these warehouses were constantly being filled. Carriages continued to pull up and fill the warehouse with commodities, but it was like the warehouse was a bottomless pit.

Alodia didn’t suspect the use of spatial equipment within the warehouse. He instead thought that there was a secret passage inside. That they were using that to ship commodities out. He secretly wrote this down in order to inform Carlo.

Alodia knew, however, that this would be difficult. He knew Laura wouldn’t let them off. Since he was able to notice the commodities entering Faith Mansion, he knew Laura didn’t try to avoid their attention. As such, he knew Laura decided not to let them off. Yet, he was still holding onto the belief that, somehow, they would be able to go on living.

That night, as per usual, Alodia observed and counted. Since the time Laura had begun transporting commodities into Faith Mansion till now, it had been a full ten days. It wasn’t an exaggeration to say that the amount of commodities was enough to fill the whole of Faith Mansion. Oddly, everything that entered Faith Mansion seemed to have disappeared. Alodia didn’t truly understand how Laura was able to move those things.

Alodia lay quietly on the bed, thinking about Laura’s recent actions. He didn’t understand why Laura was doing such things so suddenly. Why did she suddenly dare to challenge Carlo. Who was it that she depended on? Was it only due to the virtue of Evan’s few words? That’s highly unlikely, no?

As he thought about this, Alodia suddenly smelled a fragrance. The smell grew stronger and stronger until he found it difficult to breathe. Alodia woke up fiercely. He wanted to jump out of bed and tell everyone that Laura was poisoning them.

Even though his mind issued the jump, his body wasn’t able to carry it out. His body felt as though it weighed half a ton[1]. He wanted to shout, but found that he couldn’t, that it was too strenuous to do so. Alodia couldn’t help but marvel at what kind of poison this was. It was truly too fierce. These were his last thoughts.

*    *    *    *    *

This poison was naturally derived from the toxin of the seven-coloured flower. It was Zhao Hai who had Cai’er place this poison. Since Alodia and his team had to die without much noise, Zhao Hai decided to let Cai’er use the poison.

The poison taken from the toxin of the seven-coloured flower was further strengthened due to the Space. Compared to how it was before, it wasn’t only just formidable. Before, it could be regarded as a simple chronic poison. Now, however, it was merged with the toxicity from the Space’s pesticide and could now be described as highly poisonous.

That night, the silent execution of Alodia and his team didn’t cause too much noise. Zhao Hai turned them into undead afterwards. Unfortunately, Alodia didn’t seem to know much. Aside from his knowledge of the relationship between Carlo and Boric, Lycra knew more than him.

Although Alodia shared some information on Carlo’s situation, this wasn’t very important to them. Compared to the powerful Southern King Boric, Carlo was, at best, a jumping clown.

On the eleventh day, Laura didn’t transport anything to Faith Mansion. The commodities they’d transported the last several days had already been excessive and might soon affect the necessities market within the Purcell Duchy. Laura didn’t want to offend the Purcell clan in their last moments.

Laura started to send people away. If they wanted to be free commoners, Laura gave them severance pay and allowed them to go home. The rest were the most loyal part of her subordinates and would follow Laura. Quinn John had already counted them before and, altogether, they amounted to a total of fifty-four people. Twenty-two of them were warriors while the rest were slaves Laura had bought when she first started out in the Purcell Duchy.

These people weren’t stewards and the matters they handled couldn’t be considered important. On the other hand, it could be said that they were the most loyal of her subordinates. Three of them were carpenters, and another three were blacksmiths. There were also six who were specialized in raising magic beast, also called grooms if they were on Earth.

Besides those people, the remaining individuals were clan members. The men were generally servants while the women were maidservants or cooks.

Adding in Laura, Quinn John, Nier, Karen, Kiel, and Searle[2], there were a total of sixty people joining the Buda clan. Starting today, they were no longer members of the Markey Dell clan, but people of the Buda clan.

* * *

Footnotes:

[1]千斤 – Qiānjīn. 1000 jin, with Jin being half a Kilogram. As such, I just stuck with “half a ton”, a ton being 1000 Kilograms. Just sounds better. 500 Kilograms is about 1100 pounds.

[2]It’s either Searle or someone new named Sean… 肖恩 – Xiào ēn, are the characters.

Chapter 218: Wait[1]

After everyone finished preparing, Zhao Hai took them away. Laura, Green, Quinn John, Nier, and Meg, however, stayed back in Faith Mansion along with Zhao Hai.

They were waiting, not for anyone else but Carlo’s people. How many of his men were currently in Casa City? They would tidy them up before leaving.

Right now, they were forced to leave Casa City and the Purcell Duchy. They’d suppressed that anger in the heart, but if they couldn’t vent, then it would become very uncomfortable.

Zhao Hai knew that in two days time, those mercenaries would arrive in Casa City. When that time comes, they would make their move. For the past two days, they lived honestly. They were in seclusion, the gates of Faith Mansion completely closed as they declined any visitors. Nobody came in or out. Compared to the busy atmosphere from before, it seemed like another world.

Even though the forces within Casa City thought it was strange, they weren’t too surprised as Laura had sent away many of her people. They thought she’d already secretly left with the supplies stored in Faith Mansion. The large firms didn’t care much. For large merchants like Laura, they each had one or two of their own secrets. Commodities could easily be moved through a secret passage.

Big firms had big businesses as their livelihoods. The top merchant firms on the continent created headquarters within major cities and made secret passages to move from inside the city to outside. This was an open secret, and no one would know how vast the passages were or where they led to.

It could be said that these passages were secrets the large merchant firms used to maintain their livelihoods. They were the clans’ most valued secrets. Nobody knows of it except the core members of the clan. This was why the large firms weren’t that concerned about the whereabouts of those commodities.

Conversely, Laura’s actions made those firms think of another point. One must know that the secret passages were used as a clan’s final lifeline. So long as one didn’t face a life and death crisis, one wouldn’t use it. With Laura moving through the secret passage, it showed that they were facing a situation. This puzzled those who didn’t know of Boric.

The large firms thought Laura’s retreat was due to the Purcell clan withdrawing their support of her. Because of that, Laura couldn’t stand against the Markey Dell clan, so she decided to give up on everything and prepare to leave.

Those large firms, however, still didn’t make a move against Laura. In their opinion, although the Purcell clan wouldn’t help Laura, they still thought she wasn’t affable. A few days ago, Zhao Hai had entered Faith Mansion and hadn’t left. They had seen how formidable Zhao Hai was. With that recognition, they didn’t want to offend such a powerful black magician.

Laura’s stores were still continuing their business. Nobody dared to grab those businesses because the Purcell clan had made a public statement that said she’d transferred the Higanbana stores over to the Purcell clan. From now on, they were a part of the Purcell clan.

The large firms attached great importance to this news. Higanbana stores now controlled 40% of the Purcell Duchy’s daily necessities market. This was really too high. Laura had cooperated with the Purcell Duchy before, so she hadn’t been suppressed. Now, however, it was different. Those shops were now owned by the Purcell Duchy. In other words, within the Purcell Duchy, the Purcell clan now controlled the bulk of the daily necessities market. Wishing to storm into this line of business in the future would be impossible.

Since they knew Laura had to leave, they didn’t feel in the mood to pay her any attention. Instead, they placed their attention towards the Higanbana stores. The Higanbana commodities had been turned over to the Purcell clan. Future changes to the daily necessities market within the Purcell Duchy would be difficult to foresee.

The mercenaries didn’t let Laura and Zhao Hai wait too long. On the fifteenth day, the mercenaries entered Casa City.

When they entered Casa City, the Purcell clan set their eyes on them. They had to know what movements the mercenaries would make and report it to Laura. Evan had felt quite guilty towards Laura, and thus wanted to compensate by doing something for her.

Laura was grateful with regards to Evan’s good intentions. Although she had her own intelligence network, she didn’t move them. After all, the Higanbana stores had already been given over to the Purcell clan. She’d make the Purcell clan unhappy with her petty actions. As such, she’d wait for the gust of wind to cross first. Then she’d make use of her intelligence network at that time.

These days, Laura didn’t idle. Those that were willing to leave with her were sent to Fort Iron Mountain. Zhao Hai hadn’t intended to place humans at Stony Mountain, so Cai-er had withdrawn her seven-colored flowers and vines. Furthermore, the black fog had dispersed. But since it was still a known domain of Zhao Hai, no one dared to go up because of his reputation.

As a place where a black magician had stayed, not many had the guts to venture there. They feared the toxins. Other than that, there was a stipulation set for an individual’s property. This stipulation had defined provisions. For example, Zhao Hai bought Stony Mountain, so if anyone broke into it there would be repercussions and Zhao Hai could kill them.

They weren’t afraid that those sent to Fort Iron Mountain would run away. Even if there was a spy among them, Zhao Hai wasn’t scared. Outside of Fort Iron Mountain were undead defending the area, along with Eagle Virtuous Phantasms patrolling the skies. Simply put, even if they knew of the situation within Fort Iron Mountain, it was simply impossible for them to pass on the news.

Moreover, these past few days, Laura had arranged for the things she’d moved from Faith Mansion to be placed in Fort Iron Mountain. The problem was that Faith Mountain wasn’t small and there were many good things in there. Zhao Hai hadn’t decorated Fort Iron Mountain before, so there were only a few simple furnitures placed within and it looked very rough. Since Laura now transferred her items over from Faith Mansion, Fort Iron Mountain exuded a little more of a noble’s aura.

During their wait, Zhao Hai led Laura and the others around and let them adjust and understand the situation within Fort Iron Mountain. He brought them to the tarn and mine tunnels where he raised the rabbits. Quinn John and Laura sighed and sighed after seeing those places. They hadn’t expected Zhao Hai to have achieved so much in such a short period of time.

Zhao Hai didn’t hide the truth from them and led them to the Space Ranch in order to check it. It was now Level 5. We can say it was now Level 5 due to Laura. Previously, Laura gave Zhao Hai many magic beasts that he then raised within the Space. Some of those were many-legged insects[2] or long-haired swine[3].

With the help of those, Zhao Hai’s ranch was upgraded. Furthermore, he could now raise a hundred more animals, which made Zhao Hai happy. He immediately raised a number of those long-haired swines.

The Space’s rating for those long-haired swines was Level 4 magic beast. Outside the Space, however, it was given a rating of Level 1 since it had no aggressiveness and was known as the continent’s most common carnivore[4].

Zhao Hai didn’t raise many of the long-haired swines since the Higanbana stores weren’t something Laura considered anymore and was just being managed by the Purcell clan. Zhao Hai raised them for the purpose of providing meat and saving for future use.

Laura and the others now had quite a good understanding of the Space after several days of observation. In regards to the Space’s magical items, they had become used to them. The most free and unfettered of them now, however, was Karen.

After taking over the basement of the Spatial Villa, Karen made it his experiment room and rarely came out. He was busy doing experiments inside and once he tired out, he’d pass out asleep or take a stroll outside in the prairie. He was completely loose and unburdened and passed the days comfortably.

In Zhao Hai’s view, Karen was simply more of an otaku than himself when he was on Earth. He stayed home all the time and never went out. Aside from eating and sleeping, he would mostly be staying inside his experiment room. When he was tired, he’d just take a short stroll but never said anything about leaving the Space.

In Karen’s words, he didn’t like to see many people. Back in Faith Mansion, he didn’t leave the mansion and only went in and out of his room when he was tired. He’d also walk around in the courtyard, but never passed the gates of Faith Mansion.

When Zhao Hai heard him, he became speechless. Karen was simply a higher quality otaku. He also wanted higher quality goods than Zhao Hai.

Zhao Hai was tolerant. Wanting an otaku to contact the outside was a very difficult thing to do. Not to mention that Karen was focused on his research, so he was that kind of otaku. Making him get involved with others and wanting him to change was too difficult.

Zhao Hai didn’t want him to change anyway. Now that Space had grown, he could go out and stroll around whenever he wanted. Not wanting to leave his room was alright as well since the air within the Space was good. He didn’t need to fear any dangers occurring and it was actually good for his body to stay inside the Space[5].

Zhao Hai didn’t inquire into Karen’s experiments. Even if he did ask, he wouldn’t be able to understand it anyway. What Karen researched were magic arrays and formations. Although Adam had known about magic in the past, he didn’t dabble in magic arrays and formations. It was due to his ignorant and incompetent disposition back then. Nowadays, Zhao Hai was also busy and didn’t have the time to study such things, so he didn’t understand them.

In the end, he had people keep watch over Faith Mansion. This was due to Evan occasionally sending them information. Zhao Hai and the others were counting on this information.

The info they received today was very simple. This evening, the mercenaries would attack Laura. Moreover, the mercenaries had visited Evan and told him to not interfere with their matters tonight.

Originally, Evan had wanted to scold those people. He endured their tone in the end, for the Purcell clan. Evan, however, told them to not make any large moves, else he would be impolite.

* * *

Footnotes:

[1]Otherwise known as the ultimate filler chapter.

[2]多足虫 – Duō zú chóng. Many/Multi. Legged/Foot. Insects/Worm/Invertebrate.

[3]长毛猪 – Cháng máozhū. Long. Hair/Fur. Swine/Hog/Pig. Think of a really hairy pig…

[4]It’s either 食肉动物 – Shíròu dòngwù which is Carnivore, or the author somehow means the literal characters, which is 食, Food, 肉, Meat, and 动物, Animal. So meat animal? I dunno.

[5]Ultimate NEET world.

Chapter 219: Black Magician Alliance[1]

With the information she held in her hands, Laura smiled wryly and said to Zhao Hai, “This situation is somewhat difficult to handle. Boric even told the Purcell clan to not interfere with what’s going to happen tonight, and the Purcell clan agreed. Luckily, Grand Duke Evan is a good person, else he would just pretend to cooperate with us, but is in fact working with Southern King Boric to deal with us. Even if we have Brother Hai’s Space, I fear it will be difficult to escape this unharmed.”

Quinn John nodded as he understood what Laura meant. Although Zhao Hai had the Space, if not for Evan being in an alliance with them, Zhao Hai wouldn’t have been able to travel to Casa City. If not for all of these matters being pushed forward, Zhao Hai and Laura wouldn’t have come to such a result.

These kinds of feelings required a due process. Love at first sight. Such a thing only existed in legends. Even if there was truly such a thing, it wouldn’t have been borne within Zhao Hai and Laura’s bodies.

What was undeniable was the fact that Zhao Hai had saved Laura’s life. This had created a favorable impression of Zhao Hai from Laura. Zhao Hai, on the other hand, also had a favorable impression of Laura, and this was somewhat due to her likeness of Taylor Swift[2]. Aside from that, Laura had helped him a lot by selling the crops he harvested from within the Space. This was equal to helping Zhao Hai in a big way and deepened his impression of Laura.

Although they had a very good impression of each other, the time they’d spent with one another was still too short to reveal much. Now, however, they were being forced to leave their homes and face an unclear future. This was a person’s most vulnerable time, and was also a time where sentiment can be easily built up. They would be more impulsive and even the smallest of emotions could be boundlessly enlarged.

Zhao Hai and Laura had a mutually favorable impression of one another. Adding their emotions to this fact, and the couple had sparked something to life. Their hearts and minds were open to the other and had reached this current stage.

Now, after deciding upon this matter, Zhao Hai and Laura were able to confidently face the opposing party. Their feelings have already reached the destination and their hearts have already recognized the other as their lover. This naturally calmed them and made them more confident.

Individuals were like this. When things happen, their hearts would feel uneasy and cower easily in the absence of positivity. When they truly faced something head on, however, and solved the matter, they would naturally feel more confident.

All that had happened were a series of coincidences. If not for Carlo pressing harder and harder, some of this may not have been borne. Even if it did, it wouldn’t have been so quick. One could say that Carlo’s actions had been the catalyst that sped up this relationship.

Zhao Hai smiled lightly. “No wonder Evan, though he has a large clan, is still able to manage it. He has achieved this degree of power and is still good. After all, unlike us, he didn’t have to give up everything here and leave the Aksu Empire. So long as he is still within the Aksu Empire, he has no choice but to give Boric several points of face. This, however, doesn’t apply to us. As such, we can just deal with this attack.”

Laura faintly smiled. “Yes, we can deal with it. These days there has been a foul air. The feelings in my heart haven’t yet been released.”

Quinn John and the others smiled. They weren’t afraid of the oncoming attacks at all. Even though they could also be attacked by strong Rank Nine experts, they also had two of their own Rank Nine experts. So long as the black smog continued to cover Faith Mansion, people on the outside wouldn’t be able to see what happened within. With this, they could openly fight.

Boric, however, probably didn’t dare to truly send Rank Nine experts to Casa City just to chase them down. If he really did send one, then it would be equal to giving no consideration for the Purcell clan’s face. This would cause the Purcell clan’s Rank Nine expert to be impolite.

There was an unwritten rule within the continent. For a city guarded by a Rank Nine expert, other Rank Nines weren’t allowed to enter without a reason. Otherwise, it would be seen as a challenge towards the guarding Rank Nine expert.

Although the Purcell clan was still uncertain of Wind Saint Buffy’s fate after he’d entered the Carrion Swamp, they still had the Universal Origin Sword Saint to assume command. The Universal Origin Sword Saint was very famous within the continent. Most wouldn’t dare to stroke a tiger lightly.

It was precisely due to this that Zhao Hai wasn’t worried. So long as there wasn’t a Rank Nine expert, Green could just deal with them. As such, they needn’t be afraid.

Just then, Green’s complexion suddenly changed. With a cold voice, he said, “You out there, come out. Otherwise, don’t blame me for being impolite.”

A gloomy voice sounded, “You are indeed ferocious. Worthy of being a peak Rank Eight expert to be able to see through my Ghost Sneaks Technique[3].”

Upon hearing the voice, Zhao Hai immediately stood up. Meg took out her Sealed Magic Iron Tome and cast a great deal of light element protection magic upon Zhao Hai. Quinn John also moved to protect Laura’s back.

Green stared at a corner of the room and coldly said, “Rank Eight black magician. A powerful existence has suddenly appeared. It’s a pity you aren’t all that proficient in using the Ghost Sneaks Technique.”

Ghost Sneaks Technique was an advanced level black magic. This magic was mainly used for assassination or for running away from an enemy. This was a specialized black magic technique and there was no way for other magicians to learn it.

This Ghost Sneaks Technique, once used, allowed one to become invisible like a ghost and stop others from feeling their existence. Due to these characteristics, it was called Ghost Sneaks Technique.

Green had, however, seen this Ghost Sneaks Technique before. On the battlefield, the opposing force would do anything to kill the other side. Green became famous and was known as the Spiritwind Battle General during such a time. As such, assassinations aimed for his life was a common occurrence. This Ghost Sneaks Technique was something he’d witnessed several times. This had caused him to become experienced in its use, otherwise he’d have been unable to detect the presence of the black magician just now.

As soon as the person heard what Green said, he chuckled a few times. Although it was a laugh, there was a gloomy air about it. It didn’t weaken the sound, but it did make them feel uncomfortable.

As the laughter echoed, a man slowly emerged. He wore a black magic robe that looked a bit old and held a wooden magic staff. Although it was made of wood, it was completely black. At two meters long, it was covered in many strange symbols and the head of the staff was carved into an odd shape. It looked very strange.

Green looked coldly at the person and said, “Who are you? Who sent you?”

The black magician smiled and bowed to them. “Please allow me to introduce myself. This one is an elder of the Black Magician Alliance, Maru[4].”

Zhao Hai and the others looked puzzledly at Maru. This was the first time they had heard of this so-called Black Magician Alliance. Don’t even mention Zhao Hai, the well-informed Laura also hadn’t heard of such an alliance on the continent.

Maru obviously saw their puzzled looks and faintly smiled. “I see everybody hasn’t heard of the Black Magician Alliance, but this isn’t surprising. The establishment of the Black Magician Alliance dated back only five years ago. As such, besides the black magicians that have joined, nobody else knows of the organization’s existence.”

Green knitted his brow and said, “Don’t waste your breath with so many words. Just tell us your purpose for coming here.”

Maru wasn’t angry. Instead, he smiled faintly and turned to Zhao Hai. “I came here this time to invite Mister Zhao Hai to join the Black Magician Alliance.”

As soon as Zhao Hai and the others heard what Maru said, they all gawked. Zhao Hai looked at Maru and asked with confusion, “What is the reason for inviting me?”

Maru smiled and said, “Please allow me to sit before explaining.”

Aside from appearing without warning in the beginning, Maru’s words had been very polite and he seemed like a gentleman. Zhao Hai and the others’ vigilance within their hearts had lowered. With Green’s presence, Zhao Hai wasn’t worried about his own security, so he let Meg put away her Angel of Protection[5] and allowed Maru to sit down.

After he sat down, Meg gave Maru a cup of tea. Maru’s expression showed politeness and this made Zhao Hai curious about him. From the beginning until now, Maru’s performance gave off the air of a noble, one that was a great deal higher in status than him who was just an ungraceful aristocrat.

Maur sipped his tea before placing the cup down. He looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Mister Zhao Hai is a black magician, so you should certainly feel that black magicians have been isolated on the continent. Walking outside is very inconvenient. Most feel badly of us and compare us to mercenaries, that is, killers, thieves, swindlers. They look at us as though we are evil, that we would eat humans at any time.”

With regards to this, Zhao Hai had felt it as well. Although it could be said that when a black magician arrived, no one would dare to annoy them, in truth it was just as Maru said. Black magicians were being pushed into isolation by the humans of the continent. In their eyes, black magicians were synonymous with evil, which wasn’t a good thing.

Maru saw Zhao Hai’s nod and continued, “In fact, it wasn’t like this in the beginning and people didn’t think of black magicians like that. Although black magicians are somewhat strange, we do develop pharmaceuticals and research black magic to treat people of their wounds in order to help them. We black magicians were once called creatures of the dark and were an indispensable part of an aristocrat’s or major force’s army. Our essential battle strength had made it so that none would dare go wild at night.”

This time around, it was Quinn John’s turn to nod. Quinn John had dealt with many people, so he knew what Maru said was true. Before, many aristocrats and countries tried to please black magicians. It was due to their characteristics of increasing their battle efficiency during the night that black magicians became an indispensable part of their army. As of now, however, most national armies didn’t have a single black magician within their ranks.

Maru watched them and the smile on his face grew larger. He quickly put away the smile and said to Zhao Hai and the others, “This situation, however, has slowly changed. I don’t know when such a rumor spread throughout the continent, but black magicians soon became a symbol of evil, the incarnations of devils. People slowly began to isolate the black magicians. At first, we didn’t realise the problem, but later on this became a very big issue and we had already been isolated from the people on the continent.

Here, Maru’s voice held a trace of heaviness. It was very obvious that the seriousness of the problem had exceeded his imagination. As such, he became very solemn.

* * *

Footnotes:

[1]黑魔法师联盟 – Hēi mófǎ shī liánméng. No real confusion here.

[2]Which makes every other reader go dull-eyed.

[3]幽灵潜行术 – Yōulíng qiánxíng shù. Ghost/Spectre. Sneak. Technique/Art/Method. I like the use of Ghost Sneaks cause it’s a rather nice image.

[4]玛鲁 – Mǎ lǔ.

[5]天使之护 – Tiānshǐ zhī hù. Questionable whether this is the actual technique name.

Chapter 220: Radiance Church[1]

An occupation, but isolated by all. This meant it would have no way to continue its existence and was destined to perish. An occupation needed to be inherited; what it needed were the people. This was the most important part, the people. Unfortunately, no one favored the occupation, so no one could continue it. An occupation that loses its inheritance is similar to a clan that loses its inheritance. Sooner or later, it would perish.

This was the reason why Maru was so serious about the matter. The inheritance of black magicians would be broken if no one was willing to become one. With regards to black magicians, this wasn’t good news.

Maru said, “Since this situation occurred, we immediately began to investigate. These rumors didn’t appear on the continent for no reason at all. It’s certain that some people were specifically aiming for this. After careful investigations, we found that the ones behind these rumors and promoting it amongst the people came from Radiance Church.”

To be honest, this answer wasn’t out of Zhao Hai’s expectations. On the continent, black magicians had been isolated, yet light magicians earned a great deal of respect. The reason for this status was their extermination of black magicians everywhere.

If these rumors were said to be unrelated to light magicians, then no one would believe it. Yet, for those in power, this issue didn’t harm them. Radiance Church’s religious doctrine stated that the commoners shouldn’t bitterly stand against their rulers and stay in their status quo. The reasoning given by Radiance Church’s religious doctrine was that by going against them, you would suffer hardship and wouldn’t even be able to enter heaven after death.

What is heaven? Nobody has seen it, but the Radiance Church’s religious doctrine states that it is a world of beauty. It is a place where people didn’t need to do anything, yet would be able to eat good food and wear extravagant clothes.

Without a doubt, such a doctrine was favored by those in charge and wouldn’t be opposed by many who ruled countries. As such, Radiance Church missionary work went unimpeded and they continually suppressed the black magicians while also taking an uncaring attitude to everything else.

Maru looked at Zhao Hai and found that he didn’t look that surprised. He smiled bitterly as he ridiculed himself. He’d observed that these people already knew of this issue. Zhao Hai and the others looked as though they’d already guessed this before while those on Maru’s side had spent so long to come to such a conclusion.

Maru smiled bitterly and said, “It was due to this insight that the black magicians set up their own organization, the Black Magician Alliance. There are two main purposes for this organization. First is to oppose the Radiance Church. The second is to pass down the magical techniques of black magicians.”

Zhao Hai nodded and looked Maru in the eye. “So this is the reason you looked for me? To have me join the Black Magician Alliance because I am a black magician?”

Maru nodded. “Yes, it is because you are also a black magician. A black magician like you will certainly be hunted down by the Radiance Church. Some time ago, Garan[2] had tried to harm you. It was actually the Radiance Church that sent him to deal with you. Furthermore, you still do not know how strong the Radiance Church is. Their power is a great deal stronger than what was displayed back then.”

Zhao Hai and the others looked at Maru, who also looked back at them. “You may not believe it, but right now, many small duchies are currently being directly controlled by the Radiance Church,” Maru said with a cold voice. “Furthermore, Southern King Boric is a Protector Knight[3] of the Radiance Church and was also ordered to deal with you. So aside from Carlo, this was definitely due to the Radiance Church.”

This was contrary to what Zhao Hai and everyone else anticipated. They didn’t think that the powerful and influential Southern King Boric would willingly become a Protector Knight of Radiance Church. This truly surprised them.

Maru looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Don’t be so surprised. Radiance Church is composed of three divisions. First are the various archbishops headed by the Pope. Next are the Protector Knights of the Round Table Knight Order[4]. The last division are those who follow the teachings of suffering monks and make up the Monk Order[5], and the three groups are relatively independent of one another.

“The main task of the Pope is to manage the daily operations of the church. The Round Table Knight Order protects the church while the Monk Order’s main duties constitute missionary work.”

Zhao Hai and the others listened quietly. Hearing such a detailed explanation from Maru showed that they hadn’t been investigating Radiance Church for only a few days. It seemed like the phrase, “the person you understand the most is your enemy,” wasn’t wrong.

Maru continued, “Although the Pope manages the daily operations of Radiance Church, he doesn’t have the power to control the Round Table Knight Order, nor the Monk Order. The knights within the Round Table Knight Order of Radiance Church are in fact made up of members that are powerful figures of various countries. The identity of each individual isn’t simple and they manage the Round Table Knight Order, which is similar to managing the entirety of the church’s armed forces.

“The Pope, in addition to managing the daily affairs of his archbishops, also controls some of the church’s outside powers, such as a few assassin organizations and mercenary groups. Compared to these two, the Monk Order seems relatively weaker, but could be considered Radiance Church’s most devout followers. They generally wear coarse clothing and travel for a long period of time around the continent in order to spread the teachings of the Radiance Church. As they do so, they heal people of their illnesses and do not possess riches. They do not hunt for their food, but instead rely on charity. The Monk Order is composed of magicians, but since the church is getting more and more rich, fewer individuals are willing to become suffering monks. There are only a few true suffering monks left.”

After telling them of such, Maru couldn’t help but reveal a color of admiration. It was clear that he had a high level of approval of those suffering monks. It was sad, however, that they were now enemies of the Radiance Church.

This was the first time Zhao Hai had heard of such self-torture as an occupation. It sounded relatively similar to what he knew of monks, but they were also different. They sounded a great deal stronger than regular monks.

Maru sighed. “If the Radiance Church could be like those suffering monks, then the continent would be very lucky. What a pity. Nowadays, only a few of those magicians could endure such hardship and become a suffering monk. Right now, the Radiance Church is controlled by the Pope and the Round Table Knight Order. They resort to finding ways of increasing and enhancing the status of the Radiance Church in the hearts of the people on the continent. They are hanging onto the laws of the land in order to make money. They are greedier than merchants and have a darker heart than politicians[6].”

Maru clenched his teeth as he said this. It was obvious that the suppression of the black magicians had been led by the Pope and the Round Table Knight Order.

Maru calmed down and looked at Zhao Hai, saying, “You may not believe it, but previously, the Immortal Mercenary Group that had attacked Laura was controlled by the Radiance Church. It was also the same with Garan[7], and those three black magicians that had been hired to attack you. The ones behind the scenes is the Radiance Church. No one knows of this, however. On the outside, the Radiance Church shows a benevolent and compassionate appearance, but are actually secretly participating in evil deeds comparable with devils.”

Zhao Hai and the others were shocked. This news, for them, was truly too shocking[8]. They had no way of knowing who had commissioned the Immortal Mercenary Group. They never thought that such shadowy killing organizations like this had links with the Radiance Church. Moreover, Maru knowing this information meant that they’d carried out a detailed investigation. It seemed that the Black Magician Alliance wouldn’t be a good crop[9].

Maru watched Zhao Hai’s face and smiled faintly. “These issues are matters we investigated clearly. If we didn’t have such strength, then we wouldn’t be able to match up against Radiance Church. The reason why they pitted Boric against you was, first, because they wanted to get their hands on your Taoyuan products. The second reason was because you are a black magician. They are afraid that you’ll join the Black Magician Alliance. If you did so, then with your financial support, the Black Magician Alliance would become a greater threat to them.”

Zhao Hai and Laura were both surprised for a moment. The two of them couldn’t help but look at one another. Although Maru’s words meant nothing on the surface, Zhao Hai had actually deciphered the fact that the Black Magician Alliance was lacking in finances.

They weren’t fools. Maru could give such a confidential performance because he had a reason. At first, Zhao Hai didn’t know what it was. Now, however, he understood. To put it bluntly, they needed him for his money.

Maru saw their expressions and immediately knew what they were thinking. With a righteous air, he said, “Please, Mister Zhao Hai, don’t misunderstand. I invited you to join the Black Magician Alliance not because of your money. As an organization, we, the Black Magician Alliance, do not have distinctions between upper and lower ranks. The alliance does not have a leader, but an Elders Assembly. The Elders Assembly will not order its magician members. If they want a magician to do something, then they would first listen to the magician’s opinion on the matter.

“This time, the main reason we are asking Mister to join the Black Magician Alliance is simply because you are a black magician. Aside from those controlled by the Radiance Church, we invite all black magicians to join the alliance.”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “After joining the alliance, we will I need to do?

As soon as Maru heard what Zhao Hai said, he knew this matter had passed through open doors. Thus, he immediately said, “There are no excessive requirements, just two. First, since it’s difficult to meet all the magicians in the alliance, members should lend a hand to each other when they can. The second is to collect any information on the Radiance Church and deal with them however possible on one’s own. These two are the only requirements.”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “What can the alliance provide me then? Of course, I don’t mean in the financial aspect, but what can they provide me in other aspects?”

Maru smiled slightly. “Of course there will be benefits. The alliance can provide you with information and intelligence. We can also provide you with manpower to help you. Naturally, the manpower provided will require a cost to be handed to the alliance. Furthermore, you will need to commission every person you take in.”

* * *

Footnotes:

[1]光明教会 – Guāngmíng jiàohuì. Light/Bright/Clear light. Church. I wanted to keep this separate from Light Magicians—光明魔法师—since the church doesn’t really house only Light Magicians. As such, Radiance Church. Light Church is also generic sounding…

[2]The RAW said Zhao Jia, but he shouldn’t know Zhao Hai changed the guy’s name to Zhao Jia… Or that he has a light magician undead…

[3]护教骑士 – Hù jiào qíshì. Protect/Guard (护). Religious (教). Knight (骑士). If people want, it can also be Guard Paladin or something, but that sounds too impressive… Guardian Knight would also have been a choice… but Guardian is 衛士, and 士 means knight/warrior, so it’s weird, kinda.

[4]What a mouthful. 圆桌骑士会 – Yuánzhuō qíshì huì. 圆桌 = Round Table. 骑士 = Knights. 会 = Conference/Association/Society.

[5]This was a difficult one. 行者会 – Xíngzhě huì. The 会 is the same as above, but the first two 行者 were so confusing… I asked another TL and they said 行者 can mean monk, so I just went with it…

[6]Don’t ask. There seems to be politicians in this world ruled by a rather strict class system…

[7]Again, he uses Zhao Jia…

[8]It’s also a common cliche nowadays.

[9]Farming idiom I don’t get.

Chapter 221: Joining the Alliance

Zhao Hai nodded. Such conditions were acceptable for him. If the Black Magician Alliance was truly this loose, then joining wouldn’t be an issue.

Maru watched Zhao Hai’s expression, smiled, then said, “So long as you join the alliance, some common and ordinary intelligence will be provided free of charge. If you wish for the alliance to help you investigate matters with special circumstances, or to look up a specific individual, then  the alliance will request a fee. This fee will be based on the difficulty of obtaining this information.

“Naturally, the alliance will also give missions you can partake in. For example, some magicians might also with to obtain information on certain individuals. How much you help in their investigations will become the basis for the amount you gain off the alliance’s commision. If there is a magician that requires a magic beast and you help in catching it, then the alliance will also pass a commision for that as well.”

Zhao Hai smiled and thought the Black Magician Alliance was interesting. It seemed like a common mercenary guilds in novels back on Earth. The things they did were similar, except that the alliance catered to black magicians.

Smiling, Zhao Hai said, “What do I need to give in order to join the alliance?”

As soon as he heard the question, Maru understood Zhao Hai’s intent. He was excited and immediately replied, “We do not require anything. It’s fine if you just agree to join. Later on, you cannot spread matters pertaining to the alliance and you cannot betray it. If you agree, then take this and become a full fledged member of the alliance.”

As he spoke, Maru took out a small badge. The badge was similar to the size of a yuan coin back on Earth. On the front side was a dark cloud pattern while the back had a pin, allowing it to be attached to one’s clothing

Zhao Hai carefully inspected the simple badge. After a while, he looked at Maru and said, “Such a simple badge, aren’t you afraid of fabrications?”

Maru smiled. “No. Although this badge looks insignificant and made of simple metal, it was actually made by an elder of the alliance. They performed a few magic experiments and obtained this. Although it isn’t a hard metal, it has very good elasticity. It can change its shape when subjected to external force, then slowly change back to its original state. Moreover, the badge has a number that prevents others from making a counterfeit.”

Memory metal[1]!

As Zhao Hai listened, he thought the material of the badge was similar to memory metal. He really didn’t think there would be such a thing on this continent.

Zhao Hai took up the small badge and carefully checked it, yet he couldn’t see anything peculiar about it. He placed the badge back on the table and turned to Maru. “If the alliance had a lot of rules, I wouldn’t have agreed to join.”

Maru couldn’t help but feel happy. He had a certain understanding of Zhao Hai. He knew Zhao Hai was very strong. During the time Garan[2] had tried to cope with Zhao Hai, his group disappeared without a trace. There was also the attack on Laura by the Immortal Mercenary Group that he repelled. Later on, they too had vanished from the continent. This had proven Zhao Hai’s strength. Such a powerful black magician joining the Black Magician Alliance would definitely increase their strength. This was what made Maru truly happy.

Obviously, the Black Magician Alliance was more into preservation when compared with the Radiance Church. Their aim was simple. Just as Maru said, they aimed to first help other black magicians and pass down their magic techniques. The second goal was to resist the Radiance Church.

Compared to Radiance Church, the Black Magician Alliance’s organization structure was quite loose and less utilitarian. Because of this, Zhao Hai decided to join the alliance.

Once he saw Zhao Hai taking the badge, Maru felt relieved. He smiled and said, “Good. From now on, you are a member of the Black Magician Alliance. Our alliance’s main goal is to help other black magicians and resist Radiance Church. For the rest of the time, you can do your own thing and needn’t worry about being restrained.”

Zhao Hai smiled. “This is good. Since Sir Maru has come this time, we must entertain sir well. Laura, order some people to make preparations. In a while, I will ask sir to join us for a meal. After dinner, I would also like to ask sir to enjoy a play.”

Laura smiled faintly and said, “Alright, I’ll order them to prepare. We happen to have several fire fish at the moment, so it will be good so serve it to sir.” She then told Nier to start preparing.

Maru looked at them strangely. After hearing him speak Laura’s given name, it seemed that Zhao Hai and Laura had some sort of relationship. It wasn’t just that of a collaborator with her benefactor, but instead displayed a sort of intimacy.

What was more important was that he heard Laura telling him to eat fire fish. Although fire fish was not an advanced level magic beast, it was very difficult to eat some. Maru was only a black magician and hadn’t eaten fire fish before. Laura suggesting this was truly surprising.

Before, Laura had returned with fire fish from her visits to Zhao Hai’s place. It wasn’t a gift, but something they ate privately and it also hadn’t been sold to her. As such, no one else on the continent knew Laura had a large amount of fire fish in her possession.

Maru felt extremely flattered with the accommodations. One must know that fire fish were very high quality. With the present status of black magicians, few could eat such delicacies. He hadn’t expected he would taste some today.

With regards to the play Zhao Hai had invited him to watch later, he understood what Zhao Hai had meant. He had investigated earlier before he came. For the past two days, Boric had sent his people into Casa City. It seemed that they were here to deal with Zhao Hai. He didn’t understand it at first, but now that he was being asked to deliberately stay here a bit longer, he knew Zhao Hai’s intentions. Zhao Hai had stayed back in order to wait for the people Boric sent.

Maru, however, didn’t say anything about that. He stayed and waited. In any case, Boric was also a member of Radiance Church, so tidying up his men would be a good thing.

Zhao Hai turned to Maru and said, “Sir Maru, may I know how many members the alliance has?”

Maru nodded. “Naturally. We currently have a total of 13,600 members. Although this may look like a lot, one must understand that the alliance aims to invite every black magician on the continent. While there are some black magicians we cannot contact, there are also those who are reluctant to join. On the continent, about forty or so out of a hundred meetings result in recruitment. If we only have so few, then our days will be tough.”

Zhao Hai nodded. Although he didn’t understand much about the situation of the Ark Continent, he had a certain understanding of the Purcell Duchy. As such, he knew the population of the Ark Continent was immense, and its size was probably greater than that of Earth. The population shouldn’t be lower than that of Earth. In this case, as an organization of the Ark Continent, even with a member count of over ten thousand it was a very skewed ratio.

Zhao Hai turned to Maru and asked, “Does the alliance have any semblance with the church? Like, do we control several mercenary groups?”

Maru smiled and said, “As you know, the alliance is an organization wherein those in direct control have no great power. Some magicians, however, have established their own forces, such as yourself. At present, your influence isn’t small. In the future, the alliance may ask for your help when necessary. Your strength is a part of the alliance and unlike the Radiance Church, we don’t directly order our members. We generally please the magicians working with us. As such, we usually give notice to the magician beforehand and seek their advice. If you don’t wish to help, then we won’t force you.”

Zhao Hai curiously asked, “What if a magician always declines to help? Will the alliance still provide information to him? Wouldn’t this be a loss for the alliance[3]?”

Maru chuckled. “The alliance isn’t a merchant group. It was established to help black magicians and help them pass down their magic. At the same time, we resist the Radiance Church. Helping the alliance is voluntary. We won’t force anyone.”

Zhao Hai somewhat admired Maru and the alliance. So far, the things that had been presented by the alliance showed that they wished to help black magicians. Furthermore, the utilitarianism wasn’t forced. Seeing this, it truly was actively trying to help the black magicians.

Nodding seriously, Zhao Hai said to Maru, “Sir Maru, please help me pass a message along to the Elders Assembly. If there is anything I can help with, please don’t be polite. So long as I can help, I shall.”

Maru laughed. “Alright. I will certainly pass on this message. Zhao Hai, we black magicians have been pushed into a dead end now. If we do not give our all, then it will be our own bad luck in the end.”

Zhao Hai nodded. Although he wasn’t a true black magician, helping the black magicians whenever he could was equal to gaining a patron. If anything happened in the future, then he could ask the Black Magician Alliance for help. This was very important for him.

Around this time, the food had finished being prepared. Zhao Hai and the rest moved to the dining hall and Meg immediately set the meals.

The truth was, these meals had been prepared within the Space. They’d been prepared by Meirin. What Laura had said earlier had just been a cover. Maru had invited Zhao Hai to join the Black Magician Alliance, and Zhao Hai didn’t wish to be malicious. It was just that the Space wasn’t something Zhao Hai could easily share with Maru. This was his greatest secret. Except for those whom he was intimate with, like Laura, in which he was sure wouldn’t betray him, he wouldn’t easily tell others about it.

The reason Zhao Hai didn’t conceal this secret from the slaves was because it was impossible for those slaves to betray Zhao Hai. In addition, it would be impossible for them to establish themselves anywhere else on the continent. If they weren’t under a master and ran away to some other place on the continent, then they would be called a runaway slave and captured. This was the reason why Zhao Hai wasn’t afraid of them speaking out irresponsibly.

The meal was very sumptuous. Of course, the main course was fire fish. There was also beef, pork, rabbit meat, and various kinds of vegetables. Maru looked at the vegetables and couldn’t help but swallow his saliva. These years, due to the suppression of the Radiance Church, the life of black magicians had become very bad. He himself hadn’t eaten such a grandiose meal as of late.

* * *

Footnotes:

[1]https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Shape-memory_alloy.

[2]Again, it’s shown as Zhao Jia, which makes no sense.

[3]He can ask an intelligent question but can’t remember something had happened a few days ago when he’s suddenly in trouble… Yea, I’m talking about the Rank Nines in the swamp…

Chapter 222: Become My Slave

The meal made Maru very happy. Moreover, it surprised him that the meat on the table was all made with advanced level magic beasts as they contained a high level of magic elements.

As a magician, Maru was very sensitive to magic elements. In addition to this, Zhao Hai had used ingredients prepared from the Space. The beef was a common cattle meat used on the continent called a fierce cow[1].

Fierce cows were a very strange kind of magic beast. Their bodies didn’t have any wool and instead had thick skin and a lot of meat. Its strength was also very high. This type of cattle could be used to plow arable fields, and the meat could be used as food. Laura raised several fierce cows, but not for farm use. The fierce cows were raised for their meat.

Previously, Laura had raised a lot of wind falcons. These wind falcons alone ate a lot of meat. Now that she raised the eagles, their appetite was also quite large. Providing meat for the wind falcons and eagles had required her to raise several fierce cows. Afterward, Zhao Hai received them inside the Space.

The Space’s evaluation of fierce cows wasn’t very high, only level 4 magic beast. This was just the rating inside the Space, however. Outside, the rating of fierce cows was only level 1. The highest level of animals within the space was level 50, but on the Ark Continent the highest was only a level 9 magic beast. Reaching level 10 would be the same as reaching godhood and that only existed in legends. This was the reason why the assessment of animal levels inside and outside the Space was different.

The reason why Zhao Hai raised fierce cows was for their meat. They were all used to eating Space produced meat, so the meat outside always tasted off. This was why they were currently eating products taken from inside the Space.

Products that were produced from within the Space was of high quality. These were good ingredients which, in turn, naturally enhanced the flavor of the dish. Along with the use of cooking methods from Earth, Maru’s appetite was greatly increased.

After dinner, they went into the parlor room where Nier and Meg served them tea. Zhao Hai drank a mouthful of the tea and looked at Maru, smiling as he asked, “Sir, what do you think of tonight’s meal? Was it delicious?”

Maru replied with a smile, “Delicious, it was too delicious. Is this the continent’s famous Taoyuan products? They are truly extraordinary. I really didn’t expect Mister Zhao Hai to have such good things. No wonder Boric has thoughts about them.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly. “Yes, good things are always on a person’s mind.”

Just then, Zhao Hai’s expression changed. He turned to Maru and said, “I didn’t think that the play would start just after we finished eating. Interesting.”

As soon as Maru heard what Zhao Hai said, he knew the play was being staged. He smiled and said, “Yes, ah, just finished dinner and we can already see a good play. Haha, I hope it’s a splendid play.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly. He turned to Laura and said, “Open the doors and let the people acting in the play come onto the stage. Let us have those watching the play be comfortable. There’s nothing else we can do but show our due respect for their feelings.”

Laura smiled faintly and nodded. Nier and Meg ran to open the doors and windows of the parlor room.

Maru didn’t know when it happened, but the entire courtyard began to be filled with undead. Some of those undead wore the armor of warriors while others looked like magicians in their presentation. They appeared in the courtyard one after the other and stood motionless like statues.

Furthermore, the entire courtyard was covered with a black fog. One simply couldn’t see the situation outside, but could only hear the sounds of footsteps. The number wasn’t small.

Maru looked at Zhao Hai with astonishment. These undead were obviously being summoned by Zhao Hai, but he didn’t see when Zhao Hai had summoned them. There weren’t movements of any sort, nor did he make any sound. What’s more, he didn’t feel any magical fluctuations. This surprised him.

Many black magicians would study how to hide magical fluctuations. After learning how, they would only be able to use it for casting low level magic. This made it difficult for others to detect their magical fluctuations and it could be used for sneak attacks.

This method, however, required a lot of preparation. If the opposing magician noted them, then using this method would be difficult.

Hiding magical fluctuations using any method wouldn’t completely erase the presence of magical fluctuations either. Rather, it could only weaken it. When a person didn’t pay close enough attention, the magical fluctuations wouldn’t be felt. If one were to carefully observe, however, then it could be found.

Maru felt nothing when Zhao Hai summoned his undead. There were no magical fluctuations of any kind, which was the most surprising part.

Naturally, it was impossible for Maru to know that Zhao Hai didn’t use the common dark summoning magic technique. If he knew this, then he wouldn’t be so surprised.

Zhao Hai didn’t pay attention to Maru. He watched the front of Faith Mansion and wanted to see what method the intruders would use to break through the walls and enter Faith Mansion.

Just then, a knock suddenly sounded at the door. Zhao Hai and Laura were surprised for a moment. How come there was someone knocking at the door at this time[2]?

Zhao Hai couldn’t help but smile gently. “The people at home are resting. Come back tomorrow.”

As he said this, Zhao Hai and Laura laughed. They didn’t need to ask for the identity of those currently knocking as they were surely those people were sent by Boric. The opposite party’s action of knocking on the door was supposed to make them feel tense, as though they despised them.

Unfortunately, Zhao Hai answered with a joke which ruined their plans completely. They wanted to pressure Zhao Hai, but were instead ridiculed.

Sure enough, after Zhao Hai’s joke, a voice was heard from outside. “Junior, you have some balls.”

After they heard those words, a loud bang sounded from the front doors. The two thick wooden doors fell inward.

Zhao Hai and the others didn’t pay any attention to the fallen doors. They did, however, look towards the doors in order to see who had come this time around.

Five individuals stood outside. Those five all wore white magic robes and carried white magic staffs in their hands. Zhao Hai understood that these five were all light magicians. Moreover, their ranks weren’t low. The five light magicians stood beside an extravagant looking carriage. The body of the carriage was colored a pure white that glistened in the night. There weren’t any ordinary horse-shaped magic beasts pulling the carriage, but lion-shaped ones. Those lion-shaped magic beasts were also white and didn’t only exude a fierce battle aura, but also an aura of holiness.

Laura whispered to Zhao Hai, “A carriage made of sacred light wood[3]. It seems these are people of Radiance Church, and their statuses aren’t low. From their appearances they should be white-clothed bishops. Pulling their carriages are level 6 light element magic beasts, Moonlight Lions[4]. Their battle quality is high and they also use light elemental magic.”

Standing behind the five white-clothed bishops was a platoon of knights. The appearances of those knights was quite distinct. They each had a cross beneath their uniforms and rode white-horned warhorses. Those white-horned warhorses were equipped with bright silver armor. Each knight wore bright silver body armor and held a four-meter long knight spear in their right hand. A large tower shield was held in their left hands and there were white feathers that stuck out of their body armor. Beneath the spearhead of their knight spears was a triangular flag. The spears pointed toward the sky, allowing the triangular flag to wave in the air.

Zhao Hai examined the appearance of those mighty knights and muttered, “I have to say, the look of those fellows is really good. It’s just that I don’t know what’s beneath the armor. Would there be a human, or a ghost?”

As Zhao Hai’s voice faded, a colder one came from one of the white-clothed bishops. “Are you Zhao Hai? Dirty black magician. Today, for the glory of god, we’ll make you disappear forever.”

Zhao Hai looked at the five white-clothed bishops and smile. “How many times have you said that line? How can you say it so smoothly? Today, didn’t you promise the Purcell clan you wouldn’t make such a big ruckus? Listen to me. We should speak from the heart and not use any actions. I may have attacked first, but this way we can save a lot of trouble[5].”

When she heard Zhao Hai, Laura couldn’t help but smile. She didn’t expect Zhao Hai to be such a rascal at this time and unexpectedly say these words.

Zhao Hai’s disposition was quite cheerful, but he was a person who stayed at home for too long so he appeared a bit dull. In addition, he’d just moved to the Ark Continent. Because of the pressure, he hadn’t been able to joke a lot. Today, however, he had joined the Black Magician Alliance and was about to leave the Purcell Duchy. As such, he loosened his heart a bit. He couldn’t help but say a couple jokes with the white-clothed bishops.

Those white-clothed bishops didn’t expect Zhao Hai to be this relaxed when he saw their lineup. The bishop in the middle couldn’t help but angrily say, “Junior, you dare speak such nonsense. A dirty human like you needs to be purified under the brilliance of god. That’s the only way out.”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “That’s a good choice. You came at the wrong time, however. The brilliance of god can purify in the day, but at night the brilliance of god is replaced. Haha, I see your fancy carriage and big cats pulling it. I also see the knights behind you look very good. I am quite reluctant to make you all my slaves.”

Maru sat beside Zhao Hai and, to be honest, he was currently very nervous. One must know that within Radiance Church, those white-clothed bishops were existences that stood just beneath the Pope and the archbishops. Each of them would be at least a Rank Seven magician in strength. In addition to the magic staffs they held, the carriage and magic beasts pulling it could superimpose with their strength and increase it. It could be said that their strength wasn’t any lower than that of a Rank Eight expert. Five Rank Eight light magicians. With this, their battle strength wasn’t something that could be lightly called a play.

Light elemental magic was the nemesis of black magic. This sentence wasn’t false. In front of a light magician, black magicians suffered innate disadvantages. What’s more, the opposite party had sent magicians of such high strength in order to deal with Zhao Hai. Seeing Zhao Hai so indifferent when dealing them made Maru feel admiration towards Zhao Hai.

* * *

Footnotes:

[1]蛮牛 – Mán niú. 蛮 = Fierce/Savage/Barbaric/Rough. 牛 is bull, cow, cattle in general. Since I have no idea of the gender of the meat, I just stuck with cow.

[2]When fighting your mortal foes, it is best to appear as polite as possible. “Gentlemen Battles 101.”

[3]圣光木 – Shèng guāng mù. 圣 = Holy/Sacred. 光 = Light. 木 = Wood.

[4]月明狮 – Yuè míng shī.

[5]Questionable. It’s a very confusing sentence, but I tried to assume this was what he meant to say…

Chapter 223: Undead with Light Magic

After Zhao Hai spoke, he turned to Laura and asked, “What do you think, Laura? Is the idea good or bad? If a black magician sat on that sacred light wood carriage as it’s pulled by undead Moonlight Lions with an undead bishop coachman. it must certainly ride like the wind.”

Laura and the others were shocked. Although Laura was very confident in Zhao Hai, hearing him say such things still surprised her.

No one could blame them for being surprised. Zhao Hai’s words were truly too astonishing. If Zhao Hai did this, then it would be tantamount to slapping the face of the entire continent’s Radiance Church. The Radiance Church wouldn’t let this go.

Among them, the most surprised was Maru. Maru was one of the first to join the Black Magician Alliance. These past few years, they had resisted Radiance Church so he had a certain understanding of exactly how powerful the Radiance Church was. To be honest, many wouldn’t speak like Zhao Hai. Even Rank Nine experts wouldn’t dare to easily say such things. The Bright Church didn’t only have a single Rank Nine expert, so a common Rank Nine expert wouldn’t be so bored as to speak out like this.

Maru, however, was very excited. The Black Magician Alliance had been resisting Radiance Church for years, yet they were only participating in secret and used sneak attacks. The majority of the people on the continent didn’t even notice. Moreover, they were still afraid of the Radiance Church’s retaliation. They did minor acts, but what Zhao Hai said he would do to the white-clothed bishops… they didn’t even dare to think of it.

Those white-clothed bishops were stunned after hearing what he said. What followed was boundless anger. They didn’t think that a black magician would dare to speak such insolence towards them. The power and influence of a bishop was no less than that of a middle-rank aristocrat on the continent. Now, however, someone had dared to speak such insolence towards them. They were even ignored, which had truly made them angry.

The bodies of those white-clothed bishops shook with anger, and one of them loudly shouted, “Dirty black magician! Your thoughts have been poisoned by the devil. Come and accept a baptism from god.”

Zhao Hai laughed and looked at the bishop as he said, “Were your heads caught in the door? Is that why you can say such things? Can you find someone on the continent that would just let their heads be chopped off if they were asked by someone to do so? Does the Radiance Church really have such idiots in control?”

The eyes of the bishop turned red with anger. Just as he was about to say something, the bishop beside him said, “We are not of Radiance Church. We are just mercenaries that do not understand black magicians.”

Zhao Hai looked in this bishop’s eyes. While the other white-clothed bishops were also filled with anger, this one appeared calm. This bishop hadn’t been angered or affected by Zhao Hai’s taunting.

Zhao Hai watched the person’s appearance and knew that this was a person with a deep and profound background[1]. Such a person couldn’t be compared with the others that were easy to mess with. Zhao Hai, however, didn’t care. He smiled and said, “Clear-sighted people shouldn’t speak lies. Who you are is something we are crystal clear about. You do not have the right to speak of evils since the Radiance Church isn’t so clean itself. Saying so many words, the cost isn’t something such hands could pay..”

After saying this, he waved and several undead dressed as magicians appeared before the white-clothed bishops.

Those undead were Zhao Zui and his team[2], Zhao Jia[3], Zhao Shi and Zhao Jie[4], Lycra and his trio, and Buffy. Those fifteen undead magicians suddenly appeared and frightened them. Zhao Hai had feared that people might recognize them, so they appeared as skeletons instead of zombies.

Those white-clothed bishops looked at Zhao Hai’s expression and grew more angry. They were light magicians, the nemesis of black magicians. Now, however, Zhao Hai unexpectedly had his undead deal with them. This made them despise him greatly.

One bishop couldn’t bear it anymore and spoke first. He angrily shouted at Zhao Hai, “Junior, today we shall let you know that the brilliance of god is everywhere!” After he shouted, he raised his staff and recited a spell incantation. A white light suddenly shot at Zhao Zui. This spell was expectedly a Rank Six light element area of effect attack, Sacred Light Descends[5].

Maru sat quietly beside Zhao Hai. When Zhao Hai bickered with the bishops, his heart couldn’t stop beating. Seeing Zhao Hai send the undead to deal with the white-clothed bishops worried Maru. The difference was too great. One must know that one cannot easily mess with a bishop.

Everyone, however, was surprised after seeing how the scene unfolded. They saw an undead magician suddenly step forward. This magician wore a white magic robe and held a white staff. They didn’t see anything until, suddenly, a light element magic shield appeared, blocking the attack directed at the nearby undead skeleton magicians.

Including Laura, the white bishops were startled and froze for a moment. Maru, who was also startled, suddenly stood up. They had all thought that the skeleton magicians would use black magic to deal with the white-clothed bishops. They didn’t expect, however, that it would actually use light magic.

This skeleton was naturally Zhao Jia. He himself was a light magician. After the improvements from the Space, his magic had been preserved. Thus, it was natural for him to be able to use light magic.

This, however, made Maru and the others very surprised. They hadn’t seen an undead before that could use light magic. The simple fact of it seemed like a joke. This was like a man holding the knife that would cut his own body. It was purely suicidal behaviour.

Zhao Hai didn’t want to make a move since he wanted to see the effect. He also wanted to let Maru know that he wasn’t afraid of Radiance Church.

At this time, Zhao Zui and his team made their move. Zhao Zui and his team were true black magicians and they shot black magic attacks that covered the sky and overwhelmed the white-clothed bishops.

Zhao Shi and Zhao Jie also moved, along with Buffy and the others. Zhao Shi and Zhao Jie were earth element magicians while Buffy was a wind element magician. Adding in Zhao Zui and his team, the attacks of three magic elements was magnificent and unparalleled.

Zhao Zui and his team’s actions moved the souls of everyone. Maru looked with shock at Zhao Hai and asked, “Mister Zhao Hai, this… what is this all about? How can your undead use light elemental magic?”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “Sir Maru, don’t worry about it and sit down. Listen to my explanation. This undead using light elemental magic was Garan, who had attacked me in the past. After I killed him, I turned him into an undead. To my surprise, he suddenly became a variant undead that could use light elemental magic. I was also surprised after seeing this back then, but I don’t actually understand how it happened.”

After hearing Zhao Hai’s explanation, Maru felt relieved. Black magicians had their own system for summoning undead. Sometimes, there would also be variations. As such, while Zhao Jia’s ability was strange, it wasn’t completely out of the norm.

Even though Maru had calmed down, he still felt it was inconceivable. An undead that could use light elemental magic. Even though he personally saw it, if he told others they wouldn’t believe him.

Maru still didn’t feel this was right. He turned to Zhao Hai and asked, “What about the other skeleton magicians? What’s going on with them? What are their ranks?”

A low ranking undead wouldn’t be able to use magic. Since Zhao Zui and his team could use magic, Maru knew that they were all high ranking undead.

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “How should I put this, I’d say it’s all thanks to my lucky magic cane that I found. I don’t know what it’s made of. While I was hunting for magic beasts in the forest, I fortunately found it. This magic cane has a very special ability. Using it to cast the Bone Forging technique on the dead blesses it with the Spirit Trap technique. That’s the reason why I can summon high-level undead.”

Maru stared at Zhao Hai’s Ghost Cane with a pair of shining eyes. Zhao Hai laughed inside his mind. He remembered what Sir Wei Xiaobao[6] had said. An explanation should be nine parts true, one part false. Even if he lies, there was no way for others to figure it out[7].

At this time, several of the white-clothed bishops couldn’t withstand Zhao Zui and his team’s attack. Those Radiance Knights behind them also saw this and shouted. The spears those Radiance Knights held lowered as they rushed Faith Mansion.

Zhao Hai didn’t move. Instead, he made the warrior-clothed undead form a square formation. They blocked the entrance into the mansion. The entire courtyard of Faith Mansion became a battlefield.

Zhao Hai wasn’t worried. Even though those Radiance Knights were formidable and had good numbers, he himself had many undead with strengths comparable to that of Rank Seven warriors. Such a strength couldn’t be overlooked by anyone. He believed that those undead could block the Radiance Knights.

All of this made Faith Mansion very lively. The people around seemed to sleep soundly, however. They didn’t make any sound, so there was no problems with killing everything here.

Such a great ruckus should have already alarmed the city guards into action. The city guards, however, seemed to have taken a vacation. Not one figure could be seen. It seemed that the Radiance Church really had made a call to Grand Duke Evan.

With regards to Evan’s response, Zhao Hai understood it. Although the Purcell clan was a large clan, the combination of Boric and the Radiance Church going into action was too strong, so the Purcell clan had given in. That warning earlier was enough for them.

Sure enough, following Zhao Hai’s thoughts from before,  the Radiance Knights were repelled by the undead warriors at the front doors. They hadn’t been able to crash into Faith Mansion.

Suddenly, at this time, shadows of several courageous people appeared as they crawled up the walls surrounding Faith Mansion and leapt over. Those people wore mercenary clothes and held weapons. They looked at Zhao Hai, the person they were to deal with.

* * *

Footnotes:

[1]Questionable.

[2]I guess we should do some reflection. Zhao Zui and his team were the Immortal Mercenary Corps.

[3]Zhao Jia is Garan.

[4]Zhao Shi and Zhao Jie were the two earth magicians that were with Garan.

[5]圣光降临 – Shèng guāng jiànglín. Same 圣光 from sacred light wood.

[6]A character from Louis Cha/Jin Yong’s the Deer and the Cauldron.

[7]

What was true in his explanation? What was the point in making someone greedy for his cane? If he didn’t say anything, would Maru have been angry? Now he made the man envious and maybe made the entire Black Magician Alliance curious about his cane. Congratulations.

Chapter 224: The Final Blow

Maru also saw these people. Although they wore mercenary garbs, their movements were very neat. At a glance, it could be seen that they had good coordination and weren’t your average mercenaries. They should have received regular military training.

Zhao Hai watched the mercenaries. The number of people that had jumped over the wall numbered several hundred. When they entered the courtyard, they didn’t immediately attack Zhao Hai. Instead, they stood in place and changed their positions slightly to form ranks. Although they used up a bit of time, they had already lined up properly and into formation. After that, they charged at him.

On the other hand, Zhao Hai wasn’t worried. He himself was surrounded by many undead and at this time, he’d only used the human-shaped undead. Those beast-shaped undead hadn’t yet been mobilized.

Zhao Hai counted the knights attacking Faith Mansion from the front and came up with 18. These 18 knights had very good coordination with one another and were Rank Six experts.

Soon enough, no matter if it was Maru or the white-clothed bishops, they realized the abnormality of the situation. Those undead were really too special as they didn’t fear the attacks of the Radiance Knights.

One must understand that the weapons and equipment of the Radiance Knights had been blessed with light elemental magic. In addition, those knights themselves had very high battle strength. Zhao Hai, however, had only sent a hundred undead to withstand the attacks of the Radiance Knights. This was simply inconceivable.

Knights and warriors were different. The general understanding of the populace was that knights were a more advanced profession than warriors. Knights could be called the aristocrats of warriors.

An ordinary warrior wore leather armor at best and were equipped with a poor quality weapon. If a warrior wore armor and had a good weapon, then they wouldn’t simply be called a warrior.

A knight on the other hand must have a horse and wear full body armor. Their weapons weren’t like of warriors who only used a single type of weapon. Knights must have a knight spear along with a tower shield and a heavy sword[1]. Once they had those items, they could be called a knight[2].

Warrior, however, only needed to take care of themselves. Even if their weapon was damaged, they could just replace it. The cost also wouldn’t very high.

Knights, aside from looking after themselves, needed to take care of their mounts. Their knight spears was a weapon that could be easily damaged, so they needed to replace it if it was damaged. The price of a knight spear, however, was simply too expensive when compared to ordinary weapons[3]. Due to these reasons, from an ordinary warrior’s point of view, knights might be powerful but was an occupation that burned a lot of money[4]. If one wasn’t an aristocrat or a rich person, then there was no way to become a knight.

Also, due to the fact that knights were so rich, many of them would have a knight attendant. The knight attendant would usually take care of the day to day life of the knight, such as looking after their mounts. When the knight goes into battle, they would be beside the knight[5].

The battle strength of a knight was, without a doubt, formidable. Their strength was directly related to their mounts. If the mount was formidable, then the knight would be formidable. Naturally, if they wanted a formidable mount, then they would need to spend a considerable amount of money.

These Radiance Knights had uniform mounts. Each of them had a Rank Five magic beast, a unicorn[6]. Unicorns were Rank Five light element magic beasts and there were rumors that the Rank Nine saint beast of the elf race had a blood relationship with the unicorns. They had a very high battle strength and could carry heavy loads. These were very good mounts.

The knights of Radiance Church mostly used these kinds of unicorns as their mounts. This wasn’t only because of their battle strength, but also because it looked very strong.

When fighting against a hundred ordinary warriors, an eighteen member squad of knights would be more than a match for them. A single mounted knight’s strength could easily tear apart a warrior’s formation with ease. After a few assaults, they could easily kill those hundred warriors.

Unfortunately, this time the knights were not facing ordinary warriors, but undead as strong as a Rank Seven warrior. The knight charge didn’t go smoothly and they didn’t have a method to tear down these undead. This was truly a very rare matter for them[7].

Dealing with common undead was a very simply problem for these Radiance Knights since their weapons were all blessed with light element magic. So long as they encountered undead, they could inflict great damage to them. The problem was these undead weren’t normal, common undead. These undead were not afraid of light element magic.

Maru stared as he watched the situation. What he saw today was something he’d seen in the past: a battle between Radiance Knights and undead. Today, however, the battle had gone beyond his cognition. The undead and Radiance Knights both resisted the other greatly and didn’t fall to the wind. This, in his opinion, was a fantastical scene.

The undead surrounded by those mercenaries blocked their attacks continuously. Zhao Hai just sat there like one of the old gods. It was as if he truly was watching a play before him instead of a live battle.

Maru didn’t know what Zhao Hai was thinking. He suspected Zhao Hai wasn’t just a madman. A madman wouldn’t be able to do such a thing. Maru didn’t know whether it was right or wrong to invite such a super madman into the Black Magician Alliance.

At this time, Laura looked at the people outside and said to Zhao Hai, “Brother Hai, don’t drag this out for too long. It’ll be bad if you do this and have to give a confession to the Grand Duke.”

Zhao Hai nodded and waved his hand. Suddenly, a lot of undead magic beasts appeared within Faith Mansion. The characteristic of these undead was that they were all very large. Each undead was at least two to three meters in height. Some were even five to six meters tall. Moreover, their skeletal bodies were dark green in color and had spikes protruding from their bones. They didn’t look like something one should mess around with.

When these undead appeared, the sharp spikes on their bodies flew out fiercely like a brutal arrow being shot. They flew towards the mercenaries and shot down many of them.

After the spikes flew, the magic beasts quickly overran them. Maru, however, noted that behind those mercenaries were many undead. Those undead were like death as they mainly used assassination tactics. They were silently getting rid of the mercenaries at the back. Many of the mercenaries now had nobody at their back and were easily killed.

This disaster had come too fast. The mercenaries didn’t have enough time to react before they were killed. Those that hadn’t been killed yet were now caught in a circle of undead and weren’t able to escape.

To deal with these mercenaries, only a few undead had been used. Most of the undead were instead surrounding the Radiance Knights and the white-clothed bishops.

Maru didn’t know what to say. He never would have expected Zhao Hai to have so many undead. Moreover, the battle strength of these undead was very high. This time around, the Radiance Church would eat a loss.

Those five white-clothed bishops had also realized that things were not looking good. They didn’t expect Zhao Hai to have such unexpected strength. Slowly, they began to grow desperate. They knew that today, they had to do everything they could to desperately stay alive and fight.

Zhao Hai stood at this time and watched the five white-clothed bishops. He knew that these were the leaders. Others could run, but these five couldn’t.

He secretly gave Cai’er an order. So long as the white-clothed bishops made any movement, she was to immediately move against them.

The reason Zhao Hai ordered Cai’er to prepare was because of a single bishop’s calmness. When he released the magic beast undead earlier, all four of the white-clothed bishops’ facial color changed. All except for one. This was the one Zhao Hai was talking about, the one bishop he thought was very calm and might be planning something.

This bishop was very calm, and his calm didn’t seem to be due to his own strength. The might of this bishop was average when compared to the other four. He was, however, extremely calm, as if he didn’t have any fear.

Such a person must be hiding something in their hands. This kind of person with a deep background must certainly have a last card to play. Moreover, no one knew what card he had. As such, Zhao Hai paid special attention to him. This was why he ordered Cai’er to deal with him.

Laura and the others had observed the same scene. They looked at the white-clothed bishops and knew they couldn’t run away.

Maru didn’t know, but the rest understood that they had two Rank Nine experts on their side. At a moment’s notice, the Rank Nine experts would follow the command and get rid of their opponents. Even if the opposing party had an ancient magic tool, like a non-directional transfer scroll, they still wouldn’t be able to escape.

Battle was full of chances. So long as one was ready, all accidents could be inevitably avoided. Zhao Hai, this time around, was ready. He was waiting for all of his enemies to arrive. If the enemies didn’t come, then there was no problem. If they did, then they wouldn’t be able to escape.

The mercenaries went down one after another, and the battlefield didn’t give off any suspense anymore. Both the Radiance Church and Boric’s plans had been completely defeated.

Just then, three shadows appeared from the white-clothed bishop’s’ carriage. Three white-clothed bishops weren’t able to react before three piercing swords claimed their lives.

Although the white-clothed bishops used a light element protective shield, they weren’t able to block the attack of those piercing swords. As such, the three white-clothed bishops died in the blink of an eye.

At this time, Zhao Hai was still paying attention to the calm bishop and saw his facial expression finally change as he gritted his teeth. He looked maliciously at Zhao Hai as he extended a hand to his breast. Just as he was about to touch it, vines erupted from the ground and thrust towards the chest of the two remaining white-clothed bishops. When the vines came, a flash of white light appeared and tried to block the vines, but failed. The white-clothed bishop was killed on the scene, his eyes full of disbelief as he died.

* * *

Footnotes:

[1]重剑 – Zhòng jiàn. This is a bit weird since the MTL says Epee, but the literal characters say Weight/Heavy (重) Sword (剑). I don’t see knights using epees—those dueling swords used in fencing—so Heavy Sword was fine.

[2]Who cares about skill and ability. Wallet Warriors ftw!

[3]So they just look cool and have no real value as a weapon? Cause something so fragile sounds like it has a 1-hit use.

[4]A bit odd since they don’t have paper money back then, right? How do you burn gold? Might as well say you toss money down a well or something. It’ll just sink to the bottom.

[5]Knights sound incredibly disappointing… They can’t even fight well by themselves…

[6]独角马 – Dú jiǎo mǎ. Interestingly, the 角马 can mean wildebeest/gnu… So my imagination now makes fun of knights.

[7]So, ummm, eighteen knights haven’t instantly died after charging a hundred Rank Seven undead? I can’t deal with this math. Other than good mounts and good equipment, what exactly are their positives? Rank Six stays Rank Six and equipment can only do so much. With their blessed equipment having no effect, I’m wondering why they haven’t been pulled down and killed yet. I understand the light magicians being able to repel the greater number of black magicians due to the magic themselves not really changing (Light > Dark), but these are just Rank Six Knights… Sure, maybe a good lower ranked person can beat someone a rank higher, but these are one damned hundred undead. At least kill one knight…

Chapter 225: Destroy

Maru saw it all, and even the eighteen Radiance Knights were dumbfounded. Regardless of what had happened, they weren’t able to believe that five white-clothed bishops could just die so unexpectedly.

This was especially true for that white-clothed bishop that had tried to reach for something in his chest. That white-clothed bishop had a deep background and even though the Radiance Knights didn’t know what he was taking out, they did know that the white-clothed bishop had something in his possession, one protection ring[1].

A protection ring was a common magic item on the continent. This type of magic item was imbued with magic arrays that had been founded from the research circles. After a long period of research, they were able to seal protection magic into a ring, which is where it got its name.

Protection rings were divided into several grades. Low-level protection rings were disposable, one-time use items. The materials used for such an item weren’t special and were common materials like wood or stone with low level protection magic sealed within. These were relatively cheap and common.

High level protection rings, however, were made of metal alloys which could seal high level protection magic. They could also be repeatedly used and were regarded as a more precious magic item.

The father of this white-clothed bishop was a red-clothed archbishop and a Rank Eight expert. To ensure his son’s security, he had given that white-clothed bishop a high level protection ring. It could even block a Rank Eight expert’s attack without breaking.

This pitiful ring, however, couldn’t block Cai’er’s attack. Cai’er’s strength was greater than that of a Rank Nine’s, and her casual attack had the same strength of a regular Rank Nine. Because of this, the white-clothed bishop wouldn’t have been able to block her attack.

Those eighteen Radiance Knights were aware of his identity. The reason the white-bishop had gone with them was to obtain some merit. No one would have thought he’d die instead.

His death didn’t really matter[2], but it meant the knights wouldn’t be able to live anymore. They knew the father of that white-clothed bishop wouldn’t let them off.

The eyes of the Radiance Knights immediately turned red. They knew that no matter what happened today, they would die. If they died in battle, then their family members wouldn’t be affected. If they came back alive, however, their family members would receive bad luck.

These Radiance Knights had been trained by the Radiance Church. The church had selected talented children and trained them from childhood. As such, their loyalty towards the Radiance Church didn’t have any issues. Moreover, their detailed backgrounds were archived by the Radiance Church.

It was because they were loyal and absolutely wouldn’t betray the church that there were clear about its internal matters. They knew the Radiance Church wasn’t as bright as they appeared to be and was actually quite tarnished on the inside, yet they weren’t able to betray the Radiance Church. One could say that these people wearing the clothing of knights were already dead.

The eighteen Radiance Knights made their move at almost the exact same time. They discarded their tower shields simultaneously and pierced their knight spears into the ground. Then they all pulled out their heavy swords from their saddle and swung it down on their left hands.

Zhao Hai was surprised for a moment. He didn’t understand what they were trying to do until Green said aloud, “Master, we must kill them. They wish to use Sacrifice[3].”

Sacrifice was a unique skill used by knights. This skill meant they intended to go all out as they sacrificed their flesh and blood and dedicated it to their god of knights. By doing so, they would gain a strength that was a greater than what they currently had. This skill, however, once used would claim a knight’s life. Sacrificing oneself to obtain greater power. The skill’s duration was just an hour as well. After that hour, the knight would die, so the use of Sacrifice was akin to suicide.

Once a knight used sacrifice, they would generally obtain a boost in strength of two ranks. In other words, once these Radiance Knights used sacrifice they would be able to reach Rank Eight. On the continent, a Rank Eight knight was a master, an almost invisible existence below Rank Nine deities.

Zhao Hai smiled coldly and waved his hand. Several vines drilled up from the ground and straightened, thrusting at the heads of the knights. The eighteen Radiance Knights didn’t even have a chance to groan before they died.

Although Sacrifice was very powerful, it still needed time to prepare. The eighteen Radiance Knights weren’t able to complete their preparations in time before they were killed by Cai’er.

Zhao Hai didn’t want to wait, so he made Cai’er attack twice. He didn’t care if they died several times over. In a flash, Cai’er killed the remaining mercenaries and ended the battle.

One couldn’t say that the strength of the opponents were weak, just that Cai’er was ridiculously strong. Even if those Radiance Knights were to complete their Sacrifice, they would at most amount to a Rank Eight knight. Compared to a Rank Nine expert, those Rank Eights were just too weak[4]. It was just like when the Rank Eight expert, Green, faced the Rank Nine expert, Wind Saint Buffy, and didn’t have a chance to fight back. Don’t even mention Buffy, Cai’er didn’t have trouble with these mercenaries that were weaker than Rank Eight.

Almost instantly, Faith Mansion became quiet. Zhao Hai waved and the undead all picked up a corpse. He then took them back into the Space. The living unicorns and moonlight lions hadn’t been received by Zhao Hai yet. He had to wait till Maru left before he could do so.

After the corpses were taken away, Zhao Hai turned to Maru and said, “Sir Maru, we shall leave this place immediately. You must also leave. While the sky is still dark, you should leave Casa City as soon as you can. The Radiance Church has eaten such a big loss and certainly wouldn’t give up. In the future I shall not contact you. If there is any matter, then come to Stony Mountain and knock on the ground three times. Write the matter on paper and place it in a room. I will then contact you at an appointed time.”

Maru looked at Zhao Hai deeply and found that he had many secrets and a strength beyond his imagination. He, however, wasn’t ready to inquire into it. In any case, Zhao Hai had already joined the Black Magician Alliance and him having such strength would be beneficial for the alliance. Why would they inquire into his secrets when it might offend Zhao Hai[5].

Maru breathed in deeply, then nodded and said, “Alright, then we’ll keep in contact in the future. If Mister Zhao Hai needs help from the alliance, then you mustn’t hesitate to contact us. We have members of the Black Magician Alliance here within Casa City. If there is any matter, you can go and look for them.”

After he said this, he handed over a small book to Zhao Hai. This small book had obviously been prepared to be given out earlier, but he gave it now.

Zhao Hai wasn’t polite and received the small book. He nodded and said, “Alright, if I have any matters I will immediately contact you. I won’t send you off.”

Maru nodded his head and bid Zhao Hai farewell, then his stature flashed and disappeared in place.

Zhao Hai asked Cai’er to check on Maru until he left. He then received the sacred light wooden carriage along with the unicorns and moonlight lions.

He then turned to Laura and she also turned to Zhao Hai. Taking a deep breath, Laura carefully looked at Faith Mansion, then turned back to Zhao Hai and said, “Brother Hai, let us begin.”

Zhao Hai nodded and pointed his Ghost Cane towards the floor, then took Laura and the others and disappeared from the courtyard. As they disappeared, the ground beneath Faith Mansion began to shake fiercely. The area affected by this quake was small and didn’t bother the neighbors of the mansion.

Not long after, except for the walls of Faith Mansion, there was not a single building within the area. All of the houses had been taken down. Laura actually did have a secret passage, but it had disappeared without a trace due to this violent quake.

This was an earth element magic spell that Zhao Hai and the others had agreed to be used in order to eliminate their tracks. Although they wouldn’t face problems when they moved into the Space, they had to destroy Faith Mansion in order to lessen suspicion. This was the real reason why Zhao Hai felt sorry for Laura.

Upon entering the Space, Zhao Hai first went and moved the unicorns and moonlight lions into the Spatial Ranch. Zhao Hai had just entered the ranch with the two magic beasts when the Space suddenly prompted:

[Discovered unicorn-shaped animals. Evaluating level; Level 25 animal.

This animal can be raised inside the Space. It has a maturity time of 36 hours and can give birth to a foal every 12 hours. A total of eight foals can be birthed.

Digitizing animal. Animal can now be purchased from the Spatial Shop.]

[Discovered lion-shaped animal, new form variation. Evaluating level; Level 30 animal.

This animal can be raised inside the Space. It has a maturity time of 40 hours and can give birth to a cub every 12 hours. A total of eight cubs can be birthed.

Digitizing animal. Animal can now be purchased from the Spatial Shop.]

[With the discovery of new animals, the Spatial Ranch has reached the requirements for upgrade.

Spatial Ranch has been upgraded to Level 6.]

In all honesty, Zhao Hai wasn’t surprised by the Spatial Ranch’s upgrade. What he didn’t expect was that the unicorn and moonlight lion would be given such a low rating by the Space.

Yes. In Zhao Hai’s view, the unicorn and moonlight lion’s ratings were low. One must understand that these two were magic beasts that, on the Ark Continent, were Rank Five and Rank Six magic beasts. They would be considered the equivalent of young masters. Yet, the Spatial Ranch had assessed them as Level 25 and Level 30 respectively, which wasn’t high[6].

In the original list of animals for the Spatial Shop, a Level 25 animal was a crane, and a Level 30 animal was a hippo. Although the crane could fly and a hippo’s battle efficiency wasn’t low, they were quite lacking when compared to magic beasts. How come the Space ranked those two magic beasts so low[7]?

Yet, while this idea circled Zhao Hai’s head once, he didn’t think much of it. Anyway, there were more magic beasts on the Ark Continent. When the time came that his level increased, he would be able to buy animals from the Spatial Shop and be able to compare them and know.

Right now, Zhao Hai needed to deal with the corpses of the five white-clothed bishops. These white-clothed bishops were core members of Radiance Church. They certainly knew more matters about the church. For Zhao Hai, this information was of very great use for him. Anyway, both of his identities were now considered enemies of the Radiance Church. As such, he needed to understand more about them. To know them as intimately as he knows himself.

* * *

Footnotes:

[1]守护戒指 – Shǒuhù jièzhǐ. Note that the protection ring’s activation had nothing to do with what he was trying to take out.

[2]To the fight, btw. Avoiding confusion.

[3]献祭 – Xiàn jì. Offer. Sacrificial offering.

[4]Yet, you know, eighteen Rank Six knights could rush a hundred Rank Seven undead and not even get scratched.

[5]Yet, you know, he was fine to tell lies and give some random explanation and make his cane super OP.

[6]I don’t understand this. The Space ranks things from 1 to 50, yet the Ark Continent ranks things from 1 to 10. That means rank one magic beast on the Ark Continent would be levels 1-5 for the Space. Based on math, a Rank 5 magic beast should be levels 21-25, and a Rank 6 would be levels 26-30, no? Is it not progressive? Sounds mighty confusing if this isn’t so.

[7]Broken system. Too many mods ruined it.

Chapter 226: Blessed Magic Arrays

Zhao Hai returned to the Spatial Villa. Laura had stayed behind and was currently sitting in the living room, her mood obviously quite low. Zhao Hai didn’t speak and just moved to Laura’s side quietly. He placed a hand on her shoulder and sat down to accompany her.

Zhao Hai knew Laura was currently sad. Seeing the home they’d built with their own hands destroyed had given her a strange feeling. Saying anything to comfort her at this time was unnecessary. So long as he silently stayed with her and gave her a shoulder to lean on, it would be enough.

Laura leaned gently against Zhao Hai’s shoulder, her tears flowing freely. Faith Mansion wasn’t just a simple home, but an enterprise. It had her sweat and tears, and was also the home of her heart.

Holding Laura’s hands tightly, Zhao Hai said with a low voice, “Laura, rest assured that we will come back sooner or later. When that time comes, we’ll build something grander and more attractive than Faith Mansion.”

Laura’s tears didn’t stop, so Zhao Hai then whispered, “It’s alright, don’t cry. Crying isn’t beautiful. Although you have lost Faith Mansion, you gained the Space and Fort Iron Mountain, and also me. What aren’t you satisfied with[1]?”

When she heard what Zhao Hai said, Laura smiled through her falling tears. Zhao Hai looked at Laura and said, “Don’t cry. If Grandpa Quinn John and the others see this, they might think I’m bullying you. If your father sees this, then it’ll be a lot more serious and he might blow up my house.”

When she heard his words, Laura wasn’t startled but began to smile more than cry. Her tears fell more, but this time around they were tears of joy. Zhao Hai couldn’t help but pat his head as he murmured, “Again, Laura, don’t you want to go down and have a look at uncle? This time around, the explosion wouldn’t be small.”

Laura shook her head and smiled. She laughed so much that she couldn’t reply to Zhao Hai’s words, and Zhao Hai also couldn’t help but join in.

Since Karen had taken over the basement of the Spatial Villa and made it his experiment room, an explosion could be heard every other day. Sometimes, they might hear several go off in a row. Zhao Hai and the other had already gotten used to these explosions by now.

Zhao Hai felt a little resentment from it. Karen performed his experiments at random times and sometimes, it happened while Zhao Hai was sleeping. When the explosion occurred, he’d wake up and have a cup.

The Zhao Hai of Earth was an otaku writer. Due to him staying up late in the night, he had a slight nervous breakdown. He’d fall asleep and then wake up in the middle of the night and it would be difficult for him to get back to sleep again. Therefore, when Karen made those explosions, Zhao Hai would take a cup[2]. He now thought he wouldn’t get any sleep this night too.

He couldn’t, however, say anything to Karen and continued to endure it. At the moment, it was better. Even though there would be an explosion at night, he’d just turn over and sleep. One had to admit that a human’s ability to adapt to changes was truly amazing.

After some time, Laura stopped laughing. She turned to Zhao Hai and said, “Brother Hai, you haven’t dealt with the white-clothed bishop corpses yet. Why not deal with them now?”

Zhao Hai nodded. “Their processing has a been a bit long. Let’s go see and you can ask them anything. Moreover, the bodies of those white-clothed bishops should have a lot of good things on them. I just happened to have brought them for you.”

Laura smiled and said, “If there is a good magic item, then we might as well give it to father and have him study it. Perhaps we can get something good from them through his research.”

Zhao Hai smiled helplessly. He followed Laura outside the Spatial Villa and took out the corpses. He first made those ordinary mercenaries into undead. He only left two corpses back and turned them into high ranking undead, then asked these two leaders his questions.

These mercenary soldiers really had been sent by Boric. They were from a regular mercenary group and were Boric’s men; a mercenary group under Boric’s control.

Aside from this they didn’t obtain any better information. They were, after all, just a mercenary group and could only be regarded as one of Boric’s external forces that wouldn’t have any contact with his core strength.

Since he didn’t obtain any useful items from these mercenaries, Zhao Hai gave up on them. He then transformed the eighteen Radiance Knights into high ranking undead. These knights knew more than the mercenaries, but what they knew consisted mostly of knowledge about the Radiance Church’s teachings for their Protector Knights. They were part of the commonly used Radiance Knight groups.

The entirety of the Radiance Knight group was, on the surface, quite small. They were said to have only five hundred individuals, and most of this group didn’t have unicorns as their mount. After all, a unicorn was a Rank Five magic beast that wasn’t easy to obtain.

Their actual numbers, however, amounted to a thousand Radiance Knights. Among this thousand, a good two hundred were unicorn mounted knights that were considered the elites. This time around, they had sent eighteen of them to deal with Zhao Hai. It was obvious to see that the Radiance Church had attached great importance to this black magician.

These Radiance Knights, however, didn’t know much. They weren’t administrators of the church, so they only knew a bit of the church’s secrets.

Although Zhao Hai was a bit disappointed, he couldn’t say anything about it. These Radiance Knights had all been turned into undead by now. Their appearance didn’t change greatly from when they were alive. Even if they had cut off their left hands, their strength was still comparable to when they lived[3].

After Zhao Hai moved the Radiance Knights away, he began to turn the white-clothed bishops into undead. The one that had wanted to take out something was named Lyndsay Baker[4]. His father was Rooney Baker[5], a red-clothed archbishop.

This Lyndsay Baker had a really good item in his possession. There wasn’t just a high-level protection ring, but also an ancient magic scroll—a non-directional transfer scroll.

This scroll hadn’t been something Rooney Baker had given to Lyndsay, but was instead something Lyndsay had obtained on his own. He was innately selfish. Although his father was good to him, he didn’t even tell his father about the scroll and had secretly hidden it. He’d placed it on his body as he was afraid of losing it. He’d also killed everyone who knew of the scroll, so no one else knew he had such an ancient magic scroll in his hands.

Zhao Hai held the ancient magic scroll and looked at it foolishly. Ancient items made long ago referred to something that had become incredibly aged, yet this thing didn’t seem all that old to him. It glittered as if it were made of gold, but Zhao Hai was sure the material wasn’t metallic.

At this time, the Space suddenly prompted in a tone:

[Unknown magic item.

Analyzing item’s function. This item is a simple space system magic item.

This item can produce a non-directional, indeterminate distance spatial channel.

Extracting functions. Incorporating functions into the Ghost Cane.

Use of the Ghost Cane will now allow the creation of a non-directional, indeterminate distance spatial channel.]

[Unknown magic item.

Analyzing item’s function. This item is an autonomous stimulation-type protective magic item.

When the host is suddenly attacked, the item will produce a protective shield to guard the host.

Extracting functions. Enhancing functions. Incorporating functions into the Ghost Cane.

Ghost Cane can now automatically protect the host if attacked.]

[Multiple magic arrays.

Extracting magic arrays.

Storing into Spatial Files. Facilitating options so that host may view them at any time.]

[Appearance of blessing-shaped magic arrays.

Extracting magic arrays. Incorporating magic arrays into the Space.

Incorporating magic arrays into machine-type humanoid objects of Space. Strengthened machine-type humanoid objects.

Improving magic.

Combining magic arrays with sprite-type biological body. Strengthened sprite-type biological body.]

Zhao Hai and Laura listened to the prompts. This time, the prompts hadn’t been short yet the two of them actually understood what they had heard.

To keep it simple, the Space had extracted the abilities of the ancient magic scroll, then incorporated it into the Ghost Cane. The protection function of the protection ring had also been extracted, strengthened, then incorporated into the Ghost Cane.

The Space had also extracted several magic arrays and placed them into a Spatial File, then extracted a blessing-type magic array from the armor of the Radiance Knights. Those were placed on the undead as well as the other creatures such as the stone giants which then resulted in an increase in strength[6].

Zhao Hai hadn’t thought that the Space would have such powerful abilities. He could now regard the Ghost Cane as a protection ring and a non-directional transfer scroll. These two functions would be very useful in saving his life.

Moreover, those magic arrays had strengthened the undead within the Space. Their battle strength naturally received a boost. Although he didn’t know to what degree their strength had grown, it should be much higher. This made Zhao Hai happy.

Zhao Hai breathed lightly to calm his emotions. He passed the protection ring and ancient magic scroll to Laura and said, “This protection ring can still be used, so please take it. With regards to that magic scroll, it won’t be as useful. Better to give it to uncle so that he can study it.”

Laura didn’t say anything and just nodded as she received the items. She wouldn’t be polite around Zhao Hai. In any case, the functions of these two items had already been extracted by the Space and incorporated into the Ghost Cane. Zhao Hai could already use those functions, so being polite was useless.

Zhao Hai looked over the other white-clothed bishops. Although they did possess some items, they weren’t as good as what Lyndsay Baker had. Zhao Hai only glanced at them before throwing the items into the warehouse without managing them.

After dealing with these things, Zhao Hai turned his eyes towards the white-clothed bishops themselves. Compared to the items he obtained, he was more interested in what information they could give him. For him, intelligence was something more valuable than items.

* * *

Footnotes:

[1]So smooth… let us give Zhao Hai an award for his inconsideration… girl sad? Tell her she’s ugly when she cries and praise yourself… >.>

[2]Yep, by now I still have no idea what this means. Have a cup… meh 杯具了 is meh…

[3]What does this have to do with anything? Did the hand not come back? How does that work? He cut off Buffy’s head, yet couldn’t reattach a hand? They’re both high ranking undead now…

[4]林赛贝克 – Lín sài bèikè.

[5]鲁尼贝克 – Lǔní bèikè. Looney Baker makes him sound… looney.

[6]To be honest, their ability to understand these prompts while Zhao Hai couldn’t understand the old prompts makes me wonder if there are multiple authors with varying levels of intelligence.

Chapter 227: Strength of the Radiance Church

Zhao Hai, Laura, Green, and Quinn John sat quietly within the living room of the Spatial Villa as they listened to Lyndsay Baker’s report about the Radiance Church.

After he’d finished transforming those white-clothed bishops into undead, he began to ask them about matters relating to the Radiance Church. Unsurprisingly, the one with the most detailed information was Lyndsay Baker. As such, he kept Lyndsay Baker back as he called for Green and the others before allowing him to continue to detail what he knew of the Radiance Church.

The Radiance Church was a great deal more formidable than what Zhao Hai and the others had thought. They currently controlled a dozen large and small duchies. Furthermore, several influential aristocrats from a few empires had already enlisted themselves as members of the Radiance Church. Specifically, they became the Radiance Church’s Protector Knights or elders.

Unfortunately, Lyndsay Baker had only been a white-clothed bishop. Although his father was a red-clothed archbishop, he didn’t have too much information to share. He only knew of some Grand Dukes and other influential nobles that had joined the Radiance Church; nothing more than that.

In addition to these influential nobles, Lyndsay Baker also knew of several mercenary groups and medium sized merchant firms that were affiliated with the Radiance Church. Several of those were even managed by him.

Other than that, Lyndsay Baker didn’t know anything else. Zhao Hai, however, had already benefited significantly from this. They now had a deeper understanding of the Radiance Church’s strength.

The Radiance Church was truly too formidable. When Zhao Hai had heard that the Black Magician Alliance had ten thousand black magicians, he’d thought the alliance was already pretty good. Now he understood that compared to the Radiance Church, they were really too far off.

They were really too clever as they pulled those influential aristocrats and Grand Dukes into their camp and made them either Protector Knights or elders. If the Radiance Church had a matter, then they would naturally help. Don’t underestimate the strength of these people. Even if they themselves didn’t directly assist, they would only have to say a few words and those lower aristocrats would naturally follow them as a way to curry favor and they would act on their order.

Because of all this, the Radiance Church had developed quickly within the past several years. The church didn’t just pull aristocrats in, but also used them to spread their influence. Due to a variety of benefits, those aristocrats were tied tightly to the church’s chariot.

With the help of those aristocrats, the black magicians had been repulsed within the continent. In such a short amount of time, black magicians had become isolated.

Compared to the Radiance Church, the Black Magician Alliance fell short. Maru didn’t speak of how many aristocrats had joined the Black Magician Alliance. This was, in fact, a weakness of the Black Magician Alliance.

One must understand that on the continent, the rules of aristocrats governed the commoners. Once the commoners had a preconceived idea about something, it would be very difficult to change it.

When comparing the Black Magician Alliance with the Radiance Church, the biggest flaw of the alliance was that it wasn’t under a unified leadership. The Radiance Church, however, was like the headquarters of light magicians. All light magicians were members of the Radiance Church and were under unified leadership. It goes without saying that all of their actions would naturally have a purpose. They had the upper hand when fighting against the divided black magicians.

While the black magicians had recently established the Black Magician Alliance, this alliance was, in fact, very loose. Wanting to achieve victory over the Radiance Church to any degree was impossible several times over.

Zhao Hai, however, didn’t think the black magicians would be suppressed by the Radiance Church to such a level. After all, the Black Magician Alliance was a loose organization with a lot of freedom. It was precisely because of this that they could develop anywhere. If the Radiance Church was the shining rays of the sun in the day, then the black magicians would be the dark clouds of the night sky. Wherever the sun doesn’t shine, there will always be a place for them to survive.

Furthermore, the Radiance Church wasn’t in a state of crisis at the moment. While they grew quickly and desperately pulled aristocrats into their camp, for any empire this became a factor of instability. Those great empires might possibly go against the Radiance Church. When this happens, the Radiance Church wouldn’t be able to continue their arrogance.

Zhao Hai thought that if the great empires were to deal with the Radiance Church, it would create a large opportunity for the black magicians. A great aristocrat didn’t wish to see one side being dominant; they wanted the play to be balanced. To deal with the Radiance Church, there was no more appropriate enemy than the black magicians. Once the Radiance Church began to threaten their rule, the great empires would start to check and balance them. They would begin to move their own influence in a battle of wits against the Radiance Church, and the black magicians would be a vital part of this.

Of course, at present, these were all just Zhao Hai’s conjectures[1]. Those great empires wouldn’t dare to easily move. Here on the Ark Continent, beliefs were free. Anyone could have faith in anything. If those great empires really had to deal with the Radiance Church, then they could just introduce new beliefs to replace the church’s. This way, they wouldn’t even need to use the black magicians.

The suppression of black magicians by the Radiance Church had been viewed with indifference by the great empires. Those great empires didn’t have a good impression of black magicians anyway, so they wouldn’t necessarily ask the black magicians to help deal with the Radiance Church.

After they listened to Lyndsay Baker’s explanation, Green and the others were in a heavy mood. The strength of the Radiance Church was beyond their imagination. Later on, when they began to act on the continent, they feared it would be difficult for them to move.

Zhao Hai waved and recalled Lyndsay Baker. He then turned to Green and said, “What does Grandpa Green and Grandpa Quinn John think of this?”

Green pondered for a moment. “They’re not easy to provoke. It seems we will have to implement our plans. First, we hide in the Beastfolk Prairie for a while.”

Quinn John nodded as he said, “Although the strength of the Radiance Church is formidable, it’s impossible for their influence to reach the Beastfolk Prairie. For the beastfolk, there is only one god. The Radiance Church is radically unpopular there. As such, nobody would buy into their words. After arriving in the Beastfolk Prairie, we will need to stay there for some time. After we’re out of the limelight, we can come back.”

Meirin[2] also nodded. “That’s good. Right now, the Radiance Church only knows the black magician identity of the Young Master and not of the Buda clan. If they knew of that, then we wouldn’t only be facing the Radiance Church, but the whole of the Aksu Empire[3]. If that happens, then we’ll need to hide in the Beastfolk Prairie for our lifetime. It’s good that they don’t know our identity. We’ll first hide in the Beastfolk Prairie and do business with the beastfolk. With this, they won’t be able to find out anything about us.”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “Even if we’re in the Beastfolk Prairie, we have to be careful. This time around, we bought many commodities. Those with high aspirations have surely looked into what we’ve bought and know we’re going to the Beastfolk Prairie. No matter if it’s the Radiance Church or Boric, they have both suffered losses at our hands and will surely retaliate. I fear that even if we hide in the Beastfolk Prairies, they won’t let us off.”

Green smiled faintly and said, “After they’ve attacked us several times, those fellows still want to retaliate against us. We have to think about this. I fear that the next time, we may have to deal with a Rank Nine expert.”

Quinn John chuckled. “That won’t be possible. As long as we’re in the Beastfolk Prairie, they won’t dare to send a Rank Nine expert to deal with us. It’s impossible for a Terran Rank Nine expert to enter the Beastfolk Prairie, otherwise a Rank Nine expert of the Beastfolk Prairie would strike at them and kill them on the spot. Moreover, it might provoke a war between the Terrans and beastfolk. Whether it is the Radiance Church or Boric, do either have the courage to do so?”

Green smiled. He certainly knew of this matter as he had participated in a war between the Terrans and beastfolk in the past. Beastfolk were a militant group. If the Terrans really did sent a Rank Nine expert to run around in the Beastfolk Prairie and cause storms, then what awaiting the Terrans would be thousands of cavalries.

Laura also smiled. “Actually, we’re thinking about this a little too much. Although Lyndsay Baker had told us a lot, don’t forget that he stated a few other points. The influence of the Radiance Church within the Rosen Empire isn’t very strong, and the Rosen Empire is the most powerful empire on the continent, incomparable.

“If the Radiance Church wants to win over the aristocrats of the Rosen Empire, then it would be too difficult. Once the king of the Rosen Empire knows, then the Radiance Church wouldn’t be able to move within the empire. The strength of the Rosen Empire is the same as the combined strength of several other empires. This can be an opportunity for us. With the Space, we can set up a transfer point within the Rosen Empire. We can slowly start developing within the Rosen Empire without needing to fear the Radiance Church.”

Quinn John shook his head. “We still need to be careful. Although the Rosen Empire is powerful, they probably don’t like black magicians. If the Radiance Church uses this point and tells them that they are dealing with black magicians, then they might turn and deal with us. This won’t make it easier for us.”

Laura nodded and Zhao Hai smiled slightly as he said, “Actually, we’re just repeating things over and over again. The issue here is my status as a black magicians. Don’t forget, everyone that as a magician, I can also use earth element, wind element, and light element magic. Light magicians are members of the Radiance Church, so this wouldn’t be a good choice of disguise. An earth element magician or wind element magician could be something I can pretend to be. Those people wouldn’t be able to keep a constant eye on me.

“Moreover, the Rosen Empire is quite a distance from the Aksu Empire[4]. How would the Aksu Empire’s great aristocrats know of my Buda clan identity there? Also, the Rosen Empire and Aksu Empire aren’t friendly neighbors. They wouldn’t help the Aksu Empire’s aristocrats deal with us, right?”

Everyone’s eyes couldn’t help but light up when they heard what Zhao Hai said. They had forgotten that Zhao Hai could use four types of elemental magic. Black magic and light magic couldn’t be used, so he would just use the other two. It was the same since he could still pretend to be a magician, which was a good idea.

* * *

Footnotes:

[1]Intelligent thoughts that make no sense when coming from a nobody like Zhao Hai. His intelligence is all over the place…

[2]She came out of nowhere.

[3]You’re already facing the whole of the Aksu Empire. Boric = King of the Aksu Empire. Radiance Church = Boric’s boss. Zhao Hai = enemy of Radiance Church. I doubt the aristocrats really care about you enough to really count in this. It’s basically Boric as the source of all Buda clan problems and Radiance Church as the source of all Zhao Hai black magician problems. I’m surprised Boric hadn’t already declared war on Zhao Hai.

[4]What? I thought they were right beside each other? Didn’t Boric’s old land border on the Rosen Empire’s lands?

Chapter 228: Beast God City

Meirin frowned. “Will this be alright? Aside from black magicians, almost all of the other magicians don’t wear magic hats. If the Young Master doesn’t wear a magic hat, then he’ll be identifiable. Even if we’re speaking about the Rosen Empire and don’t need to fear the aristocrats of the Aksu Empire, the Young Master had still drunk the Water of Nothingness. This fact is known by all. If they know of Young Master’s identity, then we will face greater troubles. After all, the Water of Nothingness is known to have no cure. If we make it known that we can cure the toxin of the Water of Nothingness, then it’ll cause trouble. Even if the Young Master denies it, they might find out about the Ghost Cane. If this secret gets out, then it’ll cause trouble as people try to grab it[1].”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly. “Alright then, I won’t pretend to be a normal magician. I’ll just stick to being a Divergent Warlock. Anyway, one doesn’t need to cultivate to use a Divergent Technique.”

Green frowned. “Actually, what the Young Master said about him being a Divergent Warlock isn’t incorrect, it’s just that his Divergent Technique is truly too formidable. As such, we shouldn’t let others know of it. If the Young Master reveals his identity, then we will gain more problems. No matter what, the identity of the Young Master shouldn’t be shown there. We cannot let them know of the Young Master’s identity.”

Quinn John nodded. “This is right. If we let them know of Zhao Hai’s identity, then it’ll be very troublesome for us. How about this? Why don’t we let him wear a mask? There are many Divergent Warlocks on the continent with unique appearances, so if Zhao Hai wore a mask then nobody should be able to recognize him.”

Zhao Hai frowned. “But if that’s the case, I won’t be able to wear this magic robe. This magic robe was given to me by Laura, so I like it very much.”

When she heard Zhao Hai’s words, Laura’s face turned red[2]. As the others laughed, Laura turned more embarrassed. Although her heart felt sweet, Laura still stretched out a hand to pinch Zhao Hai’s back.

Laura’s attempt to hide it naturally wasn’t hidden to Green and the others, and this made them laugh louder. Only Meg’s facial expression was gloomy as she’d paid attention to Laura and saw it all clearly[3].

Meirin smiled and said, “Young Master won’t need to worry about your magic robe. We can just change your attire. Whatever a Divergent Warlock uses, so long as the style of the robe is altered then nobody will be able to see through it.”

Zhao Hai nodded. “The mask is something that’s needed, but I don’t want it to be the type that blocks the entirety of my face. That’ll be too stuffy.”

Everyone laughed. It seemed that everything had been set. It can be said that the matters within the Purcell Duchy has been left behind.

Once the laughter stopped, Laura[4] continued, “Since we’re going to the Beastfolk Prairie, we will need to find a place to live. I had some businesses in the Beastfolk Prairie, but trade there isn’t great. Only a handful of ethnic tribes do business with me, and none of them war tribes. As such, the income isn’t great. I had kept a steward in the Beastfolk Prairie named Artest[5]. He’s a very loyal person and someone we can rely upon completely. He is, however, there to work. One must know that things are very different within the Beastfolk Prairie. Generally, if we make agreements with the buyers of our commodities, we then transport the cargo. If we just place it wherever, then we may get robbed.”

Zhao Hai didn’t do any research about business, nor did he have any contact with the beastfolk. As such, he didn’t understand much and had no real say in these matters.

Quinn John nodded. “Right now, what we must do is establish a relationship with one of the war tribes first. So long as we create a business around a war tribe, nobody would dare to touch us later on in the Beastfolk Prairie. When we act within the Beastfolk Prairie, we can rely on a tribe’s War Flag. No one would dare to move against an ethnic group within the prairies.”

Zhao Hai wasn’t able to understand any of this, but Green knew that the war tribes were the kings of the Beastfolk Prairie. In fact, it could be said that the Beastfolk Prairie was a collection of several large and small bandit groups. The larger tribes would be the bigger bandit groups, while the smaller tribes were smaller bandit groups. The bigger bandits robbed the smaller bandits. This was the rule of survival within the Beastfolk Prairie.

Because of this, if the beastfolk had a harder time making a living, they would rob from others. To continue living was one of the reasons why the beastfolk and Terrans fought against one another.

These war tribes were the powerful fighting ethnic groups within the beastfolk race. They were the biggest tribes—the big bandit groups.

If you only did business with some regular ethnic tribes or ordinary war tribes, then you’d be unsafe. Only when you did business with the formidable war tribes would you be safe from danger. This was how business was done within the Beastfolk Prairie.

Each war tribe had their own flag, and this war flag represented the dignity of the war tribe. Anyone who dared to offend those with that war flag would be hunted down endlessly by that war tribe and killed.

War tribes held a high degree of respect towards the merchants they worked with. To ensure the safety of those merchants, they would give them their war flag and allow them to raise it upon their caravans. This way, they could guarantee the safety of those merchants. Otherwise, the caravans would meet with smaller bandit tribes within the Beastfolk Prairie, which was unsafe.

Zhao Hai nodded. “What commodities are best sold within the Beastfolk Prairie?”

Quinn John smiled lightly. “Food[6] is ranked first. Second is salt and weapons take third place. These are the things that are scarcest within the Beastfolk Prairie.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly. “Salt and iron, these items are ones we can’t get. Food, however, isn’t a problem. In any case, once we arrive in the Beastfolk Prairie, they won’t be able to gain control of our food supply. This is the same for those beastfolk if they tried to rob and steal from us. We can grow a variety of grain products within the Space and then supply it to the beastfolk.”

Quinn John nodded. “This is exactly what we want. Since the price of food in the Beastfolk Prairie is high, if we lower our prices then we will most certainly become the most popular merchants there. Moreover, vegetables is also one of the most scarce produce for those beastfolk. Since we have the Space, we won’t have any problem with transporting vegetables. If we can transport vegetables, then I believe they will certainly sell well.”

Zhao Hai nodded. “While I say we cannot supply their other needs, if it’s just vegetables and grains, then we can openly and widely supply them. We can also trade large quantities of magic beasts with them, which is a good thing.”

Laura smiled. “With the things you have here, I don’t need to be worried. I do think, however, that we should first set up a transfer point within the Beastfolk Prairie. We will also need to set one up inside the Rosen Empire. We cannot always take magic beasts from the Beastfolk Prairie and just keep them stored. We’ll need to get rid of them, and we can do that by selling them to the Rosen Empire. As such, we can turn grains and magic beasts into money.”

Zhao Hai nodded. “This is also good. Right, Laura, where are your people located within the Beastfolk Prairie at the moment?”

Laura quickly replied, “Right now, they’re at Three Paths Curve[7] near Yaja River[8]. It’s the largest of two rivers in the Beastfolk Prairie, and Three Paths Curve is the reason why the riverway bends and the basis for its fame. The appearance of the water is gentle, and it isn’t too far from the border near Black Mountain Fortress within the Purcell Duchy. It’ll take us five days to reach there.”

Although Zhao Hai hadn’t been to the Beastfolk Prairie and didn’t know the situation there, he did have a certain understanding with regards to Yaja River. He knew that it stemmed from the Extreme North Ice Origin[9], which was one of the continent’s five great restricted areas. It shared this honor with the Carrion Swamp. This river crosses through the entire Beastfolk Prairie and into the Purcell Duchy. Once it reached the Purcell Duchy, it took up the name of Jade Belt River[10].

That was right, Yaja River was the upper part of Jade Belt River. As such, the Purcell Duchy had a detailed record about Yaja River. The Yaja River was also the Beastfolk Prairie’s most famous river and was referred to as the beastfolk’s mother river.

No matter if it was herding or for living, the beastfolk and water were inseparable. The Yaja River wasn’t only the largest flowing body of water, but it was also a gentle one. The beastfolk wouldn’t just be able to fetch water from it, but also fish from it. For the beastfolk, the Yaja River was their mother. Generations of beastfolk were raised by it.

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “That’s not too far from the Purcell Duchy then. Right, which tribe are you in contact with? Is it safe?”

Laura smiled and said, “It’s secure. My business has contact with two tribes. One is the Cattle-people Tribe[11], the other is the Fragrant Pig Tribe[12]. These two are ethnic groups. The Cattle-people Tribe raise cattle while the Fragrant Pig Tribe is also very famous on the continent. These two beastfolk tribes are very mild. Moreover, they are near to the Purcell Duchy. The magic beasts they produce are meat producing magic beasts, and the income from this is quite good.”

Zhao Hai nodded. His understanding of the beastfolk wasn’t much[13]. One must know that there were a thousand different beastfolk races. Take, for example, the Cattle-people Tribe. They were divided into rhinoceroses, yaks, oxen, longhorn cattles, buffaloes, and many other dozens of races. Wanting to memorize all these races was like trying to memorize a whole book. Zhao Hai didn’t have that kind of ability[14].

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “First, we’ll go and see Three Paths Curve and have a look. Then we’ll proceed onward into the Beastfolk Prairie. Since the Beastfolk Prairie is big, we must find a suitable place to set up the transfer point. It has to be near a region inhabited by a large tribe.”

Laura thought about it for a while, then her eyes shone brightly. “I thought of a place. Although the place is far and deep within the Beastfolk Prairie, it is the holy land in the hearts of the beastfolk.”

After Laura said this, the people in the room knew what Laura meant[15]. Although they couldn’t have possibly gone there, they had all heard of it; the only city within the Beastfolk Prairie—Beast God City[16].

Beast God City was famous among the beastfolk. Within the Beastfolk Prairies, there was only vast and endless grasslands. There were no mountains, no stones for production. As such, constructing a city was too difficult.

The establishment of Beast God City, however, was actually a miracle. A beastmen-created miracle.

* * *

Footnotes:

[1]Congratulations. You already revealed the Ghost Cane was special. For no true reason, people will assume it’s the reason for your OPness and aim for that. Even if you say it can’t be taken from you, then how about if you die?

[2]Probably from embarrassment, cause that was sappy as heck and creepy. Author, please go on a date…

[3]Does anyone else feel a bit awkward when reading the author’s attempts at romance? I get creeped out just editing it…

[4]RAWS says Meirin spoke here, but Laura is the one with contacts… I am also wondering if all my previous uses of Meirin was actually Laura…

[5]阿泰 – ā tài. Cause no point in ruining a good GTL name choice.

[6]I should note that 粮 can mean either food or grain and 粮食 generally means food/food so food. Sometimes, only 粮 is used, so we use context to switch between grains and food, which can get confusing. Even worse when he’s a farmer and grains is his fastest growing produce. This issue was most prevalent during the food crisis.

[7]三道弯 – Sān dào wān.

[8]雅加河 – Yǎ jiā hé.

[9]极北冰原 – Jí běi bīngyuán. Tentative name. Can also be Polar North. Can also be Ice Source.

[10]Jade Belt River was the place where the Universal Origin Sword Saint had fought that other unknown Rank Nine and turned the river into a lake.

[11]牛人族 – Niúrén zú.

[12]香猪族 – Xiāng zhū zú.

[13]Oh my… we get it already, he knows nothing. Must be the 4th time this came up. We should just rename this chapter to “Clueless about Beastfolk–Zhao Hai.”

[14]No, but as MC he has selective plot memory. If something happens around him, he’ll have read some obscure entry about it in a book somewhere. Or someone else would have. Like when the Devouring Blood Mosquitoes came up. “Unknown, unknown, oh, now we both remember it.”

[15]Probably except for Zhao Hai, who knows nothing about anything there.

[16]兽神城 – Shòu shénchéng.

Chapter 229: Occupying an Area

Everyone understood what Beast God City signified. It was the holy land in the hearts of every beastfolk. The city was placed on the original land of the beastfolk, and was made of hay and mud. But the water used for the mud wasn’t ordinary water. This mud was instead created with the blood of various magic beasts that they had originally raised, so one could actually call this beast blood mud.

Due to the lack of lumber in the Beastfolk Prairie, the wood that should have been used within Beast God City was instead replaced with the bones of magic beasts. These reasons were the basis for the city’s name of Beast God City.

To construct Beast God City, every beastfolk tribe had to live frugally for decades. They didn’t even know how many magic beasts had been sacrificed to complete the city.

This was the holy land in the hearts of every beastfolk. The position of Beast God City was close to the Extreme North Ice Origin. This was because the beastfolk had repelled the demons within the Extreme North Ice Origin, so they constructed Beast God City as an icon to commemorate that victory.

Furthermore, there was no City Lord or city garrison. Beast God City, however, was the safest city on the entire continent. The beastfolk population within Beast God City numbered almost one million. Within a thousand miles around the city, violence and theft wasn’t allowed. The penalty for either was execution on the spot.

This was the custom of Beast God City and it had been set during its founding. No one could destroy Beast God City because of the formidable war tribes that lived there. Moreover, it wasn’t just a single ethnic race that lived there, but a cohabitation of various ethnic races. This was the area where the most violent beastfolk became the most honest.

After many years of development, Beast God City became the Beastfolk Prairie’s largest commodities distribution center. Every day was lively as merchants from every race and tribe did business within Beast God City.

Although violence wasn’t permitted in Beast God City, if a merchant dared to deceive a beastfolk then they would certainly be unfortunate. What Beast God City prohibited was violence among the tribes and ethnic races, so if a Terran dared to act unreasonable, then Beast God City’s law enforcement team would act. These beastfolk weren’t ones to be trifled with. They would kill the Terran, and moreover wouldn’t have any regard over their circumstances. If one dared to deceive a beastfolk, then no matter what tribe, they wouldn’t give any opportunity for an explanation and would just move to execute.

For merchants like Laura who didn’t wish to make dirty money, Beast God City was the best destination. Although they wouldn’t be able to set up a store there, a tent could still be established to start their business.

Before, Laura had wanted to go to Beast God City, but unfortunately her business had still been too small scale back then so she was unqualified to trade there. If someone wanted to do business in Beast God City and the commodities they had on hand came up short, then they’d be extremely embarrassed. To be able to make transactions in Beast God City, one must have at least 5 million kilograms of food[1]. Laura didn’t have capital that large to bring in such an amount of commodities back then.

Now, however, things were different as they had the Space. If Zhao Hai saved all the bamboo rice being harvested, then they could hoard 10 million kilograms of bamboo rice per day. This wasn’t a small amount. With so much food in their possession, Laura could certainly dare to walk into Beast God City to do business.

Due to these reasons, Beast God City became famous on the continent. Whether it were the Terrans or other races, they had all heard of it. After all, the beastfolk were a large and numerous race on the continent, and in the hearts of these beastfolk, Beast God City was their holy land.

When he heard Laura refer to Beast God City with her description, Quinn John nodded and said, “I also think Beast God City is the most appropriate place. If we do business there and don’t deceive the beastfolk, then we won’t have to worry about trading there. What’s more, security is guaranteed. Within a thousand mile radius of Beast God City, violence and theft isn’t allowed. Even the beastfolk wouldn’t dare to create any disputes, not to mention us Terrans. If someone dares to move against us there, then they are just courting death[2].”

Green also nodded. “I agree. I heard that in Beast God City there are five Rank Nine experts there all year round. Although they don’t manage the city, they’ll immediately move to execute any expert that dares make trouble in Beast God City. Those five beastfolk within Beast God City are called the Five Great Law Enforcers.”

Nodding, Quinn John said, “Those Five Great Law Enforcers are famous beastfolk experts. Their battle strength is formidable. Also, several large war tribes live near Beast God City and those large tribes also have their own Rank Nine experts. If a matter occurs in Beast God City then those Rank Nine experts will be able to rush forth at a moment’s notice and ensure the security of Beast God City. I can say that the quantity of Rank Nine experts in Beast God City wouldn’t be less than ten.”

Zhao Hai was surprised. He didn’t think that the defenses of Beast God City would be at such a level. Ten Rank Nine experts. This almost caught up to the defense of Flower City[3].

This was about right. At the moment, no matter what Zhao Hai’s status was, it would be equal to zero in Beast God City. The beastfolk wouldn’t accept any status given by Terrans. Even if a Terran was a murderer or arsonist, to the beastfolk they didn’t care as they only saw you as a Terran. They wouldn’t treat you like a criminal so long as you were honest within the Beastfolk Prairie.

This was what Zhao Hai wanted. The Radiance Church had a strong influence within Terran territories, so he had to avoid it. Zhao Hai could provide food, something the beastfolk needed the most, and so long as he established a relationship with the beastfolk, the Radiance Church wouldn’t be able to move against him so casually.

This thought made Zhao Hai smile. “That’s right, it’s only with Beast God City’s security that we can feel relieved enough to do business there. With this, we can start tomorrow and immediately leave. First, I’ll order an Eagle Virtuous Phantasm to bring the Ghost Cane into the Beastfolk Prairie. Then we can use a saddled horse carriage to head for Beast God City. This trip will allow us to understand how the beastfolk live and learn their habits as well as observe the surrounding terrain. What do you all think of this?”

Green nodded. “I agree. In the end, our biggest secret is this Space, and it needs to be upgraded as soon as possible. That is our most pressing matter. Since the Beastfolk Prairie not only has an abundance of magic beasts but also a variety of plants, then even if those plants aren’t magic plants, they can still contribute to the upgrade of the Space. Also, the Spatial Ranch level is too low. I think we should increase its level as soon as possible.”

Laura and the others simultaneously nodded. With regards to the Space’s mysterious ability, they had understood a little of it after several days. This Space was truly too mysterious. If they could upgrade it as soon as possible, then the benefits for them would be very large.

Nodding, Laura said, “Alright, I think we should do this. As the matter stands, even though it would take a long time for us, the benefits we will obtain would also be very large. Let’s do it.”

Zhao Hai nodded. “We will now prepare the food so that later on, we won’t be in short supply once we do transactions with the beastfolk. Moreover, we must finish the transformation plan for the Black Waste as soon as possible. We should also prepare a carriage. When we arrive in the Beastfolk Prairie, we can start to sell food to any tribe that wants it. This will certainly make our products very popular.”

Laura nodded and said, “Clearing the way with food. This is the best way to do it, but we must overcome problems and lay a foundation ahead of time in order to let those large war tribes notice us. With this, once we move into Beast God City, it’ll help us a lot. One must know that occupying a place in Beast God City isn’t easy.”

Quinn John nodded. “In the past, we’d planned to go and do business in Beast God City. Unfortunately, our foundations was still too thin and we gave up in the end. We do, however, understand a little about the situation of Beast God City. We know that there is a million beastfolk living in the city. It can be regarded as a great city, but since way back then, major merchant clans on the continent have already put up shop there. The places that could be occupied by merchants have already been taken. If we go there and want to occupy a place, I fear it won’t be easy. If we can show them that we have a lot of food in our hands that we can sell, then there will be more certainty of being able to occupy a place there.”

Laura nodded. “In the Beastfolk Prairie, so long as the beastfolk think that we’re good people, we can occupy a place in Beast God City. With that, we will be able to stand firmly there.”

Quinn John looked at Zhao Hai and said, “There’s no need to be so curious. Although they constructed Beast God City, the city had been built using the blood of magic beasts to make mud for the construction. As such, there weren’t many buildings created. The majority of the city is just stretches of open land. There wouldn’t be any stores, but tents instead. If we wish to open a shop there, you’d need to occupy an area and then it would be alright.”

Zhao Hai nodded. He thought about how there wouldn’t be any high rise buildings in the city. A large city with a population of a million, how much area did this cover? Furthermore, the city was also built using magic beast blood mud. How many magic beasts did they need to kill? To be honest, if the beastfolk could build a modern urban constructed city, then it would be a miracle. How much force would be needed to do so? If the city had high rise buildings, then needless to say the amount of magic beast blood mud would reach an astronomical figure. He feared the beastfolk couldn’t afford to do so.

With this thought, Zhao Hai’s eyes shone brightly. “The Space can produce a lot of fruit trees and we can also move a lot of stone through it. So long as we can occupy a place, we can construct a wooden house. There is only one Beast God City so by the time we head there our names won’t be unknown.”

Laura nodded. “This is also a good idea. Those beastfolk handle matters in a very direct manner. If we want to obtain their respect, then we cannot hide anything and must show off our strength. This will allow the beastfolk to see that we have the skill, and with this they will place importance on us.”

Zhao Hai nodded. “Alright, things are set. Cai’er, arrange it like this. First, plant a lot of bamboo rice, but don’t stop planting the fruit oil. We want a lot of them as we will primarily be selling those low-end products first.”

Cai’er complied immediately and made the preparations.

* * *

Footnotes:

[1]Original was 10 million jin, with a jin being 0.5 kg. 5 million kilograms is 11 million lbs, give or take 23,000 lbs.

[2]I hope the author realizes that he could have gotten rid of all that narrative before this paragraph and used this as the description for BGC…

[3]So he does still remember the Rank Nines there. Damn coward.

Chapter 230: Into the Prairie

The next morning, Zhao Hai followed the plan they’d agreed on yesterday and released two blood-colored Eagle Virtuous Phantasms and gave them his Ghost Cane. Then he ordered the blood-colored eagles to fly in the direction of Ironwall Fortress[1].

Ironwall Fortress was very far from the Black Waste. If one were to travel by saddled horse carriage, then it would take about half a month to reach it. By horse it would take around ten days. Of course, this was assuming one were traveling leisurely and without haste.

This Ironwall Fortress was the first line of defense for the Purcell Duchy against the Beastfolk Prairie. It was the firmest defensive line in the Purcell Duchy and garrisoned 20,000 elite Benniu Guards[2] the whole year round. These 20,000 elite Benniu Guards, when facing the non-elite beastfolk army, could stand against 100,000 of them. They could even hold that defensive line for several days.

The most important part was that the Purcell clan kept a magician corps inside Ironwall Fortress. This magician corps couldn’t actually be called a corps, but instead a squad. Altogether, there were only 50 Rank Four to Rank Six magicians in the corps, and around 200 Rank One to Rank Three magicians.

There were many Rank One to Rank Three magicians on the continent. Some of those magicians could only drift along with a mercenary group and wouldn’t have many good days. As such, defending Ironwall Fortress was comparatively better. The allowance was good and so long as there wasn’t war they would be very safe.

Although the number of magicians in this corps didn’t amount to much and were of low ranks, in a war they wielded a might that was quite powerful. A common soldier wouldn’t be able to do anything while a magician would be able to cast area of effect offensive magic techniques. With regards to a battle, this was very useful.

Drawing on a modern analogy, a common soldier could be compared to a millet and rifle soldier. They could only attack one at a time like a single-shot rifle. A magician, on the other hand, would be like a machine gun. When they were connected, magicians would be able to cause mass destruction. This was the difference[3].

The reason Ironwall Fortress was called such was due to the brilliant record made by the Purcell Duchy’s elite Benniu Guards. With 50,000 soldiers they were able to block a 500,000 strong beastfolk army’s offense for half a month. When the Aksu Empire’s reinforcements finally arrived, the 50,000 strong elite Benniu Guard was down to a mere 5,000 and the walls of Ironwall Fortress was dyed with blood.

Due to this service done by the Benniu Guard, they became famous. As such, the Purcell clan, after this battle, obtained the position of a Grand Duke household. This was the time when the present Purcell Duchy was established.

It could be said that Ironwall Fortress wasn’t only famous for the Terrans, but also for the beastfolk. The beastfolk had tried many times to invade, but was always blocked by Ironwall Fortress.

Zhao Hai and the others sat in the living room, watching the scenery shown on the screen. To be honest, Zhao Hai didn’t know much of the Purcell Duchy[4]. These days, he only understood the situation in Casa City. He’d only travelled from Black Mountain Fortress to Casa City, so with regards to the foundations of the city, he didn’t know much.

Now he had the opportunity to gain a better understanding. Although he could only take a glance at everything since the Eagle Virtuous Phantasms were flying, it was still better than nothing.

By the time the sky turned dark, the blood-colored Eagle Virtuous Phantasms had left the boundary of the Purcell Duchy. They had not officially entered the Beastfolk Prairie and was now over a hundred kilometers[5] away from Ironwall Fortress[6]. They hadn’t seen any beastfolk tribes yet, but this wasn’t surprising. Beastfolk tribes wouldn’t be so close to Ironwall Fortress, otherwise the garrisoned troops would rush out and exterminate them. This was due to a fear that the beastfolk might spy on their military.

With regards to this situation, the beastfolk accepted it since the Terrans couldn’t arbitrarily send many armed soldiers into the Beastfolk Prairie either.

Now that the eagles were over a hundred kilometers from Ironwall Fortress, Zhao Hai took the blood-colored Eagle Virtuous Phantasms back. They were preparing to travel on via carriage starting tomorrow. After all, they were now in the Beastfolk Prairie. If they wanted to do business with the beastfolk, then depending on the flying blood-colored eagles wouldn’t be enough.

In the evening, Zhao Hai went back to the Black Waste to continue improving the land. With relation to the Space’s recent upgrades, he could now improve more land each day. He improved 700,000 square meters[7] of land, which wasn’t a small area.

Zhao Hai, however, was very careful. He improved the land that was covered by the smog while those outside the area stayed the same.

After such long use of Spatial Water in the irrigation process, the outer perimeter of Fort Iron Mountain could now be planted with ordinary vegetables. In addition, the corn within the valley was about the mature.

This was very good news for Zhao Hai. The Spatial Water could be used to irrigate and unexpectedly it could also reduce the maturity time for the crops. For Zhao Hai, this was very important.

Laura was also very busy. She hadn’t been to the Black Waste before, but since this was her home now, she naturally had to understand the Black Waste.

Laura understood that the Black Waste was a really large place. This excited her and increased her enthusiasm. She was ready to regulate the Black Waste and go all out.

Zhao Hai was tolerant of Laura’s enthusiasm. He didn’t have any reason to block it anyway. It seemed that right now, Laura had found a new and novel toy and was fiddling around with it non-stop. If he wanted to stop her at this time, she would definitely not comply[8].

Fortunately, Zhao Hai still came out of the Space the next morning with three people, Laura, Meg, and Nier.

With three beauties accompanying him, Zhao Hai was of course happy. Some time ago, Meg hadn’t been very happy after she’d determined the relationship between Zhao Hai and Laura. Zhao Hai didn’t have much time back then as he’d had a lot of matters to deal with, so he wasn’t able to have a discussion with Meg about it all. Afterward, no one knew what Laura had told Meg, but Meg was now happy. Although Zhao Hai didn’t know why this was, since she was happy he also felt relieved.

The four of them now sat within Laura’s original carriage. Snowflake celestial foals[9] pulled the carriage and the wagons behind it. All of these were once the property of Laura’s original stores. Since Laura was leaving, then naturally the wagons would be put to use.

Since they were now venturing into the Beastfolk Prairie, those wagons were loaded with food. There was a long way to go so there wasn’t much food loaded onto the wagons themselves. Each wagon held half a tonne of commodities. 50 wagons total held 25 tonnes[10].

25 tonnes of food. With regards to a small tribe, it wasn’t a small amount. For a medium sized tribe, however, it wasn’t much.

Those 50 wagons were all manned by undead. They drove the wagons and also protected them at the same time. The remaining undead were all placed in the Black Waste by Zhao Hai.

When the four of them appeared in the Beastfolk Prairie, they weren’t that surprised. The scenery in the prairie was pretty much the same as the Space’s. Since the Space now had a prairie as a background, and it was also more stunning than the Beastfolk Prairie, the scenery around them didn’t have much of an attraction.

Aside from the undead driving the wagons, Zhao Hai also released a hundred blood-colored Eagle Virtuous Phantasms. These weren’t used for attacking, but for scouting the area. Since the Beastfolk Prairie wasn’t that safe, those blood-colored Eagle Virtuous Phantasms were there to act as insurance.

Zhao Hai looked around at the prairies while Meg stared at Zhao Hai. Her gaze was filled with the infatuation of one that was charmed[11]. When she looked at Zhao Hai’s appearance, Meg remembered what Laura had said a couple days ago.

That day when Laura and Zhao Hai had secretly talked, Laura saw that Meg had followed them and seen what had happened between the two of them. She also saw Meg’s expression becoming odd. Laura was clever and understood that Meg was worried.

Later on, Laura searched for Meg and spoke with her. Laura knew from looking at Zhao Hai that he also held affection for Meg[12] and that he couldn’t forget his feelings for her. Laura, however, had decided to marry Zhao Hai. Naturally, she hoped that everything around Zhao Hai would be fine and that unpleasant things wouldn’t appear. The rear court especially couldn’t catch on fire[13].

Presently, their foundations were too thin and there were many issues that had happened. If a fire started in the rear court, then it wouldn’t do any good for Zhao Hai if every day there was a fire.

As Zhao Hai’s wife, Laura thought that she should fix this unstable factor and nip it in the bud. Therefore, Laura looked for Meg and thoroughly discussed things over with her.

Laura didn’t say much. She just told Meg that during the time Zhao Hai had proposed to her, he’d also told her that he would certainly marry the two of them, so she told Meg to not be worried.

Meg didn’t think Laura would be this frank and direct. This made Meg somewhat embarrassed. At the same time, she also accepted Laura. As such, after they spoke, their relationship became better.

These two women were in love with the same man, so they would naturally and wholeheartedly consider everything for the sake of this man. On the Ark Continent, men had the right to marry several wives, and this was normal. Thus, they weren’t jealous, and for Zhao Hai, this solved a lot of trouble[14].

Zhao Hai didn’t know any of this. To be honest, his feelings with regards to this was really dull. Fortunately, there was Laura. Otherwise the problem would have been troublesome.

Due to their conversation, the knot in Meg’s heart was untied and the last of her worries vanished. Therefore, she was very happy.

For Meg, status wasn’t important so long as she was beside Zhao Hai. After Laura told her Zhao Hai intended to marry her, everything else was ignored.

Laura also noted Meg’s performance and didn’t say anything. Her heart, however, felt slightly sour, but she didn’t have any means of mending it. After all, Meg had known Zhao Hai a lot longer than she[15]. Even if she was angry, it was useless since her heart was already firmly tied with Zhao Hai.

At this time, a blood-colored eagle Zhao Hai had ordered to fly to the east suddenly flew back and alerted them. It kept circling Zhao Hai’s head. Zhao Hai now knew that a situation had occurred in the east.

* * *

Footnotes:

[1]铁壁要塞 – Tiě bì yàosài.

[2]If people remember from long ago, we’d decided on Benniu. The equivalent names were just plain bad, such as Rushing Bull. Just treat Benniu in the same line of names as Taoyuan and Higanbana.

[3]And is also Fantasy Logic 101. Who is he explaining this to?

[4]We just had 20 chapters of him saying he didn’t know anything about the Beastfolk Prairie but knew about the Purcell Duchy, and now we get this. Zhao Hai, go back to school. Go to ‘Nobles Academy for Dandies’ or something.

[5]It said a few hundred li (里), a li being half a kilometer. A hundred kilometers is about 62 international miles.

[6]So basically, after that long ass infodump on Ironwall Fortress, we don’t even get to see it. *applauds genius author for super duper excellent amazing writing skills* I don’t care if it comes up later, it was still an unnecessary infodump.

[7]The original RAW said 1000 mu. Since we decided before that mu would only be used in the Space, this was then converted into square meters, which is 666666.7. Rounded up to a clean number of 700.000, but remember that it’s really 666666.7. 1000 mu is 165 acres.

[8]What the hell? What was the point with this paragraph? Author just demoted her to a little kid with a new toy and Zhao Hai the understanding parent, for what reason?

[9]雪花神驹 – Xuěhuā shén jū. I hope this isn’t a thing, cause this name is horrible… Anyways, Snow + Flower = Snowflake. Divine/God/Celestial + colt/foal = whatever.

[10]Alrighty, so the original numbers for each wagon was 1000 jin, with jin being half a kilogram. As such, 1000 jin meant 500 kilograms. 500 kilograms was also half a tonne, so using some math, for the total we get 50,000 jin = 25,000 kilograms = 25 tonnes. Oh yea, it’s ‘metric ton’ for people in the US and maybe Canada. Anyways, 50,000 jin = 55,000 lbs.

[11]Author, please note that just saying a person fell in love is the weakest way to write a romance… us readers find her love so random that we didn’t even realize it until you stated it the fifth time.

[12]Well, he also straight up told this to you…

[13]In ancient China, the Emperor would hold sessions with his government in the front court while the harem would stay in the rear court. The Emperor was in charge of the front, the Empress in charge of the back. The harem would have to be kept under control of the Empress, else you get chaos and all that. Well, I’m just assuming this saying had ties to this concept. Don’t kill me for my flawed history please.

[14]I just give up on Author and his wish-fulfillment thoughts on love.

[15]I think the author forgot that a good portion of that time was spent with Adam the dandy. Did that phase have 0 effect on her feelings??? Or did author just not realize it was a big part? It wasn’t even a slow progression from her dislike of Adam to love of Zhao Hai… OH! I remember! Zhao Hai threw her into his brainwashing Space and then she suddenly fell for him. If you don’t believe me, go back and check!! Damn brainwashing Space…

Chapter 231: Unyielding

Although the blood-colored Eagle Virtuous Phantasms couldn’t talk, they could still understand Zhao Hai’s words. As such, it took Zhao Hai a few days to teach them simple ways to pass him information like changing their posture in flight and through the sounds they made.

As if following a flight ratio, executing several spins in the air would tell the number of people while with a few cries it would report the number of cavalrymen, and so on. In the end, these blood-colored Eagle Virtuous Phantasms could now act as the simplest of airborne scouts.

Zhao Hai carefully watched the blood-colored eagle until it flew away, then turned to Laura and said, “The eastern area has a situation. There’s a thousand cavalrymen approaching us, and they aren’t beastfolk.”

Laura gawked and her complexion changed as she said, “I understand that the Benniu Guards would leave the walls of Ironwall Fortress every two weeks to patrol the area. It seems we were unfortunate to have crossed them today.”

Zhao Hai wrinkled his brow and asked, “Then what should we do? Should we go back into the Space and hide?”

Laura shook her head. “We shouldn’t do that. We can just give them some money and let them go. After all, everyone is aware that the beastfolk buy food here. Moreover, the Purcell Duchy also hopes that everybody can go and sell food to the beastfolk. For the beastfolk, as long as they have food and drink, they wouldn’t move. The main purpose of the cavalry patrol is to check whether or not some beastfolk tribes had ventured here[1].”

Zhao Hai nodded. “Since you have experience on these sorts of things, how much do you think we should pay in order to cross the border successfully?”

Laura smiled faintly. “For this, I fear we will need a thousand gold coins. Moreover, I can’t just go there and pay it myself. It’s better for Grandpa Green to do it. After all, he’s a Rank Eight expert so those knights wouldn’t make it too difficult for him. If I go and they see that I’m a woman, then they will make it difficult for me.”

Zhao Hai’s complexion changed. “How come? Do they dare be so rude?”

Laura forced a smile and said, “Don’t forget, if they really want to be impolite to us, then they could just kill us all. Like that, they could just explain that we were killed by beastfolk. This place isn’t that deep into the Beastfolk Prairie, nor is it a part of Ironwall Fortress. Those elite Benniu Guards could easily become robbers here.”

Zhao Hai sighed. “Does Grand Duke Evan not have any control over this?”

Laura smiled. “Control? How could he control them? The soldiers here in Ironwall Fortress must maintain their wildness since they’re situated on the border adjacent to the Beastfolk Prairie. This is a place lacking in commodities. Adding in the fact that they’ve been here for a number of years, their hearts are probably low and would need a way to vent. Therefore, even if they see it, this matter has become something that those in power would turn a blind eye towards. As I was saying, a merchant wanting to do business here in the Beastfolk Prairie would, to put it bluntly, smuggle as they are supporting the enemy. This is illegal, so even if the soldiers killed them no one would say anything[2].”

Zhao Hai nodded and he shifted into the Space. He then went to Fort Iron Mountain and called for Green and explained the matter to him.

He then took an ordinary pouch and placed a thousand gold coins in it and gave it to Green. Then he appeared with Green on the carriage.

Zhao Hai released a wind-chasing horse and let Green ride it, but the caravan didn’t stop and continued on. He knew they couldn’t move faster than those elite Benniu Guards. This place was too open and those elite Benniu Guards[3] weren’t that far. Soon they would be approaching them.

Sure enough, in less than an hour, a light rumbling sound could be heard approaching from the east. Experienced soldiers would know that this was a brigade of cavalrymen in action. Zhao Hai and the others turned their heads to take a look and saw a team of a thousand cavalrymen coming in from the eastern area at a fast pace.

Zhao Hai’s caravan immediately stopped. They didn’t, however, move normally like a caravan should and into a circle formation as it was irrelevant.

Laura and the other two ladies didn’t come out. Those three were rare beauties. If they came out, then it would attract the attention of those cavalrymen and cause trouble[4].

Zhao Hai had heard of a few stories from Earth. When the soldiers in the army were serving for three years and suddenly saw Diaochan[5], they would compete to get her. Those cavalrymen may have been stationed there for longer than three years. If they saw Laura and the other two ladies, then while their might couldn’t add up to Diaochan, whether it would be enough to hinder their trip to the Beastfolk Prairie was hard to say[6].

Leaving the carriage, Zhao Hai moved slowly to the front of the caravan and silently stood there. He wore the black magician robe and held his Ghost Cane in order to bluff the cavalry.

Green stood at the side of the carriage. He didn’t put on his full body armor and instead wore simple warrior’s clothing. No mask adorned his face, and his hair was combed neatly. With his Spiritwind Sword at his waist, he looked like the typical expert warrior.

Zhao Hai wanted this kind of imposing manner since it would be impossible for Ironwall Fortress to know of Green[7]. His imposing manner would make it so that those who didn’t know of their bottom line wouldn’t act too unreasonably towards them, else they would battle. Zhao Hai wasn’t afraid of these cavalrymen, but he didn’t wish to come into conflict with them. No matter what, Evan had still been good to them[8].

Soon the team of cavalry arrived before Zhao Hai. They were about a hundred meters away from them and didn’t attack, rather, they stopped and were sizing up Zhao Hai.

Zhao Hai also watched these people. They sat astride the Rank Three magic beast, flaming horse. These flaming horses wore heavy armor and those atop them wore heavy cavalrymen equipment. The helmet on their head had two bull horns and an iron mask covering the helmet which wasn’t put down.

Although those cavalrymen had traveled for a long time, no matter if it were the men or the horses, neither looked tired. While their full body armor didn’t look neat and there were even some parts that were damaged, it didn’t affect their imposing manner.

The bodies of those soldier gave off an imposing atmosphere with a great deal of pressure. Zhao Hai felt the murderous air around them and knew that it was the killing intent released by soldiers that had experienced many life and death battles.

Leading the cavalry was a bearded man with a massive body. His face had a scar that made him hideous to look at, and he stared coldly at Zhao Hai and company.

Zhao Hai didn’t say anything and instead waved a hand at Green. Saluting, Green rode his horse towards the team of cavalrymen. At around twenty meters from the cavalry, Green saluted them and said, “Everybody, military gentlemen, please. My clan knows that everyone has put in a great deal of patriotic labor. This little one offers a meager gift and invites you to laugh.”

After he said those words, he took out the pouch filled with a thousand gold coins and shook it.

Green didn’t do this to insult them. Since the patrol group had experienced this a lot, once they saw the pouch was shook and heard the sound it made, they knew it was filled with either gold or silver coins. So long as they got their hand on that pouch, they would be able to know how much was inside of it. As such, Green gently shook the pouch to let them know it contained gold coins.

The cavalry captain heard the sound and obviously knew the pouch contained gold coins. His eyes became more enthusiastic. Looking at Green, he said, “Oh, so your master understands the rules. A routine check still needs to be done, however.”

Green’s expression changed. He’d heard what Laura said. So long as they paid them some money, then the cavalry wouldn’t inspect them. Yet why were they now checking? Were they trying to find some kind of fault? As he thought of these matters, Green couldn’t help but change his expression into a cold one.

Straightening his body and with eyes shining brightly, he looked at the cavalry captain and said, “Oh, so the military captain will do such a thing. This is probably irregular, right?”

Green’s voice wasn’t loud, but those cavalrymen still heard it clearly. With the addition of Green’s imposing manner, his words and his changed expression had turned him from an ordinary man to a person with the aura of a Rank Eight expert that exuded a powerful momentum. This made the cavalry captain’s complexion change.

The cavalry captain was still a Rank Six knight. Since he hadn’t felt Green’s strength earlier, he’d tried to speak that way and test them. Unexpectedly, they’d found that Green was a Rank Eight expert. Moreover, he wasn’t an ordinary one. Green exuded a thick militaristic aura that made the cavalry captain understand that the opposite party wasn’t affable. This was a group one couldn’t annoy.

He immediately said, “Haha, I’m just cracking a joke with you, sir. Since sir knows the rules, then naturally sir can pass.”

As Green heard the cavalry commander, his imposing manner vanished instantly. He showed a faint smile to the cavalry captain and said, “I shall thank the military captain.”

After saying those words he bent at the waist and placed the pouch on the ground. He then turned his horse around and returned to Zhao Hai’s carriage.

Zhao Hai waited for Green to arrive by the carriage before waving his hand. The carriage then began to slowly make its way towards the depths of the Beastfolk Prairie. The cavalry captain didn’t move to pick up the pouch immediately and was instead looking thoughtfully at the carriage.

A cavalryman riding beside the cavalry captain asked, “Captain, what just happened?”

When he recovered, the cavalry captain looked at the knight and said, “Nothing, I just remembered something. Some time ago, news had spread from Casa City. During the crisis, our Purcell clan had been helped by a black magician. That black magician had a Rank Eight warrior following him, right?”

The cavalry captain was also a clan member of the Purcell clan, so he’d said ‘our Purcell clan’. After hearing what the cavalry captain had said, the cavalryman gawked for a moment. “Captain, what do you mean? Was that magician in the caravan the one that had helped the Purcell clan resolve the crisis?”

Nodding, the cavalry captain said, “Rank Eight…  well, don’t think about it too much. Go and pick up the money.”

The cavalryman complied immediately and clipped the horse’s side to move forward. He circled the pouch and then got off his horse to examine it. Once the pouch was in his hand, he returned to the cavalry captain’s side and reported, “Captain, it should be a thousand gold coins[9].”

He nodded and turned around, then shouted loudly, “Brothers, this trip wasn’t in vain. When we go back we’ll take the day off and everyone can go have some fun.”

The cavalrymen cheered loudly. Clipping the horse’s side, the cavalry captain moved forward and everyone followed behind.

* * *

Footnotes:

[1]This isn’t really a reason for not hiding…

[2]So, again, what was the reason for them not hiding in the Space? You explain it in a way that shows that the better idea was the hiding one, yet you stay for what?

[3]The use of elite is getting tiring. Let’s just call them robbers and be done with it.

[4]Trouble that could have been avoided by, I don’t know, hiding in the space.

[5]No actual idea about if this was real. https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Diaochan

[6]Again makes me question why any country would have a standing army of such disposition. It’s basically asking for someone corrupt to come and use them for a coup or something.

[7]Again, no evidence for this statement. Green was a person who fought the beastfolk, no? How would he not have relations with Ironwall Fortress???

[8]Urgh, don’t throw the Evan card. If you didn’t want anything to happen, you would have hid in the Space. And if these guys are crap human beings, then you’d really be doing Evan a favor in the long run… come on…

[9]Question, I’ve been wondering for a bit, but how heavy and large is a gold coin? Just a thousand pennies seems a bit heavy, nevermind gold coins from this medieval-esque era…

Chapter 232: Star Grass[1]

It wasn’t until the shadow of the cavalry was gone that Laura and the other two walked out of the carriage. They had observed the cavalry, so Laura turned to Green and said, “Grandpa Green, if not for your unyielding attitude, I fear those fellows wouldn’t have let us off so easily. That was really risky.”

Green smiled faintly. “It’s alright. I’ve seen many such situations before. They were just acting, so it wasn’t anything much.”

Laura smiled. “Upon entering the Beastfolk Prairie, such situations will be frequently encountered. The beastfolk themselves, on the other hand, would only take food if they wished to rob. This is the unwritten rule of the Beastfolk Prairie. They still hope that people would bring food there in the future. Moreover, in the eyes of the beastfolk, Terrans look almost identical. With this, Grandpa Green won’t have to worry if anything does happen and can stay in the Black Waste.”

Green smiled and said, “There’s nothing much to do in the Black Waste at this time. Presently, everything that needs to be prepared for the winter has already been prepared. Furthermore, there’s Quinn John there so I have nothing to do. I’ll go with you for now. If there are any issues, I’ll go forth and move to solve it.”

Laura laughed. “Alright. The scenery here isn’t much. It’s not as good as the Space’s and somewhat boring.”

Green chuckled. “The grass inside the Space is taller than the ones here. Certainly, it’s a lot more attractive in there than here, but it also looks too rigid. On the other hand, the Beastfolk Prairie will have changes along the way.”

Laura grinned. As Green had said, in the Space, no matter if it was the farm or the ranch, there wouldn’t be much difference. Everything there was digitized. The grass would be as short in length as everything else and even the few leaves would look the exact same. There really weren’t any changes.

Just then, Green suddenly saw some bushes with a cluster of florets. He couldn’t help but gawk at them, then smiled as he hit his horse into a gallop. Jumping from his horse, he took out his Spiritwind Sword and dug out several clusters of florets from their roots.

Watching Green’s actions, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but be surprised. A moment later, he understood what Green intended. Sure enough, after Green removed the florets from the soil and returned to the carriage, he gave them to Zhao Hai and said, “Young Master, this is one of the most common type of flowers in the Beastfolk Prairie—Star Grass[2]. This Star Grass is unique to the Beastfolk Prairie and is a common hemostatic medicinal herb. Ordinary beastfolk would pick this grass and dry them, then use it on injuries to stop the bleeding. It’s a very effective herb.”

Zhao Hai looked at the clusters of florets in his hands. The entire plant was only about thirty centimeters in length and didn’t seem too extraordinary. Flowers bloomed on top of the grass[3]and the flower had a total of five petals that spread to resemble a small star.

Zhao Hai shifted his hands and placed the flowers in the Space. The Space immediately prompted in a tone:

[Discovered new plant.

Identifying plant. Plant is a herbal, hemostatic plant.

Plant has hemostatic abilities and strong vitality.

Evaluating level. Plant is Level 5.

The plant is seasonal and has a maturity time of ten hours.

Digitizing plant. Plant can now be purchased from the Spatial Shop.]

Zhao Hai nodded. Turning, he saw that Laura and the others had their eyes on him. He couldn’t help but frown as he said, “It’s nothing. The Space evaluated the plant as Level 5 and it has a ten hour maturity time.”

While Green and the others felt some regret, they didn’t really expect much. If such a common type of grass could upgrade the level of the Space, then the Space wouldn’t just be Level 20 right now.

Laura’s eyes shone brightly as she looked around as if in search of something. Zhao Hai gave a faint smile. This was the first time Laura had encountered such a situation, so she felt very curious and went ahead. Nier was also curious. She, however, wasn’t very curious about the plants, but rather, with the magic beasts.

Compared to Laura, Meg was much calmer. She’d already experienced the Space leveling up. If it didn’t upgrade this time, then there wasn’t anything to be happy about.

This was, however, a good start. These plants would slowly build up the experience needed after being assessed by the Space. Since they had just entered the Beastfolk Prairie and already found a plant, it could be considered a good start.

Green watched Laura and smiled as he said, “In fact, there are a lot of plants in the Beastfolk Prairie. Unfortunately, we aren’t beastfolk so we won’t be able to notice them easily. I heard that in the Beastfolk Prairie, the grass itself is divided into different types. There is grass that the cattle could feed on, grass that the sheep could eat, and grass that the horses could eat. Haha. When we speak about our understanding of the prairies, we can’t be compared to those beastfolk.”

Laura smiled. “That’s natural. The beastfolk have been living here for generations, and the Beastfolk Prairie is their home. They would naturally understand it better, but so long as we can buy a beastfolk slave this problem can be solved.”

Green nodded in approval of what Laura said. One could say that the group with the deepest understanding of the prairie wouldn’t be a member of a war tribe, but instead a slave.

The slaves of the prairies weren’t like Terran slaves that had been marked as such. Slaves in the prairie were instead just a sub ethnic race. The beastfolk could easily recognize a slave, so they didn’t need to be marked.

Furthermore, slaves in the prairie had a lot more freedom than the Terran slaves, and they were more dependent on some war tribes for survival. In this place, they would herd and work for the war tribes. Due to this, the slaves’ understanding of the prairie was quite high. They knew which grass would be good, where good water could be found, and where magic beasts roamed.

Slaves had their own reason for existing. With regards to the beastfolk, magic beasts encompassed everything. No matter how formidable a beastfolk war tribe was, it would still be weighed by how many magic beasts they had. Magic beasts, however, were trained and raised by the slaves. So long as the slaves raised the magic beasts well, the beastfolk would reward them in turn. With this, the slaves worked very hard.

Due of this, as long as Zhao Hai bought some beastfolk slaves, they would gain a better understanding of the flora within the prairie. In fact, many beastfolk didn’t realize how important this knowledge was. Although the beastfolk did have their own writing system, they didn’t have any record of these aspects.

Here in the Beastfolk Prairie, most of the ethnic races didn’t have their own slave tribe due to their low battle strength. If they had many slaves, then they would just be snatched by those war tribes. If wouldn’t do them any good as it would just lead to a slaughter. This was a common occurrence in the prairie.

There were many ethnic races that, because of their massive properties and inability to protect them, were eliminated by the war tribes. Afterwards, they would just be converted to slave tribes. This was the law of survival here in the prairie.

Green nodded and said, “Buying slaves is a must. But don’t worry about it too much. We must move slowly. First, we will need to take a look at the situation here in the Beastfolk Prairie.”

Laura nodded, smiled, and said, “I understand this since Artest had reported much of this to me before. Unfortunately, the information collected isn’t very comprehensive, so our understanding is still limited.”

Green nodded and looked around. He didn’t see any traces of a tribe, so he turned his head to Zhao Hai and said, “Young Master, we must move a little bit faster. The cavalry soldiers from Ironwall Fortress appear and disappear in this area frequently, so the beastfolk don’t come around here. We need to find a beastfolk tribe as soon as possible. Seeking shelter for the night with them would be best.”

Zhao Hai nodded. “That’s fine. If we meet a tribe, we can also do some transactions with them. Haha, I want to see what kind of beastfolk we encounter.”

Laura also smiled. Beastfolk rarely went into Terran settlements, so the local people living in some small areas wouldn’t be able to see a beastfolk in all of their lives.

Since they needed to hurry, they raised their speed slightly. Unfortunately, they didn’t manage to encounter anyone this day. This was normal, however, as the Beastfolk Prairie was very large. In addition, they were in the buffer zone between the Terrans and the beastfolk. This place would be sparsely populated.

Evening came and they still didn’t encounter any beastfolk. They went back inside the Space and passed the night there.

Night passed without any discussion.

Next morning, Zhao Hai and the others continued to venture deeper into the Beastfolk Prairie. Zhao Hai wanted to take it easy so they moved slowly. On the way, they were observing the surroundings and also gathering and digging up many types of grasses and flowers and placed them in the Space. Unfortunately, most of the plants they encountered were common. Although some were collected by the Space, they didn’t give much experience. Since the Space was now Level 20, upgrading became difficult.

Zhao Hai, however, didn’t give up. He understood the reality of the matter and could only do things slowly. Worrying about it would be useless.

To truly understand, just the Carrion Swamp itself had a wider variety of plants when compared to the Beastfolk Prairie. The Carrion Swamp, however, was dangerous. If he let Zhao Wen and Cai-er jointly search it and the Rank Nine experts of the Carrion Swamp knew of this, they wouldn’t be friendly[4]. Right now, Zhao Hai was focusing on the Beastfolk Prairie instead.

During noon that day, Zhao Hai was called by a blood-colored eagle. Zhao Hai looked up and saw the blood-colored eagle circling in the air, giving out cries from time to time.

Zhao Hai watched for a while, then turned to Laura and said, “Not far ahead of us is a small tribe with a few hundred people. We’ll arrive there by evening and rest.”

Laura didn’t oppose, instead nodding as she said, “Alright then, but we must be careful. The beastfolk might turn out to be robbers. As I see it, we should call out a few more undead so that the beastfolk wouldn’t act too unreasonably.”

Smiling, Zhao Hai said, “No, don’t forget that I’m currently a magician. I believe the beastfolk wouldn’t so casually annoy us, so be at ease.”

As they spoke, their speed increased. Three hours later, Zhao Hai stood atop his carriage. He saw a flag fluttering a bit away and knew that this was the place.

* * *

Footnotes:

[1]星星草 – Xīngxīng cǎo. Dunno why author uses double ‘star’ character. Reinforcement?

[2]Yea, author calls the thing a flower in this sentence, 花, but names it grass, 草. Also, in the earlier paragraph, Green is cutting down florets, 小花, basically little flowers.

[3]Still unsure if it’s a flower or a grass… I’m not a botanist.

[4]Weird seeing as how Zhao Wen is one of the more average strong members and Cai’er is the effective ruler… which Rank Nine would really care if they just picked a few plants?

Chapter 233: Big Bellied Pig-headed People

Multicolored flag, a sign of a beastfolk tribe. Any beastfolk tribe, regardless of whether they were great or small, would always hang up the multicolored flag of their tribe.

These multicolored flags, with regards to the beastfolk, meant stability, auspicious luck, and good fortune. Multicolored flags, in the eyes of the beastfolk, were rainbows.

Rainbows appeared after the rain, and rain was very important to the beastfolk. Rain could make rivers larger, so there would be more available water. Rain could make the prairie more lush, allowing their magic beasts to become stouter and stronger, increasing their wealth. As such, all beastfolk tribes hung a multicolored flag.

In the prairie, so long as someone sees a multicolored flag, they would know there was a tribe nearby. This was common knowledge in the prairie. Zhao Hai had read this miscellaneous information somewhere, which was how he knew of it.

Zhao Hai breathed out, sat down hastily, and turned to Laura and the others in the carriage and said, “I saw a multicolored flag.”

Laura understood clearly what Zhao Hai’s meant. She immediately left the carriage to check and see what Zhao Hai was looking at. A colorful multicolored flag appeared in her line of sight.

Laura breathed in. “Finally, we’ve found a beastfolk tribe. Alright, we may be able to drink milk wine tonight and eat roasted argali[1].”

Zhao Hai chuckled. To be honest, in this vast steppe they hadn’t thought they wouldn’t be able to find any inhabitants after searching for a full day. Now that they suddenly found a multicolored flag, it startled their hearts. It was like when people living in darkness suddenly saw a glimmer of light.

Before long, Zhao Hai and the others saw a tent. The tent exuded a lively feeling and a flag was set atop that tent. Painted on the flag was an adorable little pig.

Zhao Hai blinked his eyes to make sure he didn’t see it wrong. It really was an adorably little piggy on the flag. Turning to Laura, puzzled, he asked, “Laura, what tribe is this?”

Laura also saw the image of the little pig on the flag above the tent. She couldn’t help but smile as she said, “Do you see the little pig on the flag? The belly of the pig is a bit large, right? This beastfolk tribe is a branch of the beastfolk’s Pig ethnic race, the Big Bellied Pig tribe. They aren’t especially tall, only about two meters in height. Among the beastfolk, they are really small, but their bellies are really big and permanently exposed. Don’t underestimate their big bellies as it’s their most tenacious part.

“This tribe is part of an ethnic race whose combat abilities aren’t very strong, but they have a unique ability; the water they drink can be stored in their bellies. They could then use that water to spurt out a stream and use it as an arrow to attack others. The water they spurt out can generally reach thirty meters, and its strength is equal to a Terran’s brutal arrow[2]. With this unique ability, they haven’t become a slave tribe.”

Zhao Hai was very curious about this. He felt that this world was very large. Such a wonder could appear in a race was truly too interesting.

Turning to Laura, Zhao Hai said, “Then what about the tribe’s character? Will they suddenly turn into robbers?”

Laura shook her head and smiled. “Their disposition is affable. They belong to the Fragrant Pig ethnic race. So long as you don’t bully them, they won’t try to snatch your things. They are a very hospitable race and mainly herd argali to live.”

Zhao Hai knew that an argali was a Rank One magic beast and one of the many Rank One magic beasts the beastfolk raised. Argali skin could be used for clothing, its wool for blankets, the meat for consumption, and the bones for weapons. One could say that the life of the beastfolk couldn’t be separated from the argali.

For the Terrans, it was rare to see people raising argali. This was mainly due to the fact that the argali had adapted to living in the prairies. If they were to be raised in Terran territories, then they would become sick. As such, for the beastfolk the argali seemed like the greatest blessing of the Beast God.

Zhao Hai nodded. “That’s good then. We’ll rest here for today. If they need, we’ll also sell them food. Right, how does transactions work with the beastfolk?”

Laura smiled. “It isn’t difficult. So long as we pull out food, they’ll take the initiative and come to us. Generally, however, they would trade with magic beasts and won’t directly use money for transactions. Only those large war tribes can use money in transactions. Therefore, we’ll also need to trade in our magic beasts and turn it into money.”

Zhao Hai asked, “How much bamboo rice will we need to trade for an argali?”

Laura smiled, “Half a tonne[3].”

“Half a tonne? Are you cracking a joke?” Zhao Hai was surprised by what he heard. What Laura had stated the price was made him startled.

The reason for Zhao Hai’s surprise was that an individual mature argali could grow up to 1.5 meters and weighed around 400 kilograms. Even if they were carried on the back of an argali, it wouldn’t be a problem for them. Moreover, an argali could produce 100 kilograms of wool. If they were to transport it back to the Purcell Duchy, an argali would be priced at around 15 gold coins even if they didn’t raise it and just brought its corpse. For half a tonne of bamboo rice, however, it would honestly be sold of just a gold coin. This was fifteen times the profit. Wasn’t this a bit too high?

Laura understood Zhao Hai’s surprise. She smiled faintly and said, “It sounds quite high, but not as high as you think it is. You must remember that transporting commodities into the Beastfolk Prairie is done through smuggling. The process of smuggling means to bribe the military at the checkpoints and do this whenever you pass a checkpoint, which isn’t a small amount to be spending..

“Also, it’s easy to get robbed here in the Beastfolk Prairie. Transporting half a ton of bamboo rice into the prairie would cost about 3 gold coins. To transport the argali back would increase your income, but on the continent an argali costs 8 gold coins. This doesn’t include the chances of being robbed. You have to remember that merchants here in the Beastfolk Prairie usually cooperate with a large war tribe. If not, then they’d get robbed. With an estimate, an ordinary merchant would be robbed three or four out of ten times. Even without this, the profit they would make from argalis would only be around 4 to 5 gold coins. This is already very good.”

Zhao Hai nodded. He understood her points. Since the costs were high, the price would naturally go up. If the cost was too low, then people wouldn’t do this kind of business. In the end, the one who would suffer the most wouldn’t be the Terrans, but the beastfolk. They wouldn’t do well if this happened.[4]

Zhao Hai turned to Laura and asked, “How much do you think we should pay if we trade with them?”

Laura smiled faintly and said, “One tonne per argali.”

Zhao Hai nodded. He didn’t have to worry about the high costs that the other merchants experienced as he was producing the bamboo rice inside the Space. Furthermore, he could also place the argali within the Spatial Ranch or just store them inside the Spatial Warehouse. He didn’t need to arrange anything or bribe anyone. With this, he almost didn’t have any extra costs to pay. One tonne of bamboo rice per argali would still mean he’d earn money. Moreover, one tonne of bamboo rice in the Beastfolk Prairie wouldn’t have much of an impact on the prices since it was still a reasonable rate.

Nier and Meg stood back and listened to the two as they discussed. Meg didn’t feel bad about this so long as she could take care of Zhao Hai. The business matters from before were all done by Zhao Hai anyway. As such, she didn’t feel any jealousy.

For bystanders, she and Laura would be considered rivals. Meg’s view of this, however, wasn’t like that. She didn’t want to fight Laura over anything. Meg only wanted to be by Zhao Hai’s side. In addition, Laura’s strong point in business was an innate talent that Meg couldn’t compare with.

Meg had already resolved her issues about this long ago. Therefore, she wouldn’t be jealous of Laura. If Laura was competent, then she would be happy. After all, Laura now represented the Buda clan. If she were competent, then the Buda clan would become stronger. This was what Meg desired.

They chatted as they walked. Before long, they arrived before the tent. As soon as the people in the tent found them, twenty shadows rushed towards them. A dog accompanied each of the shadows.

As the shadows drew closer to Zhao Hai, it became noticeable that the twenty individuals were cavalry soldiers. What made Zhao Hai smile was the fact that their mounts were unexpectedly pigs.

Yep, these were pigs. With a body around two meters long and a weight of over half a tonne, those pigs had two long buck teeth growing in their mouths. Then the riders riding the pigs made Zhao Hai think of a man, Zhu Bajie[5].

They really did look too similar. Like Zhu Bajie, they wore prairie clothing; the individuals had fur hats on their heads and were dressed in leather clothes. They had large pig heads atop a rough, thick neck and their snow-white bellies were exposed to the outside. One could see a layer of black hair on their bellies. So long as they put on a robe and held a rake, they would look just like Zhu Bajie. They didn’t even need to wear makeup.

Zhao Hai wanted to smile, but then he thought it wouldn’t be polite. If he ridiculed the beastfolk and caused a conflict, it wouldn’t be nice to look at. He refrained from it and slowly calmed his mood.

Alongside those big bellied, pig-headed riders were several dogs. Those dogs were very special as they were about a meter tall and had long hair. They ran really fast and didn’t bark randomly. With two fangs exposed over their lip, they didn’t look like something one should mess with.

Zhao Hai and the others stopped immediately. They assumed a calm and friendly appearance. Sure enough, those pig riders slowed down. Zhao Hai now found out that the weapons of those pig riders could only be described as simple. It was a big sheep’s head fitted onto a wooden handle. And some of the weapons didn’t even use wood, but animal bones.

Zhao Hai, however, didn’t dare to underestimate this type of weapon as a sheep’s head was very large and looked very heavy. If one got pounded by such a thing, then it would definitely break one’s bones and crush one’s tendons.

Right now, the Big Bellied Pig tribe people stopped 50 meters in front of them. Both sides halted, but those riders let their dogs move about and surround the sides of Zhao Hai and the others. The dogs were staring at them, a warning hum sounding from deep within their throats.

* * *

Footnotes:

[1]盘羊 – Pán yáng. Argali… basically a mountain sheep. Simple google works.

[2]I don’t know how this works. The power of an arrow but less range? Maybe cause it’s made of water?

[3]Again, 1000 jin = 500 kilograms or half a tonne. Half a metric ton for whoever. About 1100 lbs.

[4]I barely understand this marketing. The wording is either off, or the author used weird characters. Just because it’s expensive to do something, doesn’t mean people would accept the equivalent high price. And if the costs were low, how would no one participate in the business? This is like backwards economics. Are they masochistic businessmen who just like to put their hands in high cost problems?

[5]猪八戒 – Zhūbājiè. A character from Journey to the West. Also called Pigsy or Pig. https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Zhu_Bajie

Chapter 234: Precious Gift

Laura quickly left the carriage after she saw the few Big Bellied Pig tribesmen and hastily greeted them, “Fellow Pig tribe friends, we are a Terran merchant clan. We are not malicious people, so please let your faithful dogs return to the sides of their masters.”

The Big Bellied Pig tribesmen saw Laura standing beside the caravan. One Pig tribesman who seemed to be the leader quickly placed his sheep skull hammer down and returned Laura’s greeting, “Dear Terran businesswoman, please forgive our rudeness. As you may know, here in the prairie I must ensure the safety of my tribesmen.”

After he said those words, he shouted twice and had the faithful dogs return to their side.

Laura was currently out of the carriage when a few Pig tribesmen jumped off their mounts and walked towards Laura. When the distance between the two sides had decreased to a few meters apart, Laura formally greeted the Pig tribesmen and said, “Taoyuan Business Association[1] Chairwoman, Laura, has seen the brave warriors of the Pig tribe.”

The Pig tribesman was very polite as he bowed towards Laura, saying, “Big Bellied Pig tribe, Sheep-Head Hammer horde[2] chief, Spear[3], has seen the beautiful lady Laura.”

Spear’s body was around 2 meters tall, which made the 1.8 meter tall Laura in front of him look like a child. He was, however, very polite, and Zhao Hai’s impression of him became subconsciously more favorable.

Laura smiled. “Honorable chief Spear, me and my caravan wishes to stay the night at your camp. I wonder if you will allow us?”

“Haha,” Spear laughed. “Beautiful lady Laura, this matter is something we also wish for with earnesty. Please, everyone in the carriage, come along with us to our camp. I will kill a good argali and will make some milk tea and milk wine. We will entertain you with the best food we have.”

Laura smiled and said, “Thank you, generous chief Spear. Chief, please go first.”

Spear saluted Laura and turned his mount around to hurry back towards the camp. Laura and the others, however, returned to their carriage.

Zhao Hai watched the distant Pig tribesmen before turning to Laura. “Will they really kill an argali and wait for us?”

Laura smiled. “They will. The beastfolk here in the prairies welcome us merchants warmly. So long as one doesn’t have any ill intent, they will be very hospitable. Brother Hai, take out some vegetables. With regards to them, there is no better gift than vegetables.”

Zhao Hai nodded and took out some vegetables to place them on the carriages. The vegetables came from the Space, so they were all as fresh as if they’d just been harvested.

After making the preparations, Laura and the caravan moved slowly towards the Sheep-Head Hammer horde. With regards to the Sheep-Head Hammer horde’s strange name, Laura wasn’t that surprised. Within the Beastfolk Prairie, there were many such strange names. Don’t even speak about Sheep-Head Hammer, there was also a horde called Sheep-Dung. Laura didn’t feel this was that strange.

They didn’t need to wait very long before several argali came out of the horde’s campsite. These argali were ones they had grown themselves. On the backs of these argali sat Big Bellied Pig tribe children.

The children all looked over ten years old and wore leather clothing. With their big bellies and silly, small heads, they looked adorable.

The children ran up to Laura’s carriage. They looked curiously at Laura and Zhao Hai, who was wearing his magic robe. Then the tallest child went to the carriage and courteously said to Laura, “Honorable businesswoman, my father asked me to lead you.” Evidently, this was Spear’s child.

Laura smiled and immediately replied, “Adorable young warriors, please lead the way.”

Perhaps it was because Laura called them ‘young warriors’ that the little Pig children became happy. These children with small bellies walked happily in front of the carriage.

For the beastfolk, warriors were important. Once they were commended by the other party and were called a warrior, it would make them very happy. This was Laura’s first contact with the beastfolk, so she tried this with the children. It seemed that the idea was very effective.

Laura watched the children, then turned to Zhao Hai and said, “You can try to praise them as warriors, but no matter how cute they are you cannot touch their heads. If you do so, they will become angry. Also, when you are offered to drink wine by them, you cannot say no. It is considered impolite towards the host. Furthermore, if they give you a gift, then no matter what you must accept. Otherwise, the host will think you are looking down on him.”

Zhao Hai nodded. These were things that could be considered taboo among the beastfolk. As such, they must naturally remember this. They didn’t want any minor matter to suddenly turn into a big conflict with the beastfolk.

They soon arrived at the Sheep-Head Hammer horde camp. Spear stood waiting for them. Beside Spear were three Big Bellied Pig tribe young girls. Each of these girls carried a bowl of wine.

This was the first time Zhao Hai had seen a Pig tribe young girl. These Pig tribe young girls had a stature that wasn’t much different from Laura’s. Their bellies didn’t bulge, but their bodies were plump and they wore leather skirts. Although they did have the head of a pig, when compared to Spear it was smaller. They looked very cute, especially with their long hair. Their hair had some accessories in them, and although they had pig heads they didn’t look disgusting[4].

Laura took the lead as they left the carriage and stood in front of Spear. Spear smiled and said, “Beautiful young lady, please drink this wine as a symbol of friendship between you and our Sheep-Head Hammer horde.” After a wave of his hand, those three Pig tribe young girls immediately moved forward.

Laura didn’t dare be impolite and immediately received the bowl of wine from the young girl’s hand. She drank a mouthful and then spilled some wine on the ground. This was one of the beastfolk’s special accommodations for women. A woman must drink some of the wine from the bowl, then raise the bowl and sprinkle it on the ground. On the other hand, a man must raise the bowl of wine and drink it all.

After drinking from three bowls of wine, Laura’s face appeared ruddy. This, to Zhao Hai, made her appear gorgeous. Spear and the other Pig tribesmen didn’t understand how to appreciate such a sight, however. In their eyes, all Terran women looked the same. Although Spear had called Laura a beautiful lady, it was just a form of courtesy.

The beastfolk proposed a toast to those who deserved respect and could lead. Others wouldn’t have such an accommodation. Therefore, Zhao Hai didn’t drink the wine Spear had.

After drinking, Laura turned to Spear and said, “Honorable chief, please allow my servants to establish tents. Also, please do not prepare so much food as my servants are all undead. They don’t need to eat anything.”

Spear gawked and examined the zombies standing next to the carriage. Soon he found that these zombies were quite different. He didn’t care much, however, as he nodded and said, “Alright then. Beautiful young lady, please.”

Laura turned and looked at Zhao Hai, who then nodded and waved his hand. Immediately after, those undead began to construct their own camp. They made the camp close to the Sheep-Head Hammer horde camp. The undead Zhao Hai had brought were the ones that had originally been led by Alodia. Alodia himself was also among the undead. When they had killed some, most of them were ordinary caravan coachmen and servants. They weren’t unfamiliar with building a camp, so under Zhao Hai’s order they made good time.

Spear saw Zhao Hai wave his hand. To be honest, Spear didn’t have a favorable first impression of Zhao Hai. Since Zhao Hai wore a black magic robe, he felt that Zhao Hai exuded a gloomy aura which made Zhao Hai disagreeable[5].

At this time, several undead brought forward a few piles of fresh vegetables. Laura smiled at Spear and said, “Honorable chief, please accept my small gift.”

The vegetables were fresh. Moreover, there was a wide variety of them that filled the baskets. They appeared supple and tender, and Spear’s eyes shone. With regards to the beastfolk, such green goods were rare good items.

Spear wasn’t polite as he smiled and said to Laura, “Thank you, beautiful and generous young lady. These vegetables, to us, is really expensive. Please, come to my tent. My wife made fragrant milk tea.”

Laura wasn’t polite as she walked towards the largest tent in the middle of the camp with Spear. The vegetables, on the other hand, had been received by Spear. Zhao Hai wanted to laugh. Those vegetables were just ordinary vegetables and weren’t worth much.

He knew that the beastfolk lived in a prairie, so adding in the fact that only grassland occupied the land, they were unable to plant any vegetables. As such, the vegetables were mostly brought by Terran merchants. Since they can’t preserve them well, they wouldn’t be able to see vegetables all year round. Sometimes, if they were lucky, they’d be able to dig up some wild herbs in the prairie. As such, these produce became rare food for them.

Laura had given them a lot of vegetables. With regards to Spear, this was really precious. Therefore, his respect for Laura increased by a lot.

Spear led the group of people into a tent. Inside the tent were Pig tribe women wearing fur-lined robes as they moved around busily. When the two women saw Spear come in, they greeted the group hastily. Zhao Hai and the others also returned the greeting and carefully looked around the tent.

There was a pillar in the middle of the tent that supported the roof. The walls were made with animal skin and wool blankets that were surrounded by wood and animal bones to help maintain the warmth inside. The ground was covered with carpets. Near the center of the tent was a pit wherein a flame had been lit inside. On top of it was a copper pot that was being heated. The aroma of milk tea came out of the pot.

Spear asked his visitors to sit down. Each of the visitors was given a bowl of steaming hot milk tea. Zhao Hai and the others drank some and found that it was actually very fragrant. The tea didn’t seem to be the same type of tea Zhao Hai knew of, but was instead from a plant he didn’t know about. The taste wasn’t the same as tea leaves, but the milk tea was really delicious. There wasn’t any sort of fishy smell from it, so it seemed that something had been added to it. It had a slightly salty taste and a thick aroma. It was smooth and tasted great.

* * *

Footnotes:

[1]The raws says 商会, which can also mean Chamber of Commerce, but a chamber of commerce really doesn’t match the context. A chamber of commerce is “a local association to promote and protect the interests of the business community in a particular place.” As such, I used the more literal definition, which is Business Association/Society/Union.

[2]As you may have noticed, we have so many levels of beastfolk that it gets confusing. For now, we’ll try and see if this way works: Beastfolk ‘Race’. Fragrant Pig ‘Ethnic Race’. Big Bellied Pig ‘Tribe’. And then Sheep-Head Hammer ‘Horde’.

[3]斯皮尔 – Sī pí’ěr. Yea, his name is Spear… though he uses a hammer…

[4]This was a scary description… Author needs to provide pics, else I can’t imagine them. I just keep thinking of Miss Piggy.

[5]Raw says 讨厌, which can range from hate/disgust to something more mellow like disagreeable… I decided not to make him super antagonistic…

Chapter 235: Together in the Tent While Sleeping

After traveling for a day, Laura and the others felt very tired. After drinking the bowl of hot milk tea, however, they all felt a lot better.

Spear examined the appearance of his visitors and it made him smile. The mouth of a pig was big, and his smile was even larger than his big mouth. Laura and the others couldn’t bear not to smile along.

After they placed their bowl down, Spear’s wife filled them up once more with milk tea. Spear then opened his mouth and said, “Beautiful young lady, how much food have you bought and what is the price?”

Beastfolk liked to talk directly, so Spear didn’t beat around the bush and directly asked Laura about the price. Just as Spear had noted, Laura brought along food. Food, to the beastfolk, was something they all needed.

Laura smiled and said, “Honorable chief, this time we have brought 25 tonnes of food in total, all bamboo rice. In return for your hospitality, I am willing to trade 1 tonne of food per argali.”

Spear looked at Laura with uncertainty. “You said 1 tonne of food will be traded per argali? Did you not speak incorrectly?”

This was the first time Spear had spoken to Laura without adding the few words, ‘beautiful young lady’ to his sentence. It revealed how shocked he was.

Laura smiled and said, “It is as chief Spear said. 1 tonne per argali. I have not spoken incorrectly, and you have not misunderstood.”

Spear became excited about this and stood up. He then held his chest seriously and courteously said to Laura, “Beautiful lady Laura, you are as generous as the beautiful Yaja river. Starting today, you are the Sheep-Head Hammer horde’s most honored guest.”

Laura smiled. “Honorable chief, we are now friends and friends shouldn’t be so polite with one another. Also, allow me to introduce him. This is my fiancé, Zhao Hai. He is a magician, and in fact this food had been produced in his territory. The price was also set by him.”

Zhao Hai was introduced this time around because Laura didn’t want to steal all the credit from him. Furthermore, she observed that Spear didn’t seem to have a good view of Zhao Hai. Laura didn’t want Zhao Hai to be left out, so she introduced him to Spear.

Sure enough, after Laura introduced him, Spear immediately held his chest[1] to Zhao Hai and courteously said, “Honorable sir magician, please forgive my rudeness from earlier.”

Zhao Hai returned his courtesy and said, “Chief Spear doesn’t need to be polite. I understand that my identity isn’t amiable, but I do hope I can be friends with you.”

As soon as Spear heard Zhao Hai’s words, he faced him straight on and said, “Honorable sir Zhao Hai, your mind is as broad as the prairie. Today, I will do my best to entertain you!”

Zhao Hai smiled agreeably as he said, “Then I won’t be polite. Please allow me to, however, give your adorable son a gift.” Having said that, he waved his hand and an iron shield appeared.

This iron shield wasn’t big and was only a round shield instead of a tower shield. Zhao Hai had bought it in the Purcell Duchy during the time when they were purchasing items. The craftsmanship could be considered ordinary, but in the iron-lacking prairies, it was an absolutely extraordinary gift.

Spear happily received the round shield and expressed his gratitude to Zhao Hai. He didn’t know how the shield appeared, however. Since they were a beastfolk tribe situated at the edge of the Beastfolk Prairie, their contact with Terrans wasn’t plentiful. With regards to them, a magician was a very mystical occupation. The prestige of a Terran magician was extremely exaggerated within the beastfolk. When Zhao Hai, this pseudo-magician, displayed his skill in front of Spear, there was no lasting issues from Spear.

By this time, the morning sky had already long fled, so Spear turned to Zhao Hai and said, “Brother Zhao Hai, there’s a bonfire lit outside and the argali will be placed over it. Come out with me and enjoy the enthusiasm of the beastfolk.”

Zhao Hai took off his magic hat at this time. In any case, nobody knew him here. He smiled as he stood up and said, “Alright, Brother Spear. With regards to the beastfolk’s argali, I have been craving it for a long time now.”

The few people left the tent and looked outside. Sure enough, the land was lit up by the bonfire and a few argali had been placed inside the fire to roast, their juices dripping down. One pig-headed man was rotating the argali while another was paying attention to the fire. Some of the pig-headed women were carrying earthen jars filled with milk wine and sprinkling them around the bonfire.

Spear pulled along Zhao Hai and they sat beside the bonfire. They were immediately served two plates and a wine bowl each. The first plate was filled with a thin layer of salt while the other was empty. The wine bowls, on the other hand, were filled with wine.

When the Pig tribe people saw Spear coming out, they walked towards him. They took away the two’s empty plates and went over to the roasting area. Taking out a dagger, they cut away some sections of mutton. Afterward, they placed the meat on the plates and served them to Zhao Hai and Spear.

Spear’s wife also took out a dagger and placed it before Zhao Hai. Spear then smiled and said to Zhao Hai, “Brother Zhao Hai, this dagger is the one I like the most. Today, I will give it to you so that you can use it and have a taste of our beastfolk’s roasted argali.”

Zhao Hai looked at the dagger. It was shaped in a curve, resembling a sickle. The scabbard was made of sheep’s horn and had a beautiful pattern carved in it. It really did look like a work of art.

He gently drew out the dagger. Presently, the dagger emitted a cold light that shone brightly. It was obviously a rare, high quality item. Zhao Hai remembered what Laura told them earlier, that they shouldn’t decline when receiving gifts. Since that was so, Zhao Hai happily received the dagger and said, “Thank you, Brother Spear. I like this gift a lot.”

Spear laughed and patted Zhao Hai’s shoulder, almost forcing him to the ground. This made Spear laugh even louder, and even the other pig-headed tribesmen around them were laughing.

Zhao Hai was helpless since his body was really that bad. The beastfolk were also known to have great strength. Even if the Big Bellied Pig tribe wasn’t a war tribe, they were still a lot more powerful than common Terrans. As such, Zhao Hai couldn’t bear it.

Zhao Hai watched as the roasted mutton placed in front of Spear was cut into pieces by him with his dagger. Spear then moistened a piece with salt and placed it in his mouth.

Following Spear, Zhao Hai placed his hands on the roasted mutton and cut them. He then moistened the surface with salt and placed it in his mouth. The salted surfaced was melted in his mouth, giving off a salty taste as the mutton’s roasted fragrance passed by.

This roasted mutton, when compared to the roasted mutton of Terrans, had a completely different taste. The roasted mutton was very fragrant, and in this atmosphere, the taste had increased by three times. Zhao Hai currently thought that this was the best roasted meat he’d ever tasted.

After he swallowed the roast meat, Zhao Hai continued to ponder the taste and fragrance as it was very deep. Unlike the milk tea, though it was also fragrant, it didn’t really taste better. The mutton’s fragrance, however, actually managed to increase the taste of the roasted meat. This made it so that everyone wouldn’t be able to stop eating it[2].

While Zhao Hai was still pondering the taste of the meat, Spear lifted a bowl of wine and loudly said, “My people, let us pick up some mellow wine and welcome our friends from far, far away! Brother Zhao Hai, come, bottoms up!”

Everyone loudly shouted, “Bottoms up!” As they shouted those words, everyone lifted their own wine bowls and drank it all at once. Zhao Hai looked at this and understood that they had to drink the wine in one take.

Fortunately, the degree of alcohol in the milk wine wasn’t that high. Along with the aroma, the flavor itself was very good and it wasn’t difficult to drink. Zhao Hai didn’t make a fool out of himself during this scene.

After drinking that bowl of wine, Spear didn’t try to propose a toast again, but chatted with Zhao Hai. Every time he drank wine, he would call for Zhao Hai, who would then follow his lead. Before long, they had each drunk three bowls of wine and eaten two sections of roasted mutton.

To be honest, Zhao Hai’s appetite wasn’t very large. Today, however, he had a good appetite for some unknown reason. It may have been due to the roasted mutton being very fragrant, or the milk wine being too tasty. He ate two large sections of roasted mutton and, at present, he could unexpectedly still eat. This was beyond his expectations.

At this time, a Pig tribe young girl appeared and started to sing a unique beastfolk song. The tune was long and very nice to hear. Zhao Hai and the others couldn’t help but cheer up even more.

Bonfire roasting. Living in the prairie. This type of atmosphere was really good and it could make a person subconsciously excited. The atmosphere in the field grew even warmer.

In the end, Zhao Hai didn’t know how much milk wine he’d drunk or how much of the roast mutton he had. He didn’t even know how he got back to his tent, because he’d been knocked unconscious with all that he’d drunk.

Laura and the others didn’t drink too much. The beastfolk wouldn’t urge women to drink milk wine. If they could drink, then drink; if they couldn’t drink it, then they could take milk tea instead. As long as everyone eats and eats with relish, then the meal becomes joyous.

Zhao Hai had been sent off back to the tent by some Pig tribesmen since he’d gotten drunk and was knocked out. Laura and the others couldn’t return to the Space, so they had to live in the tent.

Since Zhao Hai and the others would be leaving tomorrow, they didn’t bother to set up multiple tents and only had the one built. Earlier, they only wanted to use it to pretend they were living in it, but now they had to actually stay there. The undead in the caravan wouldn’t get tired or feel cold, so they stood guard.

The next morning, Zhao Hai woke up. Although he was knocked out cold from the drinking yesterday, he had to admit that the milk wine of the beastfolk was really good. Above all that, Zhao Hai didn’t feel thirsty, nor did he have a headache. The only thing he had was some slight dizziness.

Feeling a little heat in his throat, Zhao Hai immediately drank some Spatial Water. This made him feel a lot better and sobered him up.

After sobering up, Zhao Hai found out that Laura and the others were all resting inside the tent. To his left was Laura, while Meg was on his right. Nier slept on the other side of Laura. He was unexpectedly in an unknown situation where he slept with three beauties.

Zhao Hai looked at the situation blankly and suddenly didn’t know how to act. He definitely couldn’t force himself on them, but the situation caused him some agitation.

Consider this; Zhao Hai was an otaku back on Earth[3]. Presently, he was sleeping in the same tent with three beautiful women. Although he didn’t do anything, with regards to Zhao Hai this was still a rare experience. Especially now that he could smell the fragrance they gave off, which made Zhao Hai’s heart shake.

When Zhao Hai looked at Laura’s tender white skin, it made his heart itch. He bent down to get a closer look, but Laura suddenly turned her body. Zhao Hai woke up and took a deep breath, then looked at Laura and Meg. He stood up softly and left the tent.

He didn’t notice as he left that Laura and Meg had opened their eyes. They both looked at the tent entrance, and then at each other. Both of them saw a happy light in the other’s eyes. It was obvious that the two of them had already been awake before Zhao Hai and had only been pretending to sleep[4].

They had naturally noted down Zhao Hai’s actions, so Laura had deliberately turned her body. Zhao Hai’s actions that was similar to a frightened rabbit made the two women almost laugh aloud.

The two of them, however, were touched by Zhao Hai’s actions. It showed that he respected them enough. It was a move full of love and respect.

In the case that Zhao Hai kissed Laura, then it not only meant that he loved Laura. On the contrary, this may mean that Zhao Hai’s desire for Laura exceeded his love.

With regards to love, every person expressed it differently. Everyone’s understanding of it wasn’t the same, but there was one thing that was still important; if you loved one another, then you must respect the other and don’t look down on them. If Zhao Hai had forcefully kissed Laura, then Laura might not have resisted, but she’d be disappointed in Zhao Hai[5]. That’s because she would think Zhao Hai didn’t understand her.

Laura was a very self-disciplined woman, so she hoped that her other half would also respect her. If Zhao Hai had kissed her, then while she wouldn’t resist, she also wouldn’t cooperate. Since Meg and Nier were also in the tent, if she kissed him back, then they might find her frivolous. This was unacceptable for the self-disciplined Laura.

If Zhao Hai truly loved her, then he wouldn’t forcefully kiss her. Doing so would mean Zhao Hai didn’t understand her disposition, and that he didn’t care about her feelings. Such a thing would make Laura sad.

It was obvious, however, that Laura’s worries were in vain[6]. Zhao Hai did well and didn’t force himself on Laura, instead leaving the tent. This was the result Laura wanted.

Meg didn’t have the same thoughts as Laura. She wasn’t jealous either. Meg knew that Zhao Hai liked Laura and knew that he liked her as well. If Zhao Hai did kiss Laura forcefully, however, then Meg would also be disappointed. This was because Meg wouldn’t be able to think that Zhao Hai was the same Zhao Hai she knew from the Black Waste.

Prior to them going to the Black Waste, he was Adam, not Zhao Hai. Meg, however, didn’t know this. If Zhao Hai kissed Laura, then she would think Zhao Hai was the same Adam she knew from before they went to the Black Waste. He was currently different from Adam who was a person who had flowers hanging off him and didn’t understand love. If he did kiss Laura, then that would mean that in his bones he was still the dandy, Adam. Meg would be even sadder than Laura in the end[7].

* * *

Footnotes:

[1]I assume that holding his chest, 扶胸, basically means to, like, place his palm on his chest or something. I dunno.

[2]As of here, I understand the author should never try to write a cooking novel with his limited vocabulary. Neither should we for that matter…

[3]Questionable. He probably only wore a shirt that said, “I’m an awesome Otaku.” Nothing about him seems to back up this claim.

[4]If people do not want to read weird author’s attempt at romance, it’s alright to stop here…

[5]And this completely ruins the cliche “kissing her while she’s asleep” scene.

[6]… cause he wasn’t about to kiss her…

[7]So basically, if he did anything else, they would have dumped him on the spot instead of help him. Great. Let’s do that. Romance parts are killing me…

Chapter 236: Jackal

Of course, Zhao Hai definitely didn’t know about the thoughts of the two women. Under that atmosphere, however, he could only continue to think about being intimate with Laura, so he left the tent. Naturally, that feeling had also tapered off.

After he left the tent, Zhao Hai breathed in some fresh air and looked around. He discovered that some Pig tribe women were already awake at this early hour and were busy with tasks around the camp. Some of them crowded together to milk the sheep, some were nursing the lambs, and some were cleaning the mess from yesterday’s feast. When they saw Zhao Hai leave his tent, they greeted him and Zhao Hai hastily greeted them back.

One would have to say that the ordinary life of a beastfolk was still very hard. Take Spear and this tribe; there were no slaves so they had to do everything themselves. Moreover, their main source of income came from selling argali. Selling wool was their secondary source.

Wool products from the beastfolk were famous on the continent. It didn’t only maintain warmth due the thickness, but were also strong and durable. More importantly, the surface patterns had strong beastfolk characteristics; giving off a rugged and mysterious, exotic beauty. All of this made it very popular.

The wool products, however, didn’t have a very unified production line. Instead, they were all made by hand by beastfolk using techniques handed down since ancient times. They manufactured them bit by bit. These sheepskin products wasn’t their only main sources of income, but was also a part of their lives.

Zhao Hai didn’t watch the women as they worked. His eyes were aimed at the mount Spear had used, as well as those dogs.

Those dogs were similar to another type of dog from Zhao Hai’s previous world—the mastiff. They did seem much fiercer than a mastiff, however, and this could be attributed to them being magic beasts.

Spear’s mount made Zhao Hai even more curious. They seemed like relatives to the wild boar and were really big. Based on Zhao Hai’s view, they almost seemed like a smaller version of an elephant. What’s even rarer was that they were quick. This was a very good mount.

Maybe it was due to him and Spear drinking last night, but whether it were the dogs or the pig, they didn’t show any hostility towards Zhao Hai. Several of the dogs even wagged their tails before Zhao Hai.

At this time, Spear’s voice sounded, “Brother Zhao Hai, you’re up really early. Were you happy with yesterday’s drinking?”

Zhao Hai turned to Spear. He couldn’t help but show a faint smile, saying, “Brother Spear, you didn’t get up late as well. Last night was the happiest I’ve been since birth. I’m truly thankful for your hospitality.”

Spear patted Zhao Hai’s shoulders forcefully and said, “Brother Zhao Hai, you are too polite! Entertaining a friend is an honor for our beastfolk race. Hahahaha.”

Zhao Hai understood that the beastfolk were straightforward, but with regards to Spear’s enthusiasm when he patted his shoulder, he really couldn’t enjoy it.

Shaking his numb shoulder, Zhao Hai smiled bitterly as he turned his head to smile at Spear. “Then, Brother Spear, I won’t be polite with you. I can give you 25 tonnes of food, but what I want in return are several of the argali and a dog. Also, it would better to also get a mount. What do you think?”

Spear smiled. “No problem. I can give you a dog. The pig is one of our Big Bellied Pig tribe specific and unique war beasts, so I can’t give you one directly. A few days ago, however, one of our pigs had just given birth, so I can give you the piglet and thirty argali. How does that sound to you?”

When Spear finished speaking, he watched and waited for Zhao Hai’s decision. He feared Zhao Hai might not agree since he thought that the transaction would mean a loss on Zhao Hai’s part.

Zhao Hai shook his head. “Brother Spear, you are too polite. Just give me a dog, a pig, two wool blankets, and ten of those argali. The 25 tonnes of food is yours.”

For Zhao Hai, this was enough. The Space could gain three magic beasts, and moreover he would also gain ten argali and two wool blankets. He would also only have to give 25 tonnes of food in return. The things he obtained from this would gain him several hundred gold coins if sold on the continent. It was a profit for them.

Spear didn’t think the same and thought Zhao Hai would suffer a loss. He shook his head and hastily said, “Brother Zhao Hai, you’ll suffer a loss if we do it like this. The beastfolk don’t want their friends to suffer losses, so you must accept thirty argali or more wool blankets. Anything we make, I can give to you.”

Laughing, Zhao Hai patted Spear’s arm—as he was shorter, he couldn’t reach Spear’s shoulder—and said, “Brother Spear, you don’t need to be so polite. Didn’t Laura tell you yesterday that the food had all been produced in my territory? It was planted by me, so I didn’t buy them. The investments are small. Getting ten argali is already a lot. I also can’t let you suffer, right?”

Spear looked at Zhao Hai with complex eyes. He forcefully patted Zhao Hai’s shoulders and said, “Brother Zhao Hai, from today onward, you are this Spear’s true brother. To be honest, it is the first time I’ve ever seen a Terran like you. I’ve seen many Terrans before you, and many of them were like vampires. You are, however, a naturally generous person. I am willing to give you the war flag of our tribe. This isn’t the supplier’s kind of war flag, but a brother’s war flag.”

Zhao Hai stared, puzzled, as he asked, “What’s the difference? I heard that many large caravans obtained war flags from war tribes. Aren’t war flags only used by war tribes?”

Spear laughed. “My brother, your understanding of our beastfolk is too little. Us beastfolk have many kinds of war flags. There are war flags used in war, and we don’t give those away. After all, it represents our honor. Another type, however, will be given to those merchant caravans. Although the war flags look the same, as long as one is a beastfolk, they can see the difference.

“The third type of war flag is a friendship war flag. This war flag isn’t used during wartime, but it instead represents that one has obtained our friendship. A person with this kind of war flag can be said to have obtained the friendship of the beastfolk. As long as a beastfolk sees this kind of war flag, they will know that the person is our beastfolk’s genuine friend. No matter where, he will earn the corresponding respect. Although our Big Bellied Pig tribe is only a normal tribe and not a war tribe, so long as you get our friendship war flag, it’ll be much safer than when you use a merchant’s war flag. This is because the beastfolk wouldn’t attack one of their friends.”

Zhao Hai now understood that the beastfolk had several types of war flags. He wasn’t polite as he smiled and said, “Alright then, brother. Thank you very much.”

Spear laughed. “Brother, you’re too polite. Beastfolk don’t need such politeness. Also, brother, you must still pay attention. Some time ago, I had heard of a nearby Jackal[1] tribe appearing and disappearing. That group is definitely full of robbers and thieves and shouldn’t even be called beastfolk. You must stay careful of these fellows.”

Zhao Hai nodded. With regards to this Jackal tribe, Zhao Hai knew of them due to the beastfolk records[2] that mentioned them. This ethnic race was more cold-blooded than the Snake ethnic race and were more cunning than the Fox ethnic race. They were also a lot crueler than the Wolf ethnic race. Jackals weren’t only disliked by Terrans, but also by the other beastfolk.

The Jackal tribe people were of a very special ethnic race. They weren’t as strong as the Lion race, nor as fast as the Wolf race. Speaking frankly, they also weren’t as cunning as the Fox race. Although they didn’t have abilities to the extent of these three races, their survival capability was the strongest.

Jackal tribe generally lived in the areas of the Beastfolk Prairie with the harshest conditions. To survive, they could only continue to fight, hunt, rob, and kill. If they didn’t do so, then they would starve to death.

No matter what race they faced, so long as they thought they could rob them, they would rob. Moreover, the Jackal tribe had the most outstanding hunters. They were united, patient, and had a different kind of cunning that no other beastfolk had. All of this made them the Beastfolk Prairie’s most notorious hunters, and also the most unpopular ones.

The beastfolk didn’t like them because they robbed relentlessly. Terran merchants didn’t like them because they didn’t leave anyone alive. While other beastfolk might rob them, at the very least they wouldn’t kill you so long as your didn’t offend them. This was because they needed the merchants to continue to transfer grains and food into the prairie.

The Jackal tribe, however, didn’t follow this. They didn’t only rob the commodities, but also robbed the lives of Terrans. They would even kidnap Terran merchants, resulting in many Terran slaves within the prairie. Many of the Terran merchants were kidnapped and held by the Jackal tribe, then sold. It could be said that this was their way to survive. Such an ethnic race was unscrupulous.

Another reason why the Jackal tribe wasn’t welcome by the other beastfolk was due to the fact that they didn’t have their own war flag!

War flags, to the beastfolk, held their honor and represented them. The Jackal tribe, on the other hand, didn’t have their own war flag. This wasn’t to say that they didn’t have war flags. In fact, they had many war flags. These war flags, however, weren’t theirs, but those that had been snatched from the other ethnic races.

They would use these war flags as bait. Weaker beastfolk ethnic group war flags would be used to lure in Terran merchants who came seeking shelter in their camp for the night. They would strike at that time. Among the entirety of the beastfolk, only the Jackal tribe would do such a thing. The other ethnic races, even the most aggressive Wolf race or cunning Fox race, wouldn’t do this. They had their own honor and disdained from such actions.

The Jackal tribe actually enjoyed such tactics. This was because such activities brought them an income. Many Terran merchants would fall for this type of scheme by the Jackal tribe. In the end, the Jackal tribe would swallow their goods.

* * *

Footnotes:

[1]豺狗 – Chái gǒu.

[2]Zhao Hai’s lack of knowledge about beastfolk seems more questionable by the chapter.

Chapter 237: Helping Him Solve Trouble

The Jackal tribe relied on these sorts of behaviour and eventually became the Beastfolk Prairie’s most notorious thieving tribe. They were known as shameless robbers and thieves among the beastfolk, while they were called cunning native dogs by the humans.

So when Zhao Hai heard Spear say that there was a Jackal tribe nearby, it made him surprised. He hastily said, “Brother Spear, if you knew there was a Jackal tribe nearby, then why are you still here? You should leave this area as soon as possible.”

Spear nodded. “I know this, brother. We had been preparing to leave for the last couple of days. That’s why I was so anxious when you arrived; it was due to the Jackal tribe that was close by.”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “Brother, for the safety of the Pig tribe, we must make the trade as soon as possible and leave immediately. After breakfast, we will leave the food behind. All you need to do is prepare my stuff.”

Spear looked at Zhao Hai. “Brother, where will you go? Back to the human’s stone city or deeper into the prairies? If you wish to go deeper into the prairies, then you must be careful. If you see a strange tribe, check what ethnic race they are first, then pass them if needed.”

Zhao Hai was touched. He didn’t think that these carefree Pig tribe people would think so much about him. Smiling, he said, “Brother, don’t worry. Do not forget that I am still a magician. If the Jackal tribe really dares to attack me, then I will teach them a lesson.”

Spear laughed. “Brother, I almost forgot that you were an omnipotent magician! Hahaha. I hope those hateful thieves won’t encounter you.”

Zhao Hai also laughed as the two walked towards the center of the camp. At this time, a Pig tribe young girl took out two bowls of sheep’s milk and came over. Spear then said to Zhao Hai, “Brother, have a taste of this. It’s the freshest sheep’s milk in the prairie, best for breakfast.”

He examined the two bowls of sheep’s milk and became speechless. The sheep’s milk hadn’t undergone any heating, but had instead been directly squeezed out of a sheep. It was the first time Zhao Hai had seen sheep’s milk like this.

Although it was his first time seeing such sheep’s milk, Zhao Hai was too embarrassed to reject Spear’s offer. He accepted the bowl of sheep’s milk from the young Pig tribe girl’s hands and drank it.

It was hard to imagine how much it reeked of sheep. It hadn’t undergone any type of processing or flavoring. One couldn’t imagine how much of a sheep’s smell it had. Even Zhao Hai wouldn’t eat anything with such a deep smell. Now that he had a mouthful of sheep’s stick, it made him want to almost spit it out.

After he endured past the sheep stink, he began to smell a sweet, fragrant aroma from it. This kind of aroma was something that didn’t belong to any seasoning product he knew of. Instead, it seemed to be the milk’s natural aroma. The smell made Zhao Hai close his mouth as he tried the aftertaste.

Spear watched Zhao Hai’s appearance and couldn’t help but laugh as he said, “Brother, I’m really confused about whether you are a human or a beastfolk. Many humans, when drinking fresh sheep’s milk, would spit it back out. Later on, they wouldn’t dare to drink it at all. You, however, seem to have a liking for its taste. Haha. Brother, do you have beastfolk blood in you?”

Turning, Zhao Hai looked at this fellow with the giant pig’s head and suddenly saw a slyness in this fellow’s eyes. He couldn’t help but beat Spear’s arm, saying, “Good. You actually want to see me become a joke. Haha. To be honest, this fresh sheep’s milk is very fragrant[1].”

Zhao Hai’s hit was, without a doubt, just a tickle at the most for Spear. Spear, however, liked Zhao Hai’s performance a lot, so he laughed and patted Zhao Hai’s shoulder, causing him to make an agonized face.

At this time, Laura and the others had woken up and also walked out of their tent. The reason why they came out now was because they feared Zhao Hai would suspected them, so they endured patiently until now.

When he saw Laura and the other two come out, Spear immediately asked his wife to prepare and serve them a meal. The breakfast was very simple, sheep’s milk and handed pilaf[2].

After breakfast, Zhao Hai ordered the undead to move the food from the caravan and into the Sheep Head Hammer horde camp.

Spear also took out five of the best wool blankets they produced, along with five of the best carpets. Ten strong argali, two piglets, and two of the best prairie mastiffs[3] followed. All of them were given over to Zhao Hai.

Zhao Hai thought of declining the extras, but Spear actually put on such a serious face in order to stop him. After receiving the items, Zhao Hai said goodbye to Spear, then led the caravan deeper into the prairie.

Although they had only been in the prairie for a few days, Zhao Hai currently liked it here. The beastfolk were simple, adorable, and impressive friends who didn’t have any flowery thoughts. Compared to the scheming humans, they were more pure and direct. Friends were friends, enemies were enemies. This was also why they would always suffer losses in their relationship with the humans.

Presently, Laura was looking at the Big Bellied Pig tribe’s war flag that was hung on their caravan, dazed. With regards to the beastfolk war flags, she didn’t know much about them. She also believed that many human merchants wouldn’t know its significance. As such, when she saw Spear give Zhao Hai the war flag, it made her surprised.

Zhao Hai felt nostalgic whenever he saw the Sheep Head Hammer horde war flag. He retracted his vision and looked at Laura. Smiling, he asked, “What’s wrong? Why are you always staring at the war flag?”

Laura turned her head to Zhao Hai. “Don’t you think it’s strange? Why did Spear give us their war flag? The Sheep Head Hammer horde is just a small part of the tribe, and the Big Bellied Pig tribe is just a small part of the ethnic race. A war flag from such a horde is absolutely useless. As such, they generally wouldn’t give their war flag to others.”

Smiling, Zhao Hai told Laura about Spear’s explanation of the significance of war flags. Once he finished his explanation, Laura’s eyes shone as she looked at Zhao Hai. “Great! I heard that once a beastfolk recognizes a human as their real friend, almost no beastfolk would attack them. Brother Hai, it seems that this time we’ve obtained a great harvest for cheap.

Zhao Hai nodded. With a sinking voice, he said, “I also think Spear had been really good to us. As a matter of fact, he told me about some rumours he’d heard recently. It seems that there is a nearby active Jackal tribe.”

Laura was surprised for a moment, then her complexion changed as she said, “Jackal tribe? Is it really a Jackal tribe?”

Zhao Hai nodded. “It’s really a Jackal tribe. With the Jackal tribe in this area, it’ll become a big threat for Spear’s horde. Do you think we should help Spear and solve this trouble?”

Laura was surprised for a moment. She hadn’t thought of this point. What she knew was that the Jackal tribe wasn’t something they needed to fear. She actually didn’t expect Zhao Hai to propose helping Spear solve this problem.

She did understood what Zhao Hai meant. At present, they had the blood-colored eagles that could survey a wide area. So long as they had the blood-colored eagles do a thorough search, they would certainly be able to find the Jackal tribe. With their strength, destroying the Jackal tribe was possible. So long as they eliminated the Jackal tribe, they’d have helped Spear. The alternative was that Spear’s horde of only a few hundred people would be attacked.

After thinking about it for a while, Laura said, “That’s fine. The Jackal tribe is hated by all of the beastfolk. If we eliminate them, then no one would go after us for it and the beastfolk might even be grateful to us.”

Zhao Hai smiled. “Moreover, the Jackal tribe may even have raised some magic beasts of their own that we haven’t seen yet, something like these water-spurting pigs.”

As Zhao Hai said this, Laura and the others couldn’t help but look at the back of their carriage. There, two of the carriages contained the two piglets. These were the young water-spurting pig mounts that Spear had used.

These water-spurting pigs were magic beasts that only the Big Bellied Pig tribe could raise as they had some blood relation with the magic beasts. This wasn’t some sort of curse, but rather, a beastfolk tradition.

The beastfolk had always considered themselves descendants of humans and magic beasts. As such, they had control over the same abilities as the magic beasts. These water-spurting pigs were the Big Bellied Pig tribe’s magic beast relatives. It was due to the fact that these water-spurting pigs, like them, had big bellies and drank a lot of water. In battle, they could launch out water from their stomachs to attack the enemy. The water-spurting pigs, however, could launch the water further than the Big Bellied Pig tribe and their missiles could reach as far as fifty meters. Furthermore, they could continue to launch that water ten times. The Big Bellied Pig tribe could only use it five consecutive times.

Since they were still near Spear’s camp, Zhao Hai decided not to place the argali, water-spurting piglets, or the prairie mastiff in the Space. In any case, it wasn’t so bad.

The two piglets were placed in a carriage while the prairie mastiffs and argali followed beside the carriages. The next carriage was where the wool blankets and carpets had been placed.

Laura looked at the ten wool products and smiled as she said to Zhao Hai, “This time, we’ve really gained a lot. Don’t mention the argali or the few water-spurting pigs, just the wool blankets will give us a lot of money. The beastfolk made these blankets and carpets by hand and they are really popular among humans.”

Zhao Hai smiled. “It’s precisely because of this that I want to help Spear. With a Jackal tribe in the vicinity, it’ll be very dangerous for Spear.”

Laura nodded. “Alright, let’s do it then. In any case, this matter will also be good for us.”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly and issued out orders to the blood-colored eagles.

Just then, Nier suddenly said, “Young Master, would it be alright if I raise the two piglets? They’re just too cute.”

When he heard Nier’s words, Zhao Hai became speechless. He also thought that the piglets were adorable. They had black and white skin colors, with one having a black mark on its left eye while the other had the mark on its right. It gave off the feeling that they’d collected some leaves and grass on their eyes and made them look comedic and adorable. It was no wonder Nier liked them so much.

Zhao Hai smiled as he said, “Nier, those two piglets will be raised in the Space. Once they mature and have their own piglets, I’ll take two out for you to raise. Is that fine?”

* * *

Footnotes:

[1]In the end, you can best describe all beastfolk items with this one word: Fragrant.

[2]手抓饭 – Shǒu zhuā fàn. The hand part was hard to include, but the second two characters, 抓饭 = pilaf. https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Pilaf

[3]草原獒 – Cǎoyuán áo.

Chapter 238: Strange Prompts

Because Nier was such a pure person, Zhao Hai unconsciously regarded her as a lovable little sister. As such, Zhao Hai had that kind of expression when he spoke with her.

Thinking about it for a while, Nier finally nodded and said, “Alright. When they give birth to their own piglets, Young Master must give me a couple!”

Zhao Hai nodded with a smile. He knew that Nier liked to raise magic beasts. Nier’s request wasn’t out of some temporary whim. Turning, Zhao Hai looked around and found that they were now far from the Sheep Head Hammer horde. Since no one else was around, he made Laura stop the caravan. He then brought the argali, water-spurting piglets, and the prairie mastiffs into the Space.

Afterward, they also entered the Space. The animals were currently placed in the warehouse. Once Zhao Hai brought them into the Spatial Ranch, they would be evaluated immediately.

After they entered the Space, they heard a few odd knocks. Surprised for a moment, Zhao Hai soon found that it was from Green and the others who were staying at Fort Iron Mountain. They had anxious faces as they knocked on the ground.

Zhao Hai was only surprised for a moment before he naturally understood what was happening. At the same time, he felt guilty. He’d drunk too much yesterday, so they naturally couldn’t return to the Space, nor leave Fort Iron Mountain. Green and the others were definitely concerned about them. He feared they didn’t get a good sleep last night.

Seeing this situation, Zhao Hai postponed promoting the Space. He immediately let Green and the others into the Space. As soon as Green and the others entered the Space, they saw Zhao Hai standing there with a guilty expression. Green quickly greeted him and carefully looked him over before asking, “Young Master, are you alright? Why didn’t you come back to Fort Iron Mountain yesterday? We were worried throughout this sleepless night.”

Zhao Hai guiltily replied, “I’m sorry, Grandpa Green. We met the Big Bellied Pig tribe yesterday. You know how beastfolk drink wine until they get drunk. Yesterday, I got drunk so I wasn’t able to return to the Space. Sorry.”

Upon hearing Zhao Hai’s answer, Green relaxed. He smiled and said, “So you drank with the beastfolk; no wonder. Those beastfolk wouldn’t let go of someone if they didn’t drink until their faces fell to the floor.”

Quinn John, who was talking to Laura, heard what Green said and smiled. “Yes, those beastfolk really are like that. Making Zhao Hai drink till he was drunk on the ground is normal. Right, Zhao Hai, what good things did you get from the trade this time?”

Laura didn’t want for Zhao Hai to speak as she smiled and said, “This time, we got several really good things. There’s five good beastfolk blankets and five carpets, two Big Bellied Pig tribe unique magic beasts; water-spurting pigs, and two unique prairie magic beasts; prairie mastiffs.

Presently, Quinn John and the others knew how much food was in their possession. When they heard Laura’s report, Quinn John nodded and said, “Great. Compared to using normal prices, this isn’t that bad.”

Laura smiled and said, “It wasn’t much, but Spear felt that Brother Hai was a true friend, so he gave us all of these things. Haha. Actually, other things don’t really matter. What’s important is that we obtained three kinds of magic beasts.”

Quinn John understood what Laura meant. This time, they’d obtained three magic beasts which, in other words, might upgrade the Spatial Ranch.

He immediately said, “So, what are we waiting for? Let’s quickly move them. It’ll upgrade the Spatial Ranch for sure.”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “It won’t be that easy. These three magic beasts we brought would need to be of high rank, not low. Otherwise, the Spatial Ranch won’t easily upgrade.”

Green smiled. “It doesn’t matter. We’ll take things slowly. We’ve only just entered the Beastfolk Prairie and I heard each beastfolk ethnic race has their own unique magic beast. If we can collect those unique magic beasts neatly, then I think the Spatial Ranch will upgrade. I want to see how it will look when it’s at its highest level.”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “I hope so. The problem is that these magic beasts aren’t easy to get. If I didn’t hit it off well with Spear, then it would have been impossible for him to give me those water-spurting pigs. Moreover, what he could only give me were water-spurting piglets and not adult pigs. From this, you can see that the beastfolk really favor their own unique magic beasts.”

Quinn John forced a smile. “I almost forgot about this. To the beastfolk, these unique magic beasts are, in their opinion, part of their family. Would you just hand over your loved ones to someone if they asked?”

Zhao Hai and the others were speechless after they heard Quinn John. With regards to humans, it would be difficult for them to think of magic beasts as family. For the beastfolk, however, this was a normal matter.

Zhao Hai suddenly thought of those pets being raised by lonely elders back on Earth. Those people regarded their pets as family and would even leave a large inheritance for them after they died. Compared to these elders, the beastfolk didn’t seem as crazy. They both placed magic beasts or pets in their hearts.

He didn’t say anything more, but instead transferred everyone into the Spatial Ranch. He then took out the argali, water-spurting pigs, and prairie mastiffs.

After the three types of magic beasts were released, the Space immediately prompted in a tone:

[Discovered new sheep-shaped animal variation. Evaluating level: Level 3 animal.

This animal has replaced the Space’s original sheep.

This animal has a maturity time of eight hours. Can produce wool seven times and give birth once.

Each birth will produce eight lambs. Each wool cycle will produce 100 kilograms.

Requires feed twice per hour.

Digitizing animal. Animal can now be purchased from the Spatial Shop.]

[Discovered pig-shaped animal variation. Evaluating level: Level 20 animal.

This animal has a maturity time of twenty hours and can give birth to piglets ten times.

A max of ten piglets can be birthed at a time.

Requires feed five times per hour.

Digitizing animal. Animal can now be purchased from the Spatial Shop.]

[Discovered dog-shaped animal variation. Evaluating level: Level 15 animal.

This animal has a maturity time of twenty hours and can give birth to puppies five times.

A max of nine puppies can be birthed at a time.

Requires feed twice per hour.

There is a 10% probability every birth for a chance of a variant. Evaluating level of variant: Level 30. All other data stays the same.

Digitizing animal. Animal can now be purchased from the Spatial Shop.]

Zhao Hai listened to the three long prompts and was stunned. While the evaluation of the water-spurting pig was normal, the argali and prairie mastiff had abnormal Space prompts.

It was especially amazing for the Space’s prompt for the argali. It produce wool seven times and a set of eight lambs at once. This was something Zhao Hai hadn’t encountered before.s

The prompt for the prairie mastiff indicated that there was a 10% chance of a variant being birthed, and that the variant was a Level 30 magic beast. In the end, how did this occur?

Zhao Hai immediately examined the Spatial Ranch’s storage and looked at the list. There really were three more magic beast pictures. The argali occupied the original position of the sheep while there wasn’t anything different about the other two.

He looked at the slot for the prairie mastiff and saw that there wasn’t anything different about it. In the end, how would it work? Why did the prairie mastiff have a 10% chance of producing a variant?

Zhao Hai stared at the picture of the prairie mastiff and carefully examined it. In his head, the number, ‘nine’, kept flashing, along with the word, ‘variant’. He was caught by them. The idea flashed on and off, so he couldn’t grasp it.

Laura arrived at Zhao Hai’s side and said, “Brother Hai, what’s the matter? Will the prairie mastiffs really have a variant[1]? Moreover, its battle prowess isn’t that low. Listening to the prompts, it seemed that the strength of the variant would be equal to a Rank Five or Rank Six magic beast.”

Battle prowess! When Laura mentioned those words, Zhao Hai’s thoughts finally got a few clues. He now knew why the prairie mastiff would create a variant.

On Earth, not all dogs could be considered mastiffs. Zhao Hai had once heard the phrase, “9 dogs, 1 mastiff[2].” In other words, even if all nine were supposedly mastiffs, only one could be considered a true mastiff. That mastiff wasn’t only a name or a species, but a symbol of its battle strength.

This time, the prairie mastiff could give birth to nine puppies. Nine dogs, one mastiff. This phrase maybe pointing out the reason why the Space had said there was a chance of a variant emerging. This variant, to put it bluntly, was the one out of the nine that was a proper mastiff.

After he figured it out, Zhao Hai laughed and turned to Laura. “It’s nothing. The variant is just an ordinary prairie mastiff that undergoes a mutation. As such, its battle prowess is higher, that’s all.”

Laura agreed but still said unhappily, “Even with the three different magic beasts here, the Spatial Ranch didn’t upgrade. What a pity.”

Zhao Hai smiled. “It’s not a pity. In the future, it’ll become even harder to upgrade. Alright, let’s go out. First, we’ll need to be self-sufficient. When the Black Waste grows larger after the transformations, we’ll need to be able to establish a business in the Rosen Empire.”

Laura didn’t oppose. While at present they still had the continued cooperation with the Purcell clan, they weren’t prepared to build it further. It would only be after they establish a business in the Rosen Empire that they could do so.

After Zhao Hai handled the matters of the Spatial Ranch, they all returned to the Spatial Farm. Sitting down, Zhao Hai began to explain about what happened after they came into contact with Spear and also went into detail about the war flags for Green and the others. Zhao Hai told them these matters because he was thinking that it would help them in the future for when they made further contact with the beastfolk. The experience gained from dealing with Spear had a possibility of being needed in the future.

Moreover, they might also encounter something that required Green to help solve. Therefore, it was better to let Green have a better understanding of the beastfolk’s situation. As such, Zhao Hai naturally discussed the war flag matters. He also told them that he wanted to help Spear by dealing with the Jackal tribe.

Green and the others listened attentively. To be honest, if they went and had contact with the beastfolk, then they wouldn’t have been able to do what Zhao Hai did. They were like other humans on the continent; they wanted to find out how to gain more benefits from the beastfolk. On the other hand, Zhao Hai had won the beastfolk’s friendship with sincerity and generosity. It could be said that this recent transaction didn’t only give them materials, but also the treasured friendship of the beastfolk. This was especially true when Spear gave them the friendship war flag.

After Zhao Hai finished, Green grew a bit out of breath[3]. He looked at Zhao Hai with a complex expression. “Young Master, you did a wonderful job. It was better than what I could have done. Oh, Young Master has truly grown to be a person that can deal with all sorts of situations. With this, I feel relieved.”

Looking at the somewhat excited Green, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but smile slightly. “Don’t get too excited, Grandpa Green. I still have much to learn from you, so don’t leave me. Oh, right. Do you think it was a good idea to help Spear by dealing with the Jackal tribe?”

Green nodded. “It’s fine. How can it not be fine? With regards to us, dealing with the Jackal tribe isn’t a difficult matter. Moreover, we will also obtain a few benefits. What’s most important are the unique magic beasts of the Jackal tribe. We definitely must take them. This is important as the Spatial Ranch still needs them.”

Quinn John nodded. “The best way to deal with this is for us to leave a little trace of what we did so that others will know of it. With this, the beastfolk would welcome us warmly.”

Zhao Hai and Laura laughed at Quinn John’s thoughts. They definitely wouldn’t do this as they knew Quinn John was just cracking a joke.

Although the beastfolk didn’t approve of the Jackal tribe, don’t forget that the Jackal tribe was still one of the beastfolk. Regardless of what the Jackal tribe did, it was still an internal affair of the beastfolk. If the beastfolk found out that people killed a beastfolk tribe within the prairie, then it would be difficult to imagine what kind of reaction they might have[4].

After joking around for some time, Green and the others wanted to return to Fort Iron Mountain. Although there weren’t many matters that needed to be addressed, there also weren’t a few. Zhao Hai released two of the argali and was looking for a place in Fort Iron Mountain to raise them. At the same time, he passed Green and the others the blankets and carpets.

After doing all of this, Zhao Hai led Laura and the others back to the carriage. The caravan hadn’t stopped, but had continued to move forward. Here in the prairies, however, they were surrounded by the same constant view. If it wasn’t for the fact that they were looking for plants, then they wouldn’t have wanted to stay here.

After coming back to the caravan, Zhao Hai filled one carriage with food. If they met a beastfolk tribe, then it would guarantee that they would be warmly welcomed.

To be honest, just hurrying along was quite boring. Fortunately, Zhao Hai still collected plants and this relieved him of his boredom. There were many plants in the prairie, and except for a few specific areas, everywhere else was covered with grass. All of this grass would be uniform. While Zhao Hai and the others wanted to distinguish them, they unfortunately couldn’t really tell the difference.

For Laura and the others, this was fine. They crowded together and chatted, which was quite lively. On the other hand, Zhao Hai was quite depressed as he didn’t understand many of the topics they discussed.

Noon arrived soon after. Zhao Hai and the others were ready to re-enter the Space and eat something when Zhao Hai heard the cry of a blood-colored eagle. They decided to stay as they knew they’d found the Jackal tribe.

* * *

Footnotes:

[1]You know, a smart thing to do now was to have him ask Cai’er… But then, I’ve never seen Zhao Hai as smart… he’s just really good at following whatever the plot has for him.

[2]I have never heard this before. I assume it’s like the majority of Zhao Hai’s phrases which come from nowhere, or from author’s obscure understanding of actual phrases… Rarely have I come away from here with a good, legitimate phrase. Maybe it’s from this (the site is basically like a yahoo answers site): https://zhidao.baidu.com/question/44003106.html

[3]People have weird fetishes…

[4]Yes, last chapter they discussed that the beastfolk wouldn’t care of and might even thank them for dealing with the beastfolk. Once again, I’d just ignore the inconsistency.

Chapter 239: Cattle-head King’s[1] Flag

Zhao Hai stared tightly at the blood-colored eagle as it continued to circle the sky. Laura also looked at the blood-colored eagle. They were really curious as to what information this blood-colored eagle had.

Zhao Hai understood everything after watching. The blood-colored eagles’ reconnaissance ability was strong because they could fly high and had good vision. In addition, they could understand what Zhao Hai wanted. As such, they became very good aerial scouts.

The report from the blood-colored eagles was very important for Zhao Hai. This was because the information they brought told that there were two beastfolk tribes fighting one another. On one side was the Cattle-head ethnic race while the other side was the Jackal tribe[2].

Zhao Hai frowned. He didn’t know if he should attack in this situation. If a human rashly interfered in a battle between the beastfolk, then it wouldn’t be good.

Laura and the others also understood the information passed along by the blood-colored eagles. With regards to this situation, Laura also felt it was awkward. For the beastfolk, a battle was honorable. If one intervened, then both sides might be offended. Even the side they helped wouldn’t give their thanks.

After thinking about it for a while, Laura turned to Zhao Hai and asked, “Brother Hai, what should we do?”

Thinking, Zhao Hai said, “We’ll first take a look and pretend to just be passing by. We won’t make a move first.”

Laura nodded. Zhao Hai then immediately directed the caravan in a path that would pass by the battlefield.

The battlefield wasn’t near them, otherwise the blood-colored eagles wouldn’t have taken all morning to pass along the information. In order to rush as fast as they could to the battlefield, Zhao Hai had taken back the rest of the caravan and placed them inside the Space, leaving only Laura’s carriage to move forward. They proceeded along at a faster pace this way.

After two hours, they finally arrived at the battlefield the blood-colored eagles had reported. As they got there, several war cries could be heard.

Zhao Hai didn’t expect that the two tribes could fight for so long. It was currently noon, and since the time the blood-colored eagles had found the two tribes until now, it was already a little over three hours. This wasn’t a short period.

Zhao Hai slowed down and looked out the carriage once more. He then slowly moved toward the battlefield. There wasn’t any worry since he knew that both sides were still in the midst of fighting.

Everyone soon got closer to the battlefield. In the distance, there seemed to be a camp. The size of the camp wasn’t that large, only as big the Sheep Head Hammer horde camp. This camp had a Cattle-head war flag flying above the central tent. Laura looked at the war flag and her complexion changed. “The Cattle-head King’s war flag. How could it be the Cattle-head King’s war flag?

Zhao Hai was surprised for a moment. “Cattle-head King’s war flag? You’re saying that’s the Cattle-head King’s war flag?” The reason why he was so surprised was because the Cattle-head King’s war flag wasn’t something anyone could casually obtain. Only members of the Cattle-head ethnic race’s royal family, the Titan Cattle[3] tribe, could use it.

Although the Beastfolk Prairie’s beastfolk ethnic races were numerous, there were also top tribes among the ethnic races that were given the status of a royal family tribes. One of these ethnic races that practiced such a thing was the Cattle-head ethnic race. Although there were many related tribes, such as the rhinoceros tribe and etc, they all belonged to one large ethnic race, the Cattle-head ethnic race.

The royal family of the Cattle-head ethnic race was the Titan Cattle tribe. Everyone from the Titan Cattle tribe was a born warrior. They didn’t have any wool over their bodies and their skin was golden-yellow in color. This golden-yellow skin had great defensive capabilities. With the addition of their bloodline’s innate godly strength, it could be said that their battle prowess was comparable with the other famous war tribes. They wouldn’t fare badly against them.

If one weren’t from the Titan Cattle tribe and were just a common Cattle-head ethnic race tribe, then their battle prowess wouldn’t be great. The Cattle-head ethnic race could somewhat be regarded as a war tribe in the prairie, but the assessment of the race wasn’t that of a war tribe. When one assessed an ethnic race, one would look at the overall battle strength. The Cattle-head ethnic race had many low strength tribes, so they pulled down the rest of the ethnic race. In the end, they were assessed as a regular ethnic race and not a war tribe.

No matter if it were an ethnic race or a war tribe, they were divided heterogeneously. Just like the Lion ethnic race and Tiger ethnic race, both had their top tribes represent the war tribe because they had the greatest battle strength. The Cattle-head ethnic race status was similar to theirs, but the Lion ethnic race and Tiger ethnic race were both existences at the top of the ethnic race hierarchy. Even then, those lower ranked war tribes wouldn’t be impolite towards the Cattle-head ethnic race, especially towards the Titan Cattle tribe.

The Titan Cattle tribe’s battle strength was very formidable, and their strength itself was boundless. With their powerful defensive capabilities and Bestial Soul Possession War Skill[4], they were very powerful.

Beastfolk and humans were different. Human practitioners cultivated battle qi or magic power, but beastfolk practitioners cultivated the so-called Bestial Soul Possession War Skill. In fact, this was the unique cultivation method of the beastfolk. Every beastfolk youth, upon reaching ten years of age, would be required to hunt and kill a magic beast alone. They would then use the mystical beastfolk cultivation method to absorb the magic beast’s body and soul. Every time a beastfolk fought, the magic beast’s soul and body would aid them.

This Bestial Soul Possession War Skill, however, had its own limitations. The limitations varied based on individual bloodline, and different bloodlines meant different limits for each ethnic race.

Take the slave tribes of the beastfolk for example. They also cultivated the Bestial Soul Possession War Skill, but it was impossible for them to attract a powerful magic beast’s soul. If they forcibly tried to absorb one, then instead of gaining strength, they’d cause a rebound effect. Their body would get damaged and the magic beast’s soul may control them instead, turning them into a beast.

Strong magic beasts would be attracted to beastfolk with strong battle strength. If the magic beast was a wild one, then the deciding factor was battle strength.

For example, a domesticated Rank Five magic beast wouldn’t be able to defeat a wild magic beast of the same rank. This was because a Rank Five wild magic beast would, from birth, have been continuously battling other magic beasts. Since they were constantly fighting, their natural battle strength would definitely be higher than a domesticated Rank Five magic beast.

For the beastfolk, absorbing the soul of a magic beast would enable them to use a part of the combat experience of the magic beast. For the beastfolk, this was very important.

Weaker beastfolk didn’t have the ability to capture and kill magic beasts. This was the reason why they used domesticated magic beasts, and this naturally meant a lower battle strength.

For war tribes and common ethnic races, the biggest difference between the two would be that the beast souls of the war tribes generally consisted of carnivorous magic beasts. Ethnic races would instead use beast souls from herbivorous magic beasts, those that were preyed upon.

Beast soul absorption also wasn’t very equal. For example, if one were of the Cattle-head ethnic race and wanted to absorb a lion-type magic beast soul, then they would have a very low chance of success. Even if they did succeed, it wouldn’t give them much strength. This was because there was a low degree of compatibility between them, resulting in negative effects.

For the Cattle-head ethnic race, the best magic beast soul they could absorb would be those related to the Cattle-head ethnic race. If they couldn’t attract a Cattle-head ethnic race related magic beast, then they’d be better off getting another herbivorous type of magic beast instead of a carnivorous one. This was knowledge obtained after many years of trial and error.

For the Titan Cattle tribe, their beast soul could be regarded as a unified soul. Their magic beast soul was from a Rank Six earth elemental magic beast, a stoneskin cattle[5].

This stoneskin cattle was as its name suggested; it was a magic beast with very high defensive capabilities. Its offensive strength was also quite high. Of all the magic beasts, there weren’t many with a better strength than a stoneskin cattle.

After many years of trial and error, the Titan Cattle tribe had finally decided to absorb the stoneskin cattle magic beast soul. Since the Titan Cattle tribe and stoneskin cattle had many of the same attributes, after the absorption there was a high rate of compatibility. As such, the Titan Cattle tribe used their strength to rear stoneskin cattle.

Naturally, this so-called rearing wasn’t the same as raising them in a ranch. They instead placed the stoneskin cattle in an enclosure in order to prevent them from running away. These cattle could move inside the enclosure freely, and if they encountered danger, the Titan Cattle tribe wouldn’t help. This allowed the stoneskin cattle to become more wild.

This was a common practice among the beastfolk war tribes. Long periods of trial and error was consumed to find out the best and most suitable magic beast for the tribe to absorb. They would need to only partly rear the magic beasts. When the time came that a tribe member was required to capture and absorb a beast soul, they could just enter the enclosure. They would then hunt and kill the magic beast, then absorb its soul.

All of this guaranteed the battle strength of their ethnic race. After many years of development, the beastfolk’s renowned war tribes had created their own well defined cultivation system. Compared to the beastfolk of the past, it was more effective.

Small tribes and weaker ethnic races didn’t have the capability to rear magic beasts like the war tribes. As such, their battle strength didn’t develop much. This eventually caused the current system among the beastfolk. The war tribes were getting stronger and stronger while the smaller tribes and lower ethnic races became weaker and weaker.

While the Titan Cattle tribe was a part of a weaker ethnic race, they were a tribe that raised their own magic beasts. This reflected their strength and even those war tribes didn’t provoke them so casually.

This was the reason why Laura was so surprised after seeing the Cattle-head King’s war flag. The Jackal tribe would be like a soft persimmon being pinched. With a powerful tribe like the Titan Cattle tribe, why did they try to provoke them and suddenly attack? Also, why was the Titan Cattle tribe in this area? This was still quite close to Ironwall Fortress. Within the Beastfolk Prairie, it could be considered the borderlands. The tribe shouldn’t be here.

Zhao Hai and Laura were both looking at the Cattle-head King’s war flag and were both speechless. When they saw the war flag here, they feared the matter wouldn’t be simple. Their simple passing this time around was a consequence unknown to them. The Titan Cattle tribe was here, yet they had bravely rushed over. Once the Titan Cattle tribe finished off the Jackal tribe, they feared they would turn to deal with them and silence the witnesses.

* * *

Footnotes:

[1]牛头王 – Niútóu wáng.

[2]Hrm… anyone else just wondering how he taught the eagles to explain any of this?? I’d believe it more if he just telepathically communicates with them.

[3]大力神牛 – Dàlì shén niú.

[4]兽魂附体战技 – Shòu hún fù tǐ zhàn jì. It’s an actual thing, yea…

[5]石肤牛 – Shífūniú

Chapter 240: Prophet[1]

Laura took a deep breath and carefully examined the war flag that was raised above the camp. It truly was the Cattle-head King’s war flag. Laura turned to Zhao Hai and said, “Brother Hai, it truly is the Cattle-head King’s war flag. What should we do?

Zhao Hai frowned. He had his suspicions about this. Why would the Jackal tribe unexpectedly attack the Titan Cattle tribe? Zhao Hai felt that this was strange. The problem was that he couldn’t say for sure what exactly was strange about it.

He looked at the battlefield and sighed. “Doing anything else is useless. Now that we’re near the battlefield, they should have already seen us. All we can do now is move forward.”

Laura also examined the battlefield. Sure enough, she saw that they’d already been noticed. Turning back at this time would be far too late.

They weren’t really afraid of having problems with the other party. Don’t forget that they had the Big Bellied Pig tribe’s friendship war flag raised above their carriage. If they ran, Spear would receive no small amount of trouble. After all, there was no such thing as an airtight wall in this world. No matter if it was the Titan Cattle tribe or the Jackal tribe, they were both tribes Spear couldn’t contend with.

Zhao Hai’s caravan slowly moved toward the battlefield. Their reaction was contrary to the parties presently fighting. Currently, the Jackal clan was on the offensive while the Titan Cattle tribe was on the defensive.

The Jackal tribe had mobilized two thousand tribe members while the Titan Cattle tribe only had several hundred tribe members in their camp.

While the defending Titan Cattle tribe members only numbered three hundred, they were all elite warriors. Each of them wore leather armor and held double-edged heavy axes. They didn’t ride any mounts as their mounts were stationed within the camp. The mounts were earthen-yellow bulls of around three meters tall. These bulls had thin, fine fur crowing around them and looked extremely strong. Their muscles were well built and they had a pair of angular horns about a meter long. With thick hooves that pawed the ground uneasily, they seemed to want to join in the fight.

Beyond this, Zhao Hai understood why they were called the Titan Cattle tribe.

Titan Cattle tribe members had a height around 2.5 meters with muscles comparable to a top bodybuilder. If they went to Earth and joined a bodybuilding competition, even Schwarzenegger[2] would have to step aside.

Their skin was a golden yellow color and glossy as it flashed like metal. They were comparable to the actors who played in the 18 Bronzemen[3].

They each had a giant cattle’s head and a pair of half-meter long horns. Their hands were large enough to handle a three-meter long huge double-edged war axe. Just looking at the axe’s head, its weight definitely wasn’t below a hundred kilograms.

Although their numbers were small, they had formed a circle formation and were defending the perimeter of the camp. They were like an impregnable bronze wall. Not even the Jackal tribe was able to pass through them. At the front were numerous Jackal tribe corpses.

It was the opposite for the Jackal tribe. These Jackal tribe members rode their mounts. Their mounts were like wolves, a type of canine that was similar to jackals from Earth. Their build was a lot larger, around two meters in height. They had sharp claws and teeth and cold eyes. These jackals had already revealed an extraordinary ability for assault.

The Jackal tribe members didn’t wear any leather armor, but instead wore the ordinary leather clothing that beastfolk wore. They were around 1.7 meters tall and held a variety of weapons in their hands. Their eyes were like that of a jackal’s as they exuded a flash of brutal light.

Zhao Hai didn’t really think of the Jackal tribe as very tall. They were even shorter than average humans. It was a shock that they could become the most outstanding robbers in the prairie with such stature. This astonished him.

At this time, both sides battling each other noticed him. Zhao Hai didn’t move forward in a straight path but instead made the carriage circle the area, putting on an appearance of refusing to look at either party.

The reason why Zhao Hai did this was because he was testing them. He wanted to see if the Titan Cattle tribe would move to ask him to reinforce them. If the Titan Cattle tribe seeks his help, then he would help. If they didn’t, then he would die here as well[4].

His performance, however, shocked both sides. They had seen many human merchants, but seeing Zhao Hai, a human merchant with such great courage, was their first time.

Generally, the human merchants that venture out into the Beastfolk Prairie would usually carry an understanding of the path they would take in advance and be aware of it. In this case where they were battling and a human merchant came upon them, the humans would certainly hide far away. They wouldn’t act like Zhao Hai who even went forward and put on an appearance of ignoring both parties. Their caravan didn’t have many people, so how could they go up against both parties?

It was no wonder the Titan Cattle tribe and Jackal tribe had such an idea. Presently, Zhao Hai and his caravan had fifty people altogether. Fifty coachmen and Zhao Hai with the three women[5]. Such a number and still playing cards, these people dared to put themselves out and face their enemies. One side was the Titan Cattle tribe, a strong tribe, while the other was the Jackal tribe, the Beastfolk Prairie’s most notorious bandits. This really gave the feeling that they let their heads get kicked by a mosquito[6].

At this time, a person suddenly left the tent in the middle of the Titan Cattle tribe’s camp. This person was a member of the Cattle-head ethnic race, but he was obviously not of the Titan Cattle tribe. This cattle-head member had a head of thin, black hair and a height of two meters or so. A pair of short horizontal horns adorned his head. This person wore a black cotton robe and held a beast bone cane in his hand. The cane was about a meter long and looked almost like a crutch.

Zhao Hai gawked. This was the first time he’d seen a beastfolk wearing robes. The beastfolk commonly wore leather clothes, yet this person wore a long gown that was similar to magic robes. What’s more important, this person was about two meters tall, but Zhao Hai felt the person was quite thin.

At this time, Laura suddenly interjected, “If I’m not mistaken, there must be a high ranking Titan Cattle tribe member here, otherwise there wouldn’t be a beastfolk prophet around.”

Zhao Hai stared for a while. He couldn’t say that he hadn’t heard of this beastfolk profession before. On the contrary, he knew of it. A beastfolk prophet was quite famous.

Prophets were a respected profession among the beastfolk. They couldn’t cultivated the Bestial Soul Possession War Skill, but they could roast beast bones over a fire and predict the future from the cracks in the bones. They could also use bone tablets made of magic beast bones in order to use the Soul Summoning technique[7], which could summon magic beast souls to attack. As such, the position of prophets among the beastfolk was comparable to human magicians and was quite high.

Due to a prophet’s status, only a war tribe could generally have one. Moreover, these prophets didn’t only have special abilities, but were also very intelligent members. They played a role as a military strategist within war tribes.

Zhao Hai turned to Laura and asked, “That’s a beastfolk prophet?”

Laura nodded. “That prophet is from the Water Buffalo tribe[8]. The Water Buffalo tribe is noted as the most intelligent tribe within the Cattle-head ethnic race. Most of the Cattle-head prophets come from the Water Buffalo tribe. Due to this, they have a very high status within the Cattle-head ethnic race, even though they don’t have high battle strength.”

The Water Buffalo tribe prophet also saw Zhao Hai, its eyes puzzled at first. Then he saw the friendship war flag from the Big Bellied Pig tribe and his eyes shone.

As a beastfolk prophet, he naturally understood what the beastfolk’s friendship war flag represented[9]. Since Zhao Hai was able to obtain one, it showed that they had gotten it from a horde or tribe. With regards to common merchants, this kind of goal wasn’t achievable in their lifetime.

Obtaining a beastfolk friendship war flag didn’t only mean that you obtained the friendship of the beastfolk; it also meant that the beastfolk wouldn’t consider you an outsider. In other words, Zhao Hai’s every action in the prairie could be counted as an action by a beastfolk.

Zhao Hai wasn’t aware of this. Even if he knew, he wouldn’t react to it. So long as the war flag was useful, he wouldn’t get into any trouble.

Upon seeing the war flag atop Zhao Hai’s carriage, the prophet was stunned for a moment before heading back into the tent. Before long, a Titan Cattle member came out.

This Titan Cattle member looked young and had a height of 2.3 meters. The muscles on him were overly exaggerated, and he didn’t wear leather armor but black cotton garments. The style of the black cotton clothes were very simple, but one could see that the materials it was made from were of good quality[10]. One must understand that the beastfolk couldn’t produce clothes, so clothes were quite scarce in the Beastfolk Prairie. Only a beastfolk with status could wear cotton clothing, and for high quality clothes, only those of very high status could acquire them.

Zhao Hai carefully observed this Titan Cattle tribe member. He found that this person’s horns had two golden hoops. Reflecting the sun, they shone golden rays of light.

Looking at the situation, Zhao Hai knew that those Titan Cattle tribe members were continuously protecting this person. As the beastfolk prophet stood behind him, it revealed that this person’s status wasn’t low.

Zhao Hai looked at the Titan Cattle people and they looked back at him. The black robe Zhao Hai wore was very conspicuous. It made it hard for others not to pay attention to him.

At this time, a team of two hundred Jackal tribe cavalrymen suddenly moved towards Zhao Hai. Zhao Hai didn’t do anything in return as he wanted to see what these Jackal tribe cavalrymen would do. If they only threatened him with words, then he wouldn’t fight back. If they tried to attack him, however, then he wouldn’t be polite.

Without waiting for those Jackal tribe cavalrymen to close in on Zhao Hai, the Titan Cattle leader opened his mouth and shouted, “Human friend, please come towards our camp. I will guarantee your safety.”

* * *

Footnotes:

[1]先知 – Xiānzhī.

[2]Good god, how old is this thing… when was the last time Old Arnie even competed in bodybuilding?

[3]https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/18_Bronzemen

[4]Questionable. 那他就在这里死等好了

[5]A few chapters ago, they should have put most of the caravan into the Space. I don’t know what’s happening here…

[6]Another weird saying that doesn’t make sense. Maybe the head is really empty and light enough to get kicked around by a bug?

[7]召魂术 – Zhào hún shù.

[8]水牛族 – Shuǐniú zú.

[9]Actually, based on the description given before, EVERY beastfolk should understand what a beastfolk friendship war flag is…

[10]How could one see this? What type of vision do they have?

Chapter 241: Waving a Hand to Exterminate the Enemy [1]

Zhao Hai was surprised for a moment, but then showed a faint smile. “Many thanks, beastfolk friends, but we don’t need to do so. We can solve this problem ourselves.” As he spoke, he turned to the oncoming Jackal tribe cavalry.

These Jackal tribe members were armed with weapons didn’t make them look very kind. They seemed ready to strike and kill everyone on the spot.

Zhao Hai snorted coldly and brandished his Ghost Cane. Over a hundred undead suddenly appeared around the caravan. These undead weren’t human-shaped, but were instead beast-shaped. Moreover, they weren’t zombies but skeletons.

By doing so, Zhao Hai showed he had no intention of hiding his identity. They were going to wander through the Beastfolk Prairie, so sooner or later they would be known by the other merchants. These merchants would then try to ascertain their identity. By revealing his identity as a black magician now, he would let them know that the black magician, Zhao Hai, had entered the Beastfolk Prairie.

Yesterday, Zhao Hai had taken back these undead and placed them in the Space specifically for this situation. As long as a black magician doesn’t use human-shaped undead, they wouldn’t get annoyed for it. Especially so when they were within the Beastfolk Prairie. Even then, strength was the basis for one’s right to speak within the Beastfolk Prairie. If one were to use human undead, the beastfolk wouldn’t be so repugnant about it. As long as one was strong enough, they wouldn’t act out of place so easily either.

Currently, Zhao Hai had saved around a thousand magic beast undead. A hundred of these undead were enough to deal with the current problem. As such, he didn’t release them all.

Even with this much, those Jackal tribe members were surprised. The magic beast undead that Zhao Hai released were really big. In front of these undead, the Jackal tribe members looked like 10-year-olds standing in front of a large man.

These undead had the strength of a Rank Seven magic beast, so they were a lot stronger than those Jackal tribe members. Because of the gap between the sizes of their bodies, the hundred undead were able to surround those two hundred Jackal tribe members. Since the Jackal tribe members weren’t able to react quickly enough, they were attacked twice by the undead. The two hundred Jackal tribe members were instantly defeated.

In the Beastfolk Prairie, if a human kills a beastfolk, they would be chased down by all beastfolk. If a human did it in self-defense, however, then the situation would be different and the beastfolk wouldn’t move.

After Zhao Hai released his undead, the Titan Cattle leader quickly understood that Zhao Hai could deal with the attack of the Jackal tribe. He never expected, however, that it could be solved so easily.

As a Titan Cattle prince, he had a greater understanding with regards to magicians than ordinary beastfolk. He had never seen such a magician fighting within the Beastfolk Prairie, however. After all, he lived in the Beastfolk Prairie and human magicians wouldn’t normally kill at will within the Beastfolk Prairies.

After dealing with the Jackal tribe, Zhao Hai turned his head to the young Titan Cattle tribe leader and said, “Dear beastfolk brother, we should collaborate with one another and deal with the enemies. Afterward, we can drink two cups together. How about it?”

Zhao Hai’s impression of this Titan Cattle person was quite good. When they had been in danger earlier, he had offered his help. Zhao Hai was grateful for such thoughtfulness.

As soon as the young Titan Cattle member heard what Zhao Hai said, he became stunned for a short moment. He thought over what Zhao Hai meant. While Zhao Hai wanted to help him, he also didn’t want to damage his face, so he offered his support to cooperate against the enemy—the Jackal tribe.

Although he understood Zhao Hai’s intent, the pride of the beastfolk wouldn’t let him agree so easily. Instead, he loudly said, “My human brother! I, the Titan Cattle tribe’s Wales[2], will help you exterminate those hateful dogs.”

Zhao Hai was surprised for a moment, then laughed. He liked Wales as he was very frank. Earlier, he feared Wales wouldn’t let him help, so he spoke of cooperation. He didn’t expect for Wales to be so proud that he would instead offer his help and refuse a weaker position.

The dialogue between them was clearly heard by those of the Jackal tribe, who couldn’t help but panic. They had seen the battle strength of the undead Zhao Hai had summoned and, to be honest, they weren’t very confident they could go up against that. With the addition of the Titan Cattle tribe’s three hundred warriors, they feared the situation wouldn’t go well for them.

They were about ready to make adjustments when a large number of undead suddenly appeared. These undead were just like the hundred undead that Zhao Hai had summoned previously. They were magic beasts and were a thousand in number. Those undead easily surrounded the two thousand Jackal tribe cavalry.

What was a cavalry’s most tragic situation? It would be when they were surrounded and lost the ability to charge out of the area. A rider that loses their ability to charge wouldn’t even be as good as infantry.

The reason why the Jackal tribe became the most notorious thieves in the prairie was due to their mounts. Their mounts were wind element magic beasts, cunning lightning jackals. These Rank Five magic beasts boasted a high degree of perception and flexibility. Because of this, the Jackal tribe could come and go like the wind throughout the entire Beastfolk Prairie and not allow others to find a trace of them.

But now they were surrounded. The mobility they had been so proud of had been sealed. The slender Jackal tribe had now truly become furnishings on a tea table, completely disastrous.

Soon enough, they found that they weren’t even furnishings on a tea table. To describe their situation more accurately, they were better suited in the kitchen where they would be diced up. They were surrounded by numerous undead and were doomed to a tragic outcome. It was so miserable that a tragedy might not even be the right word for their situation.

The Jackal tribe hurriedly tried to start a charge, but they didn’t know how they would deal with this situation. Zhao Hai then issued the attack and the thousand large undead began to assault the Jackal tribe.

Upon seeing the situation, Wales couldn’t help but be surprised for a moment. He quickly recovered and naturally wouldn’t miss such an opportunity to hit back against those dogs. Wales immediately issued the order to attack.

The Titan Cattle warriors had been surrounded and attacked by the Jackal tribe and their hearts had been continuously aggrieved to death. When they heard Wales’ order to attack, they shouted loudly and bristled as though they’d taken stimulants. They called for their mounts and road on the backs of the bulls, charging straight toward the Jackal tribe.

A Titan Cattle warrior’s mount wasn’t a stoneskin cattle. While stoneskin cattles were very powerful and had high defensive capabilities, they weren’t quick so they weren’t the best mount to use as cavalry. As such, what they used as mounts were instead magic beasts called earth-traversing cattle[3].

Earth-traversing cattles were Rank Five magic beasts and weren’t slow. They also had good defensive capabilities. In addition to their high strength, they became the most suitable mount for the Titan Cattle warriors. Earth-traversing cattles were not related by blood to the Titan Cattle tribe, but rather, it was the stoneskin cattle. The problem was that they killed stoneskin cattles and absorbed the magic beast soul from them. Herding blood-related magic beasts for such a task was an exceptional case within the Beastfolk Prairie.

In the Beastfolk Prairie, the beastfolk generally used their own blood-related magic beasts as mounts. There were, however, a few tribes like the Titan Cattle tribe who used other magic beasts like earth-traversing cattle as mounts instead of blood-related magic beasts.

Zhao Hai watched the charge of the Titan Cattle warriors. He had to admit that Titan Cattle warriors were truly a force to be reckoned with. Hands down, they did a great deal more damage than the heavy cavalry recorded from Earth. Imagine an army of massive warriors wielding hundred kilogram heavy war axes as they charged forth… this is what that concept was like.

Chinese martial arts community had a saying. A genuine weapon is swung, and one tael[4] equals one jin[5]. That is to say, a heavy weapon weighing one jin would increase the strength of the wielder and become ten jin of strength when it’s being swung. In ancient China, however, charging cavalry used swords that weren’t for swinging, but were instead flat and thin. They instead borrowed the force of the horse while atop the saddle to kill the enemy. Along with this, warriors in the prairies of China would use sickles[6], and the charge of a sickle-wielding cavalry was very lethal[7].

The Titan Cattle tribe’s charge, however, didn’t just involve them swinging their weapons. These were a hundred kilogram heavy weapons. Along with the power given off from the cattle they rode, just how much force could that axe possess? Zhao Hai really couldn’t come up with an estimate.

Zhao Hai was also a military otaku, so he knew of these things. The reason why ancient cavalry didn’t swing their weapons was because it would dislocate their shoulders. As such, when an ancient cavalry charge began, they used a long weapon. This kind of weapon couldn’t be held with one hand, but they could tuck the shaft beneath their arms.

During this time, common cavalrymen used spears. Once they pierced the enemy they would have to pull the spear back in order to make it useable again. Otherwise, the spear would directly break.

This was how ancient Chinese riders did their assault. While this method of assault was similar for foreign knights, those knights wore heavy armor and held a straight lance. While they changed, they must pay attention to the wooden lance in their hands. So long as they hit the enemy, the lance would snap. If the cavalry had good riding skills, then the lance would only have snapped at the tip and would still be useable.

A Chinese spear considered his problem, however, and the shaft of the spear wasn’t made entirely of wood. Instead, the spear would be wrapped around tightly with strips and resemble modern times steel wire ropes. It wouldn’t just be tough, but incomparably hard. When used to attack an enemy, the cavalryman could just use a bit of force to shrug the enemy off the shaft. Like this, after impact, the horse could keep its balance and avoid having to back up and die. The spear’s shaft in this case wouldn’t break[8].

It could be said that Earth’s ancient cavalry didn’t use the power of a human, but a horse’s strength. This time, the assault of the Titan Cattle cavalry used not only the earth-traversing cattle, but also their own strength, increasing their might greatly.

Naturally, the humans on the Ark Continent would have better bodies than those on Earth. Of course, the plants in the Ark Continent had an abundance of magic elements. Along with the natural qi in the air, it was a lot better compared with Earth. Since this was the case, the people living on the Ark Continent would have better physiques than those on Earth. They could achieve matters that the humans on Earth couldn’t.

The assault of the Titan Cattle tribe cavalry could be called, if Zhao Hai were to put it to words, beautiful. A brutal beauty, the beauty of power, the beauty of slaughter.

With the assault of the three hundred earth-traversing cattle cavalry, the fight had basically finished. While the charge didn’t exterminate the Jackal tribe completely, they did take down four hundred of them. The remaining Jackal tribe members were killed by the undead Zhao Hai had summoned.

After their assault, the three hundred earth-traversing cattle cavalry returned to camp, eyeing the corpses of those Jackal tribe members outside

It wasn’t that they hadn’t seen corpses before, just that these warriors protecting Wales hadn’t been in many battles. They sighed as they wouldn’t have expected that the two thousand large Jackal tribe cavalry would be unexpectedly destroyed just like that.

At this moment, a large amount of black smog enveloped the battlefield. When the black smog dispersed, the battlefield was cleaned up. The only thing that remained were the trampled grass of the earlier fight. No one would be able to believe that there had just been a battlefield here.

At this time, Zhao Hai’s caravan slowly moved toward the camp. Once their carriage was twenty meters, Zhao Hai and Laura walked out and slowly approached Wales. The earth-traversing cattle wanted to block their paths, but Wales shouted for them to stand down.

Zhao Hai led Laura and the other two women until they were two meters from Wales. They then made their greetings with straight chest towards Wales. “Brother Wales, hello. Zhao Hai offers the most sincere blessing to you.”

Wales also straightened his chest and grasped Zhao Hai, laughing as he said, “Brother Zhao Hai, you are truly a great magician. You easily and unexpectedly defeated the Jackal tribe with your magic. Starting today, you are a close friend of this Wales.”

Zhao Hai wasn’t able to adapt easily to Wales’ enthusiasm. After he broke free of Wales’ hug with great difficulty, he panted for air as he said, “Brother Wales, you shouldn’t hug me like that. I almost died by your hands.”

When Zhao Hai said those words, the beastfolk around them began to laugh. They started to like Zhao Hai because he spoke sincerely, not like those other hypocritical humans.

Laura and the other two also smiled. They were currently facing the beastfolk. When compared to humans where they needed to act reserved, it was more comfortable around the beastfolk. This wasn’t something they’d have imagined happening.

* * *

Footnotes:

[1]Please read the Announcement Post

[2] 威尔斯 - Wēi ěr sī.

[3]土行牛 - Tǔ xíng niú.

[4]One tael(两) is about 50 grams…

[5]Since one jin equals half a kilogram, it’ll be 50 grams (tael) to 500 grams (jin). So a 1 to 10 conversion. Hey, the raws actually matched these measurements!

[6]Common farming implement in old China… methinks. In Europe it would be pitchforks? Dunno why I’m commenting.

[7]Take everything this paragraph said with a grain of salt. I have no idea and just made it so that it sounds legit.

[8]No idea if this is true in the least. No idea if the paragraph is correct. And lastly, no idea why author went into a history lesson.

Chapter 242: ‘As Many As You Want’

Wales led the way for Zhao Hai into the tent. Compared to Spiel’s tent, Wales’ tent was more gorgeous. There was a well made goat rug spread open inside the tent, and top of it were tables and chairs. This was uncommon in Beastmen Prairie. Most of the furniture inside the tent were made of silver. This showed the extraordinary nature of the owner’s status.

But what surprised Zhao Hai was that there wasn’t a single female or child in the whole camp. In the several hundreds of people who were warriors, there was no one else other than Wales and the prophet.

When they sat down inside the tent, a Herculean Bull Tribe warrior brought them milk tea immediately. Wales raised the cup of milk tea and said, “Brother Zhao Hai, I wish to thank you for your help. Otherwise, those mongrels would’ve been really hard to deal with. Ah, I forgot to introduce you to him. This is my teacher, Prophet Yale.”

Zhao Hai stood up and bowed down to Yale. ‘One must maintain respect towards the prophets of beastmen’. This was a sentence that all humans who arrived on the prairie had to keep in mind.

After bowing down to Yale, Zhao Hai said, “Greetings, respected prophet. This is my fiancee Laura, and this is also my fiancee, Meg. This one is Nier.” Zhao Hai introduced them to Wales and Yale. It was also his first time introducing that Meg was his fiancee in public.

Laura was the one who let Zhao Hai do it. She thought that it would be fair to Meg.

When Meg heard Zhao Hai introducing her, she blushed uncontrollably, yet she was happy in her heart that her status was finally confirmed. This also made the remaining bit of worry in her heart vanish completely.

Regarding Zhao Hai’s introduction, Wales didn’t feel much of a surprise as not only human males could marry many wives. It was the same over in the beastmen tribes. In fact, this kind of situation over here was worse than humans. It was said that a Horse Tribe chief had more than 30 wives on his own. He was nicknamed ‘Seeding Horse’.

Wales bowed down to Laura and Meg courteously and then they sat down again. He drank a cup of milk tea and looked at Zhao Hai, “How did you even get the battle flag of the Big Belly Pigs Tribe, brother Zhao Hai?”

Zhao Hai smiled, “We just knew each other in some time before. I helped their Goat Head Hammer Tribe on a favor, and the tribe chief, brother Spiel, gave me that friendship flag.”

Wales didn’t say that the flag was a friendship flag because he wanted to see if Zhao Hai knew the meaning of the flag. Now that Zhao Hai said it, Wales understood that Zhao Hai knew what the flag was symbolizing.

Wales nodded and said, “Seems like you helped him in a great way, or else he wouldn’t have given you the friendship flag, hehe. I see that you’re a merchant, brother Zhao Hai? Is your wagon full of grains?”

Zhao Hai nodded, “Yes, brother Wales. Actually, I cannot count as a legitimate merchant. I have a fief and it produces grains. Right now, I have a large quantity them that I want out of my hands. Bamboo rice most of all.”

Wales’ eyes sparkled when he heard what Zhao Hai said, “My brother, what’s the price of your grains?”

Zhao Hai smiled slightly and said, “2000 kilos for 1 argali.”

Wales did a double take and then spoke with shining eyes, “My brother, did you just said 2000 kilos of grains in exchange for 1 argali goat? Are you sure you didn’t say it wrong?”

Zhao Hai smiled slightly, “Actually, it’s just a public price. If it’s for friends, this price can be lowered. And I’m not lying to you, I have a senior who likes to research magic beasts a lot, so if they’re prairie specialties, especially magic beasts, I can buy them with a great price. Of course, if you need grains, I can also exchange using grains. And I have the freshest vegetables on hand. They are as fresh as they’ve just been plucked. Meg, go get some fresh vegetables for brother Wales as a meeting gift.” Meg heeded with a sound and walked out of the tent.

Wales and Yale both listened to Zhao Hai’s words idly. They never thought that Zhao Hai would bring such terms. It was truly out of their expectations.

Wales looked at Zhao Hai and said, “My brother, how much can you provide? I mean, how many of the grains do you have in your hands?”

Zhao Hai looked at Wales, “I have as many as you want.”

The words were so boastful they bordered on insanity. Yale and Wales felt that Zhao Hai’s words were too conceited. One should know that Wales still had his position. If Wales really wanted to do business with Zhao Hai, the amount of crops required would be an astronomical sum.

Wales stared at Zhao Hai, “My brother, I think I forgot to introduce you to my identity just now. I’m Herculean Bull Tribe’s 7th son of the chieftain. If I really want to do business with you then the grains I need will be extremely numerous.”

Zhao Hai smiled a little, “I don’t mind, my brother. I know your identity isn’t common. You have a prophet teacher and you wear gorgeous robes, so your identity is surely uncommon. But please relax as I just said it. I have as many as you want. This isn’t a bluff. You can calculate the amount that your entire Herculean Bull Tribe needs, and then we’ll talk.”

Wales looked at Zhao Hai with incomprehension. He didn’t understand where Zhao Hai’s confidence came from. One should know that grains had always been the trading goods that were exported to the beastmen in the largest quantity of all trading goods. Likewise, it was also the most powerful weapon used by humans to strangle them. It was exactly because of this that the prices of grains in the beastmen parts were high on end.

Even though there were many grains transported to the Beastmen Prairie by humans, compared to the massive population of beastmen, they were far from enough. Every year there were many beastmen who had to eat their goats sparingly in order to survive the famine.

Long periods of goat eating wasn’t something good for beastmen. If they ate up the goats, they would lose more compared to trading them for grains, but when they couldn’t resort to anything else when they lacked grains.

It wasn’t as if humans didn’t bring grains to the Beastmen Prairie on purpose. In the eyes of human merchants, bringing grains to Beastmen Prairie meant getting argali back in exchange. That’s money. Why let go of such a business on purpose? But the problem lied in the fact that humans didn’t have that many grains.

Now all the large countries on the continent were adopting a ‘turn a blind eye’ attitude towards the matter of selling grains to the Beastmen Prairie. You could sell, but not too much. You couldn’t sell them to the point of affecting the grain prices of the continent. Otherwise, the royals would not let it slide.

It was because of these various reasons that there was always a large gaping hole in the Beastmen Prairie’s grain supply. Even if they were willing to trade their argali, it couldn’t be helped. There were no grains.

Wales didn’t readily believe in Zhao Hai’s words. Even if Zhao Hai had a fief, the bamboo rice production could not possibly plug the gaping hole of the Beastmen Prairie’s grain supply. How could Zhao Hai’s be so boastful?

Compared to Wales, Yale felt even stranger about this. Zhao Hai seemed to be too confident. This made Yale think of something bad all of a sudden.

There were human merchants who said such things before in front of beastmen in the past. In the end, it was proven that the merchants were all liars. They could never have that many grains, so it was them who brought some mouldy grains to deal with the beastmen. If it were mouldy rice, then it would’ve been manageable. At least the rice would be barely edible after some washing. But if there weren’t a lot of grains and the tribe were depending on the grains to get through winter, then the outcome would be very dire.

Yale remembered clearly that 5 years ago, there was a great battle tribe that had its members starved to death in grain panic because of such a liar. That tribe ate large amounts of argali and incurred heavy losses. Even now the tribe had yet to recover.

Yale was afraid that Zhao Hai was such a person as well. If Zhao Hai wanted to use this method to deal with Herculean Bull Tribe, then his appearance would not be a coincidence.

Once Yale thought to this point, he stared deeply at Zhao Hai. Before Wales said anything, Yale coughed a little and then spoke to Wales, “Wales, it was thanks to Zhao Hai’s assistance today that we could win against the mongrels. Should we serve them properly? They must also set up their camping grounds as well.”

Once Wales heard what Yale said, he knew Yale wanted to talk alone. He didn’t discuss with Zhao Hai about the grain issue any further. He just nodded and said, “Right, will you look at me, only knowing how to talk about such things. Brother Zhao Hai, you go and set up camp first, and then we’ll have a couple cups of drinks for sure.”

Zhao Hai could see them through, so he didn’t say anything and just smiled. He stood up and spoke, “Alright, brother Wales. I will go and set up camp, and then I’ll bring the vegetables over.” After speaking, Zhao Hai let Laura and Nier bow down to Wales and Yale before they all left the tent.

Just then, Meg was leading some undead creatures to bring some basketfuls of vegetables to outside the tent. These vegetables were just put into the wagon by Zhao Hai. After all, they couldn’t be put outside for too long. Otherwise, they wouldn’t be fresh anymore.

Zhao Hai didn’t let Meg enter the tent again, and just let her bring the vegetables to the guards outside the tent. He led Meg back to the team of wagons.

The camping grounds building today was very convenient. The wagons had already formed a circle formation. Just set up a tent within the formation, and presto.

When they went back to camping grounds, the tent had been constructed. Zhao Hai and others went back into the tent. It was a very simple tent; the ground ground was adorned in rabbit fur and there weren’t too many decorations so it appeared to be spacious.

When they sat down inside the tent, Laura laughed at Zhao Hai, “Hai-bro, you’re too impatient. I think Wales and Yale must’ve treated you like a liar.”

Zhao Hai laughed, “What? Do beastmen come across such liars often?”

Laura replied seriously, “It depends on whether or not the tribe is worth cheating. If a beastmen tribe’s strength is too powerful, it’s very likely that there will be this kind of liar.”

Chapter 243: Sneaky Move

When Zhao Hai heard what Laura said, he felt that there were words within her words. He looked at Laura in confusion and asked, “What do you mean?”

Laura glanced at Zhao Hai and then snickered, “It means, those liars were not real merchants. They had background. Solid background.”

Zhao Hai looked agape and asked, “You mean someone made the liars act this way? Who? For what?”

Laura let out a bitter smile and replied, “Who else could it be? The ones who are afraid of beastmen getting powerful. Among them are Fansile family, as well as Axu Empire’s royal members. There are many merchants on Beastmen Prairie right now, and they are their spotters. If they find out which tribe is very powerful, they will both think of a way to weaken that tribe. In order to weaken a tribe, there’s no move more vicious than cheating. This move doesn’t need manpower and too much wealth. Even less so for fighting, and it can let them fulfill their goal. That’s why a lot of people use this move.”

Zhao Hai seriously never thought that it was because of this. He did a double take and said, “No wonder Yale just interrupted Wales. It seems like Yale treated us as those sort of liars as well. Blame me, for I just spoke too surely.”

Laura laughed, “We can’t blame you as well. What you said was the truth. It’s just Yale doesn’t believe you. Once we make more contact, they will believe it. That’s right, Hai-bro. Do you feel that Wales’ camp is a little strange?”

Zhao Hai nodded, “It’s a little strange, yes. This camp is full of combatants, and not a single woman. This is a little inexplicable.”

Laura nodded, “I can tell as well, but from the look of Wales, it’s not like he had anything important to do, so why would he come all the way here?”

Meg, who had never spoken just now, said, “Can be it be that Wales is here for a trial? Wales is the 7th son of the Herculean Bull Tribe’s chieftain, which is basically a prince. Human nobles usually let their own children go out to brush up, and Wales’ identity is also a noble one, so he might be here for a trial of combat, right?”

Laura and Zhao Hai both did a double take, and then Laura laughed softly, “It seems like we’ve thought things to be more complicated than they really are. Yes, I also heard that the great tribes’ princes would also come out for trials. It seems like Wales is part of it as well, but the matter of him being surrounded by jackals is also full of fishiness.”

Zhao Hai nodded, “This matter is somewhat odd, but it’s not what we need to concern ourselves with. We’ve arrived at our destination and we dealt with the Jackal Tribe, right? I even stored the Jackal Tribe’s people, but none of them alive, unfortunately. Still, there are two mounts which are alive. They’re now in storage.”

After the battle, Zhao Hai put the jackal tribesmen corpses into the space. In order to avoid Yale’s suspicions, Zhao Hai personally used the black mist spell to cloud the battleground, and then collected the corpses. He didn’t turn the jackal tribesmen into undead creatures in a hurry. He still wanted to get some information from their mouths.

But he also couldn’t let Wales and Yale know that, so he used the black mist spell to cloud the battleground. By the time it dissipated, the jackal tribesmen’s corpses had disappeared. This would make Yale and others think that Zhao Hai had turned the corpses into undead creatures which he put into his summoning space.

This was also the common method used by black mages on the continent. Usually after they killed their enemies, they would turn their enemies into undead creatures and then put them into their own summoning space. Not only would this deter enemies, it would also add to their own strength. That was why Zhao Hai did it earlier. Both Yale and Wales weren’t the slightest bit suspicious.

Laura nodded and said, “Let’s wait until it’s night to sort out those jackal tribesmen. We don’t know when Wales will come look for us, so let’s not enter the space.” Zhao Hai nodded as well. He didn’t intend to enter the space at this time.

Zhao Hai and others didn’t know that Wales and Yale were talking about them at the moment.

When they saw Zhao Hai and others leave the tent, Wales spoke to Yale in confusion, “Teacher, why didn’t you let me and Zhao Hai continue on? If he has a lot of grains and they’re very cheap, then it’s great news for our Herculean Bull Tribe.”

Yale glanced at Wales and shook his head, “I feel that Zhao Hai wasn’t being truthful. Does he really have grains in his hands? Do not forget Black Bear Tribe’s lesson 5 years ago.”

The Black Bear Tribe lesson 5 years ago which Yale meant was that scamming incident, when a human merchant who had cooperated with Black Bear Tribe many times in the past promised to prepare the grains meant for lasting through winter. Because the Black Bear Tribe worked happily with the other party, they wouldn’t expect that the other party would cheat them. As a result, the black bear tribesmen never bought any grains from other human merchants to pass the winter.

Yet that human merchant had disappeared in the end, and never appeared on the prairie. By the time the Black Bear Tribe fell for it, it was already too late. They didn’t stockpile grains for that winter, and the snowing was fierce. It was hard to mobilize the forces, and the entire Black Bear Tribe faced the danger of food depletion.

Eventually, they had no choice but to eat argali and other magic beasts in order to overcome the danger. Even so, many of the Black Bear Tribe’s slaves had starved to death. The once powerful Black Bear Tribe had weakened. If it weren’t for their powerful fighting abilities, they would’ve already been terminated.

Afterwards, this matter had caused a huge backlash on the Beastmen Prairie. There was even a period of time when all the races on the prairie didn’t do business with human merchants. Many of the merchants had unrecoupable losses because of this.

When Wales heard what Yale said, he was startled and said, “It can’t be. I don’t think Zhao Hai is that sort of person, and he’s holding a friendship flag. Aren’t you worrying too much?”

Yale shook his head, “It’s always better to be a little more cautious. We must always remember the Black Bear Tribe’s lesson. Regardless of whether or not Zhao Hai has the grains, we cannot put all the fortunes on him.”

Wales didn’t object regarding this point. Putting all of one’s fortunes on someone else is too risky. He wouldn’t do it, so he didn’t object to what Yale said.

Yale looked at Wales as he said, “Don’t you think it’s very strange that we were under attack today, Wales? When did those mongrels get so gutsy and they dared to attack us?”

Wales was startled, “Then teacher, what you mean is?”

Yale replied, “There’s something fishy about this. Even though the mongrels will rob anyone, when they do, their teams have elderly and women, and usually act in a whole group. But the ones who attacked us today were all strong and of age. No elderlies and women. Have you heard of any jackal tribes that mobilized 2000 strong adults to conduct robbery before? Furthermore, we’re just here to roam so we didn’t bring a lot of valuables, and just 300 warrior guards. We’re more powerful than the smaller tribes with this kind of strength by many measures, yet the mongrels still came for us. This isn’t like their usual style of action, so I’m saying that this matter is very strange.”

Wales’ facial expression kept changing as he heard Yale’s words. He wasn’t a fool. He knew what Yale’s words meant.

Although Wales was the chieftain’s 7th son, he was his father’s most favorite son, and he was smart since he was little. This might not mean much to humans, but in beastmen tribes, it was an incredibly positive trait.

Beastmen had direct personalities. Normally when there were beastmen that weren’t too clever, they appeared to be silly in others’ eyes and easily deceived, so the beastmen placed great importance on smart children and assign a prophet teacher to them since little for education. This kind of children were often the ones to become the next chieftains.

Since little, Wales proved to be very smart, so his father assigned Yale to him when he was 5 years old. This was almost like a hint to everyone that he was ready raise Wales as a successor.

If Wales’ other brothers had ordinary strength, then it wouldn’t be much. The Herculean Bull Tribe would complete the succession smoothly. But the problem was that his brothers were powerful as well. It would be problematic.

Wales’ eldest brother Gasol stayed at his father’s side since little and always fought for Herculean Bull Tribe. In the beastmen circles, he had a glorious nickname of ‘bull-headed war god’. His strength was enough to match against a human level 8 expert. Among beastmen who admired strength, Gasol’s fame was quite large. His prestige was very great within Herculean Bull Tribe as well.

Even though Gasol wasn’t as smart as Wales, he helped their father manage the tribe’s matters all these years, so his performance could be said to be commendable. That was why many people were supporting him in Herculean Bull Tribe and wanted him to be the next chieftain.

Wales’ second brother Paul wasn’t too worth the attention. Because Paul had always been a very short tempered person, even though he was powerful and eager to battle, he was obviously not chieftain material. But Paul had a very good relationship with Gasol, and he always supported Gasol in becoming a chieftain.

Wales’ 3rd and 4th brothers were killed in action during their teenage years. The ones who could remember their names in the tribe were few.

Wales’ 5th brother Hales had a sickly body since little. He would get sick in half of every year, so he was a forgotten existence in the tribe who didn’t pose any threat.

Wales’ 6th brother Mendez had a very good relationship with Wales. He took great care of Wales since little, but his current age wasn’t very high so he couldn’t be of much help.

Wales had 2 more younger brothers, but their age was still little. They didn’t even have the right to engage in trials, not to mention helping out.

Wales had another 4 older sisters, but they were married to another bull headed race that wasn’t weak: Fighting Bull Tribe. Wales had a good relationship with his 2nd and 3rd sisters, while the eldest and 4th sisters were in good relationships with Gasol.

To really count it up, Gasol had larger odds than Wales in becoming the chieftain of Herculean Bull Tribe.

Chapter 244: Re-evaluation

Wales learned from Yale since he was little, while after becoming Wales’ teacher, Yale became deeply imprinted. Yale felt that he must help Wales become the chieftain, so he educated very attentively.

Other than being Wales’ teacher, the reason why Yale taught Wales with dedication was because of the Buffalo Tribe. Even though Buffalo Tribe had a very high standing among bull headed races due to many of their famous prophets, if Wales failed in this fight for succession, he would surely be oppressed by Gasol, and then Yale’s days would not be any better. The Buffalo Tribe which Yale hailed from would surely suffer.

It was exactly because of this that Yale must help Wales succeed the position. Only then would he be able to guarantee Buffalo Tribe’s benefits.

Buffalo Tribe was the smartest of all the bull headed races. With Yale being of high age, he had seen a lot of such family fights for succession, so he spoke of such things to Wales since little. With Wales being this smart, as soon as Yale spoke about the strangeness of being attacked, Wales immediately knew what Yale meant.

Yales said nothing while he saw that Wales went speechless. He knew Wales never wanted to resort to full open hostility with Gasol. Even though Wales was young, his education made him understand that no matter who won between them, the greatest losers would be Herculean Bull Tribe, so he never wanted to fight against Gasol.

Yet it was because of Wales being too smart since little, that Gasol always treated him like an opponent and made things hard for him. For the sake of his own safety as well as Yale and those around him, Wales had no choice but to strike back. With this, the fighting between him and Gasol had started with none the wiser.

Gasol had long years of prestige and social connections, so he had an upper hand in the succession, but Wales had a stroke of genius since little, and with his father’s support, he wasn’t in the lower hand as well.

The fighting between the two had always in behind the scenes instead of out in the open, and their fighting was within the lines, and never too far. Things like threatening the life of one another were something they never did. The matter this time was somewhat strange.

Once Wales thought this, he frowned and spoke, “I feel that there’s something weird about today’s matter. You’re saying, teacher, that this was possibly caused by Gasol, but would he want my life at this point? He wouldn’t, right? Father is still alive and well. If tries to make a move against me, father won’t let him go, and that way, he’ll have no hope of becoming the chieftain. Even though 2nd brother isn’t suitable and neither is 5th brother, but 6th brother’s performance in these years is passable. Little 8th and 9th have yet to grow up, and it’s not like there’ll be no one to become the chieftain without the two of us. He won’t have any benefit in removing me at this time, will he?”

Yale also felt very confused after hearing what Wales said. He frowned and said, “If he (Gasol) is really behind this, then unless he can immediately become the chieftain after removing you, the chieftain will not let them go unpunished. But now that the chieftain’s still alive, it’s impossible for him (Gasol) to be the chieftain. He wouldn’t dare make a move against the chieftain, since the high elders will never agree to that. From the look of this, this whole thing is really not his handiwork. Can it be that other people want to deal with us?”

Wales was also frowning. The fishy parts of this matter were too many, so he couldn’t comprehend it all at the time. Suddenly, Wales thought of something and he asked, “Teacher, do you think that this matter is related to Zhao Hai?”

Yale thought for a bit and he shook his head, “No. Zhao Hai is a human. Humans cannot possibly command the Jackal Tribe. You saw it too that the jackals had indeed perished. If Zhao Hai were in cahoots with them, he wouldn’t have dealt such a lethal blow.”

Wales nodded, “Then who can it be? We’ve never heard of which race would make contact with Jackal Tribe. Their name is too foul on the prairie. If it’s discovered that someone is making contact with them, then that someone will also have a foul reputation. There is no one who would be so daring, is there?”

Yale nodded to the statement. The Jackal Tribe’s attack this time was too eerie. On the prairie, the Jackal Tribe was always known for taking advantages instead of shortcomings. They wouldn’t touch anything they found to be dicey. Yet this time they sent 2000 of their stronger ones to kill them (Wales and others), which made Yale and Wales reach no conclusions in their minds.

After the 2 of them discussed for a while, which proved to be inconclusive in the end, Wales shifted the topic to Zhao Hai. Wales looked at Yale and asked, “Teacher, if Zhao Hai really has a lot of grains in his hands that can be sold to us at that price, should we go for it immediately?”

Yale thought for a bit and nodded, “We should, but it’s best that this matter doesn’t involve the tribe. Right now, Gasol has a greater power in the tribe, so I think we should let Buffalo Tribe and Fighting Bull Tribe make contact with Zhao Hai first. If Zhao Hai really has a lot of grains, then Buffalo Tribe and Fighting Bull Tribe’s grain problems will be solved. And because you are spearheading this matter, they will have gratitude towards you, and it will become a power in your hands. If Zhao Hai is a liar, then the only ones in loss will be Buffalo Tribe and Fighting Bull Tribe as well, and then you can solve the problem in their stead, and they won’t blame you. What do you think?”

Yale’s idea wasn’t bad. Because the Herculean Bull Tribe had Gasol, there would always be someone getting in Wales’ way, so Yale let Wales make the Buffalo and Fighting Bull tribes handle the matter.

Fighting Bull Tribe was also a branch of bull headed races with powerful fighting strength. With frequent contact between them and Herculean Bull Tribe, Wales’ 4 older sisters consequently married into the Fighting Bull Tribe in order to forge ties. For Wales, the benefit was large. If he got the Fighting Bull Tribe’s support, he would have great hope in becoming the chieftain of Herculean Bull Tribe.

Buffalo Tribe had a special place among bull headed races. Their fighting power wasn’t bad, and with the reputation of being the smartest of all bull headed races, the Buffalo Tribe had a certain influence. If Wales got Buffalo Tribe’s support, then it would achieve a certain effect in his succession of the chieftain position.

On Beastmen Prairie, when any ruling tribe of a great race wanted to select its own chieftain, it wasn’t a matter of that tribe alone. It was a matter of all the branch tribes. The words of these branch tribes would sometimes influence the positioning of the chieftain.

For example, the Herculean Bull Tribe, which was the ruling tribe of all bull headed races. If they wanted to pick their own chieftain, then it wouldn’t be something that they alone could decide. They also needed the opinions of all the other bull headed branch tribes.

The reason why this sort of situation was present was due to the fact that, a ruling tribe of a great race couldn’t order the branch tribes around during normal occasions, but when fighting great wars, the ruling tribe could hold the great responsibility of commanding all of the branch tribes of the whole race.

To make an example, if the beastmen waged war against humans, the beastmen would naturally address the battle tribes as lords. They would normally pick a marshall to command all the beastmen. All the chieftains of the various great races would be the various generals, each in charge of their own race. All of the branch tribes would be the officers under the generals, who must listen to the chieftain during this time. That was why the position of chieftain of the ruling tribe was extremely important.

Right now inside the Herculean Bull Tribe, Gasol’s fighting power was something deeply rooted in the minds. If Wales and Gasol kept fighting inside the tribe, then Wales would be the one to lose. Which was why Yale already planned to let Wales make more contact with other bull headed branch tribes. Zhao Hai’s appearance happened to give them a good opportunity.

Grains was something all of the beastmen lacked. For beastmen, there was no such thing as too many grains, so Wales using grains to forge ties with Fighting Bull and Buffalo Tribes would be a right move.

After thinking about this, Wales nodded, “I think I can do it. My sisters are in the Fighting Bull Tribe, so connections won’t be a problem. And you are part of the Buffalo Tribe, teacher, so there should also be no problems there. When we get out, I’ll discuss this with Zhao Hai.”

Yale nodded. He looked at the sky and said, “The outside should be ready by now, so let’s get out after a moment. Oh right, Zhao Hai let his people send some vegetables. Let’s go have a look.”

Wales nodded to that. For the beastmen on the prairie, fresh vegetables were definitely luxurious goods. Even the ruling tribe like Herculean Bull Tribe could not simply eat them. Wales assumed that what Zhao Hai gave them wouldn’t be more than things like magic radishes which could be easily stored, and thus paid them no mind.

Wales followed Yale out of the tent. It was now afternoon and the weather was fine. The 2 of them were dumbstruck the moment they came out of the tent, because they saw that more than a dozen of baskets were placed outside the tent. Each basket had a type of vegetable. The vegetables were rather common on the continent so Wales and Yale knew what they were. They wouldn’t be surprising. What surprised them was the fact that all of these vegetables were actually fresh. So fresh, it was like they were just plucked.

The 2 of them looked at each other and saw trembling in each other’s eyes. The reason why they came here was just as Meg guessed; They were here for a trial. This was something all the young higher ups of all beastmen had to experience. Wales was not an exception.

Going outside to roam wasn’t something others cared about, but there was a rule, which was one couldn’t bring more than 500 escorts. This was ordained in all of the beastmen tribes.

The reason why escorts were brought out during roaming was related to the situation on the prairie; Beastmen Prairie was simply too large and there were too many dangers. It would be very hard to survive on the prairie alone. In order ensure the safety of the young generation, they were allowed to bring escorts.

Young beastmen who came out to roam were often ones with prince-like identities. Those whose status was insufficient would usually have to get busy with their own tribes everyday with no time to spare. They started fighting battles with adults in the tribes since little. There was no need to take part in trials at all.

In other words, the ‘trial’ was actually something that allowed the next generation of the powerful people in the tribes to go out and see the world in order to shave off their noble attitudes.

Wales came to this place mainly to look at the human city in Iron Wall Fortress. Wales was still young and he didn’t participate in the previous war between humans and beastmen. Although there was Beast God City, there wasn’t a real stone-clad city, so Wales was always curious about the stone-clad cities of humans. He wanted to use the chance in his trial to look at a human city.

Although Wales had never been to Iron Wall Fortress before, he still knew about the travel path. He knew well that from their current location, it would take several days of travel to get to Iron Wall Fortress, and that place couldn’t possibly produce these vegetables. In other words, Zhao Hai’s vegetables came from even further away.

It meant that these vegetables had made their way here for more than a few days at least. The fact that the vegetables could retain their freshness in these few days like they were just plucked was too surprising.

Yale looked at Wales but he said nothing. He turned to go back into the tent, and once inside, he spoke to Wales, “Wales, I think we will have to re-evaluate Zhao Hai’s strength.”

Wales nodded and then looked at Yale with incomprehension, “Why are those vegetables fresh, teacher? How did they keep them so fresh?”

Yale smiled slightly, “I’m guessing that he has a spatial equipment in his hands. Spatial equipments are things researched by human mages. This type of thing seals a subspace which can be used to store objects. Things stored inside the subspace can last much longer than outside. He probably has such a thing in his hands. I just never imagined that he actually used a spatial equipment to put vegetables.”

Wales too had heard of the scarcity of spatial equipments, but there were no such things in beastmen’s possession, so everything about them was simply told to him. He didn’t understand them enough.

But he thought that spatial equipments should be very precious as well. Otherwise, with so many of the human merchants travelling to the prairie, they wouldn’t have used wagons by now. Wouldn’t they rather use spatial equipments?

Wales’ eyes sparkled and spoke, “Teacher, doesn’t that mean Zhao Hai has a method that allows him to transport the grains from the human lands in a faster way? If that’s the case, I think it’s very likely that he has as many grains as he claimed.”

Yale nodded, “His strength seems impressive, but it’s still prudent for us to be careful. Although we’re not the most powerful tribe of all the beastmen races, our strength is up there. Even compared to battle tribes, us bull headed race can manage to stay in the competition. If it weren’t for some of the branch tribes dragging out feet, we would’ve already become a battle race. This strength would indeed make many people jealous. We can’t be certain we won’t be eyed by the human liars.”

Chapter 245: Liar With A Complicated Identity

Wales knew about this point as well. Beastmen had been deceived by humans for too many times. So many, it was no longer something they could count on their own. That was why they harbored intense caution towards humans, and also why very few human merchants could get friendship flags.

Beastmen would never give friendship flags to people they wouldn’t trust, since they believed that it would be the greatest desecration to the flags themselves. In fact, other than Zhao Hai, there were no other human merchants who had ever gotten a friendship flag from the beastmen for so many years. Not even ones from smaller tribes like the Goat Head Hammer Tribe.

It could be said that the friendship flag on Zhao Hai’s wagon left Wales with a great impression towards Zhao Hai. It was also because of the flag that Wales wanted to cooperate with him.

Wales exhaled and said, “I seriously hope that Zhao Hai is a good merchant. If he has a large amount of grains and is willing to sell them to us, then I will gladly give him our friendship flag.”

Yale knew what Wales meant. What the beastmen lacked was grains. If he could really solve Herculean Bull Tribe’s grain issues through Zhao Hai, then he would get closer to the chieftain position.

Yale also hoped that it would be so, but he was also on high alert regarding Zhao Hai. With a long time in a large tribe and fighting against Gasol in secret for a period of time, Yale’s heart was still very dark.

A moment of silence in the tent took hold before Yale spoke, “Let’s go out and take a look. I am more and more curious about Zhao Hai right now. If he’s really a liar, then he must have a complicated identity. A liar with a spatial equipment? Hehe. I think he isn’t be an ordinary person, is he?”

Wales also started to laugh. Indeed, if a liar had a spatial equipment, then he must had been an incredible liar.

After looking at the time, Wales laughed, “Let’s go out, teacher. I promised Zhao Hai to give him a good toast.”

Yale chuckled as both of them walked out of the tent. Bonfires were made outside the tent and argali had been put to roast.

The beastmen were like this. To them, serving you a roasted goat would be the greatest treatment. Although Wales was out for a trial, no matter where beastmen were, they would bring a herd of goats with them. Roaming while grazing the goats was the beastmen’s life.

Actually, the argali were also their food, which was why they would bring them anywhere. The tribe wasn’t going to be able to keep the goats. Even if they could defeat the Jackal Tribe’s assault, the goats would’ve been robbed away.

But they were lucky today. They came across Zhao Hai who exterminated the Jackal Tribe’s people with no escapees, so these goats had been kept. Wales would naturally not be stingy over a few of them.

Although the ones who followed Wales were warriors, they were among the highest elite. They often served as escorts for the ranked personnel of Herculean Bull Tribe. The things they knew wouldn’t be less than normal beastmen, and what they could do were better than others. It was because when you are next to the higher ups, you must learn how to serve them.

The goats had been roasted above the bonfires. What was special about the occasion was that some tables had been placed next to the bonfires, which wasn’t a common sight. Next to every table were milk wines, and on each of the tables were 2 plates and a wine cup. The notable thing was that no matter the plates, the wine cup, or the wine pots, all of them were made of silver.

All of this displayed the extraordinary nature of the owner’s status. A common small sized tribe would never have such things. Beastmen were nomadic. If they put these things in their wagons, they would’ve needed several more wagons, which would greatly inconvenience them when moving about.

But some great races, in order to display their identities, would ready such things. Wales was a powerful contender for the chieftain of Herculean Bull Tribe, so it was a given that his identity was extraordinary. Bringing these things was not something to be wondered.

After many years of development, many of the younger generation of the higher ups were still maintaining the tradition of taking the trial of roaming, but with the protection of escorts and some of the smaller tribes’ respect, the core of their trials had changed completely. Now it was not much different from travelling.

Once Wales saw that it was about to be ready, he looked at Yale and said, “Teacher, you wait here. I’ll go and invite Zhao Hai.”

Yale didn’t object to that. In their view, putting the question of whether or not Zhao Hai was a liar aside, Zhao Hai was a mage with supreme strength, which alone could let him gain respect accordingly. Wales inviting Zhao Hai on his own was enough to explain the respect he had towards Zhao Hai.

Wales walked towards Zhao Hai’s camp with 2 guards behind him. These 2 guards didn’t bring weapons, as to the beastmen, bringing weapons to meet one’s friend was a very impolite behaviour.

There was a distance between Zhao Hai’s camp and Wales’, but Wales didn’t ride his own mount. Instead, he walked to outside of Zhao Hai’s campsite.

Zhao Hai used his wagons to form a circle outside of his campsite because of the battle earlier. Inside the formation, undead creatures were standing there like statues.

At first Wales assumed that those undead creatures were ordinary wagon drivers, but when he walked to the front of them, he realized he was mistaken. Those weren’t people at all. No matter how excellent a fighter would be, there would be no way one could stand for such a long time without blinking. There was no breathing, even.

Wales wouldn’t feel uneasy when facing human fighters, but when facing the undead, Wales still felt insecure. After all, he had never seen humanoid undead for more than a few times.

Just when Wales was deciding whether to shout out to Zhao Hai or speak to the animated corpses, Zhao Hai had already walked out of his tent with Laura and others.

Zhao Hai already knew from the undead creatures that Wales had arrived, so of course he wouldn’t be too keeping of his appearance. The other party was a prince, after all. Keeping up the appearance too much would make it look like was trying too hard.

Once Zhao Hai was out, he laughed to Wales and said, “Brother Wales, have you been waiting for me with the goats roasted? Hahaha, I’m starving!”

Wales obviously liked how Zhao Hai was speaking like a beastman. He also laughed and said, “Brother Zhao Hai, the goats have been roasted and the milk wine has been poured, waiting for us to drink.”

Zhao Hai laughed his way with Wales as they walked into the latter’s camp. Once Zhao Hai saw the placements, he was stunned. He didn’t expect that Wales would be so prepared when going outside. If it weren’t for the numerous large wagons around, he would’ve thought that Wales had spatial equipment as well.

Yale was sitting at a table while waiting for Zhao Hai and others. Next to the bonfires were many small tables, and each table could only accommodate 1 person. Notably, the tables weren’t large and small rugs were put next to the tables. A person had to sit on a rug directly.

Once Yale saw that Zhao Hai and others had come, Yale stood up to greet them. Zhao Hai and others immediately bowed down to Yale. After all, the prophets’ status on Beastmen Prairie was too special. They couldn’t afford to have the slightest inadvertence.

There was a saying on Beastmen Prairie which went, ‘Offending a prophet means offending all of the beastmen’. Of course, it was only good for the humans. For beastmen, it wasn’t too effective. Yet even a chieftain of great tribe wouldn’t easily offend a prophet.

After the formalities, all of them sat down, and someone else brought Zhao Hai and others some roasted mutton. According to the beastmen’s usual acts, they must first eat a mouthful of mutton before drinking wine. This showed their importance towards food.

After eating a mouthful of roasted mutton, Wales raised his silver cup and extended it towards Zhao Hai. The two of them weren’t far apart, but with the distance between the tables, the two of them were about 2 metres apart.

Wales spoke with his cup raised, “Brother Zhao Hai, thank you for assisting me. Please have this toast representing my gratitude.”

Zhao Hai smiled and raised his cup as well, “You’re too kind, brother Wales. We are friends. There doesn’t need to be too much of a gratitude when friends help each other.”

Wales nodded to Zhao Hai in appreciated and shook the wine up saying, “Please!” Zhao Hai also did the same, and both of them drank the wine from their cups in a single shot.

After a cup of wine, Wales started talking with Zhao Hai about casual topics. The two of them talked as they were eating the mutton and drinking milk wine. But Zhao Hai felt that he wasn’t eating very happily today compared to at Spiel’s. It wasn’t because of the good, but the atmosphere. They could eat and drink happily Spiel’s because there wasn’t any scheming, but in here, Zhao Hai felt that Wales and Yale were observing him. This made him feel very uncomfortable.

By the time the 3rd cup of wine was drunk, Wales asked Zhao Hai, “Brother Zhao Hai, do you really have a lot of grains to sell?”

Zhao Hai nodded, “Yes. Plenty. I want to exchange for some special magic beasts, even argali. Of course, some goat hair products are fine as well.”

Wales replied to Zhao Hai, “Brother Zhao Hai, it’s not that I don’t trust you, it’s just that to us beastmen, grains are too important. I really want to know how many grains you have, and then decide on how to cooperate with you. Also, I want to know about the quality of your grains.”

Zhao Hai laughed, “It’s nothing. I can tell you that right now, I have 100 million kilos of bamboo rice, and there will be even more in the future. As for the quality? Let’s see. You can let your escorts go and get some grains from my grain wagon. Any bag of them will do. You can take some extra and then bring them here. You can take a closer look after that.”

When Zhao Hai mentioned that he had 100 million kilos of grains, Wales breathed in a mouthful of cold air. This was the largest amount he had ever heard of. If he could really get the grains, then Herculean Bull Tribe wouldn’t need to worry about food problems for a very long time.

What sort of concept was 100 million kilos of grains? It was the amount enough for use by a large tribe of 10 million people for 3 days. Of course, this was because of the fact that beastmen could eat more than humans. If it were on humans, this figure would multiply for many times.

Chapter 246: ‘I Want The Battle Flag’

Wales heard Zhao Hai’s words idly. 100 million kilos of grains wasn’t enough for the entire bull headed race, but for just Herculean Bull Tribe alone, these grains could last for a very long time.

Yale had also idled at this time, but he immediately reacted. He called out a couple of warriors to bring the grains from Zhao Hai’s wagon. He wanted to see if the grains Zhao Hai brought were good or bad.

Beastmen prioritized food. It was exactly because of their importance towards food that they were extra demanding when it came to grain quality. Many beastmen were illiterate, but they wouldn’t need to look if a rice was good or bad. They could just use their hands to weigh them in order to tell the difference. They were simply that amazing.

Wales returned to his senses from Yale’s action. He looked at Zhao Hai and asked, “Brother Zhao Hai, you really have 100 million kilos?”

Zhao Hai shook his head, “More than that. To be precise, I can get 100 million kilos of grains every period of time. My fief is very large, so when I plant the bamboo rice in batches, I can harvest them once in a while, hehe.”

Wales was stunned again, and then his expression changed, “Brother Zhao Hai, I’m treating you as a sibling so don’t lie to me, ok? I don’t know how about planting but 100 million kilos would need a very large field, right? Can you really harvest 100 million kilos of grains in such a short time? How large is your fief?”

Zhao Hai had a sudden feeling of sadness when he looked at Wales. He knew that food was precious in beastmen territories, but it seemed like the merchants weren’t being truthful when talking to Wales.

The yield of bamboo rice was very high to begin with. Even outside of the space, the yield wouldn’t be much lower than in the space. As long as there were no vandalizing, the yield of bamboo rice wouldn’t be greatly affected. Bamboo rice on the continent could feed all of the races, including humans, elves, dwarves and even magic beasts.

If humans really wished to trade with beastmen, then the beastmen wouldn’t have to worry about food crisis and the prices of grains wouldn’t be absurdly high.

Yet beastmen didn’t know how to plant crops, so when the human merchants traded with beastmen, they would make crop planting out to be a very difficult thing, and lower the figure of grain yields by a lot. This created an illusion in the beastmen that grain planting was a very difficult and low yield practice. The human merchants no longer needed to lower the grain prices this way. It could be said that they were sucking the beastmen’s blood.

Zhao Hai put down the curved knife in his hand and turned to Wales, “Brother Wales, I told you I’m not a legitimate merchant. I produce my own grains, so I know very well about the grain yields. Do not be deceived by the sly merchants. Take bamboo rice for example. Just 10000 acres of land would yield 100 million kilos, and it matures once every 3 months. If the weather is fine and it could be planted in winter, 1 year 10000 acres, 3 harvests, no natural disasters or human destruction, then brother, I can get 100 million kilos of grains without a problem.”

Wales and Yale both stared blankly at Zhao Hai. To be honest, they really didn’t know about what Zhao Hai said. Beastmen didn’t know how to plant crops, just like how humans didn’t know how to graze herds. For humans, grazing was too hard. Why would the magic beasts get sick all the time? In relation to that, for beastmen, crop planting was too hard. Why would those crops always wilt? It was an unsolvable problem.

It was exactly because of this that the human merchants would speak of grains like they were treasures, and the beastmen believed it, because in the latter’s view, crop planting was truly a difficult matter.

But now Zhao Hai told them that in the human lands, grain production was very high. Wales and Yale couldn’t accept this statement completely at the moment.

The 2 of them looked blankly at Zhao Hai and hoped that what Zhao Hai said was false, because the figures Zhao Hai listed were too far apart from the figures listed by the human merchants.

Wales stammered after a moment, “Y-y-you’re telling the truth?”

Zhao Hai nodded, “Of course! Beastmen usually can’t look at the crop production areas. Once they’re there, they would know it’s real. It’s just most of the major production areas are planted with wheat instead of bamboo rice.”

Just then, the couple of guards that Yale sent out had returned. Each of them were carrying 4 sacks of rice between their arms and torsos. It should be noted that each sack had 100 kilos of rice. The fact that each of them could carry 400 kilos while running was enough to show that the strength of Herculean Bull Tribe members was as the legends said.

The guards put the 8 sacks in front of Wales. Wales and Yale stood up almost at the same time, and walked to the sacks. Both of them opened up a sack each.

Inside the sacks were bamboo rice. They were a little yellow, like someone coated them in a layer of oil, making it appear to have an oily sheen. It was the highest grade of bamboo rice.

Yale almost instinctively poured out a sack of rice and then the ground was full of rice pellets. Zhao Hai wasn’t mad, as he knew why Yale would do that. It must be due to some human merchants who had cheated them in the past, by putting good rice on top, but put mouldy ones at the bottom. That was why Yale did it.

Yale looked at the pellets on the ground and scooped them up softly. He sniffed them with his nose and then chewed them in his mouth. He stood up slowly and turned to Zhao Hai, “Mr. Zhao Hai, are all of your rice of this quality?”

Zhao Hai nodded, “All of them are as such. You can inspect them in any way you like.”

Wales didn’t say anything. He just walked to his table and poured himself a large cup of milk wine. After drinking it all down, he put down the cup and looked at Zhao Hai, “Brother Zhao Hai, I want to have a proper talk with you.”

Zhao Hai looked at Wales and knew that what Wales was about to say would be the key to matters. He nodded and replied, “You can, brother Wales. These 3 next to me are people who will absolutely not betray me. What about the ones around you?”

Wales looked at his escorts and replied, “They too can be completely trusted.”

‘Use people without suspicion, don’t use people when in suspicion’. Wales had demonstrated his ruler’s etiquette on an entry level. The reason why Wales was so sure that these people wouldn’t betray him was because their families were under his control. If these people betrayed him, they and their families would be finished.

Wales received a ruler’s education since little, so he understood very clearly that, as a higher up, just having a bright side isn’t enough. Your subordinates cannot all be proper gentlemen. You can use a gentleman’s methods against gentlemen. If you a gentleman’s methods against lesser people, you will lose greatly.

Wales’ escorts didn’t make a sound, but the eyes that were looking at Wales had changed. They were eyes of gratitude. One could say that a single sentence from Wales had grabbed the hearts of these 300 escorts.

Beastmen were very simple and their thoughts were not as complicated as humans’. To the ones they were truly grateful of, they would give their lives. They wouldn’t be swayed no matter how large of a benefit was placed before them. But if these beastmen knew that Wales had controlled their families in secret, they would fight against Wales despite the cost of their own and their families’ lives, without backing away. This was the beastmen; Direct, brave, and no sands in their eyes.

It was exactly because of this that Wales only controlled their families in the shadows and not daring to let them know. If these people really knew about it, then Wales would have no one left to use.

This is the contradicting part of a ruler. They know how to control their subordinates and get their hearts, but they always think that just having their subordinates’ hearts isn’t enough. They have to put a failsafe over their hearts.

Zhao Hai glanced at the eyes of the escorts and knew what Wales meant. He didn’t display anything and just smiled, “Then what are you waiting for, brother Wales? Speak.”

Wales looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Brother Zhao Hai, you should know that I’m the 7th prince of Herculean Bull Tribe. In fact, I’m even one of the candidates of being the chieftain. The top competitor is my eldest brother Gasol. He has the most accomplishments in the tribe and has the most following. My seniority isn’t enough, so I would like to cooperate with you.”

Zhao Hai listened to Wales’ words silently. To be honest, he felt that what Wales said was seriously cliched. It’s like the large kingdoms would always run into such things. Sibling conflicts seemed to be something all the families in high positions could not avoid.

Wales noticed how Zhao Hai went silent so he added, “If you really have that many grains, I want to cooperate with you, and use your grains to solve my tribe’s food problems. I can gain public opinion this way and maybe the position of chieftain in the tribe will be mine. If I become the chieftain, then you’ll be the Herculean Bull Tribe’s sole grain dealer.”

This temptation was huge. The sole grain dealer of a race, for any merchant, was an irresistible temptation.

How many grains does a single race need each year? No one really calculated it before, but what was certain was that it would be an astronomical sum, especially for beastmen. All of the beastmen could eat more than humans. With the same amount of population, they needed several times more food than humans. If a merchant became a race’s sole source of food, that merchant would become one of the greatest dealers on the continent almost immediately.

Unfortunately, Zhao Hai could not be regarded as a legitimate merchant, but he could still fulfill Spiel’s request. He looked at Wales and said, “I don’t care about whether or not I can become Herculean Bull Tribe’s sole grain dealer. I planted the grains myself. As long as I have the grains, I will not worry about selling them on Beastmen Prairie. I can cooperate with you, brother Wales, but I want something from you.”

Wales looked at Zhao Hai with incomprehension, “What do you want?”

“I want Herculean Bull Tribe’s friendship battle flag.”

Chapter 247: Battle Rations

It was an answer that was beyond Wales and Yale’s expectations. Friendship battle flags were very important to beastmen, which would not be gifted away easily, but compared to being a sole grain dealer to a whole race, it should be expected that everyone would choose being the sole dealer instead of a flag.

But Wales and Yale were clever people. They immediately knew Zhao Hai’s intentions. Zhao Hai was telling them, that between him and them, he’d rather choose friendship than profit.

Wales looked at Zhao Hai just as Zhao Hai was also looking at Wales calmly. After a moment, Wales raised his wine cup towards Zhao hai and said, “As you wish, brother Zhao Hai.”

Zhao Hai smiled and he raised his cup, “Thank you, brother Wales.” Both of them smiled and drank the wine in their cups in one shot.

Sometimes, friendships between men are truly strange. There is no need to say a lot and there’s also no need to do a lot. Perhaps it’s just a drink, and they will become friends. Yet sometimes, this friendship needs to be tested.

The two of them drank for 2 more cups before Zhao Hai spoke, “Brother Wales, where are you headed now? If you still want to go forward, you might run into Iron Wall Fortress’ cavalry. One mistake and there’ll be conflict.”

Wales smiled, “The reason why I’ve come here is simply because I want to take a look at Iron Wall Fortress and nothing else special. Now that I’ve run into you, I can’t possibly go to Iron Wall Fortress. Grains are more important than sceneries.”

Zhao Hai smiled, “Seems like you’re not letting us go. To tell you the truth, I want to set up shop in Beast God City, hehe. You should know that I not only have grains, but also plenty of vegetables, all fresh. Do you think opening up a vegetable shop in Beast God City will make a lot of people buy them?”

Wales looked at Zhao Hai with a bitter smile, “My brother, are you joking with me? Do you know how expensive vegetables are to us beastmen? You can use vegetables to exchange an argali of equal weight to your vegetables, and without market price. Do you think people will buy your vegetables?”

Zhao Hai smiled, “Seems like it’s really a good thing. Oh yes, brother Wales. You beastmen really like to eat mutton. Have you done a lot of research regarding the making of mutton products? Can you make canned mutton?”

Wales did a double take, and then shook his head, “We can’t, my brother. You know that things like cans could be stored for a long time, but there aren’t that many cans, so we have no way to produce them. In fact, producing cans is too troublesome, and frankly, the flavor of the cans doesn’t suit our tastes too well.”

Zhao Hai chuckled, “Then is there any method here that can create long term preservable mutton? Of course, the taste has to be good as well.”

Wales looked at Zhao Hai with incomprehension, “My brother, what are you trying to pull? Why ask these questions?”

Zhao Hai laughed, “My fief is too large, my brother, but my subordinates are few. I need people. Lots of people. That’s why I want to buy some slaves from here. My grains can exchange for a lot of argali from your place, but once they’re in human lands, they won’t survive for a long time. There’s no argali related business on the continent, so in such circumstances, the argali can only die when I bring them back. That’s why I want to find a way to process them for long term storage after killing them. This way, I can take my time to think of a way to sell the mutton. What do you think?”

Zhao Hai wasn’t telling the truth, of course. He could toss as much of the argali into the space as he wanted. But there was one thing Zhao Hai had to admit, and that was he wanted to earn even more money. If he could build a mutton processing factory, then he would be able to earn even more money.

He had a large fief right now, but just using it to plant things wouldn’t be able to earn too much money. If it weren’t for the cheating device like the space, Zhao Hai wouldn’t possibly have this many funds by now. To earn money, a factory was needed. With industry, even more money could be earned this way.

There was one more thing Zhao Hai was worried about. He could buy slaves from the beastmen, but beastmen wouldn’t know how to plant things. They may learn, but it would take a very long time. Once in winter, the slaves would have almost nothing to do. It would be better to do some side jobs.

Wales agreed to Zhao Hai’s suggestion. In fact, many merchants who did business with beastmen had meat processing factories or leather factories in human lands. The higher ups of the beastmen knew about it as well.

What were merchants? They were people who maximized profit. They wanted to bring argali back to the continent which, except for a portion which was sold directly, had to undergo thorough processing.

Goat skins can be made into clothes shoes, while cow skins and other magic beast skins can be made into leather armor or other leather products. How could the merchants be willing to leave such a big slice of the cake to others? So except for some merchants who didn’t have a lot of strength, many large dealers who did business with beastmen had their own factories on the continent. Their fortune was very shocking.

But the so-called thorough meat processing on the continent was seriously bad. Except for canned meat, which was ham and the like, there were no other ways.

After they did it in such a way, the price of mutton on the continent had become high on end and a lot of civilians couldn’t afford to eat them at all.

Zhao Hai didn’t think about changing such a situation, because that way, he would touch on a chain of profit too large to break. He had no way to withstand the backlash.

But he could develop new foods, like specialties on the prairie, which was why he asked Wales whether the prairie had mutton products that could be stored for a long time.

Wales thought about it and replied, “There IS a kind of mutton production method that’s very in line with your conditions, but there’s a catch. You humans might not like how it’s made.”

Zhao Hai laughed, “Do tell. It’s totally better than wasting it.”

Wales laughed and replied, “Battle rations. They’re the most common food beastmen bring during battles. To put it directly, this type of food is actually jerky. We kill the magic beasts and then cook them, air dry them, and after several times of processing, the meat will become jerky. The size of the jerky is very small. The meat of an argali can even fit into a grain sack in the end. But do not underestimate the jerkies, as the small size is also their greatest advantage. During battle, every beastman will bring a sack of them. Just bring a piece and cook with water. The meat will become large again. One small piece can feed an adult beastman for a meal. It’s the best battle ration.”

Zhao Hai nodded. He had heard of this method before. Back on Earth, as a pretending military fan, he once saw a forum thread which detailed the method of creation for rations created during the times of Genghis Khan. It was similar to what Wales just said. Although Zhao Hai didn’t know if the thread was being truthful or falsifying, what Wales said should be true.

The making of jerkies didn’t seem to be of much use to Zhao Hai, because making them was too troublesome. Even if they’re made, they might not be sold. People who could afford mutton wouldn’t buy the jerkies. Selling them to human troops on the continent would also be impossible, because troops had their own provision system, so they wouldn’t be having a rage over the jerkies. People who couldn’t afford mutton would also not be able to afford the jerkies, because after processing, they would be more expensive than normal mutton.

But then Zhao Hai thought about it. This type of jerky wasn’t completely without a market. In opposite, the market wasn’t small. He almost forgot that there was crowd of a very special occupation on the continent: mercenaries.

On Earth, mercenaries only existed in legends, which a homebody like Zhao Hai couldn’t possibly meet. Mercenaries on Earth wouldn’t eat the jerkies as well, because they had their own provision lines.

But on Ark Continent, it’s different. Those mercenaries would travel about in order to stay alive. Sometimes they would engage in rather special missions which would have a long duration. They would need to prepare a lot of edibles, and sometimes they had to hunt magic beasts in order to solve their hunger problems.

But many special missions wouldn’t let them receive additional provisions, so they could only only count on themselves. The main ration of the mercenaries some time ago was normally a kind of large rough flatbread. This flatbread was very hard, and it had to be boiled in water before it could be eaten. It could be stored for a very long time, but the price wasn’t cheap as well. As for the taste? Don’t count on it.

If Zhao Hai could really make the jerkies, then it would definitely be a blessing for the mercenaries. The jerkies would not only guarantee the taste, they would also be easy to carry with even richer nutrients. This would definitely be the mercenaries’ main selection.

Laura obviously never thought of all these, and neither did Wales. To be concise, the taste of this battle ration could only be said to be common. If it weren’t for a need during battles, beastmen wouldn’t make such jerkies.

After thinking about the use of jerkies, Zhao Hai’s face was full of smiles, “Thank you, my brother. This suggestion of yours is too marvellous.”

Wales looked at Zhao Hai and replied, “You must know, my brother, that the taste of jerky isn’t too great. We beastmen also don’t make them very much. We only make them when we have to fight battles, and ones that are long in time and in distance.”

Zhao Hai laughed, “Of course I know, my brother. But these jerkies are very suitable for type of people: mercenaries. Beastmen have no mercenaries, but humans have many of them. Every time and every moment there are mercenaries fighting, my brother. This kind of battle ration is like the best of delicacy to them.”

Wales and Laura were both stunned as they never thought about this aspect. Laura never made a lot of contact with mercenaries before. Her main clientele was common folk, while mercenaries were of a lower level compared to them. It could be said that they were people of 2 different worlds.

But you have to admit that on the continent, the amount of mercenaries were numerous. It was force that didn’t attract attention, but it existed nonetheless.

Once Laura heard what Zhao Hai said, her eyes sparkled. Her beyond ordinary business senses allowed her to discover the business opportunity immediately, but she thought that all of this still needed careful observation.

Wales looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Brother Zhao Hai, you are a smart person. You can even think of such an idea. Now I’m really curious as to where your fief is.”

Zhao Hai smiled, “Brother Wales, my identity isn’t too welcomed for the humans, hehe. That’s why no one knows where my fief is. Alright, let’s not talk about this. I want to open up a shop in Beast God City. I need your help in this.”

Wales laughed, “My brother, what are you opening up a shop for? I want all of your grains and all of your vegetables. What are you going to do that for?”

Zhao Hai laughed, “Believe me, my brother, you can’t digest the things in my hands. Just the vegetables alone will be more than you can handle, hehe. Of course, all of my things can supply the Herculean Bull Tribe first, and then sold to other people later, alright?”

Wales laughed, “My brother, I’ve been waiting those words. You don’t need to worry about the shop. I can help you settle it. But brother, you must ready the grains for me. We’re going to the Buffalo Tribe and Fighting Bull Tribe for a look. Buffalo Tribe is my teacher’s tribe, and Fighting Bull Tribe has relative ties to me as well. 4 of my older sisters were married into there, so I want to solve their grain problems.”

Even though Wales spoke of his situation to Zhao Hai in order to cooperate with him, he still couldn’t trust Zhao Hai completely. Besides, the things he told Zhao Hai could be heard from any tribe on the prairie. The fighting between him and Gasol had long been public knowledge. It wasn’t a big deal.

But grains were too important to Wales. If Zhao Hai really had a lot of grains, then he would have hope in defeating Gasol. But the pretext was that Zhao Hai really had the grains.

Zhao Hai didn’t object. To him, cooperating with Wales was just for the sake of getting the Herculean Bull Tribe’s friendship flag. It’s just as Zhao Hai said; he had grains in his hand and didn’t need to worry about selling them on Beastmen Prairie. But if he could get the friendship flag, it would have a lot of benefits in later business on the prairie.

He was simply selling the grains. What Wales would use them for and how to use them, wouldn’t be any of his business. To be honest, Zhao Hai really didn’t want to be dragged into the conflict between Wales and Gasol.

There was a great difference between the situation among the beastmen and the humans, and that was humans had already been treated with hostility on Beastmen Prairie. If Zhao Hai were inadvertently dragged into this sort of inner conflict of the beastmen, he would have nothing to gain. This was something he didn’t want.

Chapter 248: Healing Is Costly

Zhao Hai didn’t drink a lot today. He was friends with Wales, but this ‘friend’ couldn’t be compared to Spiel. Zhao Hai could get along with Spiel completely because of their personalities, so they truly became friends. With Wales, it was more or less mutual manipulation.

Zhao Hai and others returned to the space that night and also brought Greene and others into the space as well. Then, Zhao Hai spoke to them about wanting to make battle rations.

Greene and Kun Zheng trained outdoors when they were young, and they were also mercenaries for a period of time. The 2 of them knew well about the life of mercenaries, so they had a greater say about the matter of battle rations.

When Zhao Hai finished, Greened nodded, “This is a good idea. Some business owners on the continent treat mercenaries with importance, but I’ve never heard about it when it comes to battle rations. Many mercenaries whine that the flatbread is too hard to eat, but they have no other choice, since mercenaries have to prepare foods that can be kept for a long time. To be honest, I ate that kind of flatbread back in the day, and it was really bad.”

Kun Zheng nodded, “This can count as a low end business as well. Actually, such a low end business can bring in profit easier. I think we can turn blue-eyed rabbit meat into battle rations, so the price will be cheaper. But as for just the factory, it’s too much of a waste. If we have the time, we can purchase a poultry processing factory. Whether long-haired boars, blue-eyed rabbits or argali, we will have a place to ‘digest’ them later.”

Laura nodded, “Purchasing the factory isn’t hard, and neither is the production. The problem is the selling route. We can’t do it if we want to sell it in Fansile Duchy. Besides being too small, our names are too big over there. We have to change a venue this time.”

Zhao Hai nodded, “We’re going to Rosen Empire anyway, so we’ll leave it to you when it comes to business matters. With a ‘heavenly beauty’ like you, I don’t need to worry about things being unsellable, hehe.”

Laura rolled her eyes at Zhao Hai and then said, “There are many benefits when we form ties with Wales this time, but there are also lots of troubles as well, so we have to be careful. I think we should make a foothold in Beast God City first before we think about something else.”

Zhao Hai nodded, “Let’s rest for today. We’ve been in a hurry since yesterday, so first we plant the roots in Beast God City, and then execute our plan.”

Laura and others nodded. The plan Zhao Hai spoke of was actually the collection of special magic beasts and plants. It’s just they still knew too little about Beastmen Prairie right now, so Zhao Hai wasn’t in a hurry to collect those things.

Greene asked Zhao Hai suddenly, “Young master, what do you think about this Wales character? Is he trustworthy?”

Zhao Hai thought about it and replied, “He’s a rare clever being among beastmen. I think he’s more like a human. I’m scared about trusting him completely, but I think it’s ok to cooperate with him.”

Greened nodded, “From what you said about what Wales did, it can be said that he’s an ambitious and clever person. It’s dangerous to cooperate with such a person, but it’s good that we’re only cooperating. Whatever the case, Herculean Bull Tribe is also one of Beastmen Prairie’s powerful race tribe. Cooperating with him will bring us a lot of benefits.”

Kun Zheng spoke to Zhao Hai, “You were right in wanting their friendship flag instead of being the sole grain dealer. If we really went for the latter, other beastmen tribes would think that we’re trying to control the Herculean Bull Tribe using grains. We won’t get any benefit on Beastmen Prairie that way. There are some contradictions among beastmen, but treating humans with hostility is something common. If we do anything that makes the beastmen feel endangered, all of the beastmen will boycott us and then the Herculean Bull Tribe will deny the agreement. Instead of letting that happen, it would be more practical to get the friendship flag.”

To be honest, Zhao Hai really didn’t think that much, but he had to admit that things would probably unfold that way. Beastmen themselves had strong caution towards humans. If Zhao Hai really became the Herculean Bull Tribe’s sole grain dealer, he and others might be spited by all of the every beastman, considering the history of beastmen being cheated. It seemed that his choice at the time was correct.

After discussing about setting up shop in Beast God City again, Zhao Hai and others went to rest. But before he did so, he turned the Jackal Tribe’s people, which he stored, into undead creatures. The leader among them turned into a high level undead. He wanted to know who it was exactly that let the Jackal Tribe attack Wales.

And the result was within Zhao Hai’s expectations. It was indeed Gasol. Zhao Hai was sure that it must be Gasol after knowing about what went on between Wales and Gasol. It’s just he didn’t know about the reasons which Wales spoke of, since he wasn’t a Herculean Bull Tribe’s member.

These Jackal Tribe’s members didn’t come from a single tribe, but formed by many of the jackal tribes. Before they took action, Gasol gave their tribes lots of argali. That was why they came to deal with Wales.

It could be said that jackals were like the mercenaries of the beastmen. Zhao Hai knew after questioning, that it wasn’t the first time Gasol made them do such a thing. In fact, he would seek out the jackals every year, and let them help him deal with beastmen hostile to him. Jackals played the roles of mercenaries and assassins on Beastmen Prairie.

But all this wasn’t what Zhao Hai was concerned about. He didn’t get too many things out of the jackal, so he threw him back into Storage, and let out the 2 spirit jackals that were still alive and injured.

Their injuries weren’t light. One’s front paw was broken and was connected by only some skin, while the other’s spine was snapped. Both of them were at their last throes, and they weren’t going to make it.

Zhao Hai looked at these 2 spirit jackals without knowing what to do about them. Could they still be alive after being taken to the ranch? Would it admit them?

After a wry smile, Zhao Hai decided to test things out. With a flash of his figure, he brought the 2 heavily injured spirit jackals to the ranch.

Immediately after that, the notification voice said, <New animals discovered. Examining new animals. The animals are mutated wolf type animals. Animals are currently injured. Require treatment fee: 10000 gold coins. Level assessment will take place after treatment.>

Zhao Hai couldn’t help but cursing the system for being too black-hearted. This was practically forcing him to treat the spirit jackal’s injuries. Without treatment, there would be no rank, and they wouldn’t be able to be raised. What a black-hearted establishment. It’s 10000 gold coins! How many more must Zhao Hai sell in order to get the amount back?

But it might be a good thing after thinking about it more. When encountering injured magic beasts later on, he could bring them into the space and let it treat their injuries. That way, he wouldn’t attract attention. Gold coins could be earned after using them anyway. Compared to the coins, levelling up the system was more important.

Zhao Hai immediately chose to treat the spirit jackals’ injuries. It was good that it was simply 10000 gold coins. Otherwise, he would be even more heartbroken.

With a flash of white light, the 2 spirit jackals became alive and well in front of Zhao Hai. There were no traces of injury at all.

The notification voice also came out at this time, <Rating the animals. The animals are level 25 animals. Maturity time: 16 hours. Can give birth to offspring for 6 times. Quantity of first birth: 6. Eat 3 points of feed every hour. Converting animals into data. Can be purchased from Shop.>

Zhao Hai nodded as he was quite satisfied with the results, but Zhao Hai didn’t raise spirit jackals immediately. He couldn’t use them now, so he decided to wait and see if they could be used later. If there was no need to, perhaps he wouldn’t raise them in his lifetime.

After sorting out the matters in the ranch, Zhao Hai returned to his room in order to sleep well for a night. He drank too much yesterday and he drank again today, so his headache was beyond painful. He also had to sort out the deal with spirit jackals earlier, so now that it’s all done, he felt like he was about to fall apart.

After an uneventful night, Zhao Hai and others came out from the space the next morning. Wales sent people to invite Zhao Hai for breakfast, but they didn’t go as they had breakfast in the space. They then readied the wagons in order to leave.

Wales was indeed smarter than other beastmen, but as someone who grew up in people’s hands, he still had some bad noble habits, and one of which was the knack for keeping up appearances. If it weren’t for this, he wouldn’t have brought so many tents as well as useless things.

By the time Zhao Hai was completely ready, Wales only just finished his meal and was slowly tidying up his things. Zhao Hai couldn’t hold back a wry smile when he looked at that. With Wales’ speed, it might be noon before the things could be packed up. Zhao Hai really didn’t know how many hours out of today could he use to hasten the trip.

But there’s no helping it. He promised Wales to travel together, so he could only wait. Fortunately, the herculean bull escorts weren’t slow in packing things up. They had finished around 9 o’clock in the morning, so they would finally get on the road.

What Wales and others used to pull wagons were a type of bull shaped magic beast. These bull shaped magic beasts were the same as their mounts. They were all ground based bulls. Their forward movement speed weren’t much slower than horses, yet they were more powerful. This could be seen from their wagons.

The wagons Wales and others used were very large. A single one of them was as large as 4 of Zhao Hai’s wagons. This impressed him very much. He looked at the ground bulls and imagined when he would get one for himself.

Wales wasn’t inside a wagon. Instead, he was riding on his own mount. Although Wales was a prince, beastmen rode on mounts since little. For the beastmen, riding on mounts was more comfortable than being inside wagons.

Chapter 249: Sudden Change

By noon, Zhao Hai knew why Wales didn’t hurry earlier at morning. Wales and the others didn’t even stop during noon, and they just ate some jerkies on their mounts and drank a few mouthfuls of water. They didn’t stop during their trip.

Of course, the jerkies Wales and the others were eating were not that type of battle rations. They were a type of food that beastmen frequently ate, especially during a rush. They would prepare some when herding, and then put them in pouches to eat anytime.

These jerkies had a certain water content, so the storage time wouldn’t be too long. They were easy to make and common beastmen knew how to make them. They could count as beastmen’s dried food.

Once Zhao Hai saw this, he had to refrain from stopping as well. To be honest, when it came to sprinting, ground bulls couldn’t compare to windchaser horses. But to compete in endurance, windchaser horses would be far too worse. Zhao Hai and the others’ current speed could barely keep up with the speed of Wales’ group. If Zhao Hai stopped to eat now, it would surely affect the speed of the trip.

But this wasn’t too much for Zhao Hai. He found a time to enter the space, and then let Maylin make them a meal before returning back into the wagon, where he ate lightly with Laura and others.

Laura’s wagon wasn’t small, so it wasn’t a problem for Zhao Hai and others to eat inside it. At night, they started setting up camp. Just then, he had to admire the ability of the beastmen in setting up tents; they set up their campsite in just a short time. The whole process only took a little more than an hour. This speed was very surprising.

Luckily, Zhao Hai and others didn’t need to ready too many things. Just a single tent was needed to settle things, since it was just set up in order to put up a front.

Zhao Hai and Wales ate stewed mutton for the day, which the latter was very generous with. This was the difference between large tribes and small tribes. For people of smaller tribes, every goat was their fortune, which would be too much of a waste if eaten. But for Wales, the argali were just their food.

After the dinner, Zhao Hai didn’t chat with Wales. He felt that he and Wales weren’t of the same kind. Wales was smart and ambitious, while to be frank, Zhao Hai was just a normal person, working hard to live out his humble days.

Zhao Hai originally thought that they could reach Beast God City uneventfully, and then set up shop there to develop slowly like smooth sailing.

But he forgot about a saying, which goes ‘plans are never faster than changes’. Right at the 3rd day of their trip with Wales, a sudden change came.

They were still rushing ahead like before. As the Beastmen Prairie was too large, running into a small tribe in a few days’ time would not be an easy matter. Zhao Hai would still let blood hawks conduct reconnaissance in the sky, albeit in a very reduced range.

At noon of the 3rd day, Zhao Hai and the others were still rushing without rest. In order to ensure that their speed could keep up with Wales, Zhao Hai turned the windchaser horses that pulled the wagons into undead creatures during the 1st night when he returned to the space. With these undead that didn’t know what fatigue was, Zhao Hai’s group could easily keep up to Wales and others.

Zhao Hai drank some coya while sitting next to Laura after they had dinner. He had to admit that the design of Laura’s wagon was too ergonomic. If it weren’t for size issues, they could just sleep inside it.

Just then, a cry from the hawk in the sky grabbed Zhao Hai’s attention. Zhao Hai raised his head to look at a single blood hawk going in circles in the sky. He looked at the hawk carefully and his expression changed.

Laura and the others didn’t pay it any mind as the blood hawks would fly back to report in these days, so they guessed that it was probably due to having discovered magic beasts or some small tribes nearby. Perhaps Wales thought that the matter of grains was too important, so he didn’t go to the smaller tribes for a spin like before. Instead, he just moved forward. Zhao Hai was somewhat disappointed at this, but in order to get to Beast God City as soon as possible, he moved along with Wales like he had for the past few days.

Zhao Hai looked at the blood hawk for a while and then spoke to Laura, “Get ready. There’s a team of bull-headed cavalry coming our way. About 100 in number.”

Laura was startled and her expression changed, “Should we notify Wales?”

Zhao Hai shook his head and said, “Let’s not do so for now. Wales has the power to protect himself, since his escorts aren’t vegetarians. But why have the bull-headed cavalry come here? There are no large tribes nearby. Mobilizing 100 cavalry in one go, this tribe’s strength wouldn’t be too bad. How could they be here?”

Laura had also frowned, “Let’s not think about it too much. We’re still in the fringe areas of the prairie. The ones active here are small tribes, while the medium and large tribes are further inside. The other party is all cavalry and 100 isn’t a large number. Unfortunately, we don’t know which race they belong to.”

Zhao Hai nodded, “We’ll know it soon. The other party will be able to see us after an hour, so we’ll just have to be more careful.” Laura nodded. When it came to their safety, Laura didn’t worry in the slightest. They just didn’t want to expose themselves too much.

They were being careful, but they weren’t too worried. Now that they were next to Wales, anything could be settled by him. This was the logic of ‘a large tree is good for staying under it’.

As expected, after an hour, a very loud galloping sound came from far away. The galloping was like rumbling thunder, which would let any listener know that whatever was running would be heavy. Wales and others also went on alert.

With the galloping sounds, Zhao Hai and the others could see that a black line was slowly coming after them from their front left. Then the black line was followed by a layer of green stuff behind it. When they got closer, Zhao Hai and the others found out that the green stuff was actually broken grass raised up in hands.

Very soon, the team of people got closer, and Zhao Hai could gradually look at them clearly. But when he did, he was shocked, because they were herculean bulls as well.

What differentiated them from Wales and others was that this team didn’t raise battle flags. They had wounds, and some were even covered in bloodstains. One could tell at a glance that they had been through a great battle. This team of people was protecting a single person.

That person was also a herculean bull. He was wearing a bright yellow robe, but he had obviously been through a great battle as well, so his robe was full of bloodstains.

These 100 people were holding weapons with bloodshot eyes and faces full of fatigue, but their killing aura was soaring sky high. It was as if they had killed during every step of the way.

Zhao Hai and others were dumbstruck when they saw them, but soon they understood. The one leading this team must be a prince of the Herculean Bull Tribe. If not, why was he wearing a robe and why were they so discomposed?

Right now, Wales was even more shocked than Zhao Hai, because he knew these people. The one in the robe was exactly his 6th brother, Mendez!

If it was asked who of the Herculean Bull Tribe treated Wales the best, it would be Mendez, of course. Wales’ father also treated him well, but it was more like a form of admiration, while Mendez displayed caring love.

When Wales saw Mendez looking so worn, he was shocked before his heart sank. He knew why Mendez was in such a way; It must be that something had happened in the tribe. When he connected this to the jackals’ attack on him, a bad feeling surged in his heart.

Wales immediately made his way to the cavalry, while Yale and others also recognized them. Everyone stopped as they looked at Mendez and the others in shock.

Mendez also saw Wales, and the murderous expression on his face disappeared instantly. His eyes closed, his body swayed, and he collapsed from his mount in an instant.

Wales immediately got down from his mount when he saw this, but he never expected that Mendez’s collapse was just a start. The cavalry warriors who followed Mendez, upon seeing Mendez’s collapse, had also fallen from their own mounts one after another.

This situation was like how Chinese people put dumplings into pots. In just an instant, everyone fell down from their mounts, which frightened Wales and others a lot. Every escort got down from their mounts and ran towards the cavalry.

Zhao Hai’s group looked at all of this idly. He didn’t know what became of the trip. Why would herculean bulls, who were known for being powerful and enduring, be in such straits?

Zhao Hai immediately jumped down from his wagon and walked towards the people. He spoke to Meg as he walked, “Meg, help me out.” Meg heeded with a sound and took out her own iron scroll.

There were 5 magics in the Demon Sealing Iron Scroll;

Protection Of Angels, which was a single target protection magic, level 6;

Blade Of Judgement, which was a single target attacking magic, level 7;

Descent Of Holy Light, which was a group healing magic, as well as a group attacking magic against dark creatures, level 6;

Holy Light Step, which was a teleport type single target escaping magic, level 6;

Holy Recital, a single or group attacking mental magic, level 7.

These light magics were only level 7 at the highest, but they included 3 aspects like attacking, protecting and escaping. One could say they were very practical. In a light mage’s hands, this was an incredible treasure already.

Zhao Hai walked quickly towards the crowd of people, while Wales had embraced Mendez and called out his name. But it seemed like Mendez and others were very tired as they had all lost consciousness.

Zhao Hai walked to Wales and said, “My brother, let my fianceè take a look. She knows some healing magics.”

Wales raised his head in a hurry after hearing Zhao Hai’s words. He glanced at Laura and Meg at Zhao Hai’s side, who were wearing ordinary home clothes. He couldn’t tell how either of these 2 knew magic.

Zhao Hai smiled and spoke to Meg, “Meg, help out and see.” Meg heeded with a sound and then walked forward.

Chapter 250: Determination

Meg wasn’t that good at treating wounds. She was just a wind mage, but with the iron scroll in her hands, she would naturally have an easier time.

She walked over to the herculean bulls and opened the scroll to use ‘Descent Of Holy Light’. A pillar of white light came down and illuminated the several hundred square metres of ground they were on.

As the white light came down, the complexions of Mendez and others became much better while fatigue vanished from their faces. Those who had injuries were having their wounds closed up rapidly.

The white light faded soon after. Those people were still lying on the ground, but their complexions were much better than before. None of them woke up, however. They were breathing stably, and they appeared to be asleep. Wales no longer shouted for Mendez when he saw this. Instead, he let his people set up tents and prepare food.

These people appeared to be really exhausted, as no matter how Wales’ escorts moved and hauled them, there was no response. They used more more than 2 hours to put all of Mendez’s group into the tents.

The weapons in their hands made Wales’ group even more surprised. They were all Herculean Bull Tribe’s people, and they commonly used double-sided heavy axes. These axes and their hafts were all forged of fine iron. As for people of Wales’ status, their heavy axes were forged of fine steel, and were very rare among beastmen.

Heavy axes like these had great killing power. The axe heads were thick and sturdy so they weren’t easily damaged, which made them suitable weapons for herculean bulls. On Beastmen Prairie, other than the Herculean Bull Tribe, there were also many other powerful races whose weapons were this kind of heavy double-sided axe.

But these weapons had now been broken; some of the hafts had been seriously warped, and some of the cutting edges showed large cracks. It was obvious that they had undergone a very brutal fight.

Some of their mounts also bore wounds. One should know that ground bulls’ defenses couldn’t compare to stoneskin bulls, but only in a relative sense. The stoneskin bulls’ defenses were very freakish, so compared to other magic beasts, the ground bulls’ defenses were already high enough. Yet for them to have injuries, this explained the strength of their opponents.

Yale was at a ground bull’s side to examine the scars carefully. Even though ‘Descent Of Holy Light’ had healed the wounds, some who were too heavily injured would still leave scars behind.

It was a very large scar, from the back to the rear waist, nearly 1 metre long. Yale looked clearly at it, as if the scar had grown flowers.

Yale stood up after a while. Wales looked at Yale’s darkened face and asked, “What’s wrong, teacher? What kind of weapon did this?”

Yales glanced at Wales and replied, “It’s flying axes.”

Flying axes were heavy thrown ranged weapons. Normally much smaller than heavy double-sided axes, and weighing about 10 kilos each. But once thrown, the damage would be very large. Even a common iron shield could be shattered from a single strike by this kind of flying axe. Note: it’s shatter, not penetrate.

Normal people couldn’t use these flying axes because they were too heavy and couldn’t be thrown very far. Adding their special shape, their accuracy was difficult to grasp, so only very few people would use these flying axes as long range weapons.

But there was a race born to use flying axes. They had boundless strength and a natural grasp of flying axes’ usage. The axes they threw would be extremely accurate, which made the axes become known far and wide as one of the famous long ranged weapons. This race was the herculean bulls.

Once Wales heard that the ground bulls were wounded by flying axes, Wales’ expression changed. Even though it was a scar, it sent Wales a message: the ones who hurt Mendez and his group were very likely herculean bulls.

Mendez and the others were hurt by his own people? What did this mean? This meant that a change had taken place within the Herculean Bull Tribe, and one that was highly unfavorable to Wales.

Wales’ expression darkened. He looked at Yale and asked, “Teacher, how do you perceive this?”

Yale replied with a darkened expression as well, “Something must’ve happened in the tribe. You and Mendez are on the best of terms, and he also knew you would be coming here. It looks like he was looking for you. I’m afraid that ‘something’ in the tribe must’ve been incredible, and is likely tied to Gasol.”

Wales replied, “It can’t be. Father and the high elders are keeping watch. What tides can Gasol raise?”

Yale looked at Wales and said, “Do not forget that the 10000 Beast Festival is approaching. The high elders might’ve gone to Beast God City. If 2 of the high elders had left, then Gasol would have a chance.”

Wales shook his head, “There’s still my father….” He stopped. His father was the chieftain, but his strength was only at level 8. There was no way to compare a level 8 with a level 9. Level 9 meant invincible, while level 8 meant vulnerable.

One couldn’t possibly use any kind of scheming attacks to deal with level 9 powerhouses. Even poisoning would be very difficult to achieve. Unless it was a place filled with toxic air like Rotten Corpse Swamp, poison wouldn’t be a threat to a level 9 powerhouse.

But the same couldn’t be said for level 8. A level 8 could also be called a powerhouse, but level 8 powerhouses couldn’t fare well against poisons. There were a lot of level 8 powerhouses who had died from poisons across history.

Once Wales thought about this, his expression changed before he stared at Yale, “Teacher, you mean….?”

Yale nodded, “It’s very likely that Gasol’s lot used an unspeakable means to deal with the chieftain, and then made a sudden move to usurp the position, making it a factful succession. This way, even the high elders won’t be able to do anything if they return, since Gasol has now become chieftain.”

Wales’ bull eyes glared and even became red. His 2 hands were balled into fists and his breathing became hoarse.

Yale looked at Wales and said, “All of this is just our speculation at the moment. We will have to wait until the 6th Prince wakes up to confirm it. But Wales, right now you not only need to take care of the 6th Prince and know the truth, but there’s also him.” Yales pointed towards Zhao Hai’s direction.

Zhao Hai’s group had also set up their tent right now. They didn’t come to Wales’ camp because they knew Wales would be very busy right now. They did what they could, so it was up to Wales and the others.

Wales glanced at Zhao Hai’s campsite and then asked Yale with confusion, “What do you mean, teacher?”

Yale replied, “If Gasol has now become chieftain, it is illegal. We can rally the other branch tribes and overthrow Gasol’s rule. In order to do that, it won’t happen just by using our lips. There has to be a benefit as well, and a sufficiently large one at that. If Zhao Hai hasn’t lied to us, then he himself is a sufficiently large benefit.”

Wales knew what Yale meant. So what if Gasol became chieftain now? He had used an unspeakable means to become one. Even the high elders would be dissatisfied with him. This was Wales’ chance; If he joined with enough branch tribes, he could apply for the abolishment of Gasol’s position with the high elders. No matter how powerful Gasol would be, he wouldn’t dare to disobey the wills of the high elders.

But just parading around wouldn’t be enough, as it wouldn’t be possible to make the branch tribes follow him. He needed benefits to move them, and Zhao Hai had something that could move them.

Grains were too important for beastmen. If Zhao Hai had enough grains, he could take the position of chieftain back from Gasol.

Wales nodded and said, “When 6th brother wakes up and we figure out what really happened, then I will look for Zhao Hai. There’s no use doing so now. We don’t know what happened in the tribe at all.”

Yale nodded, “Yeah, let’s confirm what happened first. It’s strange though. I heard the human merchants saying that among them, light mages and black mages are mutually opposed. Why does Zhao Hai’s fiancee know how to use light magics? It doesn’t make sense, does it?”

Wales let out a grunt before replying, “How many truths can those human liars tell? Besides, I keep feeling that Zhao Hai has an unusual identity. You remember, teacher? He let it slip himself, that his identity wasn’t welcome over there in human lands. He must’ve gotten into trouble, or else he wouldn’t be here on Beastmen Prairie. You saw his grains. Why would he bring them here if he didn’t run into trouble? Those are the best grains I’ve seen in my life. I’ve never even seen such fine bamboo rice from lion tribes or tiger tribes.”

Yale nodded, “No matter what his identity is in the human lands, if he has the grains and can help us, it’s enough.”

Wales nodded and looked into the distance at the prairie, “Whatever happened, I will become Herculean Bull Tribe’s ruler. If Gasol really intends to harm our father, I will kill him myself.”

Yale was quiet as he just looked at Wales quietly. To be honest, he was worried, but more than that, he was happy. Wales was ambitious before, but he didn’t want to fight against Gasol. Otherwise, with his father’s affection, his force wouldn’t be smaller than Gasol’s.

Although Wales looked like he was fighting before, Yale had always felt that he had lacked something. Now he knew. What Wales lacked was a determination, which he now had.

Just then, a wave of thick aroma came. Wales looked around, and saw that it was his subordinates cooking a mutton soup. This was for Mendez and the others, who looked like they hadn’t eaten or slept for a long time. It was already a miracle that they could fight fiercely and reach here.

Chapter 251: Anytime

Wales and Yale didn’t expect that Mendez and his team would sleep until the 2nd morning before waking up. Before that, they were like unconscious brain-dead people; no one moved or even turned in their sleep.

Wales and Yale, however, were not sleeping. This display from Mendez and his team could only explain that they were too tired. The more it was like that, the more it meant that it was a grave matter.

When the sun rose on the 2nd morning, a sound came from the tents. Wales and Yale, who hadn’t slept, were startled, and then the two of them charged straight into Mendez’s tent. Mendez was resting inside.

Mendez just woke up, and he was sitting inside the tent and looking around. Although he entered a defensive stance on instinct upon seeing Wales and Yale charging in, he soon relaxed as his expression became one of elation, “Little 7th, I’ve finally found you.”

Then his expression darkened all of a sudden and he said, “Little 7th, you have to run as far away from the tribe as possible. 5th brother is dead, and so is our father. Gasol has become the chieftain now, and he wants to hunt you down.”

Even though Wales had thought about this outcome, hearing it from Mendez’s lips filled his mind with noise for a moment. His vision went dark, and he swayed where he stood. Yale immediately grabbed him before Wales would faint.

Fortunately, Wales had a bit of mental preparation for this. After a few deep breaths, he focused on Mendez and asked, “What happened, 6th brother? Please explain clearly.”

Mendez’s tears were pouring out as he nodded, “Not long after you left, the 2 high elders made their way towards Beast God City due to 10000 Beasts Festival. Not long after they left, father suddenly became sick and died in just a few days. Gasol immediately announced that before father died, he had handed over the chieftain’s position to Gasol. But me and 5th brother didn’t believe it, because when father passed away, we weren’t at his side. Gasol sent people to surround father’s tent and didn’t let us in.”

Wales’ face went ashen. He knew that his father was a level 8 powerhouse and his health was great. How could he contract an illness and pass away not even a few days after? It was absolutely impossible.

Mendez continued, “When burying father, 5th brother discovered something wrong. 5th brother wasn’t healthy and he ate medicine every year, which was why he knew some drugs very well. When he saw father’s face, he knew. Father wasn’t sick. He was poisoned.”

SPLACK!!

Wales smashed a small table at the side with his fist. His eyes were red, and his breathing was like a bellows.

Mendez only glanced at him and then continued, “When 5th brother discovered this, he didn’t voice it. He looked for me that night and spoke of it to me, in order to let me find you. But right at that time, Gasol suddenly announced that me, you, and 5th brother are Herculean Bull Tribe’s traitors, and issued an order to kill us. We went through many detours in order to find you here. If we hadn’t found you, we’d be in greater danger. Gasol must be looking for us all over the prairie right now.”

Wales breathed hoarsely, “That bastard. From this day on, he’s my enemy. I will have this revenge. I will!”

Mendez looked at Wales and said, “Wales, Gasol controls the tribe now. You can’t take revenge. It’s useless. Believe me, we can start over far away from the tribe. With your 300 escorts and my 100, we can have up to 400 warriors. We can make another tribe somewhere else.”

There were many such examples on the prairie. A tribe was exterminated, but some warriors escaped to someplace else and conquered some smaller tribes, slowly got stronger, and finally became a large tribe. Such things happened on the prairie every year.

But likewise, there were even more tribes that were eliminated. Mendez was right, however. With their 400 powerful herculean bull warriors, they were not a force to be underestimated. They could carve out a turf for themselves with this strength. Mendez had this confidence.

Wales shook his head and said, “No. I want to go back and contact the other branch races in order to make them band together and chase Gasol away from the seat.”

Mendez was startled and asked loudly, “No, little 7th, you can’t! It’s too dangerous! The branch tribes might not buy what you say to overthrow Gasol. It doesn’t benefit them. Why should they do it?”

Wales smiled, “I will give them benefits for sure. Come, 6th brother. I’m taking you to see someone.” He grabbed Mendez and walked out of the tent.

Mendez’s mind was in a blank when he was dragged out of the tent by Wales. He had forgotten about what had happened yesterday. Otherwise, he wouldn’t have been in a defensive stance when Wales and Yale walked in.

Actually, when Mendez and the others were riding on their mounts, they were already on the verge of breakdown. They were in a state of semi-unconsciousness, so when they stopped, they slept for a whole day and a half, despite having received Meg’s treatment.

Mendez saw Zhao Hai’s campsite not far away from him after he got dragged out of the tent. Their campsite wasn’t the same as the one set up by Wales’ people. Not only did Zhao Hai and the others have grains, the style of their tent was also different as well. Human tents and beastman tents were 2 different concepts.

Mendez then saw the friendship flag attached to the top of Zhao Hai’s tent. The Big-bellied Pig Tribe wasn’t a small tribe among the beastmen; they had a medium level strength as well.

But while the Big-bellied Pig Tribe’s branch tribes could use the tribal flags, the flag themselves had slight changes between each other, as each larger and smaller tribe would have different markings on their flags. It could be said that there were secret unique codes on the flags which belonged to each of their tribes. They were just hard to tell for anyone who wasn’t a beastman.

Even though it was a friendship flag from a big-bellied pig race’s branch tribe, Mendez had a great shock when it came to that. Mendez was very clear that human merchants had never gotten a friendship flag from beastmen, because they thought that true friendship never existed between humans and beastmen.

Mendez was at a loss for words when he saw Zhao Hai’s campsite. Wales let him go just then and spoke, “The one I speak of is him.” He pointed at Zhao Hai’s campsite and then detailed how he had met Zhao Hai to Mendez.

Mendez frowned after hearing the tale. He looked at Wales and asked, “Little 7th, why do I feel like this is all a lie? How can there be such a good thing in this world? Half price? Best bamboo rice? And that many? Impossible, right?”

Wales replied with a cold shimmer in his eyes, “This is our final chance. Instead of running away to somewhere else to set up a small tribe, why don’t we use Zhao Hai’s grains to make a gamble? If we can get the branch tribes’ support, Gasol’s chieftain position will not be stable.”

Mendez was still frowning as he said, “I’m afraid that they’re lying to us right now. If they are, we’re finished. We wouldn’t have the slightest chance. Little 7th, I don’t want something to happen to you.”

A trace of feeling touched flashed across Wales’ eyes, but he still spoke insistently, “Relax, 6th brother, I will meet with them shortly. Maybe you’ll change your mind once you meet Zhao Hai. Oh right, go and have a bowl of mutton soup. It was boiled for a night.”

Mendez felt an unprecedented hunger when he heard what Wales said. He felt as if his stomach had turned into a black hole that could fit a cow.

In the middle of the campsite was a large iron pot. The fire under the pot had not faded yet, and the mutton soup in the pot had been boiled to a white color which looked just like goat milk.

Next to the pot was a small table with a few bowls on top. Mendez didn’t speak any further as he walked towards the pot, filled a bowl with the soup and drank it slowly.

Mendez had never felt that mutton soup could be so delicious before. Even though he knew that it was just a thing that couldn’t be more normal than it already was, it felt like he was drinking the most delicious soup in his life.

A single bowl of mutton soup, and Mendez felt even hungrier, but he knew he couldn’t eat a lot of things right now, so he drank another bowl.

Because the soup had been boiled for too long, the mutton had already disintegrated. There were only a few bones in the soup, but the flavor of the soup had become better as a result.

After 3 bowls of mutton soup, Mendez put the bowl down. He felt that his body had completely recovered. He also felt strange, because he clearly remembered that he had injuries. How could his injuries be recovered so quickly?

Just then, others had walked out of their tents. They were Mendez’s escorts. They bowed to him when they saw Mendez, which prompted him to wave his hand, “Alright, come and drink some bowls of soup. Little 7th boiled this for a night.”

These people knew who the ‘Little 7th’ Mendez was referring to actually was, of course. They bowed to Wales immediately and then ran to the pot before drinking large mouthfuls of mutton soup. They were seriously starved.

Mendez also noticed just then that his subordinates’ injuries had all recovered. Even ones with larger wounds had recovered, and only scars were left behind.

Wales noticed Mendez’s expression. He smiled and said, “No need to look. It was Zhao Hai’s fiancee who used magic to treat your injuries. Let’s go and meet Zhao Hai.” Mendez nodded immediately and followed Wales to Zhao Hai’s campsite. He was really curious about Zhao Hai now.

They soon arrived outside Zhao Hai’s campsite, and Zhao Hai also came out from the tent immediately. It was still early, but Zhao Hai and the others didn’t wake up late, and had already eaten breakfast.

Wales immediately greeted with a chest salute when he saw Zhao Hai coming out, “Brother Zhao Hai, I want to thank you for your assistance.”

Zhao Hai smiled and returned the gesture, “Brother Wales, you’re too welcoming. Being able to help you is my honor.”

Mendez also walked forward and saluted Zhao Hai, “Mendez greets brother Zhao Hai. Thank you for your assistance. Otherwise, we wouldn’t have gotten better this quickly.”

Zhao Hai laughed in response, “Brother Mendez, you’re too kind.”

Wales saw Laura and 2 others behind Zhao Hai and then spoke to Zhao Hai, “Brother Zhao Hai, come with me to my tent. I have something to discuss with you.” Zhao Hai nodded and led Laura and the others to follow Wales to the tent.

Once they sat down, a few people immediately brought some bowls of hot mutton soup. Wales dismissed the people afterwards, leaving only Wales himself, Mendez, Yale, and then Zhao Hai and the others.

After the people left, Wales spoke to Zhao Hai, “Brother Zhao Hai, you have discovered as well, right? Something happened in my home.”

Zhao Hai nodded as it wasn’t anything strange. If he couldn’t realize even this, then he would be an idiot.

Wales continued, “My eldest brother started a coup, poisoned our father, killed my 5th brother, and then sent people to hunt us down. He even became chieftain.” When Wales spoke to this point, his face was filled with hatred, but his eyes were looking at Zhao Hai.

Zhao Hai was still being calm. He just frowned slightly and looked at Wales, “Brother Wales, what do you want me to help you with? To be honest, with my identity, if I help you, you might get further and further away from the position.”

Wales knew why Zhao Hai said that. It was because Zhao Hai was a human. If the tribe knew that a human was helping in the fighting over the position of chieftain, then Wales would only be further and further away from the chieftain position.

Wales also never planned to let Zhao Hai help him in combat directly. It couldn’t be done. However, helping with grains was possible, so he nodded, “I understand, brother Zhao Hai, but I really need your help this time. I want grains. Lots and lots of grains. They have to be at the price you listed earlier. My brother, can you tell me exactly how many grains you have?”

Zhao Hai calculated before answering, “Nearly 200 million kilos, and they are the type I showed you before. There’s also several tens of thousands of kilos of vegetables, and they’re also the same as the ones I showed you before.”

Wales looked at Zhao Hai and asked, “My brother, you must know how important the food is to me. I stake my entire fortune on this, so brother, how long until you can bring the food to the prairie?”

Zhao Hai glanced at Wales and replied calmly, “Anytime.”

Wales asked Zhao Hai with a confused look, “Did you say ‘anytime’, my brother? Even now?”

Zhao Hai waved his hand softly, and a bunch of vegetables appeared in front of him. Another wave, and the vegetables disappeared. He waved his hand again, and a bunch of grains appeared in front of him. Yet another wave, and the grains disappeared.

Chapter 252: 3 Jobs

Zhao Hai’s display had the intention of showing his hand. He wasn’t afraid that Wales would be suspicious of him. He just wanted to let Wales know that he had a storage device.

For the beastmen, spatial equipments were too mysterious, and even now they didn’t have a single one. It was because they did not have any that they treated spatial equipments like they were sacred artifacts. It was as if the space in a spatial equipment could fit an entire continent.

Zhao Hai decided to display this ability in front of Wales and the others after learning this. It could be said that Zhao Hai wanted to cooperate with Wales, because whatever the case may be, if Wales became Herculean Bull Tribe’s chieftain, he would repay the one who had always helped him. Zhao Hai didn’t need too many benefits from Wales. As long as he could be friends with Wales, it would save him a lot of trouble on Beastmen Prairie.

No matter how self-important the other humans acted, the ones who truly called the shots were still the beastmen. Only by forming good relationships with beastmen could he stand firm on the prairie.

The herculean bulls’ place on the prairie was not lower than ordinary battle tribes. Such a position was definitely not to be looked down on. Even if the smaller tribes wanted to look for trouble, they would have to consider their own strength first. Beastmen on the prairie may be fond of fighting, but they were not entirely maniacs like the jackals.

Furthermore, the grains in his possession were for selling. If Wales didn’t buy them, it would be Wales’ failure. How would that be any of Zhao Hai’s business? He was just simply selling them to Wales, while he would also sell them for the same price to others should they want to buy from him. He didn’t lower the price because of Wales.

Of course, the main reason why Zhao Hai dared to do this in front of Wales and the others was because Wales needed the food in his hands. As long as Wales needed the food, he wouldn’t speak of the spatial equipment to others. Zhao Hai would have nothing to be afraid of.

Wales and others were stunned by Zhao Hai’s display. They didn’t really know what to say, as Zhao Hai’s performance was too shocking.

Wales stood up after a while and asked, “Heavens, brother Zhao Hai. You actually have a spatial equipment, and you use it to store food? Are you mad?”

Zhao Hai looked at Wales with incomprehension, “Can spatial equipment not be used to store things? What’s the problem?”

‘What’s the problem?’ This question certainly stopped Wales in his tracks. That’s right. Weren’t spatial equipments supposed to be used to store things? What would be the problem if there were no limits?

Wales felt that he was getting a little dizzy. He spoke after a while, “It’s a big problem. Don’t you realize how precious spatial equipments are? We beastmen have never had a single one. You actually use one to store food? Isn’t it too much of a waste?”

Zhao Hai laughed, “My brother Wales, for me, these foods mean all of my fortune and money. If I don’t use it to store them, what else can I use? Besides, I can only use spatial equipment to store the food in order to bring it to Beastmen Prairie at the fastest speed. That’s how I could get away from the damn border troops.”

Wales went silent for a moment before he drew in a long breath and laughed loudly, “My brother Zhao Hai, I have to thank you! If it weren’t for your spatial equipment bringing the food over here, we would really be finished. Do you have all of your foods on you?”

Zhao Hai nodded, “All of them. If you will it, I can bring them from my fief at any time. I think I can get another 100 million kilos of them in this period of time.”

Wales looked at Zhao Hai with incomprehension, “From your fief at any time? Are you bringing your fief with you?”

Zhao Hai and the others laughed at that, because Wales had guessed correctly. Wales thought that Zhao Hai and the others were laughing because they found his question to be a joke, so he didn’t mind.

Zhao Hai laughed as he said, “Of course not! But I have a flying magic hawk. I can give my spatial equipment to the hawk and then let it fly to my fief, and then bring my food here. It saves a lot of time this way, does it not?”

Wales was stunned, and then looked at Zhao Hai like he was looking at a lunatic, “Are you mad? You are willing to give your spatial equipment to a magic beast?”

Zhao Hai smiled, “I’m not mad. This is the best way. Besides, my magic beast isn’t a normal magic beast. To put it exactly, it isn’t a magic beast, but simply a phantasmal beast.”

Wales had heard of phantasmal beasts before, of course. He just never thought that Zhao Hai would have one. He nodded, “Phantasmal beasts are more secure than magic beasts indeed. But my brother, can it really fly that far?”

Zhao Hai smiled, “Sure. That’s why I said I can give you large amounts of food. I’m not kidding. I really have them. Wales my brother, just do whatever you want to do. I can’t help you in anything else, but when it comes to grains, I can help you solve those issues. I can even get some from the human lands for you. Only when you need it, of course. I will not give the food away for free. I may not be a legitimate merchant, but I’m a merchant all the same, which is why you have to exchange for it using argali, goat skin products, slaves, magic beasts, or even rare plants on the prairie. Of course, the plants cannot be dead ones. They should only be living ones or seeds.”

Wales never thought that Zhao Hai would say this. He looked at Zhao Hai with incomprehension and asked, “My brother, isn’t that too much of a loss for you? What do you want the plants for? What use do they have?”

Zhao Hai laughed, “My brother, I’m not losing out at all. Perhaps you don’t know that I have an apothecarist senior at home. He needs all of the rare plants in this world as well as uncommon ones. He wants to build himself the most wholesome plant garden in the world.”

Wales and the 2 others were relieved to hear that. There were 2 kinds of people who were the most mysterious in this world: apothecaries, and alchemists. Not only did the humans have them, but the beastmen had them as well. Only, they were referred to a little differently. Among beastmen, apothecaries were called witch doctors, while alchemists were commonly called shamans.

Among the beastmen, there were 3 jobs that were respected the most. The 1st was prophets, of course. They were regarded as the wisest of people. The 2nd was shamans, due to the lack of metal tools at the beastmen’s disposal, while shamans were researching on how to make metal tools last long and how to make weapons sturdier. They were thought to be the ones with the greatest spirit of exploration. The 3rd was witch doctors, who were regarded as the most mysterious. They needed all sorts of herbs to treat beastmen illnesses. These 3 kinds of people were highly respected among the beastmen.

The witch doctors here would sometimes hire some tribes to help gather some plants as well, so when Zhao Hai mentioned that there was someone at home who was an apothecary, they no longer felt Zhao Hai’s methods to be strange.

Wales took in a relaxed breath and looked at Zhao Hai, “My brother, knowing you has got to be the most fortunate thing in my life, hahaha. The Beast God is truly helping me. Otherwise, I wouldn’t have been allowed to meet you. You even saved me on your own.”

Zhao Hai laughed, “Not necessarily. I do think that the Beast God let me meet you. If not for meeting you, I really don’t know which year I would have to sell all the grains in. You should know that storing the grains too long will turn them into aged rice. That won’t be valuable anymore.” Wales and the others laughed at that. In the beastmen’s territories, even aged rice could sell for a good price. It was apparent that Zhao Hai wanted to crack a joke.

But this joke of his was cracked at the right time. Wales knew what Zhao Hai meant. Zhao Hai didn’t want to let him keep putting gratitude on his mind. This was more to Wales’ taste.

Mendez now understood what Wales meant when Wales said that he would probably know what sort of person Zhao Hai was when meeting him. Indeed, from Zhao Hai himself, Mendez saw a very unique disposition, which was never seen from other humans he had seen before.

Mendez had seen many human merchants before. In fact, he was also an oddity among beastmen. He wasn’t as ambitious as Gasol, as capable of fighting as Paul, as sickly as Hales, or as smart as Wales. But he was very interested in business. It was because of this, that whenever the Herculean Bull Tribe made contact with human merchants, he would be the one to meet them. He was better at this than others. When he made contact with the humans, he could buy more things than other beastmen no matter what. This was his most unique trait.

Mendez had always wanted to become a merchant. This was something that made him different from other beastmen. Other beastmen didn’t want to become merchants since they believed that merchants were vampires and cowards. But Mendez didn’t think of it that way. He wanted to be a merchant, and a good one at that.

It was precisely because of these reasons that he could be said to be the one who had seen the most humans in Herculean Bull Tribe. Especially the human merchants.

When the human merchants met him, they put up an appearance of respecting him, but he, Mendez, could see that those merchants looked down on him. From their eyes, he could see a trace of condescension. Mendez knew that those humans looked down on beastmen. They thought that beastmen were barbarians and unenlightened races. They even thought that beastmen were beasts.

It wasn’t just one human merchant who was like this. Almost every human merchant he had approached before had been like this. Mendez was furious at first, but he was unable to be angry at this in the end, since that would only kill him.

But Mendez didn’t see those kind of eyes in Zhao Hai. Zhao Hai’s eyes were very clear and very sincere. It was outside of his expectations. Mendez believed that Zhao Hai wasn’t pretending, as he had seen those kinds of condescending eyes too many times. He became very sensitive to them to the point that he could notice them even when pretending. But he didn’t find those eyes from Zhao Hai. He noticed that Zhao Hai wasn’t looking at them with condescension and disdain. There was only sincerity.

Chapter 253: Beheading Blood Oath

Zhao Hai’s performance left Mendez with an incredibly good impression. Adding that to how Zhao Hai saved Wales before and even helped out after that, Mendez’s impression of Zhao Hai was much better than those of the other human merchants.

After some laugh-filled conversation, Zhao Hai spoke to Wales, “Wales, my brother, what are you going to do now? Food isn’t an issue, but if you want to overthrow Gasol, you must have a chartered course. Moving on without thinking isn’t going to work.”

Wales did a double take at that. To put it seriously, he still didn’t have a specific plan laid out. He just wanted to use grains to pull in the other branch races, and there wasn’t a more detailed plan of action after that.

Zhao Hai glanced at Wales and said, “My brother Wales, I think that you should have a more detailed plan, but I can’t help you much when it comes to this matter. You too know that I’m a human, and I don’t know you herculean bulls well enough. If I help you too much, it might have the opposite effect, so this matter is up to you yourselves. But after you plan things out, then you can tell me how to proceed. If you don’t want to attract attention, we can proceed separately. You just need to tell me where to deliver the food.”

Wales glanced at Zhao Hai, “My brother, the timing of your reminder is too perfect. I do have something to discuss with you right now. I hope you can agree to it.”

Zhao Hai asked with incomprehension, “What’s the matter, brother Wales? If it’s something I can do, I will do my best to help.”

Wales looked at Zhao Hai with a stern expression, “My brother Zhao Hai, I wish to conduct a Beheading Blood Oath with you.”

Zhao Hai was startled and he looked at Wales with confusion. Laura and the others were also confused. Mendez and Yale looked at Wales with shock.

The Beheading Blood Oath was a very special oath among beastmen. This oath wasn’t made by 1 person, but 2. Using Earth’s words, it was called ‘bond swearing’.

Only, the beastmen treated this oath with even more importance, because once 2 people made this oath, they would be like born siblings. Neither one could betray the other, or there would be disdain from all of the beastmen. Even more severely, the betrayer would be hunted down.

The Beheading Blood Oath wasn’t something that required your own blood. It required the 2 people who were making the oath to cut down the head of an argali together at the same time, and then collect the goat’s blood with a bowl before drinking it simultaneously. None of the 2 would be able to betray the other. When the other was in trouble, one had to do their best to help. Even if it meant bankrupting the family fortune or shattering the body, there must be no regrets.

Do not assume that this blood oath would be done willy-nilly. According to the beastmen, this blood oath was done under the witness of Beast God. If someone broke the oath, they would receive punishment from Beast God.

As for the importance the beastmen placed on the Beheading Blood Oath, it could be seen that, even though the argali was just a level 1 magic beast, it was the most important magic beast for the beastmen. That was why they wouldn’t easily make this oath with others. Even with one of the same race, not to mention someone of another.

On the Beastmen Prairie, it had been a long time since it was last heard that someone had made the Beheading Blood Oath, and that was between 2 beastmen. A Beheading Blood Oath between a beastman and a human had never been heard of.

It was exactly because of this that humans had never heard of the beastmen’s Beheading Blood Oath, as not even their records would detail it. Because such an oath was absolutely meaningless to humans, Laura and the others had never heard of this oath.

Wales knew that Zhao Hai and the others had never heard of what the Beheading Blood Oath was about from the looks on their faces. He explained, “My brother, the Beheading Blood Oath is the most important oath us beastmen can swear. Once the oath is made, we become true brothers…” And then he explained the meaning and process of the oath to them.

Zhao Hai and the others listened to Wales quietly. The Beheading Blood Oath was a bloody oath. In reality, the weight of the oath might be heavier than the beheading.

Beheading was simple. Countless people would be decapitated in a single battle, but very few people would stake their own lives to help their own friends when in trouble. The weight of the oath could be seen from this.

Zhao Hai went silent for a long while after Wales finished explaining. He understood that the Beheading Blood Oath was equal to Earth’s bond swearing, like ‘the oath of the peach garden’.

If there was a country on Earth that saw the most importance in oaths like these, it would be China for sure. Not the modern China. It was ancient China.

The oath of the three men in the peach garden was fabled to this day, which surely had its own logic to it. Perhaps only that oath could compare to the beastmen’s Beheading Blood Oath.

The oath which the beastmen put so much emphasis on made Zhao Hai feel very bewildered. He didn’t know what to do, because he really didn’t want to enter a conflict between beastmen. But if he really became brothers with Wales, sworn by blood, then he wouldn’t be able to avoid doing so. This went against his original intentions.

Laura and the others didn’t speak either. This situation made them feel awkward as well. If Zhao Hai didn’t agree, the cooperation between them and Wales would be hard to progress. But if he agreed, they would have to involve themselves in the succession conflict. This wasn’t a good thing to them.

Zhao Hai raised his head, only to find that Wales was staring at him with very sincere eyes. This made it even harder for Zhao Hai.

The relationship between Zhao Hai and Wales wasn’t even at the point of making such an oath, to be honest. But now that Wales suggested it, if Zhao Hai didn’t agree, it would be too hurtful to Wales.

Wales’ personality was different from his. Zhao Hai didn’t have any grand ambitions, while Wales did. He wasn’t proud, while Wales was. The 2 of them didn’t seem to have a lot in common, but circumstances had put the 2 of them together.

Zhao Hai suddenly wanted to laugh when he looked at Wales. Bond swearing? He never thought of such a thing before, even on Earth. He didn’t expect that a bull-headed person would seek to form a bond after he came to another world. This was too interesting.

Zhao Hai’s mood suddenly became better when he thought of this. If he really wanted to calculate, he wouldn’t have much of a loss either. If he swore with Wales, then he had to do his best to help Wales become the Herculean Bull Tribe’s chieftain. Even if he didn’t swear, wasn’t he helping Wales to become chieftain anyway? What was the difference between bonding and otherwise? Maybe it was just a formality.

Zhao Hai suddenly laughed loudly and stood up after an exhale, “Then what are we waiting for, my brother Wales!”

Wales let out a sigh of relief when he heard what Zhao Hai said. He laughed, “Good, my brother! I’ve been waiting for those words of yours! 6th brother, teacher, let’s make preparations.”

Mendez and Yale heeded with a sound, and walked out of the tent. They were still somewhat confused about Wales’ actions, but they didn’t object.

Actually, the rite didn’t need preparations. Beastmen didn’t have as many customs as humans did. For the beastmen, it was too troublesome to have so many customs, so they didn’t need them.

After Mendez and Yale walked out of the tent, Wales dragged Zhao Hai out of the tent as well. By the time Wales did so, Mendez and Yale had prepared the things. There wasn’t a lot to prepare, actually. Yale brought a bowl, Mendez pulled an argali over, and an escort brought a flying axe.

A flying axe was a small axe to the beastmen, but don’t forget that it weighed 10 kilos as well. For beastmen, who had great physical strength, it wouldn’t be a problem to decapitate the head of an argali.

With those 3 things, it was time for the rite to begin. Zhao Hai and Wales arrived next to the argali. It was a large one, so it was an adult. It was being pressed down to its knees by 2 escorts.

Wales turned to Zhao Hai and said, “My brother, according to the rules of the oath, we must both chop down its head at the same time. But from what I’m seeing, I don’t think you can lift an axe, can you?”

Zhao Hai made a bitter smile, “My brother, not only can I not lift an axe, I can’t even chop a goat’s head off. I think we should leave the head chopping to you, while I get the blood. How about that?”

Wales laughed candidly, “Alright, my brother! Let’s do that!” He then grabbed the flying axe with one hand, while Zhao Hai took the large bowl and stood next to the argali under Mendez’s instruction.

Zhao Hai had never taken a life this violently before, so he didn’t didn’t know how to catch the goat blood. Mendez had done it before, but had never done so during a Beheading Blood Oath.

Soon, they were all prepared. Wales shouted and swung the axe down toward the argali’s neck like a lightning strike. The flying axe was too sharp, and with Wales’ brute strength, it was like it met no resistance. Just a single chop was enough to cut the head of the argali clean off of its body.

The head flew far away because of the blood pressure, which caused the blood to spray out like a geyser. Mendez was indeed experienced, as the position which he had instructed Zhao Hai to stand at was enough for Zhao Hai to avoid the blood splattering. Not a single drop of blood fell on Zhao Hai as it happened.

Zhao Hai didn’t immediately collect the blood. Instead, he waited until the blood wasn’t spraying so fiercely. He then moved the bowl to fill it completely with goat blood.

Wales then handed the flying axe to his subordinate, while the 2 escorts who held down the argali moved it away as well. They were going to ‘process’ it immediately in order to eat it after a moment.

Just then, Wales walked to the bowl of goat blood which Zhao Hai had put on the ground. He and Zhao Hai knelt down together, and he spoke out loud, “Magnificent Beast God! Under your witness, I and Zhao Hai swear the Beheading Blood Oath! Starting from today, we are brothers tied by blood! If I violate this oath, I shall be trampled by 10000 beasts and become puree!”

Chapter 254: Gift

On Earth, oaths are like cold drinks. They don’t have the slightest sincerity. Especially for some people, who use oaths as a means to deceive others.

But it was different here on Ark Continent. Here, no one would make oaths inadvertently. Especially to the deities they worshipped.

Zhao Hai didn’t know if there really were deities on the continent, but he was sure about one thing; Oaths could not be made without thinking. Because he discovered that, once you made an oath, your heart would have a special feeling. It was like how Xu Wan Ying, who had sworn a blood oath, really wouldn’t be able to betray him after that. Just like that, Zhao Hai felt that he now had a special connection with Wales after the latter made his oath. It was a feeling of being bound by blood that was too vivid to be his imagination.

After saying something similar to what Wales had just said, Zhao Hai took the bowl of goat blood after Wales drank half of it in one gulp. Zhao Hai was somewhat squeamish at the sight of the blood, but he felt that his blood was heating up under the effects of the oath. He didn’t think any further and just gulped it down in one go.

An indescribable stench-filled taste filled his mouth, which almost made him vomit. But he still shut his eyes and let the blood go down to his stomach completely.

He put the bowl down after the final drop was finished, but he was clenched his mouth shut, fearing that he would puke as soon as he opened his mouth.

Wales wasn’t feeling too great, but he was a lot better at this than Zhao Hai. He looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Starting from today, we are brothers.” After that, he kowtowed with Zhao Hai. The 2 of them stood up after doing it 3 times.

Wales laughed loudly, “Since you are my brother from today onwards, let’s have you look at my 6th brother. Oh right, how old are you today?”

Zhao Hai did a double take and forced himself to swallow his saliva to hold back the stench in his mouth. He replied, “I’m 18 today. You?”

Wales laughed, “It seems like I’m gonna be the older brother. I’m 20 today.”

Zhao Hai immediately said, “Big brother.” Wales laughed and slapped Zhao Hai’s shoulder. Mendez came over just then with a small dagger in his hand. This dagger was a lot better than the one from Spiel. The grip and sheath were both golden and studded with gemstones. The whole thing looked both noble and foreign.

Mendez stood in front of Zhao Hai and handed over the dagger, “Little Hai, this is my gift to you.”

Zhao Hai noticed how Mendez had changed his way of addressing him. It seemed that Mendez really was treating him as a sibling. He didn’t hold back and took the glittering dagger. He bowed to Mendez, “Thank you, 6th brother.”

Mendez laughed, “Don’t be. You’re now already my younger brother. Where’s your gift, little 7th?”

Wales smiled, “Inside the tent.” He led the way for Zhao Hai inside the tent. After that, he grabbed a horse cane from the wall and put it in Zhao Hai’s hands, “Brother, this is my gift to you.”

Zhao Hai measured the horse cane, and what he could be sure of at first was that it was an antique, since it looked very ancient. Although it had been cleaned up nicely, Zhao Hai couldn’t deny the the scars of aging on its surface.

The cane wasn’t long. Only less than a metre long, and as thick as a thumb. The grip was made of a bone from an unknown magic beast, as dark as a black jade. Yet it wasn’t cold to the touch. Instead, there was a trace of warmth. The grip had some very intricate patterns etched upon it, and they didn’t seem to have been etched just to look ornate.

The cane body itself was made of tiny strands woven together. They weren’t normal threads, as Zhao Hai discovered that there were gold and silver-colored threads, as well as some black threads and threads of other colors. One thread on top of another, interwoven inside out; it made the cane heavy. Zhao Hai felt that it weighed at least several kilos in his hands. It seemed like it could be used directly as a weapon.

Where the cane and the grip met, there was a small leather strip acting as a guard. It wasn’t known which magic beast this strip had come from, and it wasn’t long. Only 10 centimetres long, and also very aged, which could be seen from its blackening. Despite that, it was still very sturdy.

Mendez and Yale were also looking at the cane while Zhao Hai was sizing it up. Their eyes held a trace of admiration.

Zhao Hai then saw their eyes. He felt weirded out by them and asked Wales, “Hey brother, what’s so special about this cane?”

Wales smiled, “This cane is a sort of a symbol of identity. It’s a treasure we the Herculean Bull Tribe happened upon, but one which no one knew how to use. In the end, it was passed down from one generation to the next. In every generation, the cane is passed down to the successor of the chieftain. Anyone who holds this cane has a certain summoning ability for all of the bull headed races. Holding this cane allows one to command 5000 of the bull headed race’s people.”

Zhao Hai then understood that it wasn’t just a cane. It was more like a commanding sigil. A cane that could command beastmen when held? This gift from Wales wasn’t cheap.

But Zhao Hai didn’t intend to return it to Wales. This wasn’t back when it was Laura and the others. He was in Beastmen Prairie right now, and he was facing beastmen. No need for formalities. If they gift you something, you just have to take it.

Yale also brought out something from his possessions just then. The item was a silver vial with very beautiful engravings. It wasn’t large, since it was only as large as Zhao Hai’s palm. For beastmen, it was simply too small.

Yale presented the vial to Zhao Hai and said, “Little Hai, this is my gift. When I was young, I had the opportunity to go to the Elven Forest once, where I got this vial. Don’t underestimate it though. Inside it is the Liquid Of Life: an especially precious thing for elves.”

Zhao Hai looked surprised at the silver vial. It wasn’t as though he’d never heard of the Liquid Of Life. On the contrary, he had heard of it more than once, because it was too famous on the continent.

The Liquid Of Life was a liquid secretion from the elves’ divine object: the Tree Of Life. The amount produced wasn’t high, but it had a very large effect.

The Liquid Of Life could restore stamina, battle aura and magic. It could even detoxify. It was an incomparably unique treasure, famous throughout the continent.

In the human lands, it was marketless and priceless, since it only existed in legends. No one had seen it and no one had bought it. If it weren’t for a witness of its usage, people would surely think of it as baseless fabrication.

Zhao Hai didn’t imagine Yale would give him a vial of that. To him, it was simply a precious thing. He bowed to Yale, “Thank you, Mr. Yale.”

Yale smiled without word, but Zhao Hai was a little embarrassed. Mendez’s gift aside, Yale and Wales’ gifts were extremely precious. If he didn’t gift them things in return, it would seriously be unacceptable to a degree.

Zhao Hai smiled as he thought of this. He tossed the 3 things gifted to him into the space and 3 spatial pouches appeared.

Zhao Hai put the 3 normal-looking pouches into their hands while smiling and said, “This is my gift to you. I hope you don’t find them dislikeable.”

The 3 of them glanced at the pouches. They neither opened them nor showed any reaction. They just tucked them away carefully.

Zhao Hai felt somewhat embarrassed about their looks. It wasn’t as if he wanted to test how they would react. If the 3 of them disliked his offerings, then even when he had just made the Beheading Blood Oath with Wales, he wouldn’t see him as a brother afterwards.

But obviously, he worried too much. Beastmen were indeed this simple. Even when Wales was such a calculative person, compared to humans, he would also be a simpleton.

In beastmen lands, relationships between brothers could not be measured with gifts. Even when you gave your brother a lot of gold, while your brother only gave you a blade of grass in return, you couldn’t be angry. Because you were brothers.

Zhao Hai scratched his head and said in embarrassment, “You all have to keep what I gave you well. Those are not ordinary pouches, but spatial pouches. Each has up to 10 cubic metres of capacity, and they don’t need any energy. Just loosen the rope of the pouch to use it.”

The 3 of them did a double take, and looked at each other. They quickly took out the pouches and opened them like they couldn’t wait for it.

An illusionary magic formation appeared on each pouch. Zhao Hai immediately explained, “Point the magic formation at the thing you want to keep, and think about it. That thing will automatically be put into the pouch. If you want to take it out, just open the pouch, think about what you want to take out, and you can bring it out.”

The 3 of them experimented for a bit, looked at their pouches with crazed grins, and then put their pouches away carefully, like they were the most precious things in their lives. They looked to be even more careful than if they were carving on eggshells.

Zhao Hai couldn’t help but laughing at them, “I’d say, you don’t need to be so careful. With that kind of quality, you can’t damage those pouches.”

Wales shot Zhao Hai a strange glance and said, “What do you know about being careful? What if they get broken?”

Zhao Hai snickered, “It’s alright if they do. I’ll just deliver some for you again.”

After Zhao Hai said that, the 3 of them stopped their movements and looked straight at Zhao Hai, who then asked with incomprehension, “What? What’s the matter?”

Wales yelled and pounced on Zhao Hai. Mendez pounced as well, while Yale wasn’t as fast as them so he just stood to the side and chuckled at the sight.

Wales sat on top of Zhao Hai while he kept on slapping him and asked, “You ask me ‘what’s the matter’? You actually dare to ask such a question, you brat? Don’t you know what’s the matter with you? Do you have a lot of spatial pouches? How come you’re not the slightest bit pained when you give them away?”

Mendez also didn’t let Zhao Hai off the hook. Like Wales, he was slapping Zhao Hai’s head around like a ball, which made Zhao Hai very dizzy.

The 2 of them stood up after a while, and Zhao Hai got up in the midst of dizziness. He looked at them with disdain, “I can’t believe you two. When I say I have a lot to give? Remember, I’m an Oddity Artist. Oddity. Artist. Understand?”

Wales did a double take, “Oddity Artist? Are you saying you are one yourself, my brother?”

Zhao Hai nodded at that.

Wales looked at Zhao Hai with a glimmer in his eyes, “Well I’ll be. Does your Oddity Art have something to do with the creation of these spatial pouches? What are you selling grains for? Just sell these instead.”

Zhao Hai looked at Wales unpleasantly, “Don’t bullshit me. I just said I’m an Oddity Artist. When did I say I can make these pouches? They were found by me in a cave, and there were only several of them. After giving them to Laura and 2 others, there are only these 3 left. My power as an Oddity Artist is the ability to turn corpses into undead creatures, and then put them into my space. Where else do you think those pouches and the grains are from?”

Wales and the 2 others nodded at Zhao Hai’s explanation. They had neither seen nor used spatial equipments before, but such an equipment wouldn’t be too great. If the storage space of each equipment were great, humans would’ve already circumvented the need to use horse-drawn wagons when fighting against beastmen by just transporting food to Iron Wall Fortress using spatial equipment instead. That way, the beastmen would not be able to break through the fortress.

There were Oddity Artists among both humans and beastmen. There were more than a few of them in beastmen lands, and likewise, they were very respected as a group. It was because their special abilities could help the beastmen tribes to a greater degree.

Wales asked Zhao Hai, “It’s great that you have such an endurance, brother. And I have to ask, can your space store argali and others of the sort?”

Zhao Hai was startled. He didn’t expect Wales to be this smart just from what Zhao Hai said himself. It was beyond his expectations.

Chapter 255: Plan

Zhao Hai nodded after a glance at Wales, “Sure. Why else would I want to exchange for so many magic beasts and argali? It takes a lot of time just to transport them to the human lands.”

Wales nodded, “That’s excellent, brother. With this capability, we no longer have to worry about grains. Come, let’s go and drink some mutton soup.” He was really happy that this brother he had just acknowledged was this capable.

Actually, Wales was selfish when he wanted to swear the Beheading Blood Oath with Zhao Hai. He aimed for the food in Zhao Hai’s possession, and had intended to use it to tie Zhao Hai to his war machine.

However, he had to admit that even he himself had underestimated the power of Beheading Blood Oath. It seemed to be able to alter someone’s thoughts and emotions as soon as the oath was made. It was that frightening.

It had been a very long time since people on the prairie had last sworn the Beheading Blood Oath. It was exactly because of this that Wales underestimated its power. In his view, if his own brother (Gasol) could betray him, then what effect would the oath have?

But he hadn’t expected that the oath would be very effective. If it weren’t, he wouldn’t have given the horse cane to Zhao Hai. It was a heirloom of the Herculean Bull Tribe, passed down from his father.

And it was because of Wales giving Zhao Hai the horse cane, that Yale gave him the Liquid Of Life. Otherwise, Yale wouldn’t have done so, knowing how hard it was to get such a treasure.

It was another rule of the Beheading Blood Oath that the argali used to conduct the rite must be eaten the same day, so the mutton soup was made using the one that was killed by Wales.

Now, Zhao Hai had a different identity, which was Wales’ blood-sworn brother. The escorts immediately saluted Zhao Hai with great respect in their expressions.

Zhao Hai nodded to them and then made his way to the pot of mutton soup.

Different from before, Wales let his people put the small tables closer together. They could get closer as they chatted.

Laura and the others were arranged to other small tables, now that their identity was different as well. To the escorts, Laura would now count as half a princess.

Laura and the others didn’t object to Zhao Hai swearing the Beheading Blood Oath with Wales, since Zhao Hai wouldn’t have much of a loss from it, and they all got Wales as a bonus. If this matter was settled, then no one would dare to act against them on the Beastmen Prairie.

After they all sat down, the escorts brought Wales some milk wine. Even though the escorts knew what had happened in the tribe, none of them betrayed him. For the beastmen, if they believed someone to be a person worth following, they wouldn’t resort to betrayal so easily, even when their relatives were still in the tribe.

To tell the truth, there was still a stench of blood in Wales’ mouth as he drank a mouthful of milk wine. He didn’t like it very much, but it was exciting, and it gave him a blood-boiling sensation. But he needed to think about things instead of being impulsive. He had to calm his emotions as quickly as possible.

Wales felt better after that mouthful of milk wine. He turned to Zhao Hai, “Brother, you have to help me come up with a good idea this time. What do I do if I want to drag Gasol down? It’s very bad for me now that he has control of the Herculean Bull Tribe.”

Zhao Hai didn’t have as many reservations right now. Whatever the case, he was now Wales’ blood-sworn brother. Helping Wales was a given.

Zhao Hai thought and said, “Big brother, I don’t know the situation in the tribe very well, so I can’t help you there. You still have to depend on yourself for that.”

Wales nodded, “Now that Gasol is in control, if we go there now, we might as well be going to die. So, we stick to what was discussed: find a branch tribe, get their support, and then return. I’m getting ready to find teacher’s Buffalo Tribe and the Fighting Bull Tribe. These two have high positions among the branch races, and they have a lot of influence.”

Yale agreed to that, but Zhao Hai frowned and said, “Big brother, I don’t think that’s right. You know that the Buffalo and Fighting Bull tribes have great influence, so doesn’t Gasol know that as well? Gasol wouldn’t stage a coup if not for a branch tribe’s support. Let’s not talk about other things first. Gasol should know crystal clear that Yale is your teacher. If 6th brother hasn’t been killed, Gasol will surely think that he’s found you. If you know what happened in the tribe, then Gasol would know as well. In such a situation, how can he not take extra measures? I think that there won’t be a positive outcome if we go to either the Buffalo Tribe or the Fighting Bull Tribe. Gasol might be waiting for you midway, just to kill us directly.”

Wales and the others were startled, as they hadn’t thought about this point. To put it directly, Wales appeared calm on the surface, but his mind was still blazing. Gasol had gone too far this time. The fact that he killed his own father and disregarded his own siblings was something that fueled the flames of Wales’ rage to burn outward from his heart.

That was why Wales wanted to topple Gasol from his the position in the shortest possible time. But Wales had forgotten about one thing. Could Gasol succeed just by using his own men? His father, a chieftain, the most powerful figure in the tribe, had been struck down in secret. It would have been impossible without someone behind Gasol.

Zhao Hai’s words calmed Wales down in the truest sense. Even though Wales was one of the few smart ones amongst beastmen, he had been blinded by hatred and rage. He was getting better now.

Wales took a deep breath and closed his eyes for a while. He nodded, “You are right, brother. I’ve always underestimated Gasol before, so I got into such a big trouble now. But I think this is strange. Gasol’s actions this time and his usual style are not the same. There has to be something behind it.”

Mendez suddenly spoke, “There’s something which I know, that I’m not sure if it’s related to this incident. A while before Gasol made his move, he was secretly dealing with some human merchants. You both know that whenever the tribe has to meet with human merchants, it’s always my job. But those human merchants were meeting with Gasol directly, and, they came and went in a hurry each time. Secretively.”

Wales was startled, and asked with a changed expression, “Are you saying that Gasol colluded with those human merchants and poisoned our father? He had such gall?”

Mendez made a wry smile, “Little 7th, you still haven’t grasped the situation then. Ever since father gave the horse cane to you, Gasol has gone insane. You know that the cane is only passed down to successors. Giving it to you meant that father acknowledged you as his heir. Gasol knew he had no hope, so how could he take the loss lying down? It’s not a strange thing for him to do anything at this point.”

Wales’ expression darkened and he sighed with nothing to say. Yale spoke, “This possibility is likely. If someone goaded Gasol from behind, then he might really have something planned. I think we can’t go looking for the Buffalo and Fighting Bull tribes now. Remember that the eldest princess and 4th princess are also in the Fighting Bull Tribe. If we go there, Gasol will be the first to know, even without prior placements.”

Yale had a point. Wales’ 4 sisters were all married to the Fighting Bull Tribe, but his oldest and 4th sister didn’t like him very much, and were closer to Gasol instead. If he went to the Fighting Bull Tribe, then his oldest sister would know and notify Gasol for sure. His plan would not be able to continue after that.

Wales let out a long breath, “Seems like I thought of things too simply. But no matter. The plan hasn’t been started yet. How about this: we find a small tribe first, and we proceed slowly. I don’t think Gasol is monitoring every tribe, is he?”

Mendez and Yale laughed at that. Gasol wouldn’t be that capable, of course. In fact, no ruling tribe could ever monitor all of their branch tribes. There was neither manpower nor a need to do so.

Zhao Hai laughed, “That’s good. But big brother, it’s best that you contact people you can trust in the tribe, and then let them investigate the merchants’ identities. See if this matter is related to them. If it is, then perhaps the discovery can become your weapon. They didn’t swear the Beheading Blood Oath, did they?”

Wales laughed a little and nodded, “I will make arrangements, but Gasol knows all of my subordinates. Sending them is equal to ordering them to their deaths. I’ll have to find a chance later. Oh right, little Hai. Let us send you to the Fighting Bull Tribe’s territory and have you conduct a trade with them, while I infiltrate and meet with 2nd sister. I’ll make things clear with her. Perhaps she might be of help.”

Zhao Hai nodded, “No problems there. As long as you’re not discovered, that is. But I think that the times ahead will not be peaceful. 6th brother making his way here isn’t something Gasol would not notice. I suggest you to be prepared.”

Wales nodded without a word. He just took the milk wine on his table and drank it entirely.

Chapter 256: Tool Spirit?

Beastmen couldn’t live without wine. To them, the most important thing was their mounts, the 2nd most important was their argali goats, and the 3rd most important was wine. No matter what the occasion may be, wine was ever present.

Winters in the prairie were cold. Even during summer, the nights wouldn’t be hot. They would be in trouble if they lacked wine while they had to herd every day, every year.

This was the day Wales and Zhao Hai swore the Beheading Blood Oath, so they drank quite an amount of wine. They discussed how to deal with Gasol during the process of drinking.

It was inadvisable to use force against Gasol, as he was now in control of the Herculean Bull Tribe. Herculean bulls were known for being one of the stronger races when it came to fighting power, so taking them head-on was tantamount to seeking their own deaths. Wales wouldn’t do that, because no matter what Gasol did, he was of the same race, and so were his followers. If Wales fought against Gasol the hard way, the ones suffering would be the herculean bulls. Wales hoped for the herculean bulls to become powerful, so he naturally wouldn’t do something that could harm himself and benefit others.

Although Zhao Hai could help Wales and the others come up with ideas, the ways in which he could help were limited. He lacked understanding when it came to their matters.

Zhao Hai’s group returned to their tent that afternoon. He didn’t drink too much wine, as he was now Wales’ brother. Being someone like family meant that there was a much more carefree treatment for each other.

Upon returning to his tent, Zhao Hai drank a large glassful of the space’s water. Every time he drank the space’s water after taking alcohol, he would sober up quickly without the discomfort that usually came after drinking. That was why drinking the space’s water after wine had become a habit of his.

Laura looked at Zhao Hai after he drank the water and asked, “Hai-bro, are you really going to help Wales become chieftain?”

Zhao Hai gave her a bitter smile, “What else can I do? I’m now his blood-sworn brother, so I can only help him as much as I can. I didn’t think that he would want to become my blood-sworn brother. The oath is very special too. Just like Xu Wan Ying’s blood oath. If you make the oath, there will be a sensation.”

Laura nodded, “We can tell from the name itself. Helping Wales with all our power isn’t anything much. If he succeeds, we’ll have easier days on Beastmen Prairie. But what Mendez mentioned…. What was up with the human merchants making contact with Gasol?”

Zhao Hai shook his head, “I have no idea either. Human merchants don’t usually mix themselves into the conflict between beastmen, because if that were made known to other beastmen tribes, they would never be able to set foot on the prairie. But why did they make contact with Gasol? Could it really be that they helped fueling Gasol’s actions? Which power did they belong to?”

Laura frowned as well, “Humans who set foot on Beastmen Prairie mostly don’t look into who’s from which power, because that will easily cause misunderstandings. But now that you’re Wales’ blood-sworn brother, if we defeat Gasol, we can then check out which power those merchants belonged to. Even if we can’t investigate for the time being, we can let Wales do it. Your identity is useful here.”

Zhao Hai smiled, “It looks like there are many benefits to becoming Wales’ brother. Oh right. Let’s go into the space and check out their gifts. I have a feeling that those gifts are very special.”

Laura and the others laughed at that. The 4 of them appeared in the space instantly. The gifts were inside the storage, so there was no reaction from the space.

As soon as they appeared, Cai-Er flew over immediately and sat on Zhao Hai’s shoulder, “Young master, Ah-Wen is so mean. She won’t even play with me.”

Zhao Wen also flew over, and rested on top of Zhao Hai’s head without moving or making a sound. Zhao Hai looked at Cai-Er and asked in annoyance, “Cai-Er, did you play tricks on Ah-Wen again?”

Cai-Er was very naughty, while Ah-Wen was too honest, which was the reason for Cai-Er picking on her. But Ah-Wen was good tempered and didn’t get angry in the slightest. At most, she would just ignore Cai-Er for a period of time.

Zhao Hai noticed something strange. Before Cai-Er entered the space, she was very prone to sleep, but that changed after entering the space. Not only did she not sleep, she was hyper every day as well.

Cai-Er giggled and didn’t say anything to Zhao Hai’s question. He shook his head as he couldn’t do anything about her. He simply asked, “Is everything alright at the Messystone Hill resort?”

Zhao Hai and the others had left the place, but Cai-Er left a branch behind. It was hidden inside the white fruit tree in the resort’s garden. Normal people couldn’t see it.

The branch was for monitoring Greenstone Hill resort, since they were still cooperating with the Fansile family, who would periodically obtain some Peachland products.

Cai-Er replied to Zhao Hai’s questioning, “There are quite a lot of people that have been monitoring the place for a long time, and they haven’t left. Some snuck into Messystone Hill, but they haven’t discovered anything yet.”

Zhao Hai nodded, “Be careful not to let them find something out. If they are being too forceful, then turn them into flower manure.”

Cai-Er heeded his words with a sound. Zhao Hai asked, “What about Iron Mountain Castle? Is it alright?”

Cai-Er laughed, “Great! Iron Mountain Castle is fine, and the 2 argali are being kept well. They eat magic radish leaves as well, and even eat MY leaves. Hmph.”

Zhao Hai chuckled, and then Mendez’s gift, the dagger, appeared in his hand. Zhao Hai unsheathed the dagger and found the blade to be very beautiful and eye-piercing. He touched it gently and found it to be cool to the touch. It wasn’t to say that the material of the dagger was cold, but the sensation from its sharpness could make people shiver.

The dagger had cloud-like patterns. They weren’t painted or etched. They were formed after using a special method in the forging process. The patterns could only appear after layering the metal multiple times with a special method.

Laura took the dagger from Zhao Hai and took a closer look. She nodded, “This should be a dwarven master blacksmith’s work. This cloud-patterned dagger is very precious and rarely seen on the continent.”

Zhao Hai was obviously not as in-the-know as Laura in this regard, so he just nodded and put the dagger away in the storage. No matter how good it was, it wouldn’t be very useful to him right now.

After storing the dagger, Zhao Hai took out the cane. The moment it appeared, the notification voice in the space came, <Spirit tool discovered. Examining spirit tool. Tool spirit discovered within, but has weak strength. Increasing tool spirit strength. Tool spirit is a herding-type spirit, which can manage the ranch for Host. Has a deterrent effect on animals. Extracting tool spirit abilities. Adding them to Evil Spirit Sceptre. Host can now have a deterrent effect on animals when using Evil Spirit Sceptre.>

As soon as the notification voice stopped, Zhao Hai felt the cane shaking in his hand, and then a virtual figure of a person appeared above the cane. The virtual figure looked like a 7 or 8-year-old child, wearing 5-colored clothes.

The figure wasn’t very large, as it was about the size of the cane itself. The cane itself was standing in front of Zhao Hai, which made him feel very bizarre.

The virtual figure bowed and said, “Greetings to young master.”

Zhao Hai was used to this kind of situation. He knew it had to be yet another creation of the space. He didn’t mind and just nodded, “Let’s call you Mu-Er from now on. Follow me. I’ll show you to where the ranch is.” Mu-Er obeyed with a sound, and then climbed onto Zhao Hai’s hip like a snake without further movements.

Cai-Er flew down from Zhao Hai’s shoulder and looked at this virtual figure with curiosity. She wanted to touch Mu-Er, but Mu-Er dodged. The more Cai-Er tried, the more Mu-Er resisted. Both of them went in circles around Zhao Hai.

Laura and the others laughed at the 2 of them. They were now basically immune to the abilities of the space. Zhao Hai was happy to have gotten this amazing cane.

Zhao Hai said nothing about Cai-Er and Mu-Er playing around. It didn’t take long for his head to light up as Zhao Wen joined in the fun. Zhao Hai shook his head with a bitter smile, and the vial containing the Liquid Of Life soon appeared in his hand.

The notification voice came again, <High grade water discovered. Examining water. The water contains large amounts of active components. Can rapidly restore people’s stamina, magic power, and battle aura, can be mixed into medicines, detoxify, heal injuries, and irrigate. Plants that have been dead for less than a month can be revived using this water. Extracting the components in the water. Adding them to the water spring. Water spring levelled up.>

Zhao Hai did a double take. He didn’t imagine that the Liquid Of Life could have so many good points about it. Just the part about reviving dead plants was too awesome. Later on, he could get some dead special plants and revive them using the space’s water. He would no longer need to worry about the lack of plants in the space. There was a bit of a time limit, but it was good enough.

Most importantly, since the Liquid Of Life was now fused with the space’s water spring, he would have an endless source of it from now on.

Chapter 257: Changes Of Iron Mountain Castle

The Liquid Of Life was very famous on the continent. If people knew Zhao Hai had an undepletable source of it, he would surely attract a lot of envy.

But what Zhao Hai couldn’t understand the most, was that he had never heard of anyone using the Liquid Of Life to revive any plants. Could it be that the space caused the Liquid Of Life to mutate?

The vial which Yale had given Zhao Hai was only as large as his palm. The neck was rectangular, like one of those liquor flasks he had seen before on Earth. The vial was full of engravings, which made it look very beautiful.

Laura looked at the vial and said, “This vial looks like a product of the elves. Elves love nature deeply and they have high standards regarding art. Every work of art must be made above what ‘great’ could be used to describe, and most of them are based on the mark of nature. See those engravings? Do they look like vines? Every leaf was etched so intricately that you can see the webs. There’s even a special magic formation exclusive to elves on the vial, but I don’t know what it does.”

Zhao Hai looked at the engravings carefully. They were indeed special, but he didn’t know about the magic formation part. The space didn’t notify him about it, so it didn’t seem like it was really a magic formation.

Zhao Hai liked the vial a lot. He shook it lightly and noticed that there was still half of the Liquid Of Life left. It was no longer rare to him now, so he drank it all down and smacked his lips.

The Liquid Of Life wasn’t flavorless like ordinary water. There was a very special taste. How to put it? The taste was a bit like being in the woods in the middle of a growth spurt during spring. Refreshing and natural.

Zhao Hai nodded, “Not a bad taste. All of you should have a taste. Directly from the spring, that is.”

Laura and the others laughed at that before they tried the spring water. Such a refreshing taste was very suitable for ladies.

Zhao Hai brought them to the ranch. Cai-Er couldn’t manage the ranch since she was a plant fairy, so Zhao Hai had to manage much of the ranch’s matters himself. It was good that Mu-Er had joined in right now. He could now leave matters for Mu-Er to manage.

Zhao Hai let Mu-Er get familiar with the surroundings before managing the ranch. Actually, it was excessive to do so. He didn’t know that the reason why Mu-Er appeared was because the cane was special.

The body of the cane was made of refined gold, mithril, and several other high class magic beast tendons, while the grip of the cane was made of a soul bone.

Soul bones were rare on the continent, so it could be said that only a handful of people knew about them. Someone happened upon the soul bone used in the creation of this cane. That someone only felt that the bone was very special and sturdy, so he made it the grip of the cane.

What they didn’t know was that the soul bone had a special ability, which was to seal souls. Sealing souls meant that the soul of a deceased person could be sealed into the bone, which would ensure that the soul would not disappear. At the right opportunity, when a suitable vessel was found, the soul could be extracted from the bone and put into body, and that person would be regarded as revived.

However, there was no such magic to do so on Ark Continent. Because there were no magic beasts that could produce soul bones, no one knew about them in the slightest.

Actually speaking, soul bones had another ability, which was to gain sentience on their own, little by little. But the sentience could not be called a soul, because it would be too weak.

To the space, however, a soul bone would be like a blank computer. Just add some programs into it, and the computer would function normally. It was also because of the space’s alterations that Mu-Er appeared.

Because Mu-Er was created by the space, all information related to the ranch had been inputted directly into Mu-er, which was beyond Zhao Hai’s knowledge. There was no need for familiarization.

Although Cai-Er couldn’t manage the ranch, Mu-Er couldn’t manage the farm, and Zhao Wen couldn’t intervene in neither. But the 3 of them could freely come and go between these 2 places. Especially the lively Cai-Er who kept following and teasing Mu-Er, like a child who had found a new toy.

After sorting out the matters in the ranch, Zhao Hai and the others returned to Iron Mountain Castle. Greene was there at the moment. Unless there was anything important, Greene and the others wouldn’t come into the space. Even Crune had set up a laboratory in the castle.

Humans are social animals, after all. They need to communicate with others. Greene and Kun Zheng were of similar age and experiences, so the 2 of them got along well. Since there hadn’t been an issue on the Beastmen Prairie, the 2 of them were cooped up in Iron Mountain Castle, which let them learn more about the surrounding environment, in order to prepare the place to become the most important and integral base in a better way.

The 2 sagacious old men knew clearly, that no matter where Zhao Hai and the others went, the Black Wastelands was their roots, and the foundation of Buda family’s development.

The space could provide them with assistance, but if Zhao Hai were gone, then what would Buda family depend on? It could only be the Black Wastelands.

Upon reaching the castle, Zhao Hai and the others noticed that Greene and Kun Zheng were absent. Even Maylin was gone. They learned from Blockhead that the 3 elders had gone to the underground lake.

They then went to the underground lake in the mountain, but they didn’t find the elders. Zhao Hai didn’t become anxious. The Black Wastelands was very safe at the moment, so nothing could’ve happened. It was possible that they had simply gone somewhere else.

Zhao Hai and the others returned to the castle’s surroundings. The rice milling factory was operating normally, and so was the oil squashing factory. The blue-eyed rabbits had been raised well, while the 2 argali were in top condition with no signs of sickness. Everything was in working order.

Although it had become colder outside the castle, there was no drop in the temperature inside. The temperature inside the castle was higher because of Cai-Er’s rainbow flowers.

Due to the climate, the improved soil outside could not be planted, and the corn in the valley had been harvested. However, Zhao Hai had a new idea. He let Cai-Er leave a branch in the valley, so that the temperature there would rise and the land there could be planted again.

The castle was bustling right now, as there was another couple who got married. Of course, as with before, Zhao Hai held a marriage ceremony for them and gave them a marriage certificate, while also restoring their commoner statuses.

Zhao Hai didn’t want the slaves to remain as slaves forever. A force could not be sustained with slaves alone, so Zhao Hai didn’t mind turning the slaves into civilians.

Zhao Hai wasn’t worried that the slaves would leave after gaining civilian identities. They couldn’t leave because of their brands. No one would acknowledge their civilian identities outside of the Black Wastelands. They would even be captured as runaway slaves.

The slaves were very satisfied, not only because Zhao Hai had given them civilian statuses, but also because he had given them lands and houses. Helping Zhao Hai do things gave them money to spend. While it was a given that they now had to use money when they ate food and vegetables, the prices were low. They could totally save up some money to buy necessities and what they liked.

Now, in Iron Mountain Castle, the first shop had been set up: the Lycoris Free Market. There was only one person keeping watch, and that was Ju.

This market was designed by Zhao Hai according to supermarkets on Earth. Every day, Blockhead and Rockhead would let some slaves replenish the stocks, while only Ju alone would keep watch during regular hours. Whether they were slaves or civilians, anyone could come and buy things, with identical prices of course. Ju only received payment at the entrance, so everyone bought what they liked and made payments to Ju.

Laura had never heard of such a shop before. She thought that this was totally a chance to have things stolen, but Zhao Hai went ahead with it. What surprised her was that nothing had been stolen since the opening of the market. Not even a single needle was reported to be lost.

It wasn’t just Laura who was surprised. Zhao Hai was even more surprised. He didn’t expect that the slaves, who had become civilians for only a short time, would have such a resolve.

What he didn’t know was that it was exactly because the slaves had been paid money and given civilian identities that they wouldn’t steal things. To them, being able to buy things like normal people was a happiness as well. They didn’t have a chance to do so before. Now that they had it, of course they wouldn’t let it go.

Zhao Hai didn’t build this market in order to earn money. He hoped that the civilians of his fief could lead ordinary lives. Buying and selling things was what an ordinary person could do. He didn’t want the people of his fief leading slave lives despite having civilian identities.

Iron Mountain Castle looked like a real castle right now. The slaves who worked their shifts in the rice milling and oil squashing factories would go shopping around different parts of the castle after work, or chatting around together. Their lives were carefree.

Zhao Hai was very satisfied with the current situation of the castle. He knew that changes had to come in little by little. It would have been impossible to do this when he had first arrived, but now it had all fallen into place.

Zhao Hai and the others sat in the living room of the castle. Laura looked around and smiled, “To be honest, I still like it here, because it feels like home here.”

Zhao Hai laughed, “Of course. you set up everything here by yourself. Of course it feels like home to you, hehe… What are granpa Kun Zheng and the others doing?”

Laura laughed, “It’s alright. If they said they went to the lake in the mountain, they must be there. I think that they must’ve gone to see how long it is, and where its source is. They must be trying to figure this land out.”

Zhao Hai nodded, “I heard that they want to draw a map, detailing the course of the mountain, its terrain, and everything around us. This is our home, so we should have a proper understanding of it.”

Just then, Kun Zheng’s voice came from outside. Zhao Hai and the others stood up immediately before Kun Zheng, Greene and Maylin came in. The 3 of them were startled, and then Greene asked with a smile, “Back this early today? What happened?”

Zhao Hai shook his head, “Nah. Nothing at all. We just finished our matters earlier, so we came back.”

After they all sat down, Laura described what happened during these past few days to Greene, Kun Zheng and Maylin, who listened quietly. They never thought that so many things happened on the prairie in such a short time.

Once Laura finished, Greene spoke with a frown, “Young master, you really swore the Beheading Blood Oath with that Wales? Wasn’t that too brash?”

Zhao Hai gave a bitter smile, “It couldn’t be helped. If I didn’t agree to it, then the cooperation with Wales would’ve fallen through. Currently, almost all the large tribes have their own long-term cooperating merchants, so we can’t interfere. If we gave up this chance, we don’t know when our business on the prairie will succeed, so I decided to gamble.”

Kun Zheng agreed with what Zhao Hai had done. He nodded, “I think little Hai did the right thing. The Herculean Bull Tribe has quite a high standing on the prairie. Common battle tribes wouldn’t be unreasonable with them. Even the highly-ranked battle tribes will give the herculean bulls some face. If we can form ties with them, it will be good for our business on the prairie. I’ve heard of this Beheading Blood Oath before. It’s one of the most important oaths to the beastmen. If Wales dared to swear this oath, it means he doesn’t have wicked intentions towards little Hai. This is enough.”

Zhao Hai nodded. Just when he was about to say something, his expression changed, “We have to go back. Just now, the undead saw that the blood hawk has returned. Something might’ve happened.” After bidding farewell to Greene, Kun Zheng and Maylin, he led Laura and the others back to the campsite on the prairie.

Chapter 258: A Fighting Chance

Zhao Hai and the others left the tent as soon as they appeared inside. A blood hawk was circling in the sky.

Zhao Hai noticed the blood hawk’s movements and spoke, “There are people coming this way. 2000 in number, mostly bull-headed cavalry. Oh? They seem to have aerial recon troops as well?”

Laura and the others were stunned, and then looked at Zhao Hai with incomprehension. Zhao Hai laughed, “The blood hawk discovered that there are 2 flying hawks that seem to be helping the cavalry. I’ll go and inform big brother. You should make preparations as well.” Laura and the others nodded at that, while Zhao Hai ran towards Wales’ campsite.

Wales and his people were resting, and the sky was getting dark. They couldn’t rush ahead at night, so they had gone back into their tents to rest.

Even though didn’t drink a lot this day, they were somewhat drunk due to their bad mood. It’s easy to get drunk when drinking during a bad mood.

Wales was in a bit of a blur. There hadn’t been any battle, but he felt exhausted. It was an exhaustion of the heart. It only took a bit of alcohol for him to fall asleep on the bed.

But Wales wasn’t sleeping soundly. He was having a nightmare. It was a nightmare about his own father wanting him to take revenge. Soon, he dreamt about Gasol who was trying to hunt him down.

Just then, Zhao Hai arrived at the campsite. The escorts standing guard didn’t get in his way, and saluted him instead. Zhao Hai’s current identity was Wales’ blood-sworn brother.

Zhao Hai soon arrived outside of Wales’ tent, which was guarded by only one person. This person wasn’t actually guarding Wales, but was ready to relay Wales’ orders when necessary.

That person immediately saluted Zhao Hai. Zhao Hai nodded, but he didn’t enter the tent. He asked, “What’s big brother doing?”

The escort answered, “Young lord is resting.”

Zhao Hai nodded, “Go and wake big brother up. I have an important thing to say, so hurry. You must wake him up no matter what.” When the escort saw how serious Zhao Hai’s expression was, he ran into the tent without delay.

Just then, Mendez and Yale came out of their tents after hearing Zhao Hai’s words. They didn’t sleep as deeply as Wales.

Yale’s expression changed as he saw how serious Zhao Hai’s face had become. He stood in front of him and asked, “Little Hai, what’s wrong? Did something happen? Was it the grains?” What Yale cared about right now was the grains, so he assumed that something had happened to them.

Mendez tensed up when Yale asked the question. He knew how important the grains in Zhao Hai’s possession were to them.

Zhao Hai shook his head, “No. It’s something else.” After he finished, Wales spoke out, “Little Hai, what’s the matter? Come inside.” Zhao Hai entered the tent with Yale and Mendez following behind.

Wales had just gotten up, and was drinking water. He felt his head hurting. Zhao Hai got in front of him hurriedly and said, “Big brother, there are enemies coming. They number 2000. All of them are bull-headed cavalry.”

Wales and the others were stunned, and they looked at Zhao Hai in confusion. Zhao Hai knew from their looks that they must be wondering how he had gotten such information. Zhao Hai added, “How could you forget, big brother? I have a phantasmal hawk. It can perform aerial reconnaissance. The enemies aren’t just 2000 strong. There are also 2 flying magic beasts providing reconnaissance for them. If not for my phantasmal hawk, we could’ve been the ones being discovered first.”

Wales’ expression changed after hearing Zhao Hai’s words. He asked, “You said that the enemies have 2 flying magic beasts?” Zhao Hai nodded at that. Wales’ expression darkened, “They’ve come. It looks like they are following 6th brother.”

Mendez’s expression darkened as well, “I underestimated Gasol. It seems that he really has a capable party backing him up. Otherwise, there wouldn’t be such movement.”

Zhao Hai looked at them with incomprehension. Yale saw the doubt on Zhao Hai’s face and spoke calmly, “Everyone on the prairie knows that Gasol raises 2 flying magic beasts. He has been raising those magic beasts for a long time, and they can provide reconnaissance for him and track his enemies. He accomplished a lot of battle merits for the tribe using these 2 magic beasts.”

Zhao Hai nodded, and then spoke to Wales, “Don’t worry, big brother. I will let my phantasmal beasts go ahead and cripple those 2 magic beasts.”

Wales shook his head, “Don’t, little Hai. Your phantasmal beasts are not a match for them. Those 2 are offshoot magic beasts: flame birds. Their strength can match level 5 magic beasts.”

Zhao Hai smiled and walked out of the tent. Once he did, he shouted, and 5 blood hawks came down from the sky shortly after that. Actually, these blood hawks were let out of the space in secret. He was just pretending to call out for them in order to avoid arousing the suspicion of Wales and the others.

Zhao Hai made a gesture to the blood hawks in the sky, and with a sharp cry, they flew away into the distance. They disappeared into the sky in just the blink of an eye.

Zhao Hai turned to Wales and the others and said, “Relax, big brother. They will come back after a while, and my order was, ‘I want them alive’.”

Wales looked at Zhao Hai with shock, “I’ll say, my brother. You actually want them alive? Do you know how hard that will be? They are level 5 magic beasts.”

Zhao Hai laughed, “Perfect. It’s the first time I’ve come across flame birds. I’ll capture them in order to let my senior back home study them, hehe. How about we roast one?”

Wales snickered and then shook his head, “Brother, now I really don’t know anything about this. Are you really that confident?”

Mendez and Yale were looking at Zhao Hai as well. They knew that phantasmal beasts weren’t usually as highly regarded as magic beasts on the continent. It was common knowledge that phantasmal beasts couldn’t win against magic beasts. Zhao Hai being so confident, despite having sent only 5 phantasmal beasts to deal with 2 magic beasts, was something that surpassed their imaginations.

Zhao Hai simply smiled at them, “Don’t worry about them. Let’s think about how to deal with the 2000 people. They’ll be here in about 2 hours. Are we leaving, or are we fighting?”

Wales went idle for a bit, and then said, “2 hours…. Even if we run, they might catch up to us. We can only fight, but we only have 400 people.”

Mendez spoke with a sunken expression, “How about this, little 7th? Leave here while taking 100 escorts. I will stall them here for as long as it takes. Go and hide in some other tribe’s turf for a while, and contact other branch tribes to come up with a way to deal with Gasol.”

Wales looked at Mendez. He knew that Mendez was trying to sacrifice himself in order to help him. Wales was truly moved by what Mendez was suggesting, but he couldn’t let Mendez do it.

Yale agreed with Mendez’s decision. Mendez didn’t have as high of a calling as Wales in the tribe. Wales could deal with Gasol because he had been a chieftain candidate, while Mendez had not.

From this situation, letting Wales leave meant preserving a hope of having revenge. If Wales remained, then he might die here as well, and then there would be no hope left.

Zhao Hai didn’t know what to say when he looked at how the 3 of them were acting like they were about to be separated by life and death. He just scratched his head and said, “I don’t want to break up this mood, but I am compelled to say that we seem to have a fighting chance.”

Wales, Mendez and Yale were looking blankly at Zhao Hai, who then said, “When I say a fighting chance, I mean the 400 escorts in the camp with my undead creatures added into the mix. We should be able to halt Gasol’s advance.”

The 3 of them immediately thought about Zhao Hai’s undead creatures, which were amazingly strong. They dealt with the jackals as easily as if they had been chopping vegetables and splitting melons.

Zhao Hai added, “I now have about 4000 undead creatures. We shouldn’t have a problem defending ourselves if we add them to your escorts.”

Zhao Hai actually had more than 5000 undead creatures. They were comprised of the magic beasts from the Black Wastelands, humanoids that had joined afterwards, and the jackals from the prairie.

Wales did a double take, and then his eyes sparkled, “You really have 4000 undead creatures, brother? What about their fighting power?”

Zhao Hai smiled, “So-so. About the same level as a level 9 human fighter.”

Wales and the others couldn’t help from taking in a breath of cold air. What sort of concept was that? The undead might even be harder to deal with compared to 4000 human level 9 fighters, because undead felt no fear, were unafraid of injury or death, and would never retreat.

Wales suddenly laughed and hugged Zhao Hai, “Hahaha, I didn’t expect that you would have such great power, my brother. Excellent. We will wait for them here. I want to see if Gasol is coming here himself.”

Chapter 259: Move Forward, And Move Forward Again

Yale and Mendez were smiling. They felt that Wales’ blood-sworn brother was too valuable. Not only did he have so many grains, he had a lot of fighting power as well.

Wales let go of Zhao Hai and said, “You are now my blood-sworn brother. No one will be able to say anything no matter how you help me, hahahaha. Just relax and help your big brother take back the chieftain’s seat.”

Zhao Hai laughed, “I really hope that we’re not going to fight. If we fight so hard now, the ones to die will still be people of the Herculean Bull Tribe. If there are too many casualties, other races might have a chance to take over.”

The smile on Wales’ face disappeared. He nodded, “It’s because of such considerations that I had never clashed against Gasol. I didn’t expect that he would go this far. He’s too ruthless.”

Zhao Hai nodded as he felt bummed out. Gasol had gone off the deep end this time as he killed his own father. Even though Zhao Hai had heard about such things many times before, he had not expected that such a thing would happen so close to him. If he had to put his feelings into words, they would be, ‘What a ballbuster’.

Mendez patted Zhao Hai’s shoulder, “Alright, don’t think too much. If Gasol really colluded with those human merchants to harm father, then he has no right to be the chieftain.”

Zhao Hai nodded, “Then let’s go prepare ourselves. I think my blood hawks are about to come back.” Right after that, 2 cries came from the sky. Zhao Hai and the others raised their heads to see that 5 blood hawks were flying back slowly. 4 of them were holding a couple of flying magic beasts, which were obviously not dead. They were struggling, but they could not get out of the blood hawks’ claws.

Wales didn’t expect that Zhao Hai’s phantasmal beasts would capture the flame birds so quickly, while Zhao Hai himself wasn’t surprised. It was 5 against 2. If the flame birds couldn’t be captured, he would surely make a stew out of the blood hawks afterwards.

Zhao Hai made a gesture, and the 5 blood hawks came down from the sky. When they did, Wales, Yale and Mendez discovered something strange.

These 5 blood hawks were 2 metres tall, each of them imposing and overwhelming. Phantasmal? More like ‘even more magical than magic beasts’.

The 2 large birds under the blood hawks’ feet weren’t as large, but they weren’t small either, more than 1 metre tall, with a wingspan of 5 meters. Their tail feathers were very long, especially the middle 3. Each was about 3 metres long, and a fiery red color. Very beautiful.

These 2 birds weren’t red, but pale blue in color. There were small feathers on their heads like crowns. Their bodies weren’t as stout as the blood hawks’, but they were linear and smooth. They would give off the feeling of an arrow that had been loosed should they fly into the sky.

The 2 flame birds were injured. A good deal of their feathers had been clawed out, and their wings had bloodstains. It was evident that the blood hawks didn’t held back. Zhao Hai ordered them to bring the flame bids back alive, but he didn’t say not to injure them.

Zhao Hai looked at the 2 birds curiously. He knew from the blood hawks that these 2 were very fast and had extremely powerful fighting ability. They weren’t fire type magic beasts, but wind-fire double type magic beasts, fast and strong. Zhao Hai would not have been able to bring them in if he hadn’t sent 5 blood hawks.

Zhao Hai asked Wales, “Big brother, are these the birds?”

Wales knew what Zhao Hai meant, but he was still captivated by the 5 awesome blood hawks. How did they resemble phantasmal beasts? If phantasmal beasts were all this powerful, then magic beasts should’ve already retired from the stage.

Wales lowered his head and glanced at the flame birds. They were indeed the 2 birds that had been raised by Gasol. Gasol showered these flame birds with tender loving care. He would feed them by himself every day while forbidding others from doing so. If anyone were to touch them, he would be enraged immediately. However, he would sometimes let the 2 birds show off in front of others, which made others gnash their teeth in anger.

Now, these 2 birds were on the ground like diseased little birds. Wales felt like he wanted to burst into laughter. These birds, which were said to be Gasol’s most prominent assistants in accomplishing merits, had now been crippled by Zhao Hai without hassle. He was happier than anyone else.

Wales nodded, “Indeed. These are the 2. Well done, fella. You actually got them back alive. I have to ask, you’re not seriously going to roast one, are you?”

Zhao Hai and Mendez laughed out loud at that. Zhao Hai replied, “How could I bear it? Maybe later. When I raise some more, we will roast 10 of them. Eat 5, toss 5. Hahahaha.”

Everyone laughed before Zhao Hai ‘took in’ the flame birds. He then said, “Big brother, I’m giving you these 5 blood hawks. From now on, they will be your aerial recon.”

Wales was taken aback. He admired the blood hawks greatly, but he didn’t want them. In his view, these capable blood hawks would be of greater help to Zhao Hai. Wales refused, “Please don’t, brother. Keep them yourself. They’re more useful to you.”

Zhao Hai laughed, “Don’t worry, big brother. I can raise some more, and my phantasmal beasts are different from the others. My phantasmal beasts can be like magic beasts and hunt on their own. You can also feed them some mutton or beef, just like feeding magic beasts. No need to worry about them a lot.”

Wales did a double take, “My brother, are these magic beasts or what? How can they be fed this way? No wonder they’ve grown so strong.” Zhao Hai laughed at that statement. Sometimes, beastmen were weird. When they saw a person, they would first see if a person looked strong. The stronger they were in appearance, the more the beastmen thought them to be capable. The same was applied to magic beasts.

Zhao Hai spoke to the 5 blood hawks, “Go and meet your master. That is my big brother. Listen to him.” The blood hawks nodded and then walked behind Wales step by step. Wales was shocked by such a display.

Wales looked at the blood hawks behind him, and murmured, “Are all phantasmal beasts this smart?” Mendez and Yale were speechless as well. If they had to be honest, they had never seen anyone using phantasmal beasts.

Zhao Hai giggled, “Don’t sweat the small stuff, big brother. Go and make preparations. Those people are coming. What are you going to do? Fight against them head-on?”

Wales regained his composure from Zhao Hai’s words. He said, “You’re right, brother. I intend to go head-to-head with them. Beastmen are different from humans, brother. They despise cowards. If I don’t face Gasol today, I will lose the right to contend with him in the future.”

Zhao Hai nodded, “Very well then. If he wants to fight, then we give him a fight. I will now call out all of my undead creatures to bolster your troops. It would be best not to start a major battle, however. Otherwise, the losses to the Herculean Bull Tribe will be too great.”

Wales knew what Zhao Hai meant. Zhao Hai intended to use this method to deter Gasol to stop the latter’s rash movements. Otherwise, they would not show mercy.

Wales didn’t want to fight either. If they fought, it would be the strength of the Herculean Bull Tribe which would suffer. It was the outcome Wales disliked the most.

Wales nodded, “You are right, my brother. Unleash your undead army, and let my brother witness it.”

Zhao Hai laughed as he waved his hand. A giant horde of undead creatures appeared from the space. However, Zhao Hai didn’t let all of his undead out. He just released the jackals, Zhao Zui’s group, Garan and the mercenaries, plus Carlo and his subordinates, Orloga and the others. And then there were the beasts captured from the Black Wastelands. This had already exceeded 4000 in number. Zhao Hai didn’t mobilize the ones from the Church Of Light who attacked them.

But such a deployment was already frightening enough. The middle was a horde of undead beasts, the left and right flanks were composed of undead jackal light cavalry, and the reserve was human undead.

In order to avoid causing misunderstandings, Zhao Hai let them appear as skeletons instead of zombies. The sight of a horde of skeletons suddenly appearing from the ground was still very terrifying.

Wales was happier than he expected when he witnessed this skeleton army. With his blood-sworn brother having such strength, he firmly believed that he had nothing to fear should he clash against Gasol.

Wales patted Zhao Hai’s shoulder and said nothing. Zhao Hai understood that Wales had kept this gratitude in his heart. Wales could not express his gratitude for such a help with words.

Wales had nothing to say as Zhao Hai had prepared himself. He called out all of his escorts, and 400 herculean bull warriors stood in front of Wales, watching him fixedly. Wales was their prince, and they were awaiting his orders.

They could guess who their enemies were this time, but they had no regrets. For the beastmen, having regrets meant betrayal. They would only obey their orders, take up their weapons, follow their leaders, move forward, and move forward again!

Chapter 260: Herculean Bull Tribe’s Plight

Wales looked at his warriors who had no regrets, while his heart was very emotional. On Beastmen Prairie, if one weren’t a qualified leader, no one would follow. Beastmen too had the right to choose their own leaders.

Such a thing had happened on the prairie. A tribe’s chieftain had become incompetent, and his tribesmen had gradually left him. Eventually, the tribe disappeared from the prairie.

Wales’ current situation wasn’t too good. Gasol controlled the entire Herculean Bull Tribe, and his subordinates’ families were in Gasol’s hands. If they weren’t following him out of deep loyalty, they probably would’ve left him some time ago.

Wales was touched that these people had stayed behind. He watched them calmly and said, “Brothers, I’m sure everyone has learned of what has taken place in the tribe. Your families are still in the tribe. I am happy that you are still able to stay by my side. Our enemies are coming, and after an hour, they will appear before us. We will not retreat. Herculean Bull Tribe’s warriors will never retreat. Now, brothers, ride your bulls and raise your axes. Follow me and let our enemies know, that we are the strongest warriors of the Herculean Bull Tribe.”

Wales’s words weren’t shouted. In fact, he was speaking them very calmly, like he was simply stating a fact. But the warriors were very emotional. They heeded him with a loud call and ran to pick up their weapons, and pulled their mounts by their reins.

Wales ignored them and asked Zhao Hai, “Are you coming with us, brother? By horse or by wagon?”

Zhao Hai smiled and shook his head, “No, big brother. I’m going by something better.” With a move of his hand, Xenomorph appeared in front of him.

Wales was very curious about Xenomorph’s powerful appearance. Zhao Hai smiled and walked towards its mouth, “Come, big brother. Drink some coya with me.” He then walked into Xenomorph’s mouth.

Wales and the others followed Zhao Hai inside curiously, and they soon arrived in the space inside Xenomorph. Now, its space had gone through a major change. Laura modified this space to the point that it was like her own wagon. A few boxes had been put in there, which could be used as benches. Inside the boxes were blankets and other things, while there was also a box in the middle, which had upper and lower compartments. The bottom compartment was a refrigeration block that could be used to keep things at freezing temperatures. The top compartment contained coya and other things, while a tea set was placed on top of the box. In the middle of it was a magic burner powered by a magic crystal, used to boil water.

Wales and the others looked idly at all of this. They had never expected that there was another realm inside this undead creature’s body.

Zhao Hai smiled at them, “Sit down, big brother. Want a cup?”

Wales sat down and looked around, “Not bad. We can even see what’s outside. Teacher, I think you should sit here with little Hai. I’ll settle the matters outside.”

Yale didn’t object and just smiled, “That’s fine. It’s quite nice, sitting in here. You should go out and prepare yourself. I think Gasol and his lot will be here soon.”

Wales nodded and glanced at Zhao Hai, “Little Hai, when things get rough, don’t be polite. Just act directly.”

Zhao Hai smiled, “Relax, big brother. I won’t be kind. You should hurry. They might’ve discovered where we are.”

Wales nodded and then went out of Xenomorph. Mendez also went out, while Zhao Hai and Yale stayed inside. Laura and the others stayed next to Zhao Hai, while the food wagons outside hadn’t moved.

Zhao Hai poured a cup of coya for Yale and asked, “Mr. Yale, do you think we’ll fight? Gasol shouldn’t make a move after seeing what we have, right?”

Yale shook his head in response, “Not necessarily. Gasol is a conceited individual. He won’t give up so easily. Right now, Wales is his biggest concern. If he can kill Wales, he can gain total control of the Herculean Bull Tribe. Even though there are a lot of undead, beastmen usually don’t think of them seriously, because they believe that undead aren’t powerful. It isn’t likely that they know your undead creatures are so powerful, which is why I think Gasol might make a move.”

Zhao Hai nodded. He really didn’t want to do this. He didn’t fear the act of murder. He had killed plenty of people from Ark Continent, but right now, he was going to kill the Herculean Bull Tribe’s people.

If the tribe’s losses were too great, its place on Beastmen Prairie would be lowered, and that would not be a good thing for him. Nothing else mattered on Beastmen Prairie other than strength. With strength came respect. If you didn’t have great strength, then sorry. It wouldn’t matter how powerful you were in the past as a whole. People wouldn’t give you face.

No matter what, one must retaliate when struck. Not striking back wasn’t Zhao Hai’s style. He had nothing to say about that when Wales and the others had decided to strike back.

Zhao Hai sighed, “I still don’t get it. Does Gasol want the chieftain’s position that badly? If a lot of people die because of his clash against big brother, then the position of the tribe will be lowered. What good will it do him? He harmed his own father in the process of becoming the chieftain, so his reputation is surely a bad one on the prairie. He’s at a major disadvantage. Did he never think about all this?”

Yale sighed, “You don’t know Gasol. He is a prideful person, very self-absorbed, who thinks that his own power is great. To top it off, he’s a battle maniac. I can say that, if not for such a temperament, Wales wouldn’t have to fight him for the chieftain position. Because, Wales and I are very clear that once Gasol becomes the chieftain, war will be unavoidable.”

Yale sighed again and continued, “Don’t be fooled by how powerful the tribe seems right now. There are still a lot of people provoking the herculean bulls. Just the fighting bulls are vexing enough, to name a single example.”

Zhao Hai was taken aback. He knew that the fighting bulls were a major race among the bull-headed races, and that its tribe had marital ties to the herculean bulls. Why did Yale say that the Fighting Bull Tribe was provoking the Herculean Bull Tribe?

Yale clarified upon looking at Zhao Hai, “The position of every ruling tribe of a beastmen race isn’t fixed in place. If you are powerful, then you are the ruling race. On the other hand, if you are weak, you have no right to be the ruling race. Despite the previous chieftain having battled across the prairie with great results, the tribe’s strength has been spent for a great deal. Now is supposed to be the time for rest and recovery. If a battle maniac becomes chieftain now, our losses will be even greater if new wars are waged.”

Yale stopped to drink a mouthful of coya before continuing, “The fighting bulls are a powerful fighting race among the bull-headed races. They are muscular and have immense strength, especially when leading their charges. Even herculean bulls will not necessarily maintain the upper hand when facing them. They are scary in the fact that they weren’t very powerful before, but changed after their new chieftain got the position. Unlike his predecessors, he isn’t someone who is very fond of fighting. They have been resting in all these years, and thus have become more powerful than they were before. The Herculean Bull Tribe’s late chieftain saw that the position of the ruling tribe was becoming unstable, so he wedded 4 of his daughters to the Fighting Bull Tribe. He attempted to use marriage to pacify the Fighting Bull Tribe, but it obviously hasn’t been very effective. It was because of this reason that there are decreasing amount of wars fought by the Herculean Bull Tribe. However, Gasol assumed that the late chieftain lost his ambition because of his age, so he was greatly dissatisfied with the late chieftain. The late chieftain was deeply disappointed. How could he ignore the threat by his side? That was why he gave the position to Wales. Wales isn’t fond of fighting, and he is very smart. The late chieftain could be at ease that way.”

Zhao Hai didn’t think that this fight for the succession would be serious to the extent of deciding the very future of the Herculean Bull Tribe.

Yale sighed, “We don’t know how many casualties will be lost if this war is waged. The greater the death toll, the greater the herculean bulls’ loss, and the more unstable the position of the ruling race. Sadly, Gasol cannot see this. That overly arrogant fool keeps on believing that the herculean bulls are undefeatable, and he keeps treating the fighting bulls as the good guys. He has no idea that these ‘good guys’ are saving their strength to bring him to his knees.”

Yale’s face bore an expression of mockery at this point. The one he was mocking was none other than Gasol. How could the likes of him lead the herculean bulls into a bright future? It was the reason why Yale fully supported Wales.

Zhao Hai sighed at the thought. He knew a little bit more about the Herculean Bull Tribe now, but he hadn’t gotten used to seeing someone like Gasol, who had the ruthlessness of a ruler to use any means necessary to achieve his goals. However, it would only end in tragedy when such a ruler didn’t also have a ruler’s foresight.

Chapter 261: Poetic Payback

Rumbling galloping broke the silence on the prairie, and the dust they kicked up in passing seemed to hasten the setting of the sun. Wales didn’t want to witness a scene where brothers engaged in mutual violence. He sat on his own mount in silence. He didn’t wear any armor. Instead, he wore a robe, and his large axe was stuck into the grassy ground next to him.

Mendez was in a similar get-up as Wales, but his large axe was in his hands. 400 warriors in arms had lined up behind them. Behind them was Zhao Hai’s undead army.

A black line soon appeared on the distant horizon, coming towards them like a torrent. Wales squinted at it, while Mendez and the others gripped their weapons tightly.

Very soon, the galloping sounds became greater. It was as if the earth itself were trembling because of it. But this had no effect on Wales and the others. They were standing there quietly. Wales even closed his own eyes softly.

Soon the galloping died down as it got closer. Wales knew that Gasol wasn’t far away from them now. He then opened his eyes.

The sun was about to set completely. Although it wasn’t too far, Wales was still not be able to make out the faces on the other side. Gradually, Wales was able to determine that the one in the lead was indeed Gasol.

What surprised Wales was that there weren’t many herculean bulls among the troops Gasol had brought with him. There were only 500. The rest were all fighting bulls. Wales was puzzled as to why so many fighting bulls had come alongside Gasol.

Just then, Mendez grunted coldly, “Little Hai was right. Gasol got the Fighting Bull Tribe’s support. No wonder he has such gall. What an idiot.”

Wales knew what Mendez’s words meant. The herculean bulls had held 2 attitudes when it came to the fighting bulls. One was affectionate, and another was being cautious behind closed doors. The former was Gasol and his lot’s attitude, while the latter was Wales and his father’s attitude.

Wales knew well the threat the fighting bulls posed. Gasol leading so many fighting bulls to deal with him right now was something that made Wales gnash his teeth in anger. Now, he suspected that the reason Gasol had treated his father in such a way was due to the fighting bulls giving him that idea.

Wales gradually calmed down after taking a few deep breaths. Gasol and the others slowly came to a stop about 100 metres in front of them.

Even though Gasol and the others numbered 2000, all of them were tall and brawny beastmen, which was why they appeared to be black and boundless from a distance.

Zhao Hai saw Gasol and the others, but what he noticed more, were the ones beside him.

The ones next to him were also from a bull-headed race. One thing about them that was different from the smooth-skinned herculean bulls was that their faces had short black hair, while their horns were curved instead of straight. The short length of their curved horns made them look like pairs of daggers.

Just when Zhao Hai was sizing up these bull-headed people he had never seen before, Yale let out a cold snort, “As expected of the fighting bulls. They’re the ones who have been supporting Gasol.”

Zhao Hai immediately understood that the ones he was looking at were fighting bulls. He asked Yale with incomprehension, “Mr. Yale, didn’t big brother intend to get the Fighting Bull Tribe’s support? Why is it that they’re all very close to Gasol right now?”

Yale sighed, “Actually, the fighting bulls are split into 2 sides. One side is the faction under the current fighting bull chieftain. They are close to Gasol, and they’re also the ones the eldest princess and 4th princess were married to. The other side is the Fighting Bull Tribe’s West Wonder King’s faction, who are closer to the late chieftain and young master Wales. 2nd princess and 3rd princess were married to this side. Young master was trying to meet the West Wonder King’s faction.”

Zhao Hai nodded and asked, “If the fighting bulls have never been united, how can they threaten the herculean bulls’ position as the ruling race?”

Yale sighed yet again, “Actually, the Fighting Bull Tribe was originally united, and it was much stronger back then, to the point of threatening the Herculean Bull Tribe’s position as the ruling tribe. The late chieftain discovered this, so he intentionally supported the West Wonder King, who is at odds with the fighting bull chieftain. The plan was very successful. Under the tribe’s backing, the Fighting Bull Tribe was divided into 2 factions. Although West Wonder King’s strength wasn’t as great as the chieftain’s, it wasn’t weak either. However, in recent years, the chieftain had gotten close to Gasol. In order to get the Fighting Bull Tribe’s support, Gasol started supporting the chieftain. Now, the chieftain’s strength is much stronger than it was before, and West Wonder King is now at a complete disadvantage.”

Yale continued, “Perhaps this was something they have learned from the Herculean Bull Tribe. Our tribe once supported West Wonder King, who was able to fracture the tribe, but unable to shake up the Fighting Bull Tribe’s chieftain. And in return, the Fighting Bull Tribe is now supporting Gasol to achieve the chieftain’s position, which has divided the Herculean Bull Tribe, while getting a lot of benefits in the process. If Gasol wages wars, a lot of the herculean bull young adults will perish, and the tribe’s strength will decrease greatly. When that time comes, no one will be able to stop the fighting bulls when they seize the position of the ruling race.”

To use one’s ways against them in return. Poetic payback. Zhao Hai suddenly thought about this. He didn’t expect that the beastmen, who appeared to be straightforward and inflexible, would also be capable of twists and turns. It seemed that no sentient race on this world was to be underestimated.

Yale continued after a disappointed exhale, “The Herculean Bull Tribe was vicious back then, and the Fighting Bull Tribe was split. Now, the Fighting Bull Tribe is even more vicious. They want the Herculean Bull Tribe’s roots to be cut. Grasses without roots will wither over time.”

Zhao Hai watched those fighting bulls with disbelief. He thought that the fighting bull chieftain was impressive on account that he had plotted it all out to this extent. Including perhaps even the death of the previous herculean bull chieftain.

Just then, Wales didn’t make a single move; he was just watching Gasol calmly, who was appearing to be spirited. However, Gasol’s expression wasn’t pleasant right now, especially after seeing the undead creatures behind Wales.

Gasol put down his reins softly and walked out. The 2 escorts next to him were one herculean bull and one fighting bull. They were muscular and had gruesome scars. They appeared to be ones who should not be taken lightly.

Wales put down his reins as well and walked towards Gasol. Mendez followed him with his weapon in his hands. They slowly got closer, until both sides were only 10 metres away from each other.

Gasol stared as Wales coldly, “You have indeed colluded with humans, Wales. You really are a traitor to the Herculean Bull Tribe.”

Wales spoke coldly in response, “Everyone knows who has colluded with humans, Gasol. An idiot like you is only worthy of being used by others.”

Gasol let out a cold laugh, “Your words are useless. I am the chieftain, and you are the traitor. Surrender, brother, and I will spare your life.”

Wales stared coldly as Gasol, “You could kill even our father and our sickly 5th brother. Can I even believe you? Now I’m really suspicious. Does the blood of herculean bulls flow in your veins? Or is it not blood at all, but murky bull urine instead?”

Gasol’s eyes flared at Wales. Even though he killed his own father, he hadn’t spoken a word of it. He only claimed that his father was poisoned. What Wales was doing now was like slapping Gasol on the face. How could Gasol take it?

Gasol grumbled with anger, “Who said I killed our father? I’m saying he was killed by you. You dared to team up with human black mages. Who on the continent doesn’t know that black mages are the most evil of them all? They’re the best at using poison.”

Wales laughed coldly, “Didn’t you say that father died of illness? How has it become ‘he was poisoned’ now? No matter how poisonous black mages’ poisons are, they are not as poisonous as your heart. Your heart has already betrayed the Beast God. You will be judged.”

Gasol’s expression changed, and he then spoke coldly, “Cut the bullshit. You won’t elude death no matter what you say, traitor. You think that handful of people and those loose bones will win against us? Stop dreaming and prepare to die.”

Wales retorted coldly, “I will let you know today, Gasol, that you are not invincible. I didn’t want to do this, since I thought that you would bring our tribe’s warriors. But since you have brought the Fighting Bull Tribe’s people, I don’t need to hold back. Accept death, Gasol.”

Gasol replied, “Ignorant runt. How can undead creatures compare to us beastmen in terms of strength, Wales? You’re incapable of living down your reputation of being smart. I think you are a fool.”

Wales gave Gasol a cold smile, “You are speaking too much crap, Gasol. Can it be that after a long time without battles, you have become a useless person who only knows how to move his lips?”

Gasol snorted coldly. He knew that he would never be a match for Wales in conversations, so he didn’t speak any further. He turned around and walked back to his troops. Wales also returned to his escorts.

Chapter 262: ‘Finish Him Off After Drinking’

Yale knew after watching Wales and Gasol’s expressions that the conversation had fallen through. He turned to Zhao Hai and said, “The talks have soured. Get ready to make your move.”

Zhao Hai smiled, “It’s not a big deal. Most of the people Gasol brought with him are fighting bulls. This is even better. I can use all of my might. To be honest, I’m still unwilling to fight against herculean bulls.”

Yale smiled at Zhao Hai, “I feel that you are more and more like a herculean bull yourself. On Beastmen Prairie, the power of a race isn’t just about how powerful the ruling race is. It’s more about the overall strength of a whole race. Whether it’s fighting bulls or herculean bulls, they all seem to have forgotten about this issue. We buffalos know about this, but when it comes to conflicts of interests, they rarely listen to us. That’s why, even though we have prophets, it’s useless for us to persuade them. You can see this point clearly. You don’t like to make a move against herculean bulls, yet you want to deal with fighting bulls. Although it looks like an extermination of life on the prairie, it’s a good thing from another perspective. If the Fighting Bull Tribe becomes too powerful, it will surely engage in conflict against Herculean Bull Tribe, as long as both race’s tribes are the strongest among the bull-headed races. If they don’t come into conflict, then all of the bull-headed races will be stronger. There is only one way to prevent conflict amongst them; Make one side completely stronger than the other to make the other side unable to fight back.”

Zhao Hai smiled, “I seriously haven’t thought about it that much. I’m just thinking about what’s best for big brother. The bull-headed races are a major race together. Simply having the herculean bulls’ support isn’t going to work. The other branch races have to become stronger as well, so that the entire race can be even stronger. But the situation here is that only a single powerful race can rule the entire bunch. The whole bunch of races keep engaging in conflict. How can they become stronger?”

Zhao Hai went silent after speaking to this point. He suddenly thought about ancient China. Before the Qing Dynasty’s resistance against 8 foreign powers, warlords engaged in skirmishes, industry fell behind the global pace, and there wasn’t a centralized administration. Those were the reasons why China was so far behind the world, and an incomparably painful price was paid in order to fight back against all the intruders. If the bull-headed races were to keep on fighting each other like this, the outcome would not be much better than that of ancient China.

There was only one way to strengthen the entire bull-headed race; Let the bull-headed races have only one unshakable king. That was his reason for defeating the Fighting Bull Tribe.

Of course, Zhao Hai wasn’t doing it entirely for Wales. Even though the two of them were blood-sworn brothers, he wasn’t selfless to the point of removing every single one of Wales’ obstacles.

He was actually doing it for himself as well. He currently had the best relationship with Wales and Spiel. Spiel was a given; his tribe was too small, and could be exterminated by others at any time. The only help Zhao Hai got from them was the friendship flag.

Wales was different; Wales was royalty, and right now, he was fighting for the chieftain’s position. If he could become chieftain and thus remove all the obstacles in his path, it would bring Zhao Hai unimaginable benefits.

Although Zhao Hai was having a conversation with Yale inside Xenomorph, they were also paying attention to the battleground. The sky was darkening, which could be said to be bad for prairie battles. Zhao Hai didn’t know if Gasol was going to attack at night, but he didn’t have any worries. To him, night didn’t have any affect on him.

He had undead creatures, and undead creatures were the true rulers of the night. For the undead, it was best that there was no light. They were the best night battle legion.

Now, Zhao Hai just wanted to see what Wales was going to do. If Wales wanted to attack right now, he wouldn’t hold back as well. If Wales didn’t want to, he wouldn’t make a move.

He didn’t want to steal Wales’ spotlight. Even though he and Wales were blood-sworn brothers, even born siblings would turn into enemies in the face of power, not to mention blood-sworn brothers. Even if Wales would do nothing to Zhao Hai, it would be a great loss if Wales didn’t support him. He was helping Wales in order to get Wales’ support.

After Wales returned to his formation, Mendez spoke to him after a glance at Gasol’s troops, “Are we going to hit him right now? Any later, and we will be unable to see.”

Wales smiled, “No need to rush. Let’s back away slowly. The sky is about to go dark. We can’t see them, and they can’t see us by then. But don’t forget that little Hai’s undead army is behind us. When have you ever heard of undead creatures being afraid of the dark?”

Mendez was reminded by Wales’ words. There were still 4000 undead behind them. At night, the fighting power of undead creatures would be increased. This could only be something positive for them.

Mendez had decided that this battle must be fought. After all, they no longer had any reservations. If they let go of this chance, it would be more than a little humiliating.

After Wales lifted the axe that he had planted into the ground, he waved his hand to signal the 400 escorts to move backward slowly. Just then, Zhao Hai made the undead creatures advance at a gradual pace. Although he didn’t discuss this with Wales, he made the most appropriate decision.

Xenomorph was mixed into this undead army, though it wasn’t particularly eye-catching. Gasol and his troops wouldn’t even know that there was a human mixed within this undead army.

Now, Wales and the others had gone behind the undead army, and were firmly protected by it. Even should Gasol start charging now, he would have to face the tall platoons of undead magic beasts.

Obviously, Gasol was not a battlefield virgin. He was a warrior who had been through 100 battles and was famed for being good at fighting in the Herculean Bull Tribe. It was impossible for Gasol not to know about what he was going to face.

The sun had just set, while the moon hadn’t yet appeared. It was the darkest time. Fighting against an undead army now of all times would be an attempt at self-induced defeat. Gasol would never do it, so he waved his hand as well and led his 2000 cavalry to move backward slowly. It was obvious that they didn’t want to engage in a night battle.

Wales nodded at the sight of Gasol’s retreat, with no disruption to the formation. Wales spoke to Mendez, “6th brother, I have to say, Gasol really has a touch when it comes to fighting battles. It’s unfortunate that he is so passionate about power. If he were willing to put up with us brothers, we could have made our race stronger and stronger.”

Mendez sighed, “It was because of being too good at fighting battles that he has lost sight of himself. Now he has colluded with the fighting bulls, and maybe even humans to kill father, all in order to get that position. Has he never thought about whether the position is really that important? Working with fighting bulls is just like sleeping with wolves.”

Wales spoke coldly, “The Fighting Bull Tribe has been waiting for this day, and Gasol actually went ahead and did this himself. It looks like we’ll have to talk it out with our 2nd and 3rd sisters. Once we resolve the matter with Gasol, we will have to deal with the Fighting Bull Tribe as the next step. Now that the fighting bull chieftain isn’t being honest, perhaps it’s time for us to teach them a little lesson.”

Mendez spoke coldly, “Then fight. Only fighting can make them settle down. I think it wouldn’t be bad to let West Wonder King become the next Fighting Bull Tribe chieftain.”

Wales replied, “Now is not yet the time. Besides, do you think West Wonder King is really dependable? If he didn’t have ambitions, he wouldn’t have left his tribe under father’s support. Once he has enough strength one day, will he leave Herculean Bull Tribe’s side as well? We can use such a person, but we must keep our eye on him and not let him run rampant.”

Mendez nodded and then he smiled, “Do you know why I have always supported you, little 7th? It’s because you’re really smart. You’re not like a beastman. There are too few smart people among us beastmen. You had great luck in finding little Hai. I believe he will help us, the herculean bulls, become the most famous race on the continent.”

Wales smiled upon the mention of Zhao Hai. He laughed, “If I had to put it in a way I was happy with, I’m more relaxed when it comes to Zhai Hai compared to West Wonder King. He might threaten our rule, but little Hai won’t. I’d rather trust little Hai who is a human and who cannot possibly threaten us.”

Mendez nodded, “Yeah. Compared to West Wonder King, I’d rather trust little Hai. But you have to pay attention as well, little 7th. We cannot trust him completely. Don’t forget the Black Bear Tribe’s lesson.”

Wales nodded, “Of course I won’t forget, but you don’t need to worry about this. When I met little Hai, I mentioned that, if he could help me, I could make him the Herculean Bull Tribe’s sole grain dealer. Guess what he said?”

This piqued Mendez’s interest. He hadn’t known about this yet, so he asked curiously, “What did he say?”

Wales smiled, “He said he can help me, but he doesn’t want to be the tribe’s sole grain dealer. He just wants our tribe’s friendship flag.”

Mendez was stunned, and then sighed, “He is indeed different from other human merchants. If you asked any other human merchant that question, I bet 100% of them would choose to become our sole grain dealer, because that would mean seizing our tribe’s lifeline.”

Wales nodded, “This was what I saw in little Hai. He knows what he’s doing, how to do it, and how to keep doing it. It’s a pity he’s not a beastman like us. He would be an unbelievable person otherwise.”

Mendez laughed, “I think it’s quite nice right now. I don’t know where little Hai appeared from, but at least it looks like he has no evil intentions towards us. It’s enough that he treats us big brothers with respect.”

Wales smiled, “Well, enough about that. Let’s go and have a drink from little Hai’s place. I hear that he has fine wine from the human lands. We’ll look for trouble at Gasol’s place later. He doesn’t want to fight at night? Well, he’s not the one calling the shots right now.”

Wales and Mendez gave orders to their escorts, and then rode their mounts towards Zhao Hai’s place. Although there were a lot of undead creatures, they could still recognize Xenomorph.

Zhao Hai didn’t let the undead creatures pursue Gasol due to not knowing Wales’ intentions. He stopped as soon as Gasol left. The undead creatures stood where they were in silence.

He immediately let Xenomorph open its jaws when he saw Wales and Mendez coming his way. Laura had prepared the coya as Wales and Mendez entered.

Wales sat down hurriedly as soon he entered Xenomorph’s inner space, and spoke to Zhao Hai, “Brother, make preparations. We will attack Gasol after a while. I don’t think he set up his camp too far away.”

Zhao Hai nodded, “No problem. Night battles are the undead’s expertise, so relax. Even if we can’t keep Gasol here tonight, we’ll be keeping those fighting bulls here if we have to.”

Wales laughed, “Looks like I don’t have to tell you. You have gotten the picture. That’s right. Our goal this time is those fighting bulls. We’re going to be beating them until they’re done.”

Zhao Hai smiled and poured Wales and Mendez a cup of coya each. Wales drank a mouthful and said, “I still think our beastmen’s milk wine is much better than this. Which reminds me…. Bring us 2 bottles of your humans’ fine wine.”

Zhao Hai laughed. “Fine. I’ll let you taste our humans’ fine wine. Laura, bring some fruit platters with snacks. We’ll finish him (Gasol) off after drinking.”

Laura and the others heeded with a laugh. Actually, most of the things were inside Zhao Hai’s space. Zhao Hai took out 3 bottles of wine, while the rest was handled by Laura and the others.

It didn’t take long for the appetizers to be ready. There weren’t just fruit platters, but also some famous continental snacks, which had been bought by Zhao Hai and the others and stored inside the space beforehand. After all, the space would not change their taste, and Laura and the others liked to snack on them, so Zhao Hai had readied quite an amount of them.

These things weren’t too attractive on the continent, but to the beastmen, they were incredible. Wales and Mendez had never seen most of these things before, so they ended up having their appetites satisfied.

Chapter 263: Gasol’s Frustration

Compared to Wales and the others, Gasol wasn’t so happy. He knew very well that, despite being the chieftain of the Herculean Bull Tribe, the tribesmen didn’t respect him. There was the escape of Mendez and the others. The people in the tribe had some idea as to why they had escaped and why his father had suddenly ‘passed away’. If he couldn’t settle this matter as quickly as possible, his situation would become even more difficult.

In order to nip this danger in the bud, Gasol had sought help from the Fighting Bull Tribe, by requesting a levy of troops and pursuing Mendez in tandem with his own escorts. His plan had been to find the traces of Wales’ whereabouts, and then kill them both in one strike.

What Gasol hadn’t expected was Zhao Hai’s appearance. Even further beyond his expectations was the appearance of a large undead army at night.

Gasol didn’t know when Wales had come in contact with human black mages. If Wales could mobilize 4000 undead creatures, it would either be due to a powerful black mage, or a team of black mages. Either possibility was extremely dangerous.

Gasol now regretted the fact that his pursuit was seriously untimely. If it were daytime when he found Wales, then he would have been able to attack without reservations. But he couldn’t now, because it was dark. Fighting against undead creatures in the dark was no different from seeking death.

The most nerve-wracking parts about undead creatures, were the fact that they excelled in fighting at nighttime, and the fact that they didn’t fear death. These creatures that didn’t have thoughts would never know what death was. They only knew about attacking and had no notions of death. Such enemies were the most frightening.

What gave Gasol the biggest headache was that his 2 aerial recon units had been attacked by other magic beasts before being captured. This gave him the worse heartache in his life.

Just as Wales said, a large part of Gasol’s accomplishments were due to the 2 aerial recon units that he had been raising. As long as he had the recon, he could discover his enemies first and make placements beforehand. That way, he could naturally gain the upper hand during battle.

However, his 2 aerial recon units were attacked by 5 flying magic beasts in mid-air. He could do nothing but watch as the 2 flame birds which he had spent much care in raising were captured by the red-colored flying beasts.

Gasol couldn’t help but frown when he thought about it. He felt as if nothing had gone smoothly for him lately. Other than becoming the chieftain, nothing else had gone as he had planned.

He hadn’t needed to sort out so many matters before he had become the chieftain. He had mostly needed to handle military matters while the others matters had been handled by his father. However, once he became the chieftain and truly began to deal with the tribe’s matters, he discovered that managing a tribe wasn’t so easy.

Soon it was going to be winter. Goats needed to eat grass and people needed to eat food. Timber was needed to keep warm. Everything had to be prepared. These matters gave Gasol a huge headache.

Leaders in the tribe had started to sidestep his commands. Although the Fighting Bull Tribe was still cooperating with him, they didn’t seem to be kind about it like before. His biggest worry was the fact that Wales and Mendez were still at large.

Even though there were a lot of matters that needed to be taken care of, Gasol had always believed that Wales was his biggest threat. Because Wales was still popular in the tribe, and respected the elders and various leaders in the tribe very much. Everything had been done in a seemingly low-key fashion, but it had been done right. Most importantly, his father had given the cane to Wales.

The God Bull Cane was passed down from chieftains to their successors. In other words, the moment his father gave it to Wales, in the eyes of the elders and the leaders, it meant that his father had appointed Wales as his successor.

It was exactly because of this reason that the people in the tribe weren’t pleased when Gasol said that his father made him the chieftain after being poisoned.

In order to make those people give up and acknowledge him as the chieftain, he could only eliminate Wales and the others in the shortest time possible. Only then would the elders and leaders acknowledge his place.

However, Gasol couldn’t mobilize too large of a force to pursue them, due to Wales and Mendez being princes of the tribe. He could only bring 500 of his personal guard and borrow 1500 warriors from the Fighting Bull Tribe to hunt them down.

And the 1500 fighting bulls hadn’t been loaned to him for nothing. Their price had been 10000 argali and 1000 slaves, which had been sent to the Fighting Bulls as payment.

This was exactly what Gasol was angry about. Before he had become the chieftain, the Fighting Bull Tribe was very hospitable, and would immediately provide him with help if he asked for it. But after becoming the chieftain, the Fighting Bull Tribe started listing conditions, which made Gasol feel very irritated.

But he had no other options. The Herculean Bull Tribe was internally unstable. Although he could suppress the elders and leaders now, he could neither do what he truly wanted, nor be like his father, who could move the whole tribe at his beck and call. Gasol had had no option but to seek help from the Fighting Bull Tribe.

When he had caught up to Wales, he had found out that Wales hadn’t turned around and run as he had expected. Instead, Wales led a large undead army to confront him. Night had come, and he couldn’t afford not to retreat.

Watching someone who could threaten him, yet be unable to act. Gasol felt that a bad air was being kept in his chest, like a polar bear that had swallowed an icy barnacle, neither able to spit it out nor swallow it down.

But he couldn’t let down his guard now, because he was very clear that Wales wasn’t a fool. It would be weird if Wales didn’t utilize the undead to attack him at night. That was why Gasol had prepared for a night attack when setting up the tents.

Many bonfires had been lit around his tent, and 500 people had been mobilized just to keep watch. He ordered the rest to sleep as soon as they set up their campsite. They had to take this chance to rest, in order to be prepared for the great battle that could come at any moment.

However, Gasol still underestimated the fighting ability of Zhao Hai’s undead creatures. In Gasol’s eyes, even though Wales would use them to attack him, they could be defeated. Because undead creatures only had an advantage at night.

But when Zhao Hai ordered the undead creatures to attack Gasol’s campsite, Gasol realized something strange; these undead creatures were too powerful.

Gasol was a level 8 powerhouse, but even he couldn’t gain any advantage when facing these undead beasts. This proved that these undead creatures had strengths higher than level 6. How could this be?

Gasol seriously couldn’t believe it, but the truth was right in front of his eyes. Zhao Hai commanded the undead creatures to besiege Gasol’s campsite from 3 directions. The undead beasts from the front, the jackals from the sides, and the humanoids entered the campsite from behind the beasts and the jackals. The attack was like a blitzkrieg, turning the campsite into burnt ashes in an instant.

Even though both herculean bulls and fighting bulls were known for being the most powerful among bull-headed races and good at fighting, when they faced opponents taller, larger, stronger, and with better defenses than them, they helplessly realized that all of their advantages were not advantages at all.

They could defend against neither the head-on assault of the undead beasts, nor the undead jackal cavalry flanks. Gasol hadn’t discovered that the cavalry were the jackals. He had given money to the jackals in order to have them kill Wales, but he had lost contact with them. He knew that the operation had been a failure, but he never imagined that the jackals had become undead creatures themselves.

However, Gasol finally discovered that they were the jackals after they charged in. Not only had they become undead creatures, but they had also become stronger as well.

On the prairie, the jackal cavalry wasn’t famous because of how powerful they were, but how fast they were. They were patient and able to keep tailing their enemies until they broke down. But everyone on the prairie knew that the jackal cavalry didn’t have a powerful leading charge. They were short, weak, and had fragile defenses. All these could make them only light cavalry at best.

But that had changed entirely in Zhao Hai’s hands. After having gone through the space’s strengthening, the jackal cavalry had become even stronger, more powerful, and faster. Now they totally had the ability to become a powerful armored cavalry.

For the under-calculated Gasol, who had only put 300 people on the left and right flanks, he discovered that he had made a mistake. A very big mistake. When the 600 fighting bulls and the undead jackal cavalry crossed paths, the fighting bulls were crushed in a single charge.

The main weapons of the jackal cavalry were scimitars, while fighting bull cavalry mainly used wolf-tooth clubs. Their wolf-tooth clubs were a type of heavy weapon that could not be used without immense strength. Heavy cavalry paired with these clubs in action was a very frightening thing.

Yet the undead jackal cavalry made the fighting bulls understand what ‘Nothing is too tough to break. Only speed cannot be broken’ meant. The fighting bull cavalry was like a tank when in action, while the jackal cavalry was like a wind that carried blades. When the wind blew, the tank became scrap metal.

Chapter 264: Two Blades

Gasol was running like crazy. There were only a few dozen escorts left at his side, all of whom were herculean bulls. There were nobody else other than them. Not a single one.

2000 armored cavalry, all killed in action.

Gasol felt like he was still having a nightmare. Why had all 2000 of his cavalry been crushed in just a single charge by the undead creatures? Could it be that he hadn’t brought 2000 armored cavalry, but 2000 argali instead?

If it weren’t for his escorts using their own lives to help him break through the encirclement, he would likely have died in the melee. The attacks of the undead creatures still resonated in his mind when he thought about it.

Meanwhile, Gasol thought about another thing; If he had been defeated by Wales this time, then what would Wales do next? Would Wales lead the undead into the tribe?

Gasol felt even more insecure when he thought of this, and there was another matter that troubled him deeply: the loss of the 1500 fighting bulls. They had been loaned to him. Now that they had all died, what sort of reaction would the Fighting Bull Tribe have?

Most importantly, the 500 herculean bulls that he had brought with him were his most loyal subordinates, and his most effective weapon. Now, they had fallen almost completely. Without this weapon which he could definitely depend on, his days would be even harder to get by.

Gasol had already wanted to cry. His losses this time were too great for him to bear.

In contrast to Gasol, Zhao Hai’s gains were large. 1500 fighting bull warriors, no escapees. They had all become Zhao Hai’s new underlings. Zhao Hai didn’t touch the remaining herculean bull warriors, since he had to give Wales some face. No matter whose subordinates they were, the fact that they were herculean bulls still remained. Zhao Hai couldn’t step over that line.

Wales was very happy about Zhao Hai’s actions. In Wales’ eyes, these fallen herculean bull warriors should receive their due respects.

And so, Wales buried the herculean bull warriors along with their mounts. However, he kept all of their weapons, because Beastmen Prairie lacked metal, which he couldn’t afford to waste.

Zhao Hai was somewhat disappointed that not a single mount was kept alive in this attack. Zhao Hai had lost a chance to add a new species to the space.

However, Zhao Hai felt happy when he thought about the 1500 fighting bull warriors. Now, he had over 7000 undead creatures in his possession. He could deploy the undead beasts at Iron Mountain Castle as guards, and still have enough undead hands to use afterwards.

Actually, if Zhao Hai willed it, he could reveal his family identity, given his current strength. Even with the Church Of Light as his enemy, he wouldn’t have to be afraid. He didn’t need to worry about his own safety at all with the existence of the space. He should be indulging in warfare, because if a war were fought, he would get new undead troops. If he wished for it, the number of undead would keep on increasing, and then he would have even fewer reasons to be afraid of anyone.

But he didn’t want to do it like this. To be honest, Zhao Hai was still insecure about the frequent use of undead creatures. Chinese people emphasized ‘peace in burial’. If it weren’t for the safety of he himself and the ones around him, Zhao Hai wouldn’t even wish to use the undead. Especially humanoid ones.

He didn’t like warfare either. He knew that if his identity were discovered, it would cause a war that would center around him, and then, many people would surely die. He didn’t want to become the criminal of the whole continent.

Currently, only the nobles were giving him trouble, but to Zhao Hai, it wasn’t a big deal. ‘If I don’t wanna fight, I’ll just hide’, he would think. But if a war was waged because of him, then not only would the nobles hate him, but the civilians would as well. He didn’t want that.

Wales didn’t go after Gasol immediately after their victory. He still intended to stick to his original plan of going to get the support of the branch tribes before finishing Gasol off.

Wales had considered this beforehand. Just as Yale had said, there was nothing good about the contact between the fighting bulls and Gasol. They wouldn’t just watch Gasol fail without doing anything. If Gasol fell, then the one to rise would be Wales, who had never gotten along with fighting bulls. If Wales gained the chieftainship, he would oppress the Fighting Bull Tribe. The fighting bull chieftain would never miss this detail. If Wales chose to push their momentum, it would only let the Fighting Bull Tribe support Gasol completely, and things would escalate to a higher degree.

If things really progressed to that point, then all of the bull-headed races might engage in civil war. That was absolutely not what Wales wanted to see. So, what he needed to do now was to stick to the plan, overthrow Gasol, and then ‘clean up’ the Fighting Bull Tribe.

Currently, what Gasol and the Fighting Bull Tribe didn’t know was that Wales had the greatest trump card: the grains.

The Fighting Bull Tribe and Gasol had surely assumed that Wales’ current greatest backing was Zhao Hai’s undead army. But they couldn’t be more mistaken. The undead army was just one blade in Wales’ hand. The grains were the other fierce blade in his hand.

The best weapon in the beastmen lands was food, due to the frequent food shortages experienced here. Especially some of the smaller tribes, who had food shortages not just during winter, but all the time. They couldn’t get more than the larger tribes, and the grain dealers wouldn’t come to smaller tribes. It was thus very difficult for them to buy grains.

Now that Wales had grains, coupled with his reputation in the tribe, he could definitely gain the support of the branch races, and then he could deliver the fatal blow to Gasol.

Wales and the others rested where they were for 2 days after having defeated Gasol, while actually, there wasn’t a need for them to do so, since the ones who fought had been the undead creatures.

However, Wales and the others still rested. In those 2 days, they handled the corpses of Gasol’s escorts by burying them properly. Then they left after a proper rest.

Strictly put, right now, the territory they were in wasn’t the bull-headed races’ territory. Although everyone on Beastmen Prairie lived nomadic lifestyles, every race actually had their own turf. The stronger the race, the better their grasses, and the more rivers they had. Their places would be warmer when winter came, and less likely for blizzards to pass by.

On the flip side, the weaker the race, the worse grasslands they had, and it would be impossible for their magic beasts to grow strong. Without strong magic beasts, they would not be able to get get more grains. Without more grains, they could only eat magic beasts, which would incur greater losses. This was a downward spiral.

Wales and the others were currently at the outer regions of Beastmen Prairie. The grasslands here weren’t great, and they were shared. However, this was the territory of pig-headed races. It was because of this that Zhao Hai had come across Spiel and the others. One should know that small tribes like Spiel’s would never dare to be active in the turfs of other races.

The pig-headed races had a lower standing on the prairie compared to the bull-headed races because of the difference in fighting power between them. The ruling race, the warthogs, couldn’t match up to the herculean bulls. This affected the overall standing of all the pig-headed races among beastmen.

Wales and the others made their way towards the pig-headed races’ territory, but they didn’t head towards the bull-headed races’ territories immediately. Instead, they went in a circle.

That wasn’t to say that Wales was afraid that Gasol would mobilize a force to deal with him. Wales clearly knew that, if Gasol really had the support of everyone in the tribe, then Gasol wouldn’t have brought this amount of people to deal with him, with a larger amount of fighting bulls.

The smart Wales could guess from this point that not everyone in the tribe had supported Gasol, and thus, Gasol had borrowed troops from the Fighting Bull Tribe. Not only did this expose his colluding with the Fighting Bull Tribe, it also exposed the situation of his position in the tribe.

Beastmen were a direct race. They worshipped power. If you were powerful, they would listen to you willingly. Gasol’s power was great indeed. He had fought many wars for the Herculean Bull Tribe, with more victories than losses, and had a high popularity. That was why his ambitions had inflated so rapidly.

If Gasol had done nothing more, he would’ve had a chance to become the chieftain. After all, the position could not be decided by the former chieftain alone.

But Gasol had made a wrong move. He never should’ve poisoned the former chieftain, or sent people to hunt down Mendez and Wales. Doing so made his popularity drop to the freezing point instantly.

Because beastmen’s personalities were too direct, they always got the shorter end of the stick when it came to getting along with humans. Such direct personalities also created a habit of deeply despising anyone who would use schemes. Gasol’s original image of a powerful warrior had instantly turned into that of a petty creep who used schemes. His popularity in the tribe was lost as a result. That was exactly why he couldn’t mobilize the herculean bulls to hunt down Wales and his company.

Chapter 265: Entering The Bull-headed Races’ Territory

Wales’s group didn’t advance quickly. Currently, they were still in the territory of the pig-headed races. Even though the bull-headed races and the pig-headed races had no mutual favor or enmity, it wasn’t a good thing to bumble around randomly on someone else’s turf. That was why their advance was a careful one. If they came across some small pig-headed tribes, they would need to greet them on their own. It would cause misunderstandings if they didn’t.

For the beastmen, if you didn’t bear hostilities, you had to greet them when you met with them. If you didn’t do so, there were only 2 possibilities: either you had evil intentions, or you were looking down on them. Either possibility would be enough to make them treat you with their weapons.

Beastmen liked having receptions for their friends, so you had to invite them for a feast if you came to their doorstep. Otherwise, not only would they not treat you as a friend, they’d even take you for an enemy.

Wales and everyone were just passing through, but they still had to go visit any pig-headed tribe they came across and stay for a night. Zhao Hai engaged in trade with them. Of course, he used grains, in exchange for their magic beasts.

However, most of the tribes they came across were small tribes, so Zhao Hai didn’t manage to get very powerful magic beasts. Most of them were argali, while the tribes wouldn’t give their exclusive magic beasts to him.

Beastmen treated their tribe-specific magic beasts with great importance. These magic beasts of theirs were commonly their mounts. In other words, the beasts were their beastkin.

If Zhao Hai’s personality hadn’t matched well with Spiel’s, and if he hadn’t had a lot of grains, Spiel wouldn’t have given the squirting boars to Zhao Hai, because squirting boars were the beastkin of the big-bellied pigs.

Zhao Hai was satisfied with the trades he made. Other than getting more than a few argali, he also got a large amount of goat hair products. The small tribes were generous, since they wouldn’t come across a single human merchant in a whole year. When a human merchant finally showed up to conduct trade with them, they were very delighted.

Due to the recent sudden changes, Laura and the others couldn’t stick to their original plan to rendezvous with Ah-Tai. However, Laura still sent a blood hawk to give Ah-Tai messages, in order to establish a foothold in Beast God City and gain a better understanding of the situation there.

Zhao Hai was curious about this slightly mysterious Ah-Tai. He could tell how much Laura trusted him, as he was Laura’s only subordinate on Beastmen Prairie.

He also knew from Laura that in recent years, Ah-Tai had earned a lot of money in her stead on Beastmen Prairie. If she had to count, the earnings he had made were up to ⅓ of her total assets. This was a very large sum.

Everyone knew that business could be lucrative on Beastmen Prairie, but large merchants commonly did business with battle tribes, while the ones who did business with other tribes were smaller merchants. There was a limit to how much money the smaller merchants could earn, and they would often be raided by beastmen. That was why the money they earned was less than what people would expect.

Under such circumstances, the fact that Ah-Tai could earn so much money for Laura had to have something behind it.

The people that Zhao Hai and Laura could use were few. Ah-Tai was one. Xu Wan Ying was another. And then there were Seyer and Orloga.

Zhao Hai had never seen Ah-Tai before, but Laura trusted him very much. Xu Wan Ying was helping Greene and the others attend to matters at Iron Mountain Castle, while the same went for Seyer. Orloga was currently an undead, but the fact that he could become Carlo’s attendant meant that he had certain capabilities. Orloga had now been stationed at the factories, where he did things in an orderly way.

Blockhead and Rockhead’s performances were a little worse off in this regard, but both of them liked training more. They had now reached the level of level 6 fighters. Although it didn’t seem like much, they could count as geniuses on the continent when one looked at their age.

These people were now the master staff of Zhao Hai’s management. He couldn’t use more people even if he wanted to, because they didn’t have enough capital.

Letting Ah-Tai establish a foothold was for the sake of relaying the situation in Beast God City. Although the city was controlled by beastmen, there were a large amount of human merchants that gathered there. Zhao Hai and the rest would lose out if they didn’t grasp the situation well.

Wales and the others weren’t in a rush, but he still sent a team of 50 to obtain information from the bull-headed tribes’ territory. He wanted to check the branch races’ reaction to the incident in the Herculean Bull Tribe. What had transpired shouldn’t have zero effect on all of the bull-headed races. Wales wanted to know what Gasol’s next move was after he returned. Of course, if possible, he still wanted to make contact with West Wonder King.

Wales put the idea of contacting the Buffalo Tribe on hold. He knew that Gasol wouldn’t let down the surveillance there because of Yale. Because Wales wanted to wait for information, he didn’t move towards the bull-headed races’ territory in a hurry. He knew that in doing so, he might have a high chance of being discovered by Gasol.

Now, he and his people were moving forward slowly, as if they were just travelling, while he familiarized himself with the 5 blood hawks Zhao Hai had gifted him.

Wales knew the importance of these blood hawks as aerial reconnaissance too well. There were too few races on Beastmen Prairie that had aerial scouts.

The magic beasts that could be used as aerial scouts were not few, but most of them were under the control of avian races. It would be impossible for other races to get such aerial recon magic beasts. Gasol had gotten the 2 flame birds due to a chance meeting.

Now, those flame birds had been put into the space by Zhao Hai. The level assessment of the flame birds was a shocking level 35, which raised the level of the ranch to level 6. Unfortunately, the ranch had to reach level 7 in order to keep 100 more magic beasts.

Zhao Hai was happy that the space improved the abilities of the blood hawks once again. Now, they could use simple fire and wind magics, while the flame birds had gained some of the blood hawks’ abilities. This was beyond his expectations.

This was good news to him. The blood hawks were powerful, but they weren’t invincible. They had become predators in the sky because of their strength, size, flying height and speed. But they had a weakness, and that was that they weren’t nimble when they turned in the air. They needed a lot of space to turn around, while the flame birds didn’t. Their wind magic could help them turn more nimbly in a smaller area, like a martial artist that would evade an opponent’s attacks using their agile movements.

Just from their fighting power alone, flame birds wouldn’t lose to blood hawks. Perhaps in equal quantities, they might even win against blood hawks.

However, Zhao Hai didn’t prepare to raise flame birds. Even if he did it now, he couldn’t use them. If he brought out too many of them, it would raise Wales’ suspicions.

Wales watched as Zhao Hai put the flame birds into the space, and he knew that Zhao Hai’s space could store living things. Zhao Hai had told him that it was an oddity art, which made Wales very envious. But if Zhao Hai brought out too many of the flame birds, Wales would know that Zhao Hai’s space could raise magic beasts. It would be too much of a cheat, so Zhao Hai wouldn’t let others know about this easily.

Even though Wales and the rest were moving ahead slowly, after 7 days of travelling at this speed, they still entered the outer territory of the bull-headed races. They could no longer see any pig-headed tribes from here.

Zhao Hai was in his wagon while he curiously asked Wales, who was on the back of his bull, “I’m very curious, big brother. How did you mark the territories? These grasslands all look the same. How do you do it?”

Wales laughed in response, “You don’t know, do you? Although they all look the same to you, in us beastmen’s eyes, every grassland is different. A small river, a small hill, or a dried riverbank, these things can be used as standards for marking territories. The small hill we passed was one of the signs used to mark the boundary between our territory and the pig-headed races’. Common pig-headed races wouldn’t go past that small hill.”

Zhao Hai turned his head to look at where they just went past. To be honest, it really was a simple little hill. If the distance was greater, it would only be just a little slope on the prairie. It was hard to imagine that they could even call such a slope ‘a small hill’.

Zhao Hai asked, “Big brother, how many days remain until we reach the Herculean Bull Tribe if we go from here?”

Wales glanced at the northeast direction and replied, “With our current speed, it’ll take about a month to get to the Herculean Bull Tribe’s main camp.”

Zhao Hai was stunned for a bit. He hadn’t imagined that it was so far away. No wonder Wales wanted to enter the bull-headed races’ territory from here. It was because the main camp of the Herculean Bull Tribe was too far away from here. Even Gasol would be hard-pressed to find them.

Chapter 266: Shocking News: Main Camp Lost

Zhao Hai knew too little about Beastmen Prairie. He hadn’t known that, actually, the size of Beastmen Prairie wasn’t smaller than human lands. This place could truly be called an endless plain of grass.

Wales sighed as he looked northeast, “Our tribe’s main camp has been there for nearly 1000 years. That place was called the Plum Mile, but now, people have already forgotten that name. They can only remember that it is where our main camp is set, called Bull King Camp.”

Wales felt very complicated right now. To be frank, the Herculean Bull Tribe had been more powerful than it was right now. Even the powerful tiger races wouldn’t dare to offend the herculean bulls before.

Now, however, the tribe was not as it had been. Even the fighting bulls were now daring to to challenge the herculean bulls’ might. Wales was very upset because of this.

With Gasol’s recent actions, the fighting bulls had become even worse. Wales didn’t know what to say to Gasol. If he had to call him a huge idiot, sometimes there was a bright side to him. But if he had to say that he was smart, then what about what he had just done? Gasol was truly not so smart.

Zhao Hai honestly liked this prairie a lot. The beastmen who lived on the prairie wouldn’t always have their way. They were busy throughout the whole year, and their lives were far from what other people had romanticized them to be. But to Zhao Hai, all of that wasn’t a problem. He had the space, so he could go there to rest at night. He could watch the blue sky and the white clouds during the day, as well as the endless stretches of green grass. It was an amazingly good feeling.

Just then, a hawk cry came from the sky. Zhao Hai and Wales looked skyward, and saw that it was from 1 of the 5 blood hawks Zhao Hai had gifted Wales.

Wales had now learned how to check the signs of the blood hawks, since they were too important to him. Wales even wished that he could hug them in his sleep.

Wales relaxed after looking at the blood hawks a few more times. He said to Zhao Hai, “50 people. It looks like Bogue and the others have returned. I don’t know what happened to the tribe.”

Zhao Hai nodded, “It should be fine. We’ll know after they get back.”

After he said that, sounds of galloping came from a distance. They were the 50 cavalrymen that Wales had sent to retrieve information from the bull-headed races’ territory.

Bogue was the leader of that cavalry unit of 50, and also a person of ingenuity among the bull-headed races. That was why Wales had felt confident about letting him lead the charge.

When Bogue and his company came near, Wales went idle for a bit. It wasn’t to say that Bogue and the others had injuries, since they didn’t actually appear to have been attacked. What made Wales feel strange was that the expressions on Bogue and the others’ faces were like their families had died.

Wales’ heart skipped a beat after seeing the expressions. He knew that something big had happened in the tribe. Otherwise, there would be no way Bogue and the others would have such expressions.

Soon, Bogue and his company arrived 10 metres in front of Wales. He then rolled down from his mount, yes, rolled, and cried on the ground, face down, unable to say a single word. Other cavalrymen also jumped down from their mounts and cried on their knees.

Wales jumped down from his mount and walked to Bogue’s side. He kicked Bogue to flip him around and scolded, “What are you crying for? Speak. What the hell happened?”

Bogue got up after a while, and then hugged Wales’ thigh and said, “My lord, the Herculean Bull Tribe is gone. The main camp was lost. Nothing! There’s nothing left!”

Wales felt his mind being filled with tremors. It was as if it had just been smashed by a wolftooth club. However, he immediately calmed his emotions and looked at Bogue, “What really happened? Tell us!”

Just then, Mendez and Yale had also walked over, and they looked at Bogue with unpleasant expressions. They too wanted to know what had happened. Why had something like this happen in just a short time?

Bogue then cried out the information which he and the others had heard of. It was just when Gasol had gone to hunt them down, that the Fighting Bull Tribe’s chieftain suddenly led an army to attack the Herculean Bull Tribe’s main camp. Paul, who was Wales’ 2nd brother, had been on guard at the time, but he had failed to protect the camp, and was thus killed in action; while Wales’ younger brothers, 8th and 9th, were killed in the chaos. In the end, the fighting bulls captured the herculean bulls’ main camp, while the remaining herculean bulls had fled towards the deeper parts of the prairie.

By the time Bogue had finished, Wales and the others were stunned. They hadn’t expected that things would take such a turn.

Mendez suddenly asked, “That can’t be! What about the high elders in the tribe? With them, how could the main camp be assaulted by the fighting bulls?”

Bogue answered, “I heard that 1 high elder was killed, and the other was heavily injured. In the course of the fighting bulls’ attack, there seemed to be a human mage among them. It was a level 9 human mage who injured the remaining high elder.”

Wales and the others were shocked, as they hadn’t anticipated human intervention in this matter. It was far beyond their expectations.

Humans usually wouldn’t interfere in conflicts between beastmen, because once they did that, it would be like treating the beastmen as their enemies. The battle races wouldn’t let go of anyone, let alone a level 9 expert. Any level 9 human who attempted to make a mess out of the beastmen’s territories would be hunted down by level 9 beastmen for sure.

Wales frowned and asked, “Bogue, is this information truly valid? Was there really a human in the mix? What did they do?”

Bogue shook his head. This information was something he had heard, and right now, rumors were flying around. They couldn’t know if all of this was true or false.

Wales curled his brows and asked Yale, “Whether or not humans have taken part in this, what we can be sure of is that something has happened to the main camp. Otherwise, there wouldn’t be such rumors going about. What should we do, teacher?”

Wales had calmed down right now. He had been very shocked when he had heard this information, but he had already known that the fighting bulls had been plotting against them from the start. He just hadn’t expected that the fighting bulls would make their move so soon.

Yale had calmed down as well. Although many things had happened to the Herculean Bull Tribe, none had been as shocking as this.

When a ruling race couldn’t keep its own main camp, then it wouldn’t have the right to be called the ruling race anymore. It could be said that the fighting bulls were now the ruling race, which, of course, still needed the approval of the other races on the prairie.

The conflicts between beastmen were realistic, and as such, they only respected the strong and the victorious. But, if this matter had humans meddling in the process, it wouldn’t fare well for the fighting bulls either.

Yale thought about it and said, “What we need to do right now is to set up camp here. We’ll leave the bull-headed races’ territory tomorrow and make our way deeper into the prairie. We’ll send someone to make contact with West Wonder King and find out what’s going on.”

Wales frowned, “It’s not likely going to work, is it? If things are really as the rumors suggest, then the presence of herculean bulls in the bull-headed races’ territory will surely attract a lot of attention. I’m afraid we won’t be able to make contact with West Wonder King.”

Yale nodded at that. Beastmen wouldn’t need to look at battle flags in order to tell different races apart. It could be said that right now, the herculean bulls were at the top of the rumor mill. If the herculean bulls made any movements on the bull-headed races’ territory, they wouldn’t be able to do anything because of all the attention.

Just then, Zhao Hai said, “I think you can leave the information-gathering to me. I have a human merchant identity, and I’ll be able to move around freely on the prairie. It’s not likely that the fighting bulls have any news about me. What do you think, big brother?”

Wales did a double take and then nodded. Indeed, only human merchants could move around freely and undiscovered on the prairie.

Although Zhao Hai and Wales were now blood-sworn brothers, and Gasol knew that someone had used undead to help Wales, the fighting bulls had no way of knowing about any of that. Because the fighting bulls had ransacked the herculean bulls’ main camp when Gasol was fighting the undead, Gasol would naturally not go back to the main camp, while the 1500 warriors loaned to him had all been turned into undead creatures, which couldn’t possibly report back to their former brethren. So right now, the fighting bulls shouldn’t know about the relationship between Zhao Hai and Wales.

Yale nodded, “That’s a good idea. Little Hai can get information while making contact with West Wonder King. He must be in trouble these days. It’s good that you had gifted the cane to little Hai. If little Hai presents the cane to West Wonder King to prove his identity, then West Wonder King will be able to trust him.”

Wales nodded, “This is also an opportunity. The Herculean bulls have been chased out of the main camp due to Gasol’s actions, but I think that a majority of their strength can still be preserved. What we need to do right now is find the escapees and regroup them. Now is the time they need a leader, and Gasol obviously cannot be their leader even if he finds them. Perhaps they might even kill him. This is our chance.”

Yale and Mendez both nodded at that. All of this had been caused by Gasol, so how could the herculean bulls not hate him? If Gasol appeared in front of them, he would surely be torn to shreds by the angry mob. If the ever-popular Wales could stand up in the tribe, he would surely be able to become the chieftain.

Chapter 267: Who Was It?

Wales knew that being a chieftain wouldn’t be easy. The herculean bulls had been chased out, so they must be lacking in food and clothing right now. Being the chieftain under such circumstances, and having to shoulder the hatred towards the fighting bulls on top of that, Wales could tell the difficulty of the tasks he had to face.

However, he neither wanted to back away, nor did he have a means to. He was a prince of the herculean bulls. His race was his roots. If his race prospered, he too would gain respect. If their face fell, then he too would be nothing.

Zhao Hai nodded, “I think this is a good opportunity as well, but you will surely come across a lot of tough issues, and there’s nothing much I can help you with. How about this? Laura, Meg, Nier, give me your pouches. Big brother, Mr. Yale and 6th brother, give me yours as well.”

Wales and the other 2 knew what Zhao Hai was going to do, and they gave him their pouches. Zhao Hai didn’t say anything as he simply filled all 6 pouches with grains.

After filling the pouches, Zhao Hai gave them to Wales, “Take these first, big brother. Give them to your tribesmen as soon as you find them, and then have your blood hawks come to me for grains. We have to improve this situation first.”

Wales didn’t hold back and just took the pouches. He patted Zhao Hai’s shoulder and said, “Brother, I will not say much. We’ll rest here for the day and leave tomorrow. If anything happens, we’ll contact each other using blood hawks.”

Zhao Hai nodded, “Just tell me whatever supplies you need. I can have blood hawks bring the pouches to my fief and back. It’s now the tribe’s most difficult time, and a lot of things are required. You must persist. Oh, once you return, help me prepare a map. I don’t want to go looking for West Wonder King all over the place.”

Wales smiled, “Relax, brother, I’ll take care of it.” He then glanced at Bogue and his company, “Don’t just sob on the ground. Stand up. We herculean bulls haven’t gone extinct yet. Remember that as long as we’re not gone, we are the ruling race of the bull-headed races, and we always will be.”

Bogue and the others stood up, bearing murderous expressions because of Wales’ words. Wales nodded, having been filled with fighting spirit. It was because of Zhao Hai’s support, whose grains had become his life-saving herbs.

As long as one had grains on Beastmen Prairie, one could do a lot of things. Just as Zhao Hai had said, it was the most difficult time for the Herculean Bull Tribe. Their own main camp had been lost, and 2 of their high elders had been killed or injured. Zhao Hai had to assist Wales properly as a blood-sworn brother under these circumstances.

It was then that Zhao Hai suddenly thought of something. He took out 2 things from the space immediately. He had them stored in bottles before giving them to Wales.

Wales looked at the 2 bottles in his hand with confusion. One of them seemed to contain water, and the other held a pink liquid, which he knew nothing about.

Zhao Hai explained to Wales, “Big brother, in these 2 bottles, one of them is the Liquid Of Life, which Mr. Yale had given me. I don’t have a use for it, but the flask that he gave me was very beautiful, so I kept it. Another bottle is a type of medicine that can treat injuries. Bogue just said that your high elder was injured, so I hope these 2 things can help him. Without the high elder’s support, it won’t be easy for you to deal with the fighting bulls.” Actually, the ‘medicine’ which Zhao Hai mentioned was magic peach juice. Greene had used 1 last time, and there had been 1 left, which Zhao Hai was now giving to Wales.

Wales looked at Zhao Hai without knowing what to say. Zhao Hai had been too great of a help to him, and now, he even brought out the Liquid Of Life. Now he felt that no matter what he would do, he would never be able to repay Zhao Hai’s kindness.

Wales took the 2 bottles in silence and put them away carefully. He patted Zhao Hai’s shoulder and turned to command his people in setting up camp.

Zhao Hai said nothing and went to set up camp as well. At this point, words would be excessive. He had to give Wales and his people time, in order to let him plan things out properly.

Zhao Hai and the others sat inside the tent quietly after it was set up. Laura poured a cup of coya for Zhao Hai, then frowned, “Hai-bro, it’s not a good thing for us right now when the Herculean Bull Tribe is in such trouble. What are we going to do next?”

Zhao Hai closed his eyes and said after thinking, “I keep feeling that something’s not right. What Mendez said after Gasol started his coup was that Gasol and the human merchants were being too secretive in their contact. Now, when the fighting bulls attacked the Herculean Bull Tribe, humans showed up again. Don’t you think that human activity has been too frequent on Beastmen Prairie as of late?”

Laura concurred in her thoughts. How many times was it that they had heard about humans meddling in beastmen affairs? This was too strange.

Meg frowned and spoke, “What does this mean, young master? Can it be that there’s a human force seeking to take control of beastmen?”

Zhao Hai shook his head, “It can’t be. Humans can’t possibly control beastmen. There has to be a reason for beastmen and humans to be locked in conflict for so many years. Do not presume that humans look like they’re controlling the beastmen using food. That’s because they have no other option. If they don’t give them enough food, they’ll start wars, and the food will be taken anyway, so it’s impossible for humans to use this method to control beastmen. But as for why human activity has been so frequent lately, I still can’t get a good idea.”

Laura frowned, “I can’t get a good grasp of it either. Don’t they fear beastmen retaliation? Even though the fighting bulls have taken over the herculean bulls’ main camp, their strength shouldn’t be too great. The ones who are really in charge of the prairie are the major battle races, and the cooperation between the fighting bulls and humans will greatly incite them. Do the fighting bulls think that they have the ability to withstand the pressure from the battle races?

Zhao Hai’s frown continued, “I don’t have a good idea why they’re doing this. Their methods are very likely going to make them the public enemies of all the beastmen, so why? Is it only just for the sake of being called the ruling race?”

Laura and the others were at a loss as to why the fighting bulls were doing what they were. It would be discernable if the fighting bulls were cooperating with common humans. However, a strange picture had been painted when the humans they cooperated with had a level 9 powerhouse.

Since when had it become the time for level 9 human powerhouses to come and mess around on Beastmen Prairie? When the battle races got the news, they would surely react. It wasn’t known how the fighting bulls would respond to that.

Zhao Hai spoke out after a while of sitting, “No matter how much we guess right now, it’s useless. Just reaching the fighting bulls’ turf and prodding around will do. I just feel that this matter isn’t so simple.”

Laura looked at Zhao Hai with incomprehension, “How so? Can it be something related to us?”

Zhao Hai shook his head, “It shouldn’t be. If this matter is really related to us, then it can only be our enemies who are trying to deal with us on the prairie. Our current main enemies are the Magidell family, the Church Of Light, and Southern King. The Church Of Light will not have any grip on the prairie, and there’s no direct profit-&-loss relationship between Southern King and beastmen. Magidell family is a business family, and there are a lot of business opportunities on the prairie. It’s impossible for them to just watch other people do business here, but I think that even they wouldn’t have the guts to send a level 9 powerhouse to hunt us down on the prairie, right?”

Laura nodded. She knew clearly what Magidell family was like. All they cared about was profit. Now that Zhao Hai and the others had left Fansile duchy, there had been no way for Magidell family to obtain profits from Zhao Hai. They wouldn’t pay a large price to hire a level 9 powerhouse to deal with Zhao Hai under these circumstances, since it wouldn’t fit their principles of merchants seeking profit.

But why did she keep feeling that these matters were happening so close to them? Before they had entered the prairie, it seemed that such a thing had never happened before. But the moment they had entered, all of this had happened. This was too contrived, wasn’t it?

Meg asked, “Young master, do you think that someone is trying to act upon the Herculean Bull Tribe, like how someone acted upon the Black Bear Tribe, and that’s why all of this happened?”

Zhao Hai shook his head, “It can’t be. The Herculean Bull Tribe’s strength doesn’t seem to be as great as the Black Bear-…… Wait a minute. There IS a possibility.”

Zhao Hai turned to look at Laura, and Laura looked at Zhao Hai in confusion. Zhao Hai said, “Beastmen have gotten it badly from humans in recent years. Can it be that beastmen are setting their sights on humans again, yet the humans received word about it and sent people to stir things up beforehand, in order to mess up the waters here so that the beastmen don’t have time to mobilize against humans?”

Laura frowned, “Not too likely, right? Trades between humans and beastmen have been going along smoothly, and there haven’t been great disasters on the prairie. They shouldn’t have any reason to mobilize against humans. Besides, humans wouldn’t mess things up by sending a level 9 powerhouse. That’s basically a declaration of war against beastmen.”

Zhao Hai nodded and sighed, “Forget it. I’m done guessing. We might not guess things right anyway. What we have to do right now is help big brother get information. If we take care of the fighting bulls, we’ll be closer to figuring out which human force is cooperating with them.”

Laura nodded, but she believed that it would be very difficult. The Herculean Bull Tribe was greatly crippled right now, and the fighting bulls were now on a roll. Exterminate the Fighting Bull Tribe? Difficult!

Chapter 268: Mastiffs

Compared to Zhao Hai, Wales was currently in a bigger dilemma. What he and his people had to face was a crisis. It was something he didn’t want to see, but one that he had to face no matter what.

Wales sat in his tent as a large cup of milk wine had been put in front of him. He had actually drunk 5 cups, and this was the 6th.

Mendez wasn’t any better. In fact, he had already started to drink the 8th cup. Only Yale was normal, but he was sitting there without a single word.

The news which Bogue had brought back was too shocking. They hadn’t expected that the main camp of herculean bulls, which had been inhabited for generations, had been lost. How could they face this?

Fortunately, Wales had self-restraint, so he didn’t drink any further. After downing the 6th cup, he stopped, but he still said nothing. None of the 3 who had entered the tent had spoken anything.

Wales raised his head to look at Yale after a while and said, “Teacher, what do you think Gasol is doing right now?”

Yale wouldn’t think that Wales was caring about Gasol, of course. Right now, Wales wanted Gasol to die right in front of him badly. There was no way he would care about him.

Yale sighed and said, “It’s really hard to say. If my guess is correct, then I fear that the reason why the Fighting Bull Tribe had loaned troops to Gasol, was because of having the intention to eliminate him after what is done. Kill us with Gasol’s hands, and then kill Gasol with the loaned troops, while taking over the main camp. By then, the Herculean Bull Tribe will not have the spine to threaten the Fighting Bull Tribe. The act of eliminating the fighting bull cavalry happened to help Gasol for a time.”

SPLACK!

Mendez smashed the small table in front of him into pieces, and the silver cup was also flattened. He looked at Yale with blood red eyes and said, “I better not know where he is. If I do, I will gouge him with my own hands!”

Wales took a deep breath and asked, “Teacher, where do you think the tribesmen would go?”

Yale thought for a bit and replied, “Right now, there are 2 places which they could’ve gone. One is West Wonder King’s place, but I think they wouldn’t go there. He’s a fighting bull after all, and right now, the fighting bulls are in a momentum, so they would have no guarantees there. Which leaves only one more place to go: the Mastiff Tribe.”

Wales agreed to Yale’s perspective. The Herculean Bull Tribe had always had a good relationship with the Mastiff Tribe. The Mastiff Tribe had helped the Herculean Bull Tribe for many times in the past. Now that something had happened, the herculean bulls would naturally head over to the mastiffs for refuge.

The mastiffs were a very unique race. They were the ruling race of dog-headed races, which were between battle races and civil races. The fighting power of the entire race was slightly worse than wolf race, but stronger than civil races. Relatively speaking, their position was a little higher than bull-headed races.

The Herculean Bull Tribe and the Mastiff Tribe had always maintained a good relationship. The Mastiff Tribe had helped Herculean Bull Tribe for a lot of times in the past, so now that the Herculean Bull Tribe had gotten into trouble, they would surely head over to the Mastiff Tribe.

Wales took in a deep breath and said, “Well then, our next move is to go around the horse races’ turf and go to the Mastiff Tribe.”

Yale nodded to that. The turf of bull-headed races was adjacent to the turfs of horse races, pig races, dog races and cat races. The relationship between Herculean Bull Tribe, pig tribes and horse tribes was normal; neither good nor bad. Because of being good with mastiffs, it ended up spelling a negative with cats, due to how cat and dog races had never gotten along.

And now, Wales and his men were at the point where the borders of the pig-headed races and the bull-headed races met. There were only 2 ways they could go to the Mastiff Tribe: one was to go through the bull-headed races’ turf, while the other was to circle it via the horse races’ turf. They wouldn’t go to the cat races’ turf as it was too dangerous, and the same was now true for the bull-headed races’ territory. The only choice left was to move into the turf of horses.

Wales glanced at Yale and said, “We have to trouble you to draw a map for little Hai, teacher. Our time is limited, but please be as detailed as possible. Just letting him know how to get to West Wonder King’s place is enough.”

Yale nodded, “No problems there. We still have to thank little Hai for this. If it weren’t for him, we would’ve been in a more difficult spot by now.”

Wales nodded at that and sighed, “I never thought at the beginning that just a single trial of travelling would be followed by all these events. But luckily, I met little Hai. Something gained, something lost, I guess.”

Yale gave Wales a look and said, “Wales, I don’t think now’s the time to speak of this. We can only keep little Hai’s help inside our hearts. We still have to think about how to proceed after reaching the Mastiff Tribe’s turf right now. Even though our tribes’ relationship is great, do not forget that our tribe has fallen from the spot of the ruling race. It’s hard to say for sure how the mastiffs will treat us now.”

Wales ceased his thoughts for the moment. He knew that their gratitude towards Zhao Hai was not something that could be paid in words. In his heart, Zhao Hai was like his birth sibling. It would be acting like strangers if he kept speaking of it as something they owed him for. Just as Yale said, he should be thinking about what to do when meeting the mastiffs.

Beastmen were simplistic, yet even they would have politics among them. It was a fact. Wales had made contact with the mastiffs for several times in the past, but during those times, they were as equals. Both sides were rulers. Even though the herculean bulls felt grateful, they wouldn’t feel as if they were inferior.

It was like how either of the 2 good friends were living a little better and offered a little help. The other friend would be grateful, but there wouldn’t be a sense of inferiority.

But that had changed now. The herculean bulls were now refugees who had lost their homes. They had no right to speak with the mastiffs as equals. How the mastiffs would treat them was something that needed his proper consideration.

Wales thought about this silently with closed eyes. To be honest, he didn’t have enough capital to operate on. He didn’t know how many herculean bulls escaped, and what the situation was in the tribe. The amount of supplies left, the quantity of argali remaining, were unknown to him.

His only capital right now was the grains which Zhao Hai had given him. Endless supply of food was the final thing he could depend on.

Wales looked at Yale and said, “I think that right now, the only thing we can offer is the grains that little Hai gave us. But we cannot let him be in too much of a disadvantage from this. I’m saying, once we reach the mastiffs, let’s see how they treat our people first. If they’re treating them well, we can introduce little Hai to them and have him trade with them. I think they’ll be very happy to. since his grains are very cheap. If they’re not treating our people well, then we’ll give them some grains and leave, before settling down in a horse race or pig race’s turf. What do you think, teacher?”

Yale nodded, “Only in the worst of disasters can we peer into the true nature of people. If the mastiffs are truly friends, then we’ll just introduce little Hai to them. His existence is something every beastman can only dream of. If they are friends, then we have to treat our friends well.”

Wales nodded, “We have absolutely no idea about the situation in the tribe. I just hope it’s not too dire.”

Both of them sighed at the same time. They knew that Wales was consoling himself. The situation of a race that had been chased out of their hometown was easily imaginable. It was not unlike being bankrupt. It was possible that other than their own selves, weapons and mounts, there were nothing else.

Out of things to discuss, Yale returned to his own tent and started drafting a map for Zhao Hai. However, because he had too little time, he couldn’t afford to be too detailed. He could only mark the location of West Wonder King’s campsite and some obvious geographical landmarks along the way.

The next morning, Yale gave the map which he had drawn overnight to Zhao Hai. Zhao Hai found the map to be decent. There was no indication of range, but at least it pointed a general direction and some famous landmarks were marked on it. Even tribes that could possibly be encountered were written on it.

Zhao Hai kept the map and looked at Yale who had bloodshot eyes, “Thank you Mr. Yale. Take care of yourselves, big brother. If there’s anything, contact me with the blood hawks right away. Just attach a letter to them. They can find me.”

Wales gave Zhao Hai a strong hug, “Brother, I’m not going to say thankful words now. You must take care. If the bull-headed races really want to make a move against you, don’t hold back and unleash the undead creatures. This is Beastmen Prairie, and the Fighting Bull Tribe is now the ruling tribe. They might use this authority to act against you.”

Zhao Hai laughed, “Relax. If they really dare, it would be like gifting me new subordinates, and my underlings will grow more and more. It’s nothing to be afraid of. Alright, have a safe trip, big brother.”

Wales nodded before leading his people on the trip. Watching his back, Zhao Hai sighed, “Big brother has to deal with a lot of things this time.”

Laura nodded, “I hope he can make it through. Only then, can he be the best ruler of the herculean bulls.”

Zhao Hai smiled, “I believe that under his leadership, the herculean bulls will get better and better. We can help him no matter what difficulty he faces, hehe. With a powerful collaborator, Beastman Prairie will be ours in the future.”

Laura was also happy. She understood that Zhao Hai was definitely not helping Wales out of brotherly relationship. On Beastmen Prairie, in order to do business properly, it would be impossible to lack a powerful collaborator. Although Zhao Hai was paying out right now, once Wales got into position and the Herculean Bull Tribe developed, the gains he would get would not just end at dozens of times the cost or more than that.

Zhao Hai smiled after looking at the sky, “We should leave too. Whew. To be frank, I’m really lifted from a burden today. Following Wales and his people everyday makes it really inconvenient to return to the space or Iron Mountain Castle.

Laura, Meg and Nier laughed at that. They too had felt inconvenienced. Even though they rested inside the space every night, it couldn’t be compared to moving around freely.

The convoy slowly travelled forward, and Zhao Hai once again put the large-bellied pigs’ friendship flag on top of his wagon. He didn’t get a flag from Wales, as right now, it was best not to raise the friendship flag of herculean bulls.

Wales had also been aware of this, so in order to avoid giving Zhao Hai trouble, he himself didn’t give him the friendship flag. Zhao Hai wanted to find West Wonder King’s campsite as quickly as possible, so he proceeded according to the map directly.

Although the map had no ratios, the amount of days needed to move from one landmark to the next was noted, so Zhao Hai wasn’t worried about going the wrong way.

It was in order to help Wales obtain information, but Zhao Hai wasn’t in a hurry. He knew it very clearly that the cow races were in a sensitive period. If he asked around carelessly, he would surely attract suspicion. At worst, he might come into conflict with them.

As beastmen were extremely cautious towards humans from the start, Zhao Hai believed that everything should be done with maintaining the cover as top priority in such a sensitive period of time.

After a day, Zhao Hai and the others hadn’t found a single tribe, but the map looked legit. They needed at least 3 days of travelling until they could come across a tribe. Of course, it was just speculation. A tribe might’ve been active at the surroundings, but beastmen were often moving around, so Yale also wasn’t sure if a tribe would really be there.

Now, it was the busiest time of the year on Beastmen Prairie, because they were about to enter winter. They had to prepare the grass feeds and the food needed to live past winter, so a lot of beastmen tribes would migrate around to prepare those things. Yale was a prophet, but even he couldn’t know all of the tribes like the back of his hand. If he could, he wouldn’t be a prophet, but a god instead.

Zhao Hai and his company returned to Iron Mountain Castle that night, and discussed the changes of the Herculean Bull Tribe to Greene and the others. Greene and the others believed that what Zhao Hai had done was not mistaken. Now that the Herculean Bull Tribe was in trouble, it was the best time to offer a helping hand. They would be grateful for life.

Chapter 269: Large-horned Raging Bulls

Greene and the others felt very strange concerning the appearance of humans on Beastmen Prairie, but they couldn’t get a handle on the situation over there, so they naturally couldn’t guess why humans would show up there.

Zhao Hai hadn’t wanted to get answers from Greene and the others, as they had never been to Beastmen Prairie. What they had known was told to them by Laura, so if they could guess what the humans were up to, they would be able to pose as prophets after some makeup.

The next morning, Zhao Hai and his company continued on their journey, but at a faster pace. He wanted to go faster, so long as they didn’t encounter any beastman tribe.

He hadn’t come to Beastmen Prairie to cause a ruckus. Helping Wales would bring him a lot of benefits, but what he needed more was new and unique magic beasts, and never before seen plants. Those were his fundamental reasons from the start.

Everything would be fine as long as the space levelled up, so Zhao Hai picked up his pace. However, he didn’t put the convoy into the space this time. After all, none of the coachdrivers were mortal to begin with.

On the prairie, you wouldn’t need to worry about your wagon crashing sideways. There were plenty of grasses that were thicker than rugs, which acted as natural shock absorbers, so that your wagon would never be too bumpy. However, your horses would need greater strength in order to pull the wagon as a result. But this wasn’t an issue for Zhao Hai, since the wagon-pulling animals were undead creatures.

Although Zhao Hai and his company increased their speed, they paid cautious attention to their surroundings for enemies. He had let out 2 flame birds in order to act as aerial recon.

Of course, just a couple of the birds would not be enough for him. He still let out a lot of blood hawks to engage in reconnaissance. Flame birds weren’t phantasmal beasts, so Zhao Hai couldn’t use them as easily as he did the blood hawks. However, flame birds were beautiful, and Laura, Meg and Nier liked them a lot, so he let them out and kept them as pets. If Wales saw the birds, he would just say that he had treated their injuries.

Zhao Hai watched the map while he was rushing on, and the size of the map in the space was increasing without stopping. This was good news to him. If he wandered around the prairie a lot, perhaps he would be the first person to have a complete map of Beastmen Prairie.

Zhao Hai and his company spent just 1 and ½ days to finish a 3-day trip. He couldn’t afford not to slow down when he reached an area marked on the map as having a tribe.

The marked tribe was a small one of raging bulls, which should number about 1000 people. Raging bulls were also known for their strength, and their mounts were the namesake bulls. However, the bulls were not quite the same as the the ones meant to be eaten on the continent. They were called large-horned raging bulls. They were a type of unique bovines, due to their horns being too big.

The large horns of these magic beasts were like sharpened wooden pillars. Every horn was up to 2 meters long, and the thickest they could get was a staggering half meter. They were very straight, and they grew out horizontally, like a pillar was strapped onto a cow’s head.

The raging bull race was very famous among the bull-headed races because of their cavalry charges. Their mounts, the large-horned raging bulls, might not be too fast, but once they charged, they were imposing. All because of their large horns.

When they charged, they would form a straight line. All of their horns put together was like a moving wall. The speed wasn’t very fast, but there wasn’t the slightest gap.

But this didn’t mean that the Large-Horned Raging Bull Tribe’s fighting power was great. Although such a cavalry charge was imposing, it also had a very serious flaw. Because of how large the horns were, the cavalry couldn’t change directions quickly, so the cavalry would be at a serious disadvantage when facing agile light cavalry like the jackals’.

The Large-Horned Raging Bull Tribe could be considered as a branch of the raging bull races, yet famously, their temper among the bull-headed races was anything but short. They were in the category of good guys.

Of course, none of this was written on the map which he had been given by Yale. All of it had been researched by Laura herself.

Zhao Hai was waiting for the blood hawks and the information they might be carrying. Now that they had entered the Large-Horned Raging Bull Tribe’s area of frequent activity, since Zhao Hai and the others could run into them at any moment, he let the birds increase their recon radius in order to ensure that he wasn’t going the wrong way.

The blood hawks returned after more than an hour. Zhao Hai took a glance, and noticed that they were going in circles and crying out without stopping. He turned to Laura and said, “There’s an abandoned campsite ahead. It looks like it was attacked. Let’s take a look.”

Laura nodded, and the convoy picked up the pace once more. After more than 2 hours, they discovered the abandoned campsite. There were a lot of corpses there, and all of them were the Large-Horned Raging Bull Tribe and their mounts.

The tribesmen were very similar to their mounts: tall and having large horns. The horns were longer than any other bull-headed races’ horns.

From the look of the campsite, it appeared to be of a size for about 1000 people. However, it had been attacked, and every usable thing had been taken away. Even the clothes on the dead had been stripped off.

Zhao Hai looked at this with a frown and a sigh as with a wave of his hand, he turned them all into undead creatures. He only turned one of them into a high-level undead, in order to know who it was that had attacked this campsite.

Zhao Hai counted for a bit. The tribesmen who had died amounted to more than 300. The number of youths this tribe could afford to send into battle was approximately this figure. He just picked the strongest of them all and turned him into a high-level undead, because he knew that among beastmen, the strongest ones had often been the chieftains.

Just as he had expected, the high-level undead was called Abatai, the chieftain of this tribe. Their tribe had more than 1300 people, and other than 400 youths, the rest were the elderly and women.

Their fate was normal. What surprised Zhao Hai was the ones who had attacked them. It was none other than Gasol and his people, and the attack had taken place more than 4 hours ago.

In other words, right before the blood hawks had discovered this campsite, it had been attacked by Gasol and his people. Upon reaching this conclusion, Zhao Hai immediately put Abatai and the others into the space, and followed the trail left behind by Gasol and his people.

From the trail, the direction they were headed to was most likely West Wonder King’s place. It seemed that Gasol too had learned of what had happened to the Herculean Bull Tribe’s main camp, but he wasn’t as smart as Wales, who headed over to the Mastiff Tribe’s place.

Zhao Hai couldn’t help but shake his head, as he truly felt that Gasol wasn’t a smart person. The relationship between Gasol and West Wonder King had never been good, and yet he was now going to put himself under West Wonder King’s service. Obviously, Gasol had seen how West Wonder King and the current Fighting Bull Tribe chieftain were at odds, but he had forgotten that circumstances determined how people would move. Now that the Herculean Bull Tribe could no longer provide the Fighting Bull Tribe with any form of help, it was hard to determine what sort of attitude West Wonder King would have in treating them.

But after another thought, this situation made sense to Zhao Hai. He knew of Gasol’s pain. The reason why the Herculean Bull Tribe had gotten to this point was all because of him. Perhaps he had thought about where his tribesmen would go. But what would happen even after finding them? He would only be torn into pieces by angry tribesmen, and no one would listen to him, so he could only head over to West Wonder King’s place.

It just wasn’t a good choice, Zhao Hai thought. Gasol had only several dozen guards, but from how they had attacked the Large-Horned Raging Bull Tribe, their fighting power was still great. Gasol should’ve left the bull-headed races’ territory, as staying here was only akin to waiting for death. Even if he got West Wonder King’s support, he wouldn’t be a threat to the Fighting Bull Tribe. Perhaps the Fighting Bull Tribe had never seen West Wonder King as a threat. Otherwise, the Fighting Bull Tribe wouldn’t have attacked the Herculean Bull Tribe’s main camp.

However, Zhao Hai wasn’t letting these thoughts sway his judgement. He didn’t care what Gasol’s thoughts were. What he needed to do right now was to charge forward, grab Gasol, and send a letter to Wales in order to ask about how to deal with him.

Right now, he was blood-sworn brother of Wales, not Gasol, so of course he wanted to help Wales. Whether Gasol lived or died was not within his range of concerns.

Most importantly, he had to think about the ground bulls which Gasol and his men were riding. Although he couldn’t get a hold of stoneskin bulls, ground bulls would be fine too.

Zhao Hai believed that Gasol wouldn’t be fast while bringing a lot of people with him. The latter must be having hard days. Otherwise, he wouldn’t have raided the Large-Horned Raging Bull Tribe.

Zhao Hai’s speed wasn’t slow. The wagon pullers were all high-level undead creatures. It wouldn’t be difficult to catch up to Gasol.

In order to confirm Gasol’s travel direction, he sent out his blood hawks once more, with flame birds added, of course. Now that the flame birds were his, they shouldn’t have any reaction upon seeing Gasol.

After more than 3 hours, Zhao Hai finally managed to track down Gasol’s figure. Only 2 hours later, before nightfall, he and his convoy would be able to catch up to Gasol and his men.

Chapter 270: Regretful Gasol

Zhao Hai wasn’t in a hurry after discovering Gasol, however. He started to slow down. They could catch up to Gasol after 2 hours, but it wouldn’t be nightfall by then, so it would be very bad for his attack. In any case, Gasol was a level 8 powerhouse. Without Zhao Wen and Cai-Er’s help, he wouldn’t be able to suppress him in a short amount of time.

Meanwhile, Zhao Hai was also thinking about how to deal with the Large-Horned Raging Bull Tribe’s people. Now that the tribe had lost most of its youths, this matter would definitely be a disaster for them.

If they were taken away by Gasol as they were, they would surely end up as slaves. But if Gasol didn’t care about them, their days would not be any better. Winter was about to arrive, so without the majority of their youths, there was no way they could prepare enough feeding grasses, and they had not yet migrated to a place where they could withstand the coldness of the winter. In such circumstances, it was unlikely that they would survive this winter.

Zhao Hai was sitting inside the wagon while looking at Laura with a frown, “What do you think we should do, Laura? How should we treat the Large-Horned Raging Bull Tribe’s people?”

Laura’s brows curled as she said, “They are now considered slaves. Even if we save them, their lives will not be any better. Instead, they will still become slaves if they come across other tribes. This is a really tough matter.”

Zhao Hai sighed, “As I suspected. The prairie has its own rules, but I didn’t expect that when a tribe has lost and becomes enslaved, sometimes that can be their only chance at life. What should we do with these people? Send them to Iron Mountain Castle as slaves?”

Laura was at a loss as well. Unlike the situations before where the slaves had been bought, and didn’t have any loyalty issues, the Large-Horned Raging Bull Tribe’s people were people who had been defeated in combat before being made slaves. It was hard to tell how many of them would be willing to become their slaves.

Laura looked at Zhao Hai, “Hai-bro, how about we bring them to West Wonder King’s place? If we deliver them to him, won’t they be able to safely get through this winter?”

Zhao Hai shook his head, “No. Right now, we still don’t know about his stance towards the attack on the Herculean Bull Tribe. Even if we find him, we’ll still have to observe him instead of making an immediate approach. If we bring the Large-Horned Raging Bull Tribe’s people, how will we explain where they are coming from? If we say they were seized by force, then whose hands did we seize them from? How? Besides, will West Wonder King think that we’re outside help, just like the humans hired by the Fighting Bull Tribe? The prairie has its own rules. If we just put our hands around inadvertently, it will not end well.”

Just then, Meg spoke, “What are you thinking so much about, young master? They have nowhere else to go right now, and they are considered slaves, so let them be our slaves. They won’t run away after being put into the castle, and nothing will happen if grandpa Greene keeps watch. We also have enough food to feed them, so why not?”

Zhao Hai was stunned for a bit, while Laura nodded, “That’s the best solution thus far. Gasol and his men attacked them and made them his slaves. We defeat Gasol, get his spoils, and they will become our slaves. Then, whatever we do to them is our business, and Iron Mountain Castle is an enclosed environment. It just so happens that putting them there can make them get used to life over there. There won’t be any problems as long as they don’t run away.”

Zhao Hai nodded his head. He had finally discovered something different from Earth in Ark Continent: people who had been given a slave status would be treated as merchandise and sorted at will. It was already inappropriate to view them from the angle that everyone was equal.

Zhao Hai had been thinking to release them after their rescue, but he had never thought that they had already become slaves, who were to be treated as other people willed whether they liked it or not.

If they were slaves, it wouldn’t be hard for Zhao Hai to process them. With Greene and Cai-Er’s supervision and the undead creatures guarding Iron Mountain Castle, the Large-Horned Raging Bull tribesmen would expect to leave? It would be almost impossible.

Zhao Hai nodded, “Very well then. Let’s do that. I don’t think they’ll be able to run away while grandpa Greene and the others are handling them.

Laura nodded, “We’ll have to notify them and let them make preparations. It’s more than 1000 people, after all. Preparations will be necessary.”

Zhao Hai nodded and turned to Meg. “Meg, go tell grandpa Greene about it, or else they might have their hands tied.” After that, he sent Meg into the space, and from there to Iron Mountain Castle.

Zhao Hai and the others didn’t stop. They just moved slowly in Gasol’s direction. He knew that Gasol couldn’t possibly be in a hurry at night, and he would surely stop and take a rest. If Gasol stopped, Zhao Hai could attack immediately.

As the sky gradually darkened, Zhao Hai’s convoy pushed forward, while the blood hawks were still tracking Gasol’s movements in the sky. Perhaps it was due to how Gasol wanted to reach West Wonder King’s place sooner that he and his men didn’t stop at night. Instead, their wagons had lit torches placed on them.

Although this was somewhat out of Zhao Hai’s expectations, it turned out to be much easier for the blood hawks to track him down, because beastmen didn’t usually rush around at night.

As the sky turned completely back, Zhao Hai knew it was time to make his move, as there wouldn’t be any beastmen that might come and witness the fighting between him and Gasol right now. Whether or not Gasol was rushing was no longer important.

Zhao Hai’s convoy increased its speed while he unleashed his undead creatures. He didn’t release undead beasts this time, because they were protecting Black Wastelands. Instead, he released the newly-acquired 1500 fighting bull and 2000 jackal cavalry.

Also not being released were the undead mercenaries. They were infantry, so their speed would never be as fast as that of cavalry. Zhao Hai put the convoy into the space, while he, Laura and Nier sat inside Xenomorph’s body.

Because Wales wasn’t around them this time, all the undead creatures present besides Xenomorph were in their zombie state.

Gasol was sitting gloomily on the back of his mount while his escorts were maintaining the order of his march. Most of his convoy were the weak and elderly, so their speed wasn’t fast. Just a while ago, he had killed an elderly large-horned raging bull because he couldn’t walk any longer due to his age. This infuriated the raging bull tribesmen deeply, but they didn’t dare to voice their rage.

The large-horned raging bulls knew about the rules of the prairie. They were now Gasol’s properties, and Gasol was the one in charge of their survival. Unless they could win against him, they had no choice but to accept their slavery.

Gasol felt like he was about to go insane, and truly so. He didn’t understand why things would turn out like this. The Fighting Bull Tribe, which had been on good terms with him, had suddenly occupied his main camp. When Gasol had heard the news, he had been angered to the point of vomiting blood where he stood.

It was then that Gasol had finally understood that he had fallen into the Fighting Bull Tribe’s trap from the beginning. He knew that he was finished, and would never be able to return to the Herculean Bull Tribe, so he wanted to find West Wonder King.

West Wonder King had never been satisfied with the way the current fighting bull chieftain did things. With the support of Herculean Bull Tribe, he had broken away from the chieftain’s rule and been opposed to it ever since. Gasol hoped that he could use this to borrow some troops to fight against the Fighting Bull Tribe to the very end.

It wasn’t until now that Gasol finally had a trace of regret. He truly regretted killing his father, and he felt that he really shouldn’t have hunted Wales and Mendez down.

It had also dawned upon him now that the 1500 fighting bull cavalry which he had borrowed from the Fighting Bull Tribe would have been his killers if they hadn’t been killed killed by Wales and the others.

Gasol had been blinded by power, and his logic had been overcome by greed. When he thought about the things he had done, there was only endless regret.

Yet now, he had no face to see Wales. He just wanted to borrow some troops to launch a suicidal attack on the Fighting Bull Tribe in the hopes of making up for his crimes.

Right now, Gasol was just like a gambler who had lost his fortunes, with only his own life left. The only thing he could do was throw his life at his enemies.

The first reason was that he thought it was likely that he would be able to borrow troops while West Wonder King was at odds with the fighting bull chieftain. The second was that he wanted to weaken West Wonder King’s strength. His loss made him realize a lot of things which he hadn’t been able to before. He knew that West Wonder King wasn’t a truly dependable individual either. If West Wonder King were to be in power one day, he would likely threaten the rule of the Herculean Bull Tribe. And so, he wanted to borrow some troops in order to weaken West Wonder King’s strength.

Gasol had also thought about whether or not he could really borrow the troops, but at this point, he could only hope for the best. He thought that the chances of borrowing the troops would be high. If he didn’t put pressure on the Fighting Bull Tribe’s forces, West Wonder King wouldn’t have easier days. Certainly, West Wonder King would not risk his own life to fight against the fighting bull chieftain. He should, however, be willing to see that Gasol was raring to go against the chieftain.

Chapter 271: No Chance Whatsoever

Right now, Gasol was like a madman who had calmed down completely and whose mind was now thinking of ways to throw away his life. This kind of person is the scariest of all, because there’s a word that’s synonymous to them, and that is ‘maniac’.

Right now, Gasol was like a maniac. He needed to kill people from time to time in order to appease his anger, which was why he had attacked the Large-Horned Raging Bull Tribe. On top of that, he killed people randomly along the way. He would kill anyone he found unpleasant to him.

There had been another purpose behind his attack on the Large-Horned Raging Bull Tribe, and that was to prepare presents for West Wonder King. Now that he had nothing, he would feel that he was overstepping the bounds if he went to see him empty-handed. The Large-Horned Raging Bull Tribe’s people were his presents for West Wonder King.

Of course, the tribesmen weren’t his only presents. Gasol had wanted to turn every tribe he could attack into slaves, and then send them to West Wonder King as presents. Coincidentally, the Large-Horned Raging Bull Tribe became the first sacrifice.

Right now, even Gasol’s escorts were afraid of him, because Gasol appeared to be too gloomy right now. There wasn’t a trace of the high spirits as he had been in before.

The sky had darkened, and the enslaved tribesmen had become exhausted, but they didn’t dare to stop or slow down, because as soon as they stopped, the escorts would rouse them with their whips. If they passed out, the only things waiting for them would be the herculean bulls’ axes.

Before all this, all the raging bulls had been compliant with the herculean bulls, who had never mistreated these smaller bull-headed tribes to a great extent. The herculean bulls would even help if there was trouble.

Right now, however, they just felt that these herculean bulls were not beastmen at all, but outright demons. Because the tribesmen couldn’t resist these demons who were too scary, they could only accept this fate of theirs.

Just then, sounds of galloping came. It was very rhythmic and orderly. Gasol was taken aback when he heard this galloping, which was then followed by a change in his expression. He called out loudly, “To arms!”

He was very clear that troops that were able to make such galloping sounds must be well-trained elites. It was anything but good news when such a well-trained army showed up around him and his men.

His escorts had seen many battles, so they knew what was going on. They immediately gathered at Gasol’s side and looked towards where the galloping was coming from.

The weirdest part was that they didn’t see the slightest bit of torchlight. Could it be that the opposite party wasn’t carrying any torches? As such thoughts were in their minds, the galloping sounds came closer and closer.

Although the darkness of the night had affected their vision, Gasol and his men could hear from the galloping that this group of cavalry should have more than 1000 people. This put an unpleasant expression on their faces.

All of them knew very well that, now that they could hear the galloping, it was too late to run away. Right now, all they wanted was to know who the other party was.

Slowly, a large shadow came towards Gasol from a distance. It didn’t take a moment for a whole cavalry unit to appear in their sights.

Gasol’s eyes went red as soon as he saw the cavalry, because the cavalry was composed entirely of fighting bull riders in neat rows.

Right at that moment, one of Gasol’s escorts suddenly shouted in fear. Gasol turned to look at him fiercely, as he assumed that the escort was afraid. It was far from what Gasol could tolerate.

In his eyes was the escort’s deathly pale expression. The escort’s eyes were fixated on a single direction, like he was seeing a ghost.

Gasol looked toward that direction, which had a fighting bull whose armor was broken. Other than that, there was nothing else special.

Gasol spoke coldly, “What did you scream for? Quit embarrassing us.”

However, that escort’s expression was still ugly. He turned to Gasol and said, “Chieftain, I know that guy. He’s one of the people who followed us to kill Lord 7th. He was already killed by undead creatures. How come he’s still here?”

Gasol’s expression changed immediately upon hearing that, because he thought of a possibility. When he and his men had been fighting Wales, they had been defeated by a necromancer. Now, the fighting bulls who should’ve been dead, had now appeared here. What could this mean? The necromancer had caught up to them.

Gasol couldn’t help but speak out, “Have you come, Wales? Come and face me.”

As soon as he finished speaking, an undead beast crawled over, which reaffirmed his thoughts. He didn’t know why such a bizarre undead beast would show up here.

Just then, the undead beast opened its large mouth, and the figure of a person appeared inside. That person slowly walked out of the mouth, stood in front of the beast, and looked at Gasol calmly.

Gasol was watching that person, who was wearing a black magician’s robe with a staff in his hand, silently. Obviously, he was a typical human mage, who should only be around his 20s, with average looks. At the very least, the looks weren’t anything special in a beastman’s eyes.

That person was Zhao Hai, of course. Zhao Hai wanted to look at what had become of Gasol , and right now, he had 1 word to describe Gasol’s current look: gloomy. Yet embers of madness were flickering in Gasol’s eyes, which made Gasol look especially fearsome.

Zhao Hai didn’t mind, and just smiled and bowed towards Gasol. “Greetings to brother Gasol. I am Zhao Hai, Beheading Blood Oath brother of Wales.”

Gasol did a double take, and then stared at Zhao Hai, “You’re saying you swore the Beheading Blood Oath with Wales?” As a beastman, Gasol naturally knew what the Beheading Blood Oath meant. He hadn’t expected that there would be anyone on the prairie who would swear it. And with a human, at that.

Zhao Hai smiled, “Indeed. When you came last time, little me couldn’t come and deliver greetings. That was truly impolite of me. I hope brother Gasol can forgive me.”

Gasol laughed coldly at Zhao Hai and said, “Humans are just hypocritical. You’re here for my life, yet you have to put up a joyful look. It’s disgusting.”

Zhao Hai smiled, “Your words are too harsh, brother Gasol. You should know how potent the Beheading Blood Oath can be. I cannot possibly do anything that will be harmful to the Herculean Bull Tribe. What I don’t know about is you, brother Gasol. Who were the humans you made contact with? Were they the spies that the Fighting Bull Tribe sent to help you?”

Gasol’s expression went cold when he heard that. “Cut the crap. Where’s Wales? Tell him to come see me.”

Zhao Hai smiled, “Brother Wales went for the Mastiff Tribe’s turf. I heard that the Herculean Bull Tribe’s people are there, so he’s going there to pacify his people. That’s why he’s not here, and he let me go to see the 2 older sisters in West Wonder King’s place.”

Gasol was taken aback at this, and said to Zhao Hai, “It seems like Wales really trusts you. He actually left you such an important task. So I guess you happened upon me by chance? What exactly do you want?”

Zhao Hai smiled, “Nothing much. Brother Wales has been meaning to find you, but he has his own matters to take care of. Since I’ve found you, it’s natural that I have to help him keep you here.”

Gasol’s expression changed and he snorted coldly. “That will depend on whether or not you have what it takes.” As soon as his words ended, his hand moved suddenly. A flash of light, and a hand axe was hurled towards Zhao Hai.

This attack of Gasol’s was very sudden, and well hidden. There were no signs whatsoever. This hand axe of his wasn’t the type used by the bull-headed races, but a small one that was only as large as his palm. It looked like it was meant to be a hidden weapon.

Zhao Hai wasn’t expecting that Gasol would use hidden weapons, but he was no fool, and had come prepared. Which was why when Gasol made his move, Xenomorph stepped in front of Zhao Hai and blocked the hidden weapon, followed by Zhao Hai disappearing from where he was. The fighting bull cavalry then moved towards Gasol and his men.

Instead of reacting to that, Gasol and his men turned around to run. But as soon as they turned, they saw that their path of retreat had already been cut off by jackal cavalry.

The jackal cavalry’s mounts were flash jackals, which were carnivores. Carnivores’ feet have claws instead of hooves, and claws have paws. The flash jackals’ paws allowed them to run with only very small sounds being made. This had allowed them to surround Gasol while Zhao Hai had drawn his attention.

It was also why Zhao Hai had let the undead appear as zombies. It was to keep the paws of the flash jackals, and therefore achieve the effect which Zhao Hai wanted.

Gasol was in disbelief as he looked at the jackal cavalry. He was pretty sure that the cavalry had appeared as skeletons last time. Why did they change their looks this time?

Before he could figure out what was going on, the jackal cavalry had charged forth, leaving no chance whatsoever for Gasol and his men.

This time, Zhao Hai had given strict orders to kill everyone but the ground bulls and Gasol.

If the escorts were killed, then fine. But if Gasol were to be killed, then Wales would definitely feel bad in his heart. Whatever the case may be, Gasol was Wales’ older brother. Their grievances were their own matters. Zhao Hai couldn’t intervene.

Gasol was obviously under-prepared for this pincer attack, and by the time he wanted to strike back it was already too late. The jackal and fighting bull cavalry had killed his dozens of escorts, while only their mounts were still alive. Gasol was then surrounded by the two groups of cavalry, who stood looking at him silently.

Gasol couldn’t help but make a bitter smile at this. He lifted his large axe to engage in the ‘final’ charge of his life, but right at that moment, a vine appeared behind him all of a sudden, and struck his head. Gasol felt a headache, and then nothing. He swayed before collapsing from his mount. The moment he fell onto the ground, he was wrapped by more vines before disappearing on the spot with a flash of light.

Zhao Hai then waved his staff and put the ground bulls, as well as the weapons, into the space. The corpses of the herculean bull escorts were buried using earth magic. He knew that Wales wouldn’t like to see herculean bulls being turned into undead creatures, so Zhao Hai didn’t do so. After all, having these few more underlings wouldn’t make any difference.

After the process was complete, Zhao Hai turned to look at the Large-Horned Raging Bull Tribe tribesmen. They didn’t run, but stood dumbly at the side. Some of the kids had been scared to tears.

Zhao Hai walked in front of them and said, “I am a necromancer. I’m called Zhao Hai. Starting today, I am your master. You can call me ‘young master’.”

The tribesmen watched him with fearful expressions. Behind him was Xenomorph, which was swaggering imposingly. What could they do, when the undefeatable Gasol and his men had been destroyed without a chance to resist?

With a wave of Zhao Hai’s hand, the fighting bull and jackal cavalry turned into skeletons in an instant, and then stood in formation behind him. This made the tribesmen even more afraid. A lot of the women had started to cry, and the eyes of the elderly shone with despair.

It was on purpose. He wanted to scare them in order to make them follow his orders to a tee.

Zhao Hai said, “I will send you to a place, and you will live there from now on. You have to obey the people there. Anyone who doesn’t, I will turn them into an undead myself.”

The tribesmen looked at Zhao Hai dumbly, as they couldn’t register all of this immediately. But one thing was for sure: this frightening human mage in front of them didn’t seem to want to kill them.

Zhao Hai glanced at them and spoke, “Have some leaders speak with me.”

There was a fuss before 2 of the elderly tribesmen were selected. Although they were tall, their waists were somewhat bent. It seemed as if their horns were keeping them from raising their heads. One of them spoke, “Young master, I am Alaes, Elder of the Large-Horned Tribe.”

“I am Alea. Likewise.”

Zhao Hai nodded. “Good. Assemble your tribesmen. I’m going to send you all to where you are going to be living from here on.”

Chapter 272: Complicated Human Merchant

Alaes and Alea could only address their tribesmen with lowered heads, after glancing at Zhao Hai and the undead creatures behind him.

It didn’t take more than a while for every tribesman to be assembled. There were only about 900 people left in the tribe, with more than 100 of them being youths, and the rest being the old and weak.

Everyone was looking nerve-wrackingly at the undead creatures, whose strength they had just witnessed. All of Gasol’s escorts had been experts with at least the strength of level 6 warriors. And yet, even with such strength, the undead cavalry had exterminated them in a single charge with no casualties. What sort of concept was this?

The large-horned tribe’s people were not idiots without common sense. They knew quite well that if the undead creatures had not been powerful enough, Gasol’s dozens of escorts would’ve been able to deal with several hundreds of them without breaking a sweat. But the escorts had been taken care of without a single casualty on the undead’s side. This could only prove that the strength of the undead creatures was not inferior to that of Gasol’s escorts. And since they numbered more than 3000, there was no way the tribesmen could oppose them.

If they couldn’t oppose them, then all that was left was only submission. They gathered around cautiously, with the women and children in the middle, then the elders, and finally the youths.

Zhao Hai glanced at them, then waved the staff in his hand. A cloud of black mist wrapped everyone up, which made the tribesmen nervous for a while.

Soon, the black mist dissipated, and the tribesmen discovered that they were now standing outside a castle. A real human castle.

Beastmen had always heard about such castles more than they had seen them. Now that the large-horned tribesmen were finally seeing one, they couldn’t react. They just stood there in front of it, staring dumbfoundedly at 2 people.

Yes. Not beastmen, but true humans. They couldn’t understand how they had suddenly appeared here.

Just then, Zhao Hai’s voice suddenly rang out, “Alright, from here on out, this will be where you live. Remember, you are the slaves of Zhao Hai. Me.” The tribesmen returned to their senses in an instant, and then looked at Zhao Hai at a loss for thoughts. They seriously couldn’t understand how Zhao Hai had done it. Why was he able bring so many people here from the prairie in an instant?

Without care, Zhao Hai continued. “This is my supervisor, Greene, and likewise, this one is Kun Zheng. They will arrange your accommodations, as well as clarify the rules here. Remember. Whoever dares to cause trouble, I will be turning them into a specter.”

Of course, Zhao Hai was terrorizing the tribesmen, which was something he couldn’t afford not to do. If he couldn’t make the tribesmen feel fear, then he would have to kill more people if they caused trouble.

In order to settle the large-horned tribesmen down as quickly as possible, Zhao Hai waited and watched Greene arrange them into their accommodations instead of going back to the prairie in a hurry.

Greene and the others had prepared for this. With their crazy purchases in Casa City beforehand, they were not lacking in supplies right now. It didn’t take a lot of effort to settle the tribesmen.

Most importantly, this castle wasn’t small. Zhao Hai and the others had only been able to use a part of it since they had been too few in number. With more than a thousand of the large-horned raging bulls here, it was just enough to make the castle a little more lively.

Although the tribesmen didn’t know where they were, they didn’t dare to disobey Zhao Hai’s words. Adding the fear of being in a completely foreign environment, they could only enter the castle nervously under Greene and Kun Zheng’s arrangements.

Food had already been prepared for them in the castle, so all the tribesmen needed to do was to occupy themselves in it. With Zhao Hai keeping watch, everything proceeded very smoothly. In the eyes of the large-horned raging bulls, Zhao Hai was a devil with power beyond boundaries. Otherwise, there would be no way for him to have such a large army of undead, not to mention the ability to bring them to here in an instant from the prairie.

Zhao Hai had used the space to bring them here, of course. In order to avoid letting them see what was going on inside the space, he had used a black mist spell to cover their entry, and with the speed of the transition being so fast, they could only feel the black mist covering them up before they were transported to a completely foreign location. This caused them to have an incomparable fear towards Zhao Hai’s ability.

The large-horned raging bulls were a very gentle race among beastmen, and their nature made them a little cowardly. With how ‘obeying the strong’ had always been the rule on the prairie, they could only be complacent.

By the time they had settled down, dawn was about to break, and Zhao Hai immediately returned to the prairie, where there were a lot of matters he had yet to attend to.

When Gasol had defeated the Large-Horned Raging Bull Tribe, all of their supplies had been looted, including magic beasts, food, wagons and tents, which were the most commonly-used by beastmen.

Zhao Hai had only taken care of Gasol and his men, and the matter of transporting the large-horned tribesmen to Iron Mountain Castle, while the other things had been left untouched on the prairie. Right now, they were being guarded by the undead creatures, led by Laura.

Zhao Hai entered Xenomorph as soon as he arrived, and found that Laura and the others had gone to sleep. He smiled a little and didn’t disturb them as he walked out.

The things which Gasol and his men had looted weren’t a lot, for the tribe in question was a small tribe of more than 1000 people. Even so, their supplies were not little. Just putting these things away required several hundred wagons.

One had to keep in mind the difference in size between beastmen wagons and human wagons. The wagons that Zhao Hai’s group was using could only fit up to 1000 kilos of grains each, while each of the beastmen’s wagons could carry more than 5000 kilos of grains.

Zhao Hai counted it carefully. The Large-Horned Raging Bull Tribe had up to 500 large wagons, with 300 of them containing tents and everyday necessities, while only 200 of them contained grains. However, when Zhao Hai took a look, he saw that the grains had not been fully packed. Every wagon only carried around 2000 kilos, and each had been tightly covered with leather. This showed that they treated the grains with great importance.

Some magic beasts were tied to every wagon. There were 3 kinds: large-horned raging bulls, ordinary raging bulls, and argali goats.

The first of which were obviously the tribesmen’s mounts, while the ordinary raging bulls were for pulling the wagons. The argali were naturally their most important assets.

After careful counting, there turned out to be more than 1500 large-horned raging bulls, more than 1100 ordinary raging bulls, and the argali were too many to be counted.

The beastmen certainly had a way to deal with the argali. Such a large commotion had taken place last night, yet the argali hadn’t run away, and right now, in the morning, the argali were eating grass in a laid-back manner.

After some thinking, Zhao Hai put everything into the space, while leaving only several hundred argali and a couple of supply wagons outside. One contained tents, while the other contained living necessities. Although they were meant for beastmen, they were enough for appearances.

Zhao Hai had thought the merchants on the prairie to be too simple when he had talked with Wales in some days ago. The merchants on the prairie were even more like beastmen in lifestyle. They brought large numbers of grain wagons, as well as wagons with tents and supplies, because they had to set up their own tents most of the time. It would be impossible for them to seek accommodation with beastmen everyday.

Humans who had arrived at Beastmen Prairie would normally wear clothes made of beast skins. The first reason for this was to generate a sense of positivity in the beastmen, and the second was for suitability.

It was also until now that Zhao Hai knew that human merchants were living their lives this way on the prairie. He tried to ask Laura, since Laura should’ve had known all of this since she had claimed to have done business on the prairie.

Unexpectedly, Laura rolled her eyes at him and said that businesses on the prairie had always been monitored by Kun Zheng, who had always barred her from making contact with those people (human merchants) on the prairie. Then, it had been passed to Ah-Tai, so she had only been in charge of ledger issues instead of the specifics.

In Kun Zheng’s view, the main purpose of this excursion was not to do business, but to acquire rare magic beasts and plants, so he hadn’t said too much of this to Zhao Hai and the others. Besides, with the space, there wasn’t a need to do so many things. Kun Zheng could never think of seriously letting Laura eat and sleep while exposed outdoors like the merchants. He couldn’t bear the thought.

The wagons which Zhao Hai left behind were just to keep up appearances, and he wouldn’t use them seriously. After all, they rested inside the space.

The reason why he had left the argali outside was to have them match his identity of being a merchant. On the prairie, it was very normal for merchant convoys to be followed by a large herd of argali.

The grain wagon of the Large-Horned Raging Bull Tribe was left outside, since he would use it to engage in trade from this point onwards. The smaller wagons were too small after all, and unsuitable for use on the prairie.

After sorting everything out, Zhao Hai let out 500 undead humans and 100 undead large-horned raging bulls to guard the wagons. He also let out Laura’s wagon and woke her up. They had to hurry up once again.

Chapter 273: Children Issues

Laura and the others discovered that Zhao Hai had taken care of matters as soon as they woke up. Laura couldn’t help but speak in a heartache tone upon looking at Zhao Hai’s bloodshot eyes, “Did you not sleep for the whole night, Hai-bro? Take a rest, quickly.”

Zhao Hai smiled, “It’s nothing. All of you, go into the space and clean yourselves up. I’m going to write a letter to brother Wales, tell him about the situation here, and arrange a place for our meeting to hand Gasol over to him. Having Gasol in our hands is not a solution in and of itself. With all those supplies seized from the Large-Horned Raging Bull Tribe that are meant to be used by beastmen, we have to leave them with big brother, since we can’t use most of them.”

Laura nodded, “Right. We’ll go and make ourselves presentable. Head into the space and rest as soon as you finish writing the letter. We’ll just keep watch outside. We won’t go the wrong way, after all.”

Zhao Hai nodded and turned around to write the letter, while Laura and the others immediately went to clean themselves up in the space. They had slept quite late yesterday, so they needed to wake up properly now.

Soon, Zhao Hai had finished writing a letter to Wales. It wasn’t a long letter, as it was just about meeting Gasol, having captured him, and asking about how to deal with him.

After writing the letter, Zhao Hai returned into the space and called back one of the 5 blood hawks he had gifted to Wales in order to send the letter.

The blood hawks were actually phantasmal beasts from the space. No matter how distant they would be, the space could always contact them. As Zhao Hai was the owner of the space, he could naturally command the blood hawks through the space without concern for distance.

Zhao Hai went to the ranch inside the space after commanding a blood hawk. He wanted to see the assessed levels of the 2 new types of magic beasts he had gotten yesterday.

He immediately released the raging bulls, which prompted the immediate sounding of the space’s voice, <Mutated cow-form animals discovered. Appraising animals. The animals are level 10 animals. Time of maturity, 12 hours. Can give birth to offspring, 6 times. Quantity of offspring per birth, 6. Each consumes 2 points of feed every hour. Converting animals into data. Animals can now be bought from the Shop.> Just as Zhao Hai had imagined, these large-horned raging bulls weren’t of a high level.

He paid it no mind, as long as the space had an additional type of magic beast from here on. He then released the ground bulls. Once again, the notification voice came: <Mutated cow-form animals discovered. Appraising animals. The animals are level 25 animals. Time of maturity, 20 hours. Can give birth to offspring, 8 times. Quantity of offspring per birth, 5. Each consumes 2 points of feed every hour. The animals have slight control of earth element energies. Converting animals into data. Animals can now be bought from the Shop.> Zhao Hai wasn’t in a hurry after there was nothing more from the notification. He realized that it was much harder to raise the ranch’s level compared to the farm’s. He had already gotten a lot of animals into the space by now, yet the ranch was still at level 6. It seemed that it would be very difficult to raise the ranch to higher levels.

Zhao Hai let out a sigh. He didn’t intend to raise ground bulls and large-horned raging bulls immediately, and right now, it was useless to do so. He’d be better off raising argali and raging bulls. After all, argali and raging bulls could be exchanged for money in human lands, while ground bulls and large-horned raging bulls would not have a lot of use in human lands.

Zhao Hai came out of the ranch, and saw Laura and the others, who had finished cleaning themselves up by now. They appeared to be a lot more energetic.

Zhao Hai laughed at the 3 of them and said, “I think you won’t need to head out now. Just stay here and monitor what’s outside using the surveillance function. Head out when there are people while letting the undead creatures lead the wagons. If you’re really bored, you can head to Iron Mountain Castle.”

The ladies agreed after some thought. They had grown bored of the scenery of the prairie, which was not as comfy as the space, where they could lie around and sit anywhere they pleased. They had a bigger range of activity here, too.

Zhao Hai said nothing more after knowing that the girls had agreed with him. He then went to sleep in the bedroom inside the space.

He was worried that they might get truly bored in here, so he told Cai-Er to go keep watch outside should Laura and the others want to go to Iron Mountain Castle. If something really happened while he was sleeping and Laura and the others were in Iron Mountain Castle, Cai-Er would wake him up.

Actually, Zhao Hai was still not clear about Cai-Er’s role right now. However, he didn’t need to worry; Cai-Er had managed the space so well, while the same could be said for Mu-Er and the ranch. He was relaxed in that he only had to let Cai-Er do his bidding. Until now, he hadn’t discovered anything asked of Cai-Er that couldn’t be done.

Zhao Hai was very clear that he was Cai-Er’s master after she had merged with the space. If there were something Cai-Er couldn’t do, she would tell him about it, so he felt assured about her.

After a full sleep, Zhao Hai felt very replenished. If he had to list something he was the most dissatisfied with regarding his body, it was the fact that he would be very worn out just after a bit of fatigue, which made him pathetically weak.

After cleaning himself up, Zhao Hai arrived at the living room of the villa. He noticed that the wagons were still moving (through the surveillance), and they had not deviated from their course.

He immediately returned to Iron Mountain Castle, as he hadn’t found Laura and the others in the villa inside the space. As expected, he found them in Iron Mountain Castle. They were instructing the Large-Horned Raging Bull Tribe’s people how to perform their tasks.

Zhao Hai smiled as he appeared next to Laura. Laura suddenly sensed that there was another person next to her, and realized that it was him. She smiled, “You’re awake, Hai-bro.”

Zhao Hai nodded and glanced at the tribesmen, who were lifting some goods. He asked, “How are they? Are they obedient?”

Laura nodded, “Very. They’re just a little not used to living here, but I believe it won’t take too long for them to get used to it. Just look, Hai-bro. So many large-horned tribesmen kids, running around with nothing to do. It just won’t do. How about we find some things for them to do?”

Zhao Hai nodded. He had seriously considered this problem before, back when Qi and Xi had gotten married. There was no such thing as ‘planned childbirth’ on Ark Continent. For people in this world, birthing was just a natural affair, so in the near future, there would be a lot of children here. So what about the children? Let them run around ignorantly everyday? Safety aside, it would not bring him any benefits whatsoever.

There was only one way to solve this issue: schools.

Right now, this place was a de facto independent kingdom, so these things should have been planned. Which country doesn’t have schools? Schools are an important unit in which the quality of the citizens is raised, so they must be built. If a school were to be built at this time and get on track, then future school-building would be a lot more convenient with the experience gained for building the first one, even if there were a lot of people.

There was a great saying in China: ‘Education is the foundation of a hundred year plan’. In order for Buda family to develop, the matter of education must not be overlooked.

Zhao Hai turned to Laura and said, “Let the tribesmen work first. Call grandpa Greene and the others. We’ll head to the living room and discuss some things.”

Laura nodded and let Nier go and call the people. Zhao Hai said, “Oh right. Contact Alaes and Alea as well.” Nier heeded with a sound, and ran off.

Zhao Hai and Laura walked towards the living room in the castle together, while the large-horned tribesmen looked at him with eyes full of fear. He paid them no mind and just asked Laura, “Laura, how do you think we can solve the issue with their children?”

Laura thought for a bit then said, “Schools. I think that maybe we can build a school.”

Zhao Hai smiled, “My thoughts exactly. I too want to build a school. It not only lets people pay attention to them, but by the time they grow up, we’ll have a lot of capable people.”

Laura nodded, “We bought a lot of books when we came out this time. They can be used to educate the children. Even if they won’t be able to learn martial arts and magics when they grow up, they will help us a lot.”

Zhao Hai nodded, and the 2 of them entered the castle. Right now, there were quite a few people inside the castle who had become married couples. They had not only been given civilian statuses by Zhao Hai, if they willed it, Zhai Hai would give them houses inside the castle perimeter. Of course, they weren’t the quarters of the main castle, but the servants’ quarters instead.

When the 2 of them arrived at the living room, Greene and the others were already there. Other than Greene, Maylin, Kun Zheng, Meg, Blockhead and Rockhead, Seyer, Alaes and Alea had also arrived. Right now, they were the management of the whole Buda family.

Zhao Hai let everyone sit down, while only Alaes and Alea felt uncertain and sat down carefully. He didn’t say anything about them, and just turned to Greene and the others. “The reason I’ve called everyone here today is to talk about the Large-Horned Raging Bull Tribe’s children issues.”

Greene and the others were watching Zhao Hai in confusion. Zhao Hai turned his head to Laura, which meant that he wanted her to carry on. Laura smiled and said, “Before, we didn’t have a lot of people in this castle, and there were no children, so no one has paid attention to this issue. Right now, with the addition of the Large-Horned Raging Bull Tribe, we have suddenly gained a lot of children. But with no one to keep watch over them as they run about everyday, besides not having learned anything, it is simply unsafe. There is a moat outside this place. If they play around there, it will easily cause accidents.”

Greene and the others did a double take, and then nodded, while Alaes and Alea were looking dumbstruck at Zhao Hai and Laura. Although they were beastmen, and therefore not as smart as humans, with age came wisdom, or so the saying goes. They knew what Zhao Hai and Laura meant. They saw that Zhao Hai and Laura seemed to want to make a school.

Chapter 274: National Policy

Schools. Not only humans had them, but beastmen as well. However, only major battle races had schools. The most famous school was in Beast God City, which was the oldest one in the long history of beastmen. But in that school, only the high ranked battle races and some prophets, shamans and witch doctors were taught. Common beastmen would never be able to take lessons there.

It was exactly due to this reason that schools had a very high standing in the hearts of beastmen. Due to old age and the fact that they had experienced a lot of things, Alaes and Alea got the impression from Laura that she wanted to build a school, since the purpose of schools for the major battle races was to conduct concentrated management and training.

The 2 of them looked emotionally at Zhao Hai, who glanced at Greene and said, “In the days to come, our population will be higher and higher, and with it, the number of children. In light of this, building a school is inevitable. I think we should build one now, when our population is still small, and compile the experience. That way, if we want to build schools when the population becomes greater, we will not have our hands tied.”

Greene nodded, “Young master has a point. A school should be in order. There are quite a number of rooms in the castle right now, so we should do it immediately.”

Kun Zheng also nodded and said, “I think we should make a magic-martial school. Examine the children when they’re little, put the ones that are good at martial arts to be taught martial techniques, and the ones that are good at magic to be taught magic spells. The teacher for martial arts can be settled with Seyer. As for the magic teacher, how about Meg?”

Zhao Hai shook his head and said, “No, that’s too broadly laid out. If we want to build a school now, we have to do it right, for the sake of future experience. It’s definitely a ‘no’ if we do it according to the format of magic-martial schools on the continent. We need to have more detailed curriculums. How about this? First we survey the number of children and get their ages, then separate them based on their age. My plan is to have the children taught by their parents before they are 4 years old. Upon becoming 4 years old, we send them to a unified kindergarten, and have them taken care of by specific personnel. We bring them to the kindergarten every morning, and bring them back to their homes every night. They will eat there at noon. While they’re at kindergarten, we give them a rudimentary education, so that they know some basic words and arithmetics.

At 7 years old, they’ll officially go to classes, divided into literature, mathematics and martial arts classes, which will have to be conducted in the same time period. For example, the three classes could all be an hour long each. They’ll go to school and come back from it at the same times as the kindergarteners, with the same meal time.

At 12 years old, they’ll be officially split by categories. Like for the ones talented in martial arts, most of their time will be spent on martial lessons and general learning. For the ones talented in magic, their attention will be mainly put into magic spells and general learning. If there are ones who have talent in neither, they can then focus on learning other lessons, and we can then hire some workers to teach them some skills. That way, even if they aren’t good with words and numbers, they will have some skills to ensure their own safety. Even barring that, at least they will know about basic arithmetic, which can only be good for them. What do you think?”

Greene and then others didn’t expect that Zhao Hai had actually taken everything into consideration. They knew from his words that this wasn’t a spur of the moment plan, because the plan which he had just proposed was very detailed. It could be said that the magic-martial schools on the continent were not as detailed as what Zhao Hai had suggested, and starting from 4 years old at that. One should know that schools on the continent generally started from 6 to 7 years old, during which only basic training and words were taught and nothing else. They couldn’t possibly know that Zhao Hai had simply brought Earth’s education over after giving it a facelift.

However, they had to admit that Zhao Hai’s schooling plan was far better than that of the other schools on the continent. If they managed to pull it off, it would definitely be a one-of-a-kind school on the continent, which would make it a historical first.

Because the people of the continent valued martial strength, magic-martial schools normally taught martial techniques and magic spells as their main curriculums. However, the school which Zhao Hai had proposed was different, as it was mainly teaching writing and mathematics. From start to finish, the importance was put upon those, which for Greene and the others was something they had never heard of before.

Laura frowned, “If we do it as you say, Hai-bro, the cost we will need to put into it will be hefty. For example, children from 4 to 7 years old are very hard to take care of, and with the amount of different lessons, and the ones who will need to be in charge of making meals and babysitting, they all need people. Who do we put in charge of them? Every member of this kindergarten has to eat, and teachers have to get their wages. Do we have to pay them ourselves? The investment will be a bottomless pit, and there are too many things in need of budget allocation when it comes to developing the Black Wastelands. I’m afraid it won’t work.”

Greene and the others nodded, as they knew what Laura meant. Indeed, if they did set up such a school program as Zhao Hai had suggested, the amount of investment would be too great. They might not be able to feel it right now when they were few in number, but if there were a lot of people, the expenditure would be an astronomical sum.

Zhao Hai nodded, “I know about that, of course, which is why lesson fees will have to be received. But we can’t take too much. The students’ parents will pay a portion, while we will pay another. That way, the school can be built. My plan isn’t made based on a fief’s, but a country’s outlook. Schools have to be managed by a country directly, instead of leaving them to someone else. Besides, we are few in number and have almost no commerce, but once there are a lot of people, there will surely be merchants, and we will have taxes. What are taxes for? Just to equip troops? I think there’s no need to. We can implement military style management in the school. That way, when there’s any kind of battle, we won’t have to worry about a lack of soldiers. For the sake of Buda family’s prospects of becoming a long-lasting dynasty, I think we will have to look at taxes rationally. The taxes we receive must be used on the right places, in accordance to these words, ‘from the people, for the people’.”

Laura and the others were stunned. It was the first time they had heard of Zhao Hai’s ideal, which was different from all the other countries on the continent when it came to the view on taxes. Currently on the continent, the highest rulers were royal families, followed by nobles. Although a part of the taxes which they received was used on necessary construction and military expenditures, little was put into other aspects. Even the schools on the continent required lesson fees. What Zhao Hai had proposed was something they had never heard of.

Everyone went silent for a moment before Kun Zheng slapped his own thigh and said, “Great! Very well put, little Hai! Your words are too appropriate. For the sake of Buda family’s great future, this is what we should do. Otherwise, what’s the use of losing our entire home for the sake of piling up money? I support little Hai.”

Greene wasn’t someone uncultured. He was simply taken aback for a bit due to the shock of all this. He had never thought that Zhao Hai would plan so far ahead. Thanks to Kun Zheng, he returned to his senses and spoke with a face full of excitement, “Right! Too right! I support young master.”

After the words of those 2, the entire matter was basically settled. All that was left was finding a place and teachers.

Maylin said, “Finding a place isn’t hard, but for children, we will have to find a more quiet and spacious place, so that they can learn martial arts. They can also play under the supervision of adults. I choose the back of the castle.”

Behind the castle was a place that was originally intended to be a place for storage, servant quarters and stables.

No one had been there, but the houses were intact. Just some cleaning, and they could be used for schooling. They were distant from the outer parts, far away from the oil and milling factories. This quietness was exactly the ideal condition for a school.

Right now, the one who was the most knowledgeable about the castle was Maylin, so when she made her point, no one opposed her. Zhao Hai nodded, “Then let’s pick the back of the castle, and have granny Maylin be in charge. Next up is the selection of teachers. We can have Seyer handle the role of martial arts teacher, but due to a majority of children being large-horned raging bulls, we will have to let one of the tribesmen become a teacher. I will leave you to it, Alaes. Find a warrior from your tribe to teach the children, but remember to find someone smart. We’re teaching children here. If he cannot even speak and doesn’t even know how to teach, the children will be brought up wrongly.”

Zhao Hai knew that the martial arts of beastmen and humans were very different. Evidently, humans couldn’t teach soul fusion-related techniques to beastmen children, thus, Zhao Hai wanted to select a teacher from the tribe.

Alaes and Alea suddenly knelt down in front of Zhao Hai, with the former proclaiming loudly, “O great magician, your heart is as wide as the prairie itself, and your power is as omnipotent as the Beast God. Your knowledge is even greater than prophets, and you are as kind as the Mother River. Please be at ease, for we will surely handle what you have asked of us well.” After those words, the 2 of them kowtowed to Zhao Hai 3 times.

Zhao Hai didn’t expect that they would act this way. He waved his hand before Blockhead and Rockhead held both of them up. Zhao Hai looked at the 2 of them and said, “Remember that while you are my slaves, I am different from other humans. In here, you and humans are equals, but you must never betray me. If you do, I will have you become a part of my undead army.”

Alaes bowed down and said, “Benevolent master, please relax. Once a beastman acknowledges a lord, it will never change for life.”

Zhao Hai nodded, “Also, do not forget that the tribe is already no more. Tell your people to get used to the life around here as soon as possible. If there’s any assistance you require, just find any of the people you see in this meeting. That reminds me, do you still have your tribe’s friendship flag?”

Alaes nodded, “We still do. Do you need it, master?”

Zhao Hai nodded, “Bring it to me after a while. I need friendship flags in order to do business on the prairie.” It was something Zhao Hai had thought up all of a sudden. The Big-bellied Pig Tribe’s friendship flag which Spiel had given him had garnered a lot of positive feelings from a lot of beastmen, which made the importance of such flags clear to Zhao Hai. Now that Alaes himself was his, using his flag was even less of a problem.

Alaes nodded immediately, “Relax, my master. I will immediately bring it to you after I return.”

Zhao Hai nodded, “Alright, sit down. Remember to call me young master. Didn’t I tell you that already?” Alaes and Alea both heeded with a sound before sitting down.

Zhao Hai turned to Greene and the others and said, “Seyer is the martial arts teacher, and there will be another one from the large-horned raging bulls, which should be enough for the time being. If Seyer has matters to attend to, have Blockhead or Rockhead take care of it. However, both of them are still primarily about martial training. When it comes to the magic teacher, I pick Baphay. Even though he’s become an undead creature and his level was decreased by a lot, he should be able to manage. He was once a level 9 mage after all.”

Maylin and the others didn’t want to let an undead creature teach the children, but there was no other way. They had no suitable candidates right now. However, having Baphay act as a teacher wouldn’t be too big of a deal. Beastmen couldn’t learn magics, so Baphay only had to teach the children how to react to magical attacks.

Once Zhao Hai saw that no one had anything to say, he continued, “Making meals won’t be an issue. Select 2 women from the large-horned tribe, and another 2 women from among the slaves. Teaching the kids about reading and writing will be more difficult. Oh right. We can let Orloba try his hand at that. He can teach them about words and mathematics, which should be possible. What do you think, granny Maylin?”

Maylin felt that this was the only way. They didn’t have a lot of people at their disposal right now. Maylin could do it, but she didn’t have the time for it. They could only do as Zhao Hai suggested.

Once he confirmed that there were no objections, Zhao Hai spoke to Greene and Kun Zheng, “Grandpa Greene, grandpa Kun Zheng, I’ll leave these matters to you both. We’re heading back to the prairie. Contact me if you need anything. Alaes, bring me the friendship flag.”

Alaes and Alea heeded with a sound and left. Zhao Hai spoke to Maylin, “Beastmen mostly eat meat. They will not get used to our eating habits right now. Their lifestyle will have to be changed little by little as well. Keep an eye on this, granny.” Maylin nodded. Just then, Cai-Er told him that the blood hawk had returned.

Chapter 275: Teaching Material Frustrations

This was the 2nd time the blood hawks had returned this day. The 1st time was when Zhao Hai had been sleeping, but he had left the letter which was meant for Wales with Cai-Er, who had then passed it over to the blood hawk. This time, it must’ve brought back Wales’ reply.

As it turned out, the moment Zhao Hai appeared in the space, he saw a blood hawk standing in front of Cai-Er. When it saw Zhao Hai, it walked over to him and used its hook-like beak to peck on his face gently as a show of affection.

Zhao Hai patted the blood hawk’s large head gently while Cai-Er passed a letter to his hand. Zhao Hai could easily tell that Wales had been worked up, since the words on the letter were hastily written.

Even so, Zhao Hai understood what the letter was trying to say. Wales’ intention was to have him hand over Gasol. On the back of the letter was a very simple map, and he let the blood hawk lead the way.

Zhao Hai didn’t have an opinion on this matter, since he was going to West Wonder King’s territory for a few days. He wasn’t in a hurry, so he returned to Iron Mountain Castle once more after putting the letter away.

Greene and the others were now discussing the matter of building the school . Fortunately, there were relatively few people in Iron Mountain Castle, so it would be easier to set things up.

But what Zhao Hai had meant was that they must not do things half-heartedly just because they only had a few people. The framework must be set properly in order to make a decent example. If there were other schools to be made later, they would be able to use their first school as an example to do so.

Just then, Alaes and Alea both returned from outside. They were bringing a battle flag in their hands, which had a head of a bull with large horns painted on it. It was none other than the friendship flag of the Large-horned Raging Bull Tribe.

Zhao Hai took the flag, glanced at it, and passed it over to Meg, who was at his side. He turned to Alaes and said, “Alaes, you must count the number of children you have as fast as you are able to, and find a teacher. The school must be built at once.”

Alaes and Alea both heeded his order with a sound. Zhao Hai turned to Greene and said, “Grandpa Greene, I’m leaving this to you. We still have to return to the prairie. I just received word from Wales to give Gasol to him.”

Greene nodded. “Relax, young master. Everything’s normal in the castle and nothing has happened. The firewood for winter has also been prepared, so there’s nothing to worry about.”

Zhao Hai laughed. “Very well, then. Actually, we don’t need too much firewood for winter now. Cai-Er’s flowers can spread heat during the winter, so that the castle will not be too cold. We now have so much food we will never be able to finish it all, and there’s no lack of meat. Right now, I still think we should build a battle ration factory as soon as possible. With Alaes and his people joining in, producing the rations should be easy. We aren’t short on argali, so everyone will have something to do during the winter. What do you think?”

Greene nodded, “How many argali have we gotten this time, young master?”

Zhao Hai ‘glanced’ at the space, and said, “About 30000 of them, all from Alaes’ tribe.”

Alaes and his people did not show any sign of discontent. Since they now belonged to Zhao Hai, the ownership of the argali was not even a question. However, Alaes frowned slightly and asked, “Young master, I recall that our tribe had more than 50000 argali. How did it go from that to 30000?”

Zhao Hai did a double take, thought for a bit and replied, “They probably ran off during the fight between me and Gasol. No matter. 30000 is enough for us. Looks like we’ll have to raise more of them. Right now, the blue-eyed rabbits which we’ve been raising in the ranch can more or less supply the Fansile Duchy. Later on, we will focus primarily on argali.”

Greene nodded, “Very well. Oh right, young master. We can also open a goat hair product factory. We’ll hire Alaes’ people for this as well, and let the slaves learn from it. What do you think?”

Zhao Hai nodded, “Alaes and his people are the best in this field. You just arrange things accordingly. We don’t need to worry about the goat hair processing. With them, we can now do what we couldn’t before.”

Alaes and Alea couldn’t help but straighten their backs. Beastmen were so simple; they had been afraid that Zhao Hai would look down on them after becoming his underlings. Now, with Zhao Hai’s words, they felt truly happy.

Zhao Hai glanced at them before continuing, “Grandpa Greene, find an empty plot of land specifically for cavalry training. Alaes and his people are beastmen, so we must not let them forget their roots as riders. Besides, we have the room. Preparing a training field for them isn’t a difficult matter. When those kids take their lessons, we’ll have to set up riding lessons for them as well. We’ll let Alaes and his people pick someone to be the teacher for those lessons, while grandpa Kun Zheng can also provide some guidance. After all, humans have their own ways when it comes to riding.”

Kun Zheng laughed, “Alright. I’ll teach them well.”

Zhao Hai nodded and looked at the sky. “I’m heading to the prairie first to alter our course. I’ll come back for a meal in a bit. Laura, Meg, Nier, stay here. I’ll be on my own.”

Laura nodded, but Meg said, “I’ll go with you, young master. I have nothing to do here anyway.” Zhao Hai didn’t object, and just brought her along.

Upon arriving at the prairie, Zhao Hai immediately released the blood hawk, then ordered the undead coach drivers to follow it. He then brought Meg back to Iron Mountain Castle once again.

No one could notice anything different about this convoy from its appearance. Laura’s wagon was completely sealed, so no one could tell if there were any people inside.

Zhao Hai and the others still returned to rest inside the space at night, under Laura’s insistence. It was because she knew that Zhao Hai had drunk the Water Of Void, and the space was good for his body. That was why she wanted Zhao Hai to sleep inside the space every night.

Zhao Hai knew that Laura’s insistence was due to her caring for him. He didn’t object to that. After all, no one would disturb his slumber in the space, which was good for him. There was also no noise. He could sleep well there.

Crune’s laboratory, which had originally been inside the space, had now been moved to Iron Mountain Castle. Crune had originally wanted to stay inside the space, but Laura could no longer stand him, and had chased him out to Iron Mountain Castle.

Crune didn’t mind. He could settle with just a laboratory that had been readied for him. To be honest, he had willingly relocated to Iron Mountain Castle, since the environment there wasn’t bad.

Over the next few days, most of Zhao Hai and the others’ focus was put into the construction of the school. There were more than 200 kids from the Large-horned Raging Bull Tribe. More than 40 were over 12 years old, and more than 100 were under 12 years old, while more than 3 dozen were between 4 to 7 years old and around a dozen were under 4 years old.

Zhao Hai and the others organized them. The children over 12 years old would mainly learn literature and martial arts. The children between 7 and 12 years old would learn mathematics on top of those. The children from 4 to 7 years old would be taught like they were budding talents, with simple language and simple physical training first.

But now there was a problem, and that was teaching materials. There weren’t a lot of concrete teaching materials on Ark Continent. Normally, teachers would teach the students about words, and then start by bringing out the magic or battle aura books, expecting the children to know what was written in them. Almost every school on the continent taught like this.

Zhao Hai thought that this wasn’t a very good method. Kids were active, and books like the basics of magic and battle auras were some of the most boring and tasteless things. Normal children would find it very hard to be interested in them, so Zhao Hai believed that such books were not suitable to become teaching materials.

Zhao Hai had never wanted to write his own teaching materials, for it would take too much time. They could only look through the books that they had right now for something suitable.

However, Zhao Hai knew after searching that the spiritual well-being of the people in this world was sorely lacking. Books in this world were divided into 4 major kinds. 1st was magics, which included basics, techniques, visualization, research of magic formations, low-level, mid-level, and high-level usage manuals, and nothing more. One would seldom see the recollections of high class mages, because such a book would not be circulated, and would instead passed down to their own apprentices.

2nd was battle auras, which included basics, basic techniques, utilization of weapons and such, and nothing else. Like magics, recollections would be passed down to close disciples.

3rd was alchemy and medicine concoction. Such books were few in number, with few readers and fewer writers. These books would only contain basic knowledge, and nothing of post-learning thoughts.

4th was notes. Books like these consisted mainly of travelogues, which mostly introduced the lifestyles of the local countryside and special legends. Such books were many, but were not written according to a standard. Normally, they had been written by mages or some high level warriors regarding their experiences and impressions. Zhao Hai liked these books a lot, for he could learn a lot of special customs from them.

But if teaching material were to be selected from these 4 kinds of books, it was evident that none of them were very suitable. In the end, Zhao Hai decided that children from 4 to 7 years old would mainly learn literature, which would be from travelogues. Such books introduced all sorts of curious tales, which a lot of children should like. Children from 7 to 12 years old would also learn from travelogues, but such books would not make up the main part of their education, which would mostly be composed of the basic books of magics and martial arts. The teaching materials for children over 12 years old would have to be decided after confirming their development.

Chapter 276: ‘You Have Won’

No one went against the plan Zhao Hai put forward. On the continent, children were enrolled in school at around the ages of 6-8 years old. Children that enrolled at around the age of 6 came from well-off families like merchants or nobles, and children that enrolled at around the age of 8 were from families that were not well-off, mainly commoners.

But the school enrollment age that Zhao Hai had set was 4 years old, two years younger compared to those noble children. Teaching these children some basic knowledge wouldn’t be detrimental, and wouldn’t affect their martial arts studies.

Zhao Hai carefully examined the map that Wales had given him. Right now, Wales should have reached the horse-headed race’s territory and become very familiar with them. Based on this, he should hurry and catch up with him.

From Zhao Hai’s current position, he would have to walk around five days or so to reach Wales’ position, but Zhao Hai did not want to waste that much time walking. His undead did not need rest anyway, so he could just let them walk without stopping. This way, they could reach Wales’ position in around two days.

During these two days, they did not meet anyone on the prairie. Zhao Hai did not care about the prairie, and let Cai-Er manage everything. He was currently busy constructing the school with Maylin.

Although the size of their school was not very big, it still needed to contain several hundred people. Zhao Hai had just realized that they did not have enough teachers, but they did not have enough workforce available. They were especially lacking in people that were literate and could teach mathematics.

One person that was literate and could do mathematics that Zhao Hai had prepared was Orloga. Even though Orloga was an undead and did not need rest, there were too many children, and it wasn’t enough for him to do it alone.

But the problem was that Zhao Hai could not take people out to act as the children’s teachers, which made Zhao Hai feel very difficult. Eventually, he had no choice but to pull out some undead mages to teach the children how to read and write, and the person he chose was Zhao Jia.

Zhao Jia was a great light-element mage, so naturally he was literate. But the students were all Large Horned Raging Bull children, and they could not learn magic, so letting him teach the children how to read and write was very normal. As the matter stood, the literacy aspects would be handled by Zhao Jia, and the mathematics would be given to Orloga.

As for the children aged 4-7 years old, Zhao Hai did not pull out a teacher for them. Rather, he selected two female slaves, as well as a female from the Large Horned Raging Bull Tribe, to teach these children. The children aged 4-7 were still young and needed to be nurtured, so it was better to let females do this.

At the same time, there was another matter that was causing headaches for Zhao Hai, and that was textbooks. He had already decided on the teaching material, but what would he do about textbooks? They did not have enough books on hand to give each child a book.

In the end, Zhao Hai had to come up with another method. He gave each child a stack of white paper which was bound together by strings. They would be using these to write down what the teachers taught them. Although it would slow down the teaching process, it was still a good method.

Although they would need a large supply of paper and ink to teach the children like this, it did not matter. On the continent, buying paper was much cheaper than buying books.

On Ark Continent, there were currently no moveable printing presses; what they used was a simple primitive engraving printing, so books were much more expensive. There were many commoner children on the continent who couldn’t afford textbooks in schools, so they used the same method Zhao Hai was using now.

Zhao Hai gave those children the steel pens he had prepared for them. Zhao Hai had purchased these in bulk when they were still in Casa City. He had originally bought them for the beastmen, but now they were being used by the children.

But Zhao Hai had said that the children had to treasure the pen and paper in their hands. They had to take notes everyday, and the teacher would check them the next day. The teachers would also check their pens. If their pens were even slightly damaged, they would receive punishment.

Of course, it wasn’t any kind of corporal punishment, and Zhao Hai did not want the teachers to hand out corporal punishment. But this punishment which was to not let them go to physical education class, was quite serious to a child.

If one had to say which class was the favourite class of all among the students, it would be physical education, because they would be allowed to go out and play. But the physical education they taught here was different from the one Zhao Hai had on Earth. Here they used physical education class to teach the children martial arts and riding skills.

This kind of physical education was very beloved by the children. Once they heard that if they even slightly damaged their pens, they would not be allowed to go to physical education, to them this was the most serious punishment possible, and thus the children all treated their pens with care.

With the full support of Zhao Hai and the others, the school was finally finished, and those Large Horned Raging Bull children became the first batch of students. But they were only daytime students. Once the children were let out of school, all the people in the castle could go to school to learn how to read, write, and do arithmetic. This was something Zhao Hai had stipulated, since the teachers for language and arithmetics were all undead, they wouldn’t get tired, and could give extra lessons to the beastmen and servants.

These two days also allowed Zhao Hai to completely understand how vast Beastmen Prairie was. After moving non-stop for two days, Zhao Hai had not met a single beastman on the road, which completely surprised him.

After two days, he had already gone from the Bull Head Tribe’s territory to the Horse Head Tribe’s territory. Because this was the adjacent area between the two territories, there were few people that came here, out of fear of causing a misunderstanding.

But once they entered the Horse-headed races’ territory, not much time passed before Zhao Hai saw a camp not far away. The camp was not very big, but the ruling flag of Herculean Bull Tribe fluttered in the wind above the camp.

Zhao Hai couldn’t help but reveal a faint smile. He knew that Wales was a very proud person, and although his Herculean Bull Tribe had been defeated by the Fighting Bull Tribe, he would not hide his identity. He would always show his ruling flag high on his tent wherever he went.

Zhao Hai did not say anything, as he just sped up and hurried towards Wales’ camp. He did not release Gasol because he was being held by Cai-Er. Cai-Er had been controlling Gasol, or rather, it was more accurate to say that Gasol had been in a half conscious state the whole time. Cai’er had been giving him water from the space, which was why Gasol had not starved to death yet.

Actually, not only had Gasol not died, he was living quite well. It had to be known that the water from the space was the water of life, which was a rare treasure on the continent. It would have been strange if something had happened to him instead.

It was very obvious that Wales had also seen Zhao Hai, as people came rushing out from his camp, their hoofbeats creating a shocking sound. When Zhao Hai saw this, he gave a faint smile and turned his head to speak to Laura, “It seems big brother Wales is anxious to see Gasol. What do you think they will do to him?”

Laura gave him a bitter smile, “How will they treat him? You can tell by the brothers from my family, fighting to the death over their positions. Big brother Wales is still alright, but Gasol caused the death of his father, so he definitely will not let Gasol off. Even though they really need people right now, Gasol will not be able to live.”

Zhao Hai nodded; he understood Laura’s logic. The Herculean Bull Tribe needed people right now, and Gasol was a level 8 expert, which would be a great help to the current Herculean Bull Tribe. But because the grudge between Wales and Gasol was too deep, Wales would definitely not let him go.

When Wales appeared in front of Zhao Hai, he did not greet him, but instead immediately asked, “Little Hai, where’s Gasol?”

Zhao Hai smiled and waved his hand, then Gasol appeared in front of Wales. The vines on his body had already disappeared and he was still unconscious.

When Mendez who had followed Wales saw Gasol, he immediately released a roar of rage and jumped down from his bull. An axe head then flew at Gasol.

With a “dang” sound ringing out, Wales blocked Mendez’s axe. Mendez’s eyes were blood red as he turned to look at Wales and angrily roared, “Little Seven, what are you doing? I want to kill him, I must kill him!”

Wales spoke with a cold expression, “Calm down, sixth brother. He is still unconscious right now, so if you kill him, he wouldn’t be aware of it. That would be letting him off too easy. We’ll wake him up and then kill him.”

Zhao Hai quickly said, “Big brother, don’t get worked up first. Let’s go to the camp first, I have some things I want to discuss with you.”

Wales nodded and waved his hand. A subordinate immediately came over and turned his head. Without dismounting from his bull, he grabbed Gasol and placed him onto his bull as he followed Wales back into the camp.

Once they arrived at the camp, Zhao Hai saw Yale standing in front of the camp. Yale’s complexion was a little thin and pale; it was clear that he had been running around the past few days settling the worries of the Herculean Bull Tribe.

Zhao Hai and Laura dismounted from their wagon and greeted Yale. Yale returned their greetings, and then looked at Gasol on the back of the bull with a complicated gaze. He was not a part of the Herculean Bull Tribe, so his hatred towards Gasol was not as deep as Wales and the others’.

Wales and the others also jumped off of their bulls, and Wales looked over at Gasol. He said to Zhao Hai, “Little Hai, how do we wake him up?”

Zhao Hai gave a faint smile and said, “Just dump a bucket of cold water on him.”

Wales did not have any cold water. He just walked forward and sent Gasol flying two meters with a kick, which woke him up.

When he opened his eyes, Gasol saw Wales and the others, as well as Zhao Hai standing beside Wales, and he understood what was happening. He did not show a trace of nervousness and slowly stood up. Looking at Wales, he suddenly revealed a faint smile and said, “You have won in the end, haven’t you.”

Wales went forward and grabbed Gasol by his collar. He punched him to the ground and angrily scolded, “Bastard! Are those the kinds of words you can still say? Are you even a member of the Herculean Bull Tribe? You bastard!” He continued to scold Gasol as he kicked him several times.

Chapter 277: Best Time To Counterattack

After kicking Gasol a few times, Wales finally stopped. Gasol did not put up any resistance, and Wales’ kicks were quite heavy, making Gasol spit out two mouthfuls of blood.

Wales did not want to kick Gasol to death like this, so he stopped. Looking at Gasol, he said, “What is your brain made of? Is it full of goat shit? Did you feel like our father had mistreated you from the beginning? Is it because you achieved the greatest merits in battle, and did the most for the tribe, but you still couldn’t become the chieftain?”

Gasol gave a cold snort and said nothing else. It was very clear that he was agreeing with what Wales had just said. Wales looked at Gasol’s appearance and suddenly felt an an urge to laugh. He really wanted to laugh at the fact that Gasol was too foolish. Even now, Gasol still did not realize why their father did not want to give him the position of chieftain.

Wales shook his head and sighed as he said, “Gasol, I had always thought that you were a smart person, but now I finally realize that you are just an idiot. A fool that could not be any dumber. Did you not realize that our tribe had been fighting less and less with foreign tribes? A few years ago, father had the same idea as you. He wanted to prove that our Herculean Bull Tribe was the number one tribe amongst the bull-headed races, but then what? Our father found that after every expedition, although we obtained many slaves, the strength of our own tribe was slowly being consumed, and slowly, most of our youth were dying out. But because he chose not to fight for a year, the youth population of our tribe slowly began to increase once again. Our father realized this, and chose not to launch any military campaigns, just so he could give our tribe a chance to rebuild our strength.”

When he said this, he saw the expression on Gasol’s face changing. Today, he decided to let everything out, so that Gasol would no longer feel like he had suffered any kind of injustice.

He took a deep breath, and then said, “After learning of the Fighting Bull Tribe’s threat towards our tribe, our father reduced the number of foreign troops, and began to support West Wonder King, who the Fighting Bull Tribe’s chieftain is at odds with. If West Wonder King broke out, the Fighting Bull Tribe would be weakened. Without our father’s support, what do you think West Wonder King would rely on to fight against the Fighting Bull Tribe for so long?”

Gasol’s expression turned even uglier. He had not seen through anything that Wales had just told him, and he had always wondered why his father would be close to West Wonder King rather than the Fighting Bull Tribe’s chieftain. It was for this reason that he had cried out for injustice from the Fighting Bull Tribe’s chieftain. It could be said that the reason why the Fighting Bull Tribe had recovered so quickly was inseparable to his support.

Wales saw Gasol’s expression and he gave a cold snort, “What? You’re regretting your decision now? You couldn’t see why our father supported the Western King, and stubbornly supported the Fighting Bull Tribe’s leader. You were completely fooled by just a few words of praise. What a joke. Just based on this one point, are you worthy of being the Herculean Bull Tribe’s chieftain? A pity. What a pity indeed. Father was too soft, and chose not to limit your military power, otherwise, the Herculean Bull Tribe would not be in this kind of situation today.”

Gasol quickly got up and said, “Nonsense, that’s all nonsense, it’s all fake. Father never thought of this, and everything was fabricated by you!”

Wales gave a cold snort and said, “You’re already clear on whether I made it up or not. In order to sit on that spot (chieftain position), you went crazy and even dared to cause the death of our father. Now you’ve even dragged your own tribe into the deep abyss. I’ll see what sort of face you make when you see the Beast God after you die.”

The beastmen all believed that after they died, they would meet the Beast God. The Beast God would look over the deeds you accomplished throughout your life, and decide whether you were to be a beastman or just a beast in your next life.

When Gasol heard Wales say this, his face turned completely pale. He had been on the verge of breakdown to begin with, but now he had already fallen to ground while continuously muttering, “It’s a lie, it’s all a lie.”

Wales looked at Gasol’s appearance, and then he turned his head to look around at his guard and said, “Prepare the white flag, brother Sixth. It’s your turn.”

The white flag was a beastman tradition. It was something that was used to wrap dead traitors. The beastmen had a legend saying that the Beast God hated the color white the most, so anyone that was wrapped in white when they died would be turned into a beastkin by the Beast God. It was because of this that beastmen executed their traitors in this fashion. They wanted them to become beasts in their next life so they could compensate for the debts they had incurred in this life.

As soon as the guards heard Wales telling them to prepare the white flag, they immediately understood what he meant. They rushed off to prepare it as Mendez picked up his giant axe.

He did not have the slightest bit of compassion for Gasol right now. How could he possibly have compassion? It was this man in front of him who had caused the deaths of his father and brothers, and caused them to lose the camping grounds that the Herculean Bull Tribe had inhabited for thousands of years. Right now, Mendez wished that he could skin Gasol alive, so how could he feel any kind of compassion?

Meanwhile, Gasol had completely lost his will to live. He curled himself up into a ball, not knowing what was happening around him at all. When Mendez lifted him up, he did not react at all.

Soon, a piece of white cloth was prepared, and Mendez helped himself to it. A single swing of the axe chopped off Gasol’s head, not giving him a chance to retaliate at all.

After Gasol died, the guards wrapped his body in the white cloth, while Mendez threw the giant axe in his hands away and broke down loudly in tears.

Wales let out a sigh. His eyes were also a little wet, and he was filled with sorrow. The Herculean Bull Tribe had been destroyed by Gasol’s hands in such a way that even if they reclaimed their main camp now, their status among the beastmen would fall by a large margin. This was a bad kind of news that could not get any worse.

After seeing them tidy up Gasol’s corpse, Wales let out a sigh and beckoned with his hand as he said, “Find a place to bury him.” The guards took the body away.

Wales felt as if he had somehow lost all the strength in his body. He stumbled back to his own tent and drank large mouthfuls out of a silver wine jug.

Although he had exacted his revenge now, he did not feel any happiness at all. On the contrary, he was deeply saddened. The sadness in his heart was getting close to driving him crazy.

Yale and Zhao Hai had also noticed that Wales’ emotions were unstable, and quickly followed him into the tent. When they saw Wales’ appearance, Yale couldn’t help letting out a sigh. He knew that Wales had been suffering a lot of pressure lately. The Herculean Bull Tribe was like a rock that kept weighing him down. Although he had exacted his revenge, he still had to kill his own brother in the process. Wales was a very compassionate and righteous person, so Yale knew that must be feeling very uncomfortable in his heart right now.

Zhao Hai did not know how he should approach Wales right now. He had never gone through anything like this, so anything he said right now would seem tactless. Zhao Hai did not say anything, and just gave a sigh. He sat down beside him and picked up another silver jug to pour himself a cup of milk wine. After drinking a mouthful, he turned to Yale and said, “Mister Yale, please sit. I have something I want to discuss with you.”

Yales looked at Wales once, then nodded and said, “Alright. Go ahead.”

Zhao Hai said, “I met Gasol in the Large Horned Raging Bull tribe’s territory while he was robbing them. He had killed almost all the youths, and was transporting something, wanting to go to the Western King’s territory. I killed all his guards, but please rest assured that I buried them all. In order to make sure that this disappearance was not spread, I sent people to bring all the Large Horned Raging Bull Tribe’s people to another location, and they will never appear in the bull-headed races’ territory ever again.”

Yale did not understand what Zhao Hai meant by this in the beginning, but after thinking about it for a bit, he immediately understood. He looked at Zhao Hai with an expression of gratitude as he said, “Thank you, little Hai. If it wasn’t for you, the Hercules Bull Tribe would not have had the opportunity to reclaim the position of the ruling race.”

“That’s right, little Hai. I, your big brother, am truly thanking you. If it wasn’t for you, the Herculean Bull Tribe would have been done for.” At this moment, Wales had already let go of his wine jug, and he looked at Zhao Hai with a grateful expression. Mendez had also just come in from the entrance.

Wales was truly a heroic figure to be able to recover himself this quickly. Actually, this was also thanks to Zhao Hai. If Zhao Hai had not talked about this matter, Wales would not have recovered himself this quickly. Compared to Gasol, he cared more about the future of the Herculean Bull Tribe.

Wales and the others were very clear that if the other bull-headed tribes knew about the matter of Gasol robbing the Large-horned Raging Bull Tribe, then the Herculean Bull Tribe would never receive the support of any other bull-headed race in the future.

The Large-horned Raging Bull Tribe hadn’t had a high status within the Bull Head Race, and they weren’t powerful in fighting ability, but they were always hospitable, and their disposition was famous. If it became known that Gasol had tried to rob them, it would have definitely incurred public outrage.

The Herculean Bull Tribe had just been chased out by the Fighting Bull Tribe, so the branch tribes would definitely not be willing to accept them. And over the years, the Herculean Bull Tribe’s chieftain had taken care of the branch tribes, so these people had not forgotten this kindness. This was very important for Wales.

If the branch tribes knew that it was Gasol who had robbed the Large-horned Raging Bull Tribe, then they would come to dislike the Herculean Bull Tribe and not support them anymore. For the Herculean Bull Tribe, this would definitely have been a catastrophe. What the Fighting Bull Tribe could only dream of, would then have been realized by Gasol himself.

Wales couldn’t help but shake his head upon thinking such thoughts. He really did not know when Gasol had become this stupid. He remembered that Gasol had not been this dumb in the past.

Zhao Hai turned his head to look at Wales as he said, “It was because I was lucky enough to bump into Gasol. Otherwise, things would have truly become troublesome.”

Wales let out a sigh and shook his head, “Little Hai, come with me to see the Mastiff Tribe. You have many things in your hands, so perhaps you can help your big brother stabilize the current situation there.”

Zhao Hai did a double take. He looked at Wales and said, “Big brother, are you serious? You aren’t going to West Wonder King? Are we not going to find out the situation with the Fighting Bull Tribe?”

Wales let out a sigh, but he did not know what to say. He wanted to find out the current situation with the Fighting Bull Tribe and West Wonder King, but he also felt as if he could not leave Zhao Hai’s side right now. This was all making him feel very conflicted.

The beastmen all worshiped the Beast God, and from what Wales could see, Zhao Hai was a benefactor sent to him by the Beast God. He had encountered all kinds of trouble during this period of time, but Zhao Hai had solved it all for him, making him want to keep Zhao Hai by his side.

Zhao Hai saw Wales’ expression and said with a smile, “Alright, big brother, no problems. We should stick to our original plan. You and others go meet the Mastiff Tribe, and I’ll go find West Wonder King to get some news. Then I’ll immediately come to the Mastiff Tribe’s territory and look for you. What do you think about that?”

Wales nodded, “It’s our only choice. You should stay here tonight and have a good drink with us, and then you can leave tomorrow.”

Zhao Hai smiled, “No problem. Oh yeah, I still have something I want to give you. Come with me.” After he finished speaking, he walked outside.

Wales and the others had confused expressions on their faces as they looked at Zhao Hai, but they still followed him outside. When they came out, Zhao Hai took out all the resources he had taken from the Large-horned Raging Bull Tribe. He pointed at the resources and said, “Big brother, these are all the items that Gasol stole from the Large-horned Raging Bull Tribe. They have all been used, and they cannot be sold on the prairie, so you should use them.”

Wales patted Zhao Hai’s shoulder and said, “Thank you brother, I won’t say any unnecessary words. Let’s head into the tent and have a drink.”

They reentered the tent and after sitting down, Zhao Hai looked at Wales and said, “Big brother, what plans do you have to attack the old camp?”

Wales was stunned for a bit. To be honest, he really did not have any plans. Right now he was only thinking about pacifying his tribesmen. He had not thought about attacking the old camp at all.

When Zhao Hai saw the expression Wales had, he knew that he had not thought about this at all. He couldn’t help but say, “Big brother, I think you should give it some more thought. Although the Herculean Bull Tribe has suffered heavy losses, the tribesmen’s hearts are also filled with hatred. As long as big brother has a supply of grains and they can eat their fill, the first thing they will think of will be revenge. Adding on the fact that the Fighting Bull Tribe has just seized the old camp and still do not have much control over the bull-headed races, there should be many tribes still in support of you, which you can make use of. If there is a need, you can also ask the Mastiff Race for help. If push comes to shove, just give them some grains. If you give the Fighting Bull Tribe enough time, they will be able to regain their footing, and your tribesmen will be disappointed in you. It will make getting revenge much harder when the time comes.”

Wales silently listened to Zhao Hai speak. This was his first time thinking about this, but he had to admit that what Zhao Hai said was right. The beastmen were like this; they worshipped the strong, but the Fighting Bull Tribe’s reputation was not good, since they liked fighting too much. Considering the fact that the Herculean Bull Tribe had ruled the bull-headed races for many years, the majority of the branch tribes all supported them. It meant that this was indeed the best time to launch a counterattack.

Chapter 278: In Need of a Maniac

Yale nodded and said, “I think what little Hai said is very right. Sometimes, hatred is not a force to be underestimated. If we can use this power well, then defeating the Fighting Bull Tribe by ourselves is not an impossibility.”

Mendez had just recovered, and he also nodded and said, “ We also have the element of surprise on our side. No one would think that we would counter attack right after a big loss. Didn’t the Fighting Bull Tribe also use the element of surprise to steal our main camp?

Wales frowned and said, “These are valid points, but the problem is that our tribe’s only high elder is injured. I’m afraid it’s not enough to deal with the Fighting Bull Tribe’s high elder. Furthermore, didn’t the Fighting Bull Tribe also hire a level 9 human powerhouse?”

When Wales laid it all out, everyone fell silent. Regardless of their plans, the presence of a level 9 powerhouse had always been a giant rock weighing down on their hearts. If they really wanted to fight against the Fighting Bull Tribe, they couldn’t do it without a level 9 powerhouse of their own.

Zhao Hai turned to Wales and said, “Big brother, do you think we can use grains, vegetables and oil to convince the Mastiff Tribe to use their level 9 powerhouse? You’d best ask the other tribes and see if we can also use what we have to bring out their powerhouses too. Also, don’t forget that, out here in the prairie, if a human powerhouse is too full of himself, the larger fighting tribes won’t let that fly. If we can bring out the powerhouses of the other tribes, we can win. Maybe with the Liquid of Life and the Magic Peach Juice, we can heal the high elder of the Herculean Bull Tribe as well. That will greatly improve our chances of winning.”

Wales frowned, “The wounds of a level 9 powerhouse don’t heal that easily. If we can actually heal the wounds of the high elder, I will immediately arrange for a counterattack. If we can’t, then we will just have to endure.”

Zhao Hai nodded at that. He still admired this careful part of Wales’ personality. He hadn’t let hatred fill his mind, and instead remained calm. This was good.

He replied immediately, “Good. If big brother has needs, I have all the grains you need. Oh yeah. Tell them that I also have vegetables and oil. All are guaranteed to be fresh.”

Wales nodded and turned to Mendez. “Sixth brother, slaughter a raging bull. Let’s have whole roasted bull today.” Mendez turned around and left.

Zhai Hai was somewhat surprised. Usually, the beastmen wouldn’t slaughter cows. Cows and bulls had many uses to them. Normally, they only served cows and bulls to the most respected of guests as a feast. He never would have thought that Wales was going to slaughter a bull.

He spoke hurriedly, “ Please, big brother, we are already a family. Why do you do this?”

Wales smiled and said, “Save it, little Hai, you don’t have to mind. I have been feeling uneasy because I haven’t been able to serve you a whole roasted bull ever since I met you. And today, I, your big brother, have settled a big grudge. We are going to have a big drink.”

Zhao Hai smiled, “Fine. Since big brother is in the mood today, we will drink till we drop, hahahaha.” After the conversation, they went outside to find the bull already slaughtered and ready for roasting.

Laura and the others weren’t just loitering around doing nothing. They were helping the guards rearrange stuff. This was permitted by Zhao Hai, as he was now the blood-sworn brother of Wales. Laura and the others weren’t outsiders, so they should be helping.

After Zhao Hai and company sat down, they began to discuss the matter of their counterattack nonstop. Even though Wales was highly conservative, he still had a fire in his heart when it came to the Fighting Bull Tribe stealing their main camp. However, now that he was the Herculean Bull Tribe’s chieftain, he couldn’t afford to make a mistake because of a moment’s rage. That was why he was being careful. If there was a chance to counterattack, however, he would still take it.

Like he had said before, he would immediately begin preparations for a counterattack once the Herculean Bull Tribe’s high elder was healed. That was his intention.

Later that night, Zhao Hai couldn’t help but get drunk again. Wales’ feelings were complicated, so he needed to drink, and Zhao Hai thus had no choice but to drink with him. In the end, everyone fell asleep drunk.

But this time Zhao Hai did not get wasted. He had arranged for Cai-Er to give him the Space’s water if he got too drunk, so he could wake up faster. He didn’t want to sleep in a big tent with Laura and the others, because while it would feel good, it would honestly still be quite awkward.

If anyone knew that Zhao Hai used the Liquid of Life as a means to cure hangovers, they would strangle him for sure. The Liquid of Life was too precious to be used as a mere hangover cure. No one would stand it.

After drinking the Liquid of Life, Zhao Hai sobered up immediately. It wasn’t too late, so Laura was just sitting in the tent chatting. When she noticed Zhao Hai waking up she immediately said, “How are you feeling, Hai-bro? Feeling well? Do you have a headache?”

Zhao Hai chuckled. “Good, no pain at all now. We have to go back to the territories of the bull headed tribes tomorrow, so we must be completely on our guard. I’m afraid the Fighting Bull Tribe might catch word of our presence.”

Laura paused. “Are you saying the Fighting Bull Tribe might obtain information regarding our meeting with big brother Wales? No way, right? We haven’t encountered that many beastmen tribes on the way here, right?”

Zhao Hai shook his head. “It’s better to be careful. We should try to avoid going outside to gather information. It should be fine if we can just be more attentive than usual. Do not actively gather information. That may attract suspicion.”

Laura and the others all nodded, then Zhao Hai turned to Wales’ camp and sighed, “The Herculean Bull Tribe has been hurt badly this time. Even if they reclaim their main camp, the humiliation they’ve suffered will be forever recorded in their history. A stain that can’t be erased. Most importantly, with their main camp stolen, it’s a death blow to their authority. It won’t be possible for the Herculean Bull Tribe to rule the bull headed tribes again in the future. There will surely be more and more challengers.”

Laura had once been part of the upper class, so of course she understood this logic. That time when she was assailed, the Magidel family had wanted to immediately take over her business. Many of her employees were thinking of betrayal, so after the incident she had mercilessly cleaned house. It was because of her ruthless policy that she was able to become completely independent from the Magidel family.

Now that Laura heard what Zhao Hai had to say, she couldn’t help but nod in agreement, “Yeah. The thing that took the biggest hit from this incident was the Herculean Bull Tribe’s authority. It will become increasingly difficult for them to rule the bull headed tribes again.”

Zhao Hai nodded, and with both eyes staring coldly, said, “If I were big brother Wales, I would mount an all-out counterattack with the entire tribe to take back the main camp as fast as possible, and slaughter all of the Fighting Bull Tribe’s members. We’ll have to eradicate all of the Fighting Bull Tribe. This must be done so that we can deter the other tribes and instill fear in anyone who plots against us. You must understand that, in this world, the most feared person is not an expert who calculates his losses and gains, but a maniac who doesn’t care about them. And right now, that is what the Herculean Bull Tribe needs.”

Laura frowned. “But won’t that just cause more problems for the Herculean Bull Tribe? How will they ever rule the bull headed tribes again?”

Zhao Hai smiled. “There will be no other tribes that will dare to fight to the death with the Herculean Bull Tribe. Even if they can knock the Herculean Bull Tribe down, will they even be able to hold on to the throne afterwards? Once the Herculean Bull Tribe takes it back in that manner, there will be no one that can easily push them off. If they can peacefully recuperate after that, there won’t be any problems in the future.”

Laura nodded. Sometimes that was what a tribe had to do. Use a moment’s rampage to bring about a longer period of peace. It was highly necessary.

Zhao Hai sighed. “Forget it, I’m not even the Herculean Bull Tribe’s chieftain. There’s no use talking about it anymore. It’s getting late, so let’s go to sleep. We still have to rush tomorrow.”

The next morning, Zhao Hai said his goodbyes to Wales and headed towards the West Wonder King’s territory. It was apparent that the movements of West Wonder King had become increasingly important. If he were to support Wales still, then the chances of Wales winning against the Fighting Bull Tribe would be greater. Of course, it would have to be under the condition that they were able to control the situation. Wales did not want to create another Fighting Bull Tribe’s chieftain.

Zhao Hai had now grown curious about West Wonder King. He thought West Wonder King had to be someone with capabilities. West Wonder King had been at war with the Fighting Bull Tribe’s chieftain, who hadn’t been able to get rid of him. With the support of the Herculean Bull Tribe, he had been able to fracture the Fighting Bull Tribe. He was not some simple personage. Zhao Hai really wanted to know what kind of person was capable of doing such deeds.

It would take around 10 days to reach West Wonder King’s main camp from their current location. They would also encounter several smaller beastmen tribes along the way, which Zhao Hai wouldn’t bother with anymore. He needed to speed up, so he attached both the Big Bellied Pig Tribe and the Large-horned Raging Bull Tribe’s friendship flags on his wagon and headed straight for West Wonder King’s main camp.

Along the way, Zhao Hai’s group mostly spent their time either in the Space or in Iron Mountain Castle. Now that the school was up and running, it seemed to be fairly effective. Although the Large-horned Raging Bull Tribe’s children had yet to adapt completely, they started to attend school under the supervision of Alaes’ group so they wouldn’t run all over the place. The school was slowly getting on the right track.

What Zhao Hai needed to do right now was to quickly build processing factories for mutton and goat hair. Also, he had had another idea, which was getting Alaes’ group to build a milk wine processing factory.

Milk wine had always been a specialty liquor of beastmen. The main ingredient came from the milk of various animals, and the refining technique was not that complicated either. However, beastmen had not yet come up with a means of distillation, therefore their milk wine was not so easily preserved, and its alcohol percentage was not as high. That was why whenever the beastmen drank, it was always one jug after another nonstop.

Chapter 279: West Wonder King’s camp

Beastmen weren’t the only ones who didn’t utilize distilling methods in their alcohol; humans didn’t use them either. This puzzled Zhao Hai greatly. Another thing was that the popular alcohols here on Ark Continent were typically fruit wines for humans, while it was milk wine for the beastmen. There were basically none that had been made using grains or vegetables. This also puzzled Zhao Hai.

Beastmen drank a lot of alcohol due to the environment they lived in. It was very cold here during the winter, and the other three seasons weren’t much better. They had to eat and sleep in the open when they herded animals, and given the unpredictable weather, a good sack of wine could sometimes be a lifesaver.

Because of that, the beastmen weren’t just alcoholic, they were inclined towards strong liquor. But right now, there wasn’t any strong liquor produced on Ark Continent, but they could make milk wine themselves, which meant that they didn’t have to go and buy liquor. That was why milk wine was still the staple on the plains.

Back on Earth, Zhao Hai would drink sometimes, but he mostly drank beer or white wine. He rarely partook in fruit wines, so he didn’t know how to judge them. But if he had to put it into words, white wine would be fine. It was strong in alcohol content, and if produced properly, he wouldn’t get a hangover the day after drinking.

But here in Ark Continent, he could only have a few fruit wines, and undistilled at that. Honestly speaking, they were really not that great.

That was why Zhao Hai had wanted to start a brewery early on, but he hadn’t known how, and the same applied to Greene and others. Although Laura’s subordinates were very capable, they didn’t know how to brew liquor as well. If they just followed the recipe books, nothing of good quality would be produced anyways. So Zhao Hai had never gotten started with the whole project.

But now they had Alaes’ group. Although they didn’t know how to make grain wines, it was enough to just make milk wines. Don’t forget, right now in Zhao Hai’s ranch, he could purchase milk cows, and their milk production was surprisingly high.

So now Zhao Hai wanted to experiment and see if he could make some grain wines. The food production of his farm in the Space was ever increasing. If he unloaded them all onto the food market of the beastmen, it would have too much of an impact. It would most definitely attract too much attention, and then every country on the mainland would investigate the cause. The result of that investigation would lead to a certain individual that didn’t exist, which would be a major problem. So he wanted to transform his stockpiles into something else he could sell, and liquor was undoubtedly the optimal choice.

Regardless of whether it was rice or corn, they were both excellent materials for fermentation. If they could manage to ferment white wine and process it through distillation, the resulting white wine would be around 40% proof. Even with only this much alcohol content, it would be considered fairly strong here in Ark. The beastmen would love it for sure.

So liquor-making has been added to the schedule. But there were still many difficulties to consider before starting. So Zhao Hai wanted to try making milk wines first, and experiment based on how they did.

Right now, Zhao Hai had 200 milk cows and 1000 sheep. This way, whether he wanted milk or wool, there would be plenty. Now he could actually go ahead with producing dairy-related products and wool processing, so he wouldn’t have to only sell rabbit meat for income like before.

However, all of this would take a long time to prepare, and Zhao Hai was not in a hurry. He had all the time in the world now; they could take it slow.

Zhao hai travelled in 4 days what would take 10 for others. That was because his carriages were pulled by the undead, which didn’t feel fatigue. So, he could just let them keep marching.

The carts that the beastmen had were all unsuited to be pulled by the scale-horned horses or windchaser horses. As a result, Zhao Hai turned all the cart-pulling raging bulls into undead with a merciless heart. And now all the raging bulls could work all day and night.

In all honestly, Zhao Hai’s heart still ached after turning all those raging bulls into undead. Even if he had simply sold those bulls on the market, they would have fetched a pretty penny. Sadly, he did not have the connections to do so.

Recently, Zhao Hai would let his blood hawks roam to see if there were any small tribes around. If there were any, they would try to go around and avoid them, which would save them some travel time.

What Wales needed the most right now was information regarding West Wonder King, so Zhao Hai went around the smaller tribes because he didn’t want to waste too much time with them.

The way Zhao Hai was moving right now might probably make West Wonder King suspicious. He was ignoring all the different territories, and heading straight for West Wonder King’s base. Normally, considering how much food Zhao Hai could hold on his carriages, he would have had to sell to most, if not all, of the smaller tribes he encountered on the way to West Wonder King’s base. It would be impossible to haul all of it safely to his base. Bigger tribes like the West Wonder King’s had their own connections with a steady food supplier if they ever wanted to buy food. When those food merchants wanted to transport the food they bought, they would have their tribes’ battle flags planted on their carriages, thus signaling who the transports were specifically for, and in turn ensure their safety.

People like Zhao Hai who did not have the support of bigger tribes would usually sell their food to smaller tribes or have them robbed; they rarely reached the bigger tribes.

On the prairie, every big tribal camp was like an open market. There was a day each month where the human merchants came and did business with smaller tribes in the larger tribes’ camp. Usually, the smaller tribes had to be lucky if they wanted to buy something from these markets, because they would have to meet a willing human merchant. If they were unlucky, they would have to wait until market day and go to the bigger tribes’ base to buy what they needed.

Among all the beastmen tribes, West Wonder King’s base was not actually considered a big base. However, they were considered at least a medium-sized one, so they were able to host open markets, but only for a day every two months.

The result was that the smaller tribes around West Wonder King’s camp found it even more difficult to get what they needed. It was also because of that that their desire to buy was very strong. Hence it was generally impossible for a passing convoy like Zhao Hai’s group who was not specifically delivering to a bigger tribe to travel safely. Their goods usually ended up being bought off or robbed.

Good thing Zhao Hai had already prepared an excuse. He could say that he thought there was a bigger tribe around here, so that’s why he hadn’t sold his food, and he was bringing a sample for West Wonder King.

After four days of restless marching, Zhao Hai had almost reached West Wonder King’s camp. He and others had also returned to the prairie from Iron Mountain Castle.

Once on the prairie, Zhao Hai immediately opened Laura’s carriage door. He looked outside and smiled. “Doesn’t it feel like we haven’t been back in a long time? It suddenly feels like the prairie looks even more beautiful than before.”

Laura and the others all laughed at that. These days, they had all been busy building the production facilities at Iron Mountain Castle. Now that the temperature around the Black Wastelands had dropped, they had stopped farming and switched their focus towards building those facilities.

But they still don’t have enough people to build all the production facilities. At first, Zhao Hai had really wanted to start a facility for making battle rations. But then he considered that even if he had the facilities, there was no market for battle rations among either the beastmen or the humans. The only thing they could do right now was make wool products. That way they didn’t have to kill the goats.

But now they had an even better product: milk wine. Although the beastmen themselves also produced milk wines, they only made the usual goat milk wine. It was incomparably inferior to the ones that Zhao Hai was now making from cow milk. The main difference was that his milk wine had been distilled, which would most definitely make it taste better than the ones the beastmen made.

Of course, in Zhao Hai’s eyes, milk wines were ultimately a lower-tier product. But because beastmen liked to drink good milk wine, he could use it to trade for better goods.

The convoy was quickly entering the area around West Wonder King’s camp. They could, in fact, already see it in the distance. The area it covered was very large. All they could see on the horizon were the tops of white-domed tents. The middle of the camp seemed the busiest; according to Zhao Hai’s estimations there had to be more than a hundred thousand people here.

Just then, with a rumbling of hooves, a group of riders came rushing out of the base and approached Zhao Hai’s convoy. Perhaps it was because they noticed the two sets of friendship war flags, but the riders slowed down and scrutinized their convoy carefully.

Zhao Hai hurried out of the carriage and bowed respectfully to one of the riders. “Hello, respected warrior. We are merchants from the humans. Is this where West Wonder King’s base is located?”

After the warrior from the Fighting Bull tribe noticed Zhao Hai’s kind behaviour, he hurriedly replied, “Hello, human friend. This is indeed West Wonder King’s camp. What business do you have here?”

Zhao Hai quickly replied, “Respected warrior, I’m a merchant. My business here is of course to establish trade with West Wonder King, and sizable trade at that too.”

The rider didn’t think too much of it; there would often be human merchants that came to make deals in their base. He looked at Zhao Hai’s convoy again, then said, “Human friend, we welcome your trade, but you don’t seem to be carrying much?”

Zhao Hai smiled, “Relax, respected warrior. These are just samples. If you agree to trade, the food will come nonstop.”

The rider nodded. “Alright then, human friend, please follow me.” He then lead Zhao Hai further into the camp.

To avoid suspicions, Zhao Hai had already put all the undead large-horned raging bulls away. There were no undead creatures in his convoy right now; they looked just like your average group of human merchants.

Zhao Hai followed the rider into the camp, and immediately discovered that this place was not the same as the smaller tribes. It was more than a matter of size; in a bigger tribe, of course the camps are bigger; the difference Zhao Hai saw was in the attitudes of the people here.

Chapter 280: Surveillance

Zhao Hai has had many interactions with small Beastmen tribes, but for a big tribe like West Wonder King’s, it’ll be his first.

Back when he met the small tribes, they would be very enthusiastic upon meeting a Human merchant, take Spear’s Sheep Hammer tribe for example, due to Zhao Hai willing to sell them grain for a small price, they’d gone and happily offered their friendship flag to him.

But in West Wonder King’s camp, that scene is non-existent, upon seeing Zhao Hai arrive they did not even show an expression of surprise. Even the children inside the tribe did not come over and surround him. Zhao Hai could instead see in the eyes of some of these people a glint of contempt.

Zhao Hai stared blankly for a moment before realizing that the reason these Beastmen looked down on them is because their caravan’s size and cargo is too small, about 200,000 jin, at most, and 200,000 jin when regards to a big tribe such as this, is really too low as supply.

Zhao Hai didn’t mind it, escorted by some beastmen cavalry, he was led towards a corner of the camp where surprisingly a tent was located, moreover the surrounding area seem to be devoid of other beastmen.

The leader of the beastmen cavalry, riding a cow, arrived before Zhao Hai and said with a strong tone, “Human friend, you can temporarily stay here, this tent is specially made for human visitors to stay in, you can move in immediately, you can also inquire other people nearby should you need anything, naturally you need to offer something in exchange.”

“Well thank you so much brave warrior, may I ask for your name?”, Zhao Hai felt somewhat flattered because he never expected that West Wonder King’ camp would provide accommodations.

The cow riding beastman grinned and said, “My name is Beta, you can call me Beta”.

Zhao Hai smiles and said hastily “Good! Brother Beta, I’ve prepare a small gift, please accept, if you have time, please help me send one to Sir West Wonder King, I have a big business to discuss with him.” As he said that he waved hand, Laura immediately took a bottle of alcohol, naturally this isn’t Milk Wine, but a genuine Human Fruit Wine.

Beta was stunned for a moment before he laughed and took the wine from Zhao Hai’s hand. “You are an interesting person, very interesting indeed! Hahaha, be at ease, I’ll tell the elders about your request.”

Patting the cow’s belly, he moo’ed towards the other Fighting Bull clansmen, then began to turn away, the team of beastmen cavalry also followed him to leave.

Zhao Hai shows a faint smile as he turned to Laura and said “A big tribe is different it seems, they unexpectedly provided a place for living. Go take a look, see if the tent has anything in it.” Laura complied with a smile and turned around towards the tent, Zhao Hai commanded his Undead to go tie up the grain carriages.

After being settled, Zhao Hai pulled out some grain and went to trade some Milk Wine and mutton to the nearby bull-headed tribesmen.

After quite some time Zhao Hai felt the West Wonder King’s tribe’s differences with the small tribes, West Wonder King’s tribe is more utilitarian.

Perhaps this is an inevitable phenomenon of societal development. The larger the population, the more utilitarian the people are, while the smaller the population, the more they stick to morals.

Time passed at their settlement, Zhao Hai was just quietly waiting, he did not go around too much and he also did not interact much with the other beastmen. His surroundings appears very peaceful without much disturbance.

However inside the tent, Zhao Hai has opened his space’s radar, he wants to look at the surrounding situation and was quick to notice some peculiarities. The surrounding bull-headed beastman warriors appear a bit too many, sometimes there would be patrols around the camp, eyeing the tent from time to time.

As Zhao Hai sees this situation, he couldn’t help but look blankly, he turned to Laura and asked, “Did we have any flaws in our actions? Why would they send some people to spy on us?”

Laura frowns and shakes her head, “I don’t know, we haven’t done anything out of the ordinary.”

Meg looked at the screen and said,” Young Master, maybe they think that we are spies sent by the Patriarch of Fighting Bull tribe? The Fighting Bull tribe has defeated the  Herculean tribe, but there was a Human expert that helped out. Then all of a sudden we appear here, wouldn’t they suspect us?”

Zhao Hai stopped for a moment, then he nodded and said, “It is possible, they have  a grudge against the Fighting Bull chieftain before, now the Fighting Bull’s power has become strong, and they have shown their their relations with humans, then suddenly we come, it is very possible that they would suspect us.”

Laura affirms and says “It seems that our decision to stay honest here is correct, otherwise they would be onto us “

Zhao Hai nods. “In this case, let’s just stay here honestly, Cai’er”. Zhao Hai called, Cai’er immediately appeared on his shoulder.

Zhao Hai turns his head to Cai’er. “Cai’er, can you record everything here so that we could watch it afterward?”. Zhao Hai remembers that there was a video recording function, he had not used it before because he didn’t have any use for it.

Cai’er nodded and said, “Can record, and if there is no command to retain it, seven days later, it will be deleted.”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “Good, starting today, record all that happens in West Wonder King’s tribe, in the evening we’ll be watching it.”

Cai’er complied, then return to the space, at this time, there is suddenly someone speaking outside, “Human friend, are you well?”

Zhao Hai was surprised, but after he heard that the voice was Beta’s he immediately replied, “Brother Beta, I am well, come inside.”

Beta walked in, saying that the tent is really nice, that the things inside must’ve been brought in by Zhao Hai, in fact Zhao Hai can just use the things provided but Laura objected, she fears that too many people have used the furniture, so they just used the furniture that they brought with them.

Inside, Zhao Hai is sitting down while drinking milk tea, this milk tea is also traded from other beastmen nearby. When he saw Beta come in, Zhao Hai beckoned and said, “Brother Beta, come and drink a cup of tea”. After which he poured Beta a cup of tea.

Beta smiled, he held the cup and downed it in one go, then he says to Zhao Hai, “Human friend, the elders in charge of outsiders wants to see you, come with me.”

Zhao Hai nodded and stood up, as he walked outside he tells Laura, “Just stay in the tent, do not wander around.” Laura complied, she escorted Zhao Hai up until the entrance of the tent.

After walking a few meters, Beta turned his head and asked Zhao Hai, “Human friend, why can I see that you’re not like any other human merchant? Other human merchants would move around to other places to get business.”

Zhao Hai gave a forced smile and said, “Brother, if I depend on that kind of business, how much money can I make? How many things can I sell? Too little, my goal now is to supply grain to your tribe, that would give me big profits, those small profits don’t have any value to me.”

Beta looked surprised at Zhao Hai’s response, “It seems that you really didn’t lie to me, do you really have large supplies of grain? For how much would you sell it?”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “A lot of grain, and the price I give is definitely the lowest in the entire priarie.”

Beta looked at Zhao Hai, he couldn’t make out if what Zhao Hai said is true, at this time they have arrived outside a big tent, this tent is bigger than most tents. Additionally, erected outside this tent is a flag, Zhao Hai didn’t know what this flag meant but he could understand that this tent isn’t so simple.

Outside the tent, there are two Fighting Bull beastman guards standing straight, each of them holding a giant mace in their hands making them look very imposing.

Beta walked towards the entrance and nodded towards the guards, he then led Zhao Hai inside. Zhao Hai felt the surroundings dim as he went inside, he sized up the tent, the inside is very big, about 40 square meters, this is not small when describing a tent.

The decoration inside the tent is very peculiar, things that most beastmen use, this tent seems to lack, instead there are books upon books stacked inside, nothing else.

On the floor there is just a plain-colored carpet, actually looking very ordinary, in the middle of the tent is a fire pit with which a steaming copper pot is hanging above. Also inside, there is a small table where sitting behind it is a old looking Fighting Bull tribesman.

Some of the hair on this Fighting Bull tribesman’s head have turned white and his face has grown wrinkles, making him look like an old senile man. But his eyes were not clouded at all, on the other hand his eyes were very clear and full of wisdom.

Beta stepped forward and gave a bow, “Beta has seen the elder.”

The old Fighting Bull beastman nodded, “Is this the merchant you were talking about?”

Beta nodded hastily, Zhao Hai stepped forward and in manner of courtesy said, “Zhao Hai has seen the elder, I thank the elder for meeting me.”

The elder nodded, he waved, Beta bowed towards the elder and promptly left the tent, Zhao Hai kept silent, he just kept standing there.

The old man looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Human friend, please sit down.” After Zhao Hai expressed his gratitude, he sat at the right side of the elder.

The eyes of the elder showed a small flash of approval, then he went on,”Human friend, I heard from Beta that you have a lot of food that can be traded with us?”

Zhao Hai nodded, “Yes respected elder, I have plenty of grain, to be honest I am not a pure merchant, I have my own territory and my territory’s product is Bamboo grain, I don’t want to sell it cheap to other merchants so I decided to sell them myself.”

The elder nodded, “How much grain do you have?”

Zhao Hai said with a serious voice, “30 million jin”. He didn’t declare too much, afraid that the elder would hold suspicion.

While in his eyes it is still less, the elder asked, “The price?”

Zhao Hai calmly replied, “every 2000 jin of grain, i’ll trade for one mountain sheep(Argali).”

The elder’s expression dropped, he looked at Zhao Hai surprised, “You say 2000 jin of grain for one Argali? Are you sure you’re telling the truth?”

Zhao Hai nodded, “Respected elder, I will not joke on this matter, what is said is true, 2000 jin for one Argali.”

The elder looked at Zhao Hai, “How is the quality of your grain? If the quality is not bad, when can it arrive so that we can immediately trade for Argali?”

Zhao Hai replied, “The quality of the grain is not a problem, I brought some samples, I’ll be honest with elder, these grains that I brought are the most inferior among their batch. But the grain that I’ll send later is absolutely first grade.”

The elder nodded, at this point Beta’s voice rang from outside the tent “Beta reports to the elder, the grains have been checked, the quality is very good.”

The elder smiled and turned his head towards Zhao Hai, “Human friend, you really did not lie? You really have more grain of such quality?”

Zhao Hai shook his head, “No elder, these grain that I have brought are the worst among the grains I have, the incoming grains would be of better quality.”

The elder looks at Zhao Hai silently for a while while Zhao Hai is staring at the elder as well. After some time, the elder nodded, “Human friend, we’ll go with this transaction, have your people transport the grain. But remember, you only have a half months to transport, bring all you can in those half months because after which winter will come and the snow will seal the road, when that happens no matter how much you want to deliver, it would be impossible.”

Zhao Hai faintly smiles and says, “Elder be relieved, it wouldn’t take too long, we’ll also be able to deliver for a little less than a month, then please allow me to excuse myself , elder, I still have some things to prepare.”

The elder gave a nod, Zhao Hai slowly exits the tent to make his preparations. At this point Beta went inside the tent, “Elder, they’re very clean, they almost didn’t leave their tent, I can’t see any issue with them.”

The elder agreed, “I also think that this young man is good, monitor them more for a few days, if they have the same behavior then we could trust them. If they do something out of the norm, like contacting other tribe members, find out what they said, if it’s just ordinary conversation then we don’t need to spy on them.”

Beta looked puzzled at the old elder, “Elder, they already acted positively, why need to monitor them further? And you also said to monitor them when they talk with tribe members, isn’t that just normal behavior?”

Chapter 281: Finding Clues

The elder looked at Beta and said, “Beta, you should know about our present situation. Nowadays is a very tense period, and this human merchant appearing is very strange. They have just arrived, so they would obviously act normal, but a merchant not reaching out to others for a few days? Impossible, therefore in these couple of days them contacting other people is normal, but if they are still acting honestly in their tent, then there is definitely something fishy, we should stay alert, do as I say. In addition, do not put all our trade resources on them, do not break relations with other merchants, we don’t dislike too much grain.”

Understanding the meaning of the elder’s words, Beta nodded, “Yes elder, I will immediately go handle it.”  The elder nodded and turned around.

The elder looked at the waving curtain and murmured, “Prince, your choice in this matter is really wrong, do you really think that the Herculean Bull tribe would be defeated easily? And that the Fighting Bull tribe invited the Humans for help, oh!”

The tent immediately fell into silence as the elder’s mood became heavy. Recently due to the defeat of the Herculean Bull tribe, West Wonder King began to think of ways in order to please the Fighting Bull tribe. The first thing he did is rounding up their tribes’ two Herculean Bull princesses who he married and sent them out to be slaves so that they’d completely lose their dignity.

Regarding this practice of the West Wonder King, the elder is very much in disagreement, Herculean Bull tribe was a great help to the West Wonder King, without Herculean Bull tribe there would be no West Wonder King today, although the Herculean Bull tribe helped the West Wonder King so that they could keep the Fighting Bull tribe in check, in the end they still helped out West Wonder King. And the West Wonder King’s current practice isn’t something that a proper beastman would do, but would instead be like what some ungrateful humans would do, the kind of humans that are despicable.

In fact, many people in the tribe are in opposition with the West Wonder King regarding this, but in the eyes of West Wonder King, Herculean Bull tribe is done. Of their two supreme elders, one is dead while the other is heavily injured, what other hopes do they have? Additionally, they lost their territory as well as all their properties, at this point, they can only become a vassal tribe to the Mastiffs. Forget about getting vengeance, they couldn’t even return to the bull-headed tribe’s territory, so West Wonder King decisively demoted the two princesses to slaves.

Zhao Hai did not know about any of these, as he returned to the camp he immediately made the undead unload the grains from the carriage and had them drive the carriage away. Zhao Hai also had them carry the Ghost Staff.

After completing all of these, Zhao Hai returned to the tent, Laura followed Zhao Hai from the side. Inside the tent Laura immediately asks, “Elder Brother Hai, do you really want to sell the grain to West Wonder King?”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “Yes, do not forget, currently we are merchants, we couldn’t afford to show any flaws, so why shouldn’t we sell? Right, starting from tomorrow do not stay inside the tent, go around the area and find if they have any special magic beasts, talk to them to see whether we could buy it.”

Laura nodded, then frowned and said, “Then should we not ask for news about the second and third princesses?”

Zhao Hai shook his head and said, “We do not need to inquire about it right now, we are acting as merchants, we’re not supposed to care about these matters as long as there is profit to be had. For now, pay special attention to special plants and magic beasts, these are also integral to our trip.”

Laura smiled, “Don’t worry, but they are still monitoring us, is it appropriate for us to walk around?”

Zhao Hai faintly smiles, “Why would it be inappropriate? We are human merchants, don’t forget about that. And human merchants that are unwilling to make contact with beastmen? Now that is unusual.”

Laura also understood, so she did not say anything, she looked at outside the tent and quietly said, “I don’t know how the 2nd and the 3rd princesses are faring right now, their situation must not be good nowadays, I just hope that the West Wonder King is a grateful person, or else their days would be much harder.”

As it is getting late, Zhao Hai returned to his Space, he also needs to pay attention to the undead carrying the goods. As soon as the undead leave the Tauren tribe’s area, they are to be filled with food so that they could come back immediately. His caravan currently has 100 large carts each able to carry 5,000 jin of grain, these 100 carts can altogether transport about 500,000 jin. Additionally, Zhao Hai still has additional 1000 or more carts available that could transport 2,000 jin each which adds more than 2 million jin of grain to the total amount. In this case, their supply would be very close to 3 million jin, a number couldn’t be considered small.

But from West Wonder King’s camp, if you want to leave the Bull-headed beastmen’s area, the most direct way was to head towards the Iron Fort. If you head straight there it would take about six days before you can leave the Bull-headed beastmen’s domain. But Zhao Hai can reduce this travel time to three days, so it takes about six days to travel back and forth, and each trip can carry almost 3 million jin each time.

A trip of 3 million jin each, in one month they could transport 15 million jin, although not at the level of 30 million, for Zhao Hai this income is already a lot. Additionally, he does not really want 30 million jin of grain to be sold to West Wonder King, 15 million is good enough.

At night, Zhao Hai entered the space to rest, but after they entered the space, they didn’t immediately went to sleep, but instead they let Cai’er bring out the recordings acquired during the day.

The recorded events isn’t just around the tent they were living in, as Beta led Zhao Hai to the tent, the camera also followed and recorded everything 2 kilometers around.

For Zhao Hai this video function seems very normal, but for Laura they look really amazing. They saw everything Zhao Hai went through throughout the day, event though she knew that these were obviously things that happened during the day, she still felt very excited and tensed.

Looking at her appearance Zhao Hai couldn’t help but smile, he didn’t say anything. This made Zhao Hai remember the first time he watched television and also similar to when he first started playing with a computer.

Zhao Hai has been observing the expressions of all the people he passed by along his way. There is nothing special about this route. Afterall, he did not go far from the camp, he’s just in the immediate vicinity.

Zhao Hai listens to Beta calling out to the foreign affairs elder, the elder seems to be the elder who manages the external affairs in West Wonder King’s camp.

There is nothing strange about the elder setting up the visitor’s tent here. The outsiders who arrive to visit naturally won’t be immediately invited to the center of the camp. Just like Zhao Hai’s caravan, they would be place on the outskirts of the camp. So the elder also erected his tent at the periphery of the camp to easily facilitate contact with the visitors. Another reason is for possible scouts to have no chance of getting inside the camp.

Zhao Hai attentively observed the elder because he found that the elder is very uncommon, his beastman body seem to express wisdom, this feeling made Zhao Hai very vigilant.

Zhao Hai has been paying attention to the tent, right now, he and Beta just came out. At this time, the tent is still in the vicinity of the record range, Zhao hai immediately said to Cai’er, “Cai’er can you transfer the camera view to inside the tent?”

Cai’er nodded: “Yes”. As she said it, the video suddenly turned, Beta and the elder appeared on screen, the words exchanged between the two entered Zhao Hai’s ears.

Upon hearing the elder’s words, Zhao Hai’s face suddenly changed, he turned to Laura, “It seems that this West Wonder King is trying to throw their lot with the Fighting Bull tribe, Laura, in the next few days, you must pay more attention to any information regarding the 2nd and 3rd princess. If West Wonder King wants to rely on the Fighting Bull tribe, he would certainly won’t be polite towards the 2nd and 3rd princesses, remember, only listen do not directly inquire.”

Laura has now been accustomed to the magic of the monitor, when she heard Zhao Hai’s command she understood immediately, then she replied with a straight face, “I did not think that West Wonder King is unexpectedly that type of person.”

Zhao Hai forced a smile and said,”If he is not that kind of person, then he wouldn’t have betrayed the Fighting Bull tribe chieftain, this situation is normal, I have already thought about this scenario, but I did not think that he’ll really disregard his morals.”

Laura sighs, “As a result, Big Brother Wales has lost a lot of strength, this has become a great blow on his part.”

Zhao Hai replied with a cold expression, “We’ll have our revenge soon, for now we should collect more information about the Fighting Bull tribe’s situation, I think there are a lot of people in this battalion that will talk about the bull-headed race’s matters, we must pay attention and listen to the 2nd and 3rd princesses’ matters, we should see if they are still alive or dead. If they are living, look at their current situation, if they’re not treated well, we’ll find a way to rescue them and then find Brother Wales, we still have a month of time in any case.”

Laura nods, “This seems to be the only way, trying to count on West Wonder King isn’t possible in our situation anymore, let’s just leave it to Brother Wales to find another solution, right Hai-ge, do you want to tell Brother Wales about the current situation?”

Zhao Hai nodded, “We should tell him, otherwise Brother Wales would still be hoping there would be no trouble here, we should find a chance to inform Brother Wales one of these days whenever possible.”

Chapter 282: We Can Start

After a wordless night, Zhao Hai started his operation right at the very next morning. They could not became overly obvious, so they just carried simple transactions with the surrounding beastmen, when they discover a good product, they would just trade according to a preferred price.

Zhao Hai has exactly one month to gather information, so naturally he wouldn’t be so impatient to complete it, what he needs to do now is to eliminate the wariness of the beastmen. How to eliminate wariness? For these beastmen, it is not talking to them nor helping them work, but instead selling them food at a discounted price.

So Zhao Hai did so, but since they need to be covert, every time they perform a transaction they try not to overly show that they want to curry favor with the beastmen, something unfitting for a merchant.

For the Bull clansmen monitoring Zhao Hai, they observed that his actions were just ordinary. There was nothing they could find suspect, and to make sure that there was no mistake, those who spied on Zhao Hai would ask those who have traded with him about their conversations. To their disappointment, Zhao Hai only focused on trading, and did not say many words.

After four days, those people lost their patience in monitoring Zhao Hai. Even the elder agreed that Beta should loosen his surveillance on Zhao Hai. Zhao Hai returned to his camp and through the screen he could see that the people gathering around and about their tent have lessened, this made Zhao Hai very relieved.

However he didn’t become impatient in gathering information, he continued his daily activities, but his activity range had grown in scope and is slowly heading towards the center of the camp.

On the fifth day after they arrived at West Wonder King’s camp, Wales’ blood hawk arrived. Zhao Hai wrote the current situation carefully and then handed the note over to the blood hawk to deliver the message to Wales.

He told Wales to not count on West Wonder King, and he fears that West Wonder King would ally with the Fighting Bull Tribe. The reason why Zhao Hai has still remained here is to monitor the situation of the Fighting Bulls community. He also wants to know about the 2nd and 3rd princesses’ situation, if the two are in a bad situation he will find ways to save them and have them reunite with Wales.

After sending the letter, Zhao Hai felt that a huge burden has been removed from the depths of his heart, at the same time, he also monitored the cargo’s progress. Tomorrow the caravan would arrive, along with it is nearly 3 million jin of grain, which is not a small number in any sense.

Zhao Hai saw the situation and immediately went to inform Beta. These days, the person Zhao Hai has the most interactions with is Beta. Although he knew that Beta was sent by the elder to monitor him, Zhao Hai has taken the initiative to interact with him often. This action would enable him to eliminate Beta’s wariness. And also, if he were to always dodge and hide from Beta, it would be impossible to have Beta’s surveillance on him relax in only these few days.

Beta is responsible for the security of the camp, therefore he doesn’t go and herd like other bulls. Everyday, he goes on to patrol around the camp, Zhao Hai could very easily find him.

In these past few days, due to Zhao Hai’s actions, Beta and Zhao Hai’s friendship has been very good. Therefore when he saw Zhao Hai, Beta immediately smiled and greeted, “Brother Zhao Hai, what are you busying with?”

Zhao Hai quickly responded, “Brother, I’ve been looking for you. I need your help on a matter.”

Beta stared surprised for a moment then replied. “Brother Zhao Hai, you’ve been very polite to me these past few days, tell me the matter you need help with, as long as I can lend a hand, I’ll help you.”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “Brother Beta, our caravan will arrive at the camp tomorrow, this time they’ve brought a lot of grain. I need to find a place to unload the goods, you’ll have to find me a good place.”

Beta became stunned, and then he replied, “To be back so soon, Brother Hai, your men does things very quickly. How much grain did you bring this time?”

Zhao Hai showed a faint smile and said, “About 3 million jin.”

Beta stared, with a startled face he looked at Zhao Hai, “Brother Hai, did you say 3 million jin? Not 300,000 jin?”

Zhao Hai laughed and replied, “Brother, how can I possibly joke about his matter with you, 3 million jin is not wrong, therefore I need a very big place.”

Beta sees that Zhao Hai is serious, he hurriedly replied. “Brother Zhao Hai, go back to your tent and wait, I’ll immediately report to the elder, in a moment I’ll provide you with an answer.”

Zhao Hai showed a smile, gave Beta a salute and turned around to walk. Beta looked at Zhao Hai’s back, then immediately turned his cow around and headed towards the foreign affairs elder.

Outside the elder’s tent, Beta didn’t give any warning and broke into the tent directly. Fortunately, there are no other people inside the tent. Only the elder was inside shuffling around with some books. When Beta came in, the elder became dissatisfied, “Can’t you be more calm? Already an adult, but still rash and impatient.”

Beta didn’t even give a salute to the elder before he said, “Elder, Zhao Hai came to find me, he asked for help in preparing an area, tomorrow his first batch of grain is arriving carrying around 3 million jin in total.”

The elder stared, his eyes lit up and said, “So quick? He really has 3 million jin?”

Beta nodded and replied, “Yes, Zhao said he was very sure.”

The elder slowly closed his eyes as he muttered, “3 million jin of grain at half-price, this may save many matters for us. Go help him find a place, be sure to find a good area, when the grain arrives tomorrow, help him unload and see how good the grain is.”

Beta issued a acknowledging sound, then turned away. When Beta went out, the elder opened his eyes and said to himself, “To ship so quickly, does he have a transit station in the prairie?”

It is not uncommon for human merchants to build transit stations in the beastman prairie. Some big merchant companies would construct stations on beastmen communities. Generally these stopover stations are made with medium or large beastmen tribe’s cooperation. Human merchants place their station on the beastmen tribe territories and pay them commissions, this is so that they could move quickly and conveniently around the prairie whenever that wanted to transport.

The elder didn’t care about whether Zhao Hai has a transit station or not, he is thinking about Zhao Hai’s grain. To be honest, Zhao Hai’s grain is very cheap. Even those merchants who often supply them with food wouldn’t dare give the price that Zhao Hai is giving. These merchants would trade their grain at a price of 1000 jin for an Argali, but Zhao Hai’s grain’s price compared with these other merchants is a full half cheaper.

What does 50% cheaper grain represent in West Wonder Kings camp? It represents more food, this is a very good news for them.

At the very beginning, when Zhao Hai came to meet him, he still didn’t believe anything that Zhao Hai said. So he let Zhao Hai as well as other merchants to deliver grain, he didn’t think that Zhao Hai’s grain would arrive very fast.

The next morning, a huge convoy can be seen slowly approaching West Wonder King’s camp, getting closer and closer. Beta stood at the side of the camp, watching caravan after caravan. The convoy is composed of more than 1000 carts, in front of the convoy are 100 carts commonly used by the beastmen followed by the carts commonly used by human merchants.

Zhao Hai is standing on the ground outside, this time the team has some undead in it, but that isn’t something for Zhao Hai to worry about. At this time Beta is watching the grain convoy. Watching this long parade of carts, Zhao Hai’s heart is very excited, this convoy is his, how can he not be thrilled.

After the arrival of the convoy, Zhao Hai and Beta led the convoy to a vacant clearing. This is the area specially prepared to store Zhao Hai’s grain. Now that the prairie is heading towards winter, there is absolutely no chance of rain. So even if they store the grain in an open area like this, they didn’t have to worry about it being wet.

Beta has been paying close attention on the grain bags on the carts. The bags look ordinary, nothing special. Beta is carefully observing, he wonders what the quality of grain that Zhao Hai has delivered this time.

Quickly after they reached the open area, Zhao Hai wanted to command the undead to unload the grain. But he didn’t think that other beastmen would run to help, Zhao Hai is too embarrassed to stop them, he can only assent.

When Beta picked up a bag of grain, he froze for a moment because the bag is too heavy. Not to say that he couldn’t move it, its just that the bag has more weight to it compared to other merchant’s bags of grain.

This made Beta stand still, his expression completely sunken. He has encountered this situation before, some grain merchants would put sand in the grain bags to make them heavier. This cheating method is the one that Beta disliked the most.

He picked up a few more bags of grain. The bags were so heavy that it made Beta’s face look unpleasant. After he picked up the bags, he pretended to handle it carelessly, and he ‘accidentally’ dropped a bag from his shoulders. The grain is placed inside cloth bags, but these cloth bags, after long periods of transportation they couldn’t possibly be able to retain their strength. After falling from Beta’s tall body, the bag split immediately.

Beta looked at the split bag of food, he wanted to mock Zhao Hai with a few words, but as he glanced at the grains,  he was stunned, the content of the bag is the highest grade grain, the individual grains seem to shine. If such grain cannot be called top grade, then the grain that they have been eating can only be inferior grain that hasn’t even matured. Most importantly, there has been no sand inside the bag, it is very pure.

Beta stared at the bag of grain, and other Fighting Bull people also gathered around, looking at the split bag, their amazed expression is the same as Beta.

This method of falling and breaking one bag, seemingly looking for trouble with human merchants, isn’t an uncommon deed for these Fighting Bull people. As long as there are problems with the food, they can seize the opportunity and purchase at a lower price. Looking at what Beta just did, everyone was ready to cause a disturbance, but when they saw the grains scattered on the ground, all of them have lost all their voices.

Zhao Hai looked at them and smiled. He knew, by looking at their expressions, that he can now carry on with his plans.

Chapter 284: Special Requests

Whoosh!

Then tent curtain was forced open, then a figured rushed in from outside. The elder could not help but frown, he knew for sure that it was Beta, no one but Beta would dare break into his tent like this. He put down the pen in his hand and looked up at Beta.

The elder could not help but pause for a moment because in the hands of Beta was a bag of grain. Beta looked at him excitedly, the elder knitted his brows, “What is it Beta, did something happen?

Beta took a deep breath, then he put the grain bag down. And with a face full of excitement he looked at the elder and then he slowly opened the bag of grain, the contents of the bag fell towards the ground.

The elder watched the actions of Beta, then shifted his gaze towards the grain on the ground. These grains were the best grain he has ever seen in his life. He couldn’t sit still, he stood up, walked towards the Bamboo grain, grabbed some with his hands and lightly chewed on them with his mouth.

Good rice! The elder looked up at Beta and said, “Is this Zhao Hai’s grain?”

Beta nodded, the elder then said, “All bags are the same?” Beta nodded again. The elder immediately told Beta, “Go ask Zhao Hai to come over.” Beta did not say anything, he immediately went outside in haste.

The elder slowly sat down, but his eyes never left the bamboo rice on the ground, such good rice, he has never seen them before in his life. If Zhao Hai supplies this rice, not to mention half price, even if he doubles the price the elder would still be willing to trade.

Before long, the sound of footsteps can be heard outside the tent, after which Beta and Zhao Hai walked in. This time the elder acted very polite. He got up and saluted to Zhao Hai, “Welcome Mister Zhao, please take a sit.” Zhao Hai didn’t dare to act big, he returned the elder’s salute, he then went towards the elder’s right side and sat down.

This is the way humans show respect, Zhao Hai sitting on the elder’s right side shows an act of modesty. This gave the elder a very good impression. After Zhao Hai sat down, the elder looked at Zhao Hai, “For Mister Zhao to bring us such high quality grain, I am very deeply grateful for that.”

Zhao Hai quickly responded. “Elder is too polite, to get into the elder’s graces, this Zhao Hai is honored.”

The elder actually didn’t care about Zhao Hai’s modesty, he looked at Zhao Hai and asked, “Mister has such good quality grain, but why sell it to us at such a low price? I ask Mister Zhao to clear my doubts about this.”

Zhao Hai showed a faint smile as he replied, “There is nothing to complex about it, there are actually only two reasons. First, because these grains are my territories’ produce, therefore the price is very low. Second, is because I have just arrived at the prairie, and seeing the the prairie operates on an open market, the prices would be naturally low, of course, this does not mean that my price would increase later, be assured elder, my food price wouldn’t change.”

The elder looked at Zhao Hai and nodded. Zhao Hai’s response was justified. The elder continued towards Zhao Hai, “How much grain could Mr. Zhao supply this year?”

Zhao Hai frowned and said, “Only 15 million pounds, my ability to transport is currently very limited, moreover I can only trade this month, after this month winter would arrive. At which point I would probably return to my territory, thus I cannot transport food here.”

The elder gave an understanding nod, humans after all would need to return to their homes. It would be impossible for them to wade the winter with the beastmen race, they are not used to that kind of life, but 15 million jin of grain wouldn’t be too less upon further calculation.

Zhao Hai looked at the elder and smiled, “Elder, I don’t know if I would be fortunate enough to meet with West Wonder King? In order to discuss the possibility of cooperation next year?”

The elder paused for a moment, then he replied, “I don’t have authority for this, I will report your inquiry to the prince, tomorrow I shall give you a reply.”

Zhao Hai nodded, he looked at the elder and said, “There is another thing that I want to talk with elder, now that my men has delivered the grain, they need to leave immediately, can you look to see if I can get the payment for this batch of grain? To save me trouble of bringing them myself.”

The elder paused, then he nodded and said, “Not a problem, but these things needs to be readied, you’ll have to wait for a day. What payment does mister want? Do you want all of them to be argali?”

Zhao Hai shook his head, “No, actually, I was going to talk to the elder about this matter. We have a few elders in the family, they are potion masters as well as alchemists. You should know, they like to collect special ingredients. Therefore, if possible, I’d want some special magic beasts and magic plants, if you were to offer your tribe’s unique magic beast that would be better. Of course, we still would accept Argali as well as wool products as payment, I ask the elder to look into these matters.”

The elder didn’t think that Zhao Hai would have a special request. He looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Mister’s meaning is, if we were to exchange the grains with some fighting bulls of our clan, then you’d offer a high price? What about magic beasts?” [TN: not the Fighting Bull clansmen but instead their ‘cousin’ Fighting Bull beast]

Zhao Hai hastily replied, “Be assured elder, I’d offer the same  high price for magic beasts, but the quantities of these beasts couldn’t be many. After all, I fear that I couldn’t raise them properly.”

The elder agreed to Zhao Hai’s request, he nodded his head and said, “Well, I can give you ten Fighting Bulls, as well as ten wild blood cows. I hope mister can exchange each cow for 10 thousand jin of grain. Then we’ll use Argali and wool blankets for the rest, what do you think?”

Zhao Hai thinks for a moment then replied, “There’s no problem, ten fighting bulls plus ten wild blood cows account for two hundred thousand jin of grain, that leaves 2,800,000 jin of grain. If 2,800,000 jin were to be traded with argali, it would be 1,400 heads. So I’d like 1000 heads, and the for the rest I’d like 600 blankets. If your tribe has any magic plants, this number can be lowered, what do you think?”

The elder nodded, “Fair enough, I agree. Tomorrow, Mr. Zhao can get the things that you requested. However, currently we don’t have the time to collect more magic beasts as well as plants for mister. The time is too short, moreover, during winter plants would wither, we can only wait for next year.”

Zhao Hai faintly smiles, “That’s fine, the elder can send some people to collect during these days. In a few days my second batch of grain will arrive, then we could trade, withered plants are okay, as long as it hasn’t withered for more than one month.”

The elder nodded, “Very well, we’ll try our best. Mister can return, if West Wonder King agrees to meet mister tomorrow, I’ll immediately inform you.” Zhao Hai expressed his gratitude, then turned to leave.

Looking at Zhao Hai going out, Beta couldn’t help but say to the elder, “Elder, why did you agree to trade him our fighting bulls? What if he studies them what do we do?”

The elder showed a faint smile, “Nothing, rest assured, humans have spent all these years researching about our soul beasts without much result. And do you think that if we don’t give them some beasts, they wouldn’t have any way to procure them elsewhere? If they really are to be greedy, then why not trade our soul beasts to bring more food for ourselves?”

Beta nodded, not saying anything, the elder turned to Beta, “You go take some people from the tribe and go search for some strange plants. If anyone were to spot some magic beasts, make sure to bring them alive.” Beta complied, then turned to leave.

Zhao Hai went to his tent while assessing his conversation with the elder. But fortunately, there are no flaws in his part, he acted like any common merchant.

He just deliberately asked the elder for their magic beasts because he is very clear that he can’t be too low-key. Human merchants tend to act high-profile towards the beastmen, so he should be the same from time to time. The opposite would cause other people to have suspicions. After all, spies would tend to be low-key, trying not to stir up trouble as much as possible, on the contrary, if you were to act high-profile, no one would suspect you.

Zhao Hai also would not be too high-profile, but he also couldn’t be a pushover. So he asked the elder for the tribe’s companion soul beast as well as some special magic plants , which could be be interpreted as a lofty request. At the same time, he also disclosed to the elder that he couldn’t get these things at another place.

Zhao Hai knows very clear, that West Wonder King isn’t most afraid of Wales. In his opinion, Herculean Bull tribe was already ruined. Wales is a prince of a declining tribe, they wouldn’t even dare return to the Cow-headed beastman domain. West Wonder King fears the grudge held by the Fighting Bull chieftain.

And Zhao Hai, by requesting for fighting bulls and wild blood cows, gave clues to the elder that he is not related to the chieftain of the Fighting Bull Tribe.

Strictly speaking, West Wonder King’s tribe is a branch family of the Fighting Bull tribe so they also use the same bulls as the main tribe. Their beasts, the fighting bulls, have bodies filled with short black hairs, a very violent ox-headed bull. The bull’s height is nearly three meters, they cannot use magic but they have great strength, ranked in the top ten among the cow-headed domain. Moreover, they also have a special ability, Rage!

Rage can be considered as a very strange ability, because of their fury, their strength and defensive ability would greatly explode. No matter what level the opposing beast is, they would still dare to charge. This point is what excels them compare to other magic beasts.

Ranks of magic beasts are very strict, like the fighting bulls which can be considered as sixth rank magic beasts. Ordinary sixth rank beasts, when they meet eighth ranked beasts, would be immobilized, thus letting the eight rank easily slaughter them. But the fighting bulls are different, they are not afraid, whether it be eight rank or ninth rank beasts, as long as they are in a state of rage, they’d dare to make the first move and charge.

The wild blood cows, are a dark-type magic beast. They place only at the fifth rank, only five levels. They can perform simple blood magic, but this beast actually is most suited for the fighting bull clan.

The name wild blood actually doesn’t conform to the cow’s nature because of its two blood magics, one is Quick Recovery and the other is Gloom.

These two magic belongs to Support-type magic, Quick Recovery can be cast on somebody to quicken their wound healing my many folds,  some being dozens of times faster. Gloom is a mental type black magic, once used, the target would become absolutely rational, like a puppet, and seemingly forgetting what anger is.

These two magics fit the Fighting Bulls perfectly. Regarding the Fighting Bulls’ temper, with which single word can cause a fight, and their mounts would be similar, once the rage skill is used, it would be in a state of extreme anger, no matter if ally or foe, it would only know to charge, which in a battlefield is very fearful.

But the two skills of the wild blood cow happens to suppress this enraged state. So the Fighting Bulls absorb the wild blood cow’s soul and train in their skills. After practicing in these skills their beastly souls would obtain two new abilities, which is to quickly recover wounds as well as make them retain a calm condition, not only them, but also to their mounts.

Their name of wild blood cows became so because they are completely blood red. Normally with black and white eyes, their eye color would turn red once in battle, like a violent man when he is angry, therefore it was given its name of wild blood.

Before, the Fighting Bull tribe is only an ordinary tribe within the cow-headed race. Their temperament is too bad along with their very disobedient mounts, they couldn’t control their temper which wouldn’t differentiate between friend or foe. Because of these qualities, they were not very well-liked among the cow-headed race.

Afterwards, after generations of effort, they finally were able to find soul beasts most suitable for them, which multiplied their battle effectiveness my many folds. Now they are famous within the cow-headed race as strong warriors.

The human race, all these years, has had researched beastmen soul beasts as well as beast relatives. They want to discover a way to crack this method that gave beastmen immense strength. But till now they still haven’t succeeded. The Beastmen are still using soul beasts but humans are still using battle qi.

Humans have always coveted this method of obtaining strength from the beastmen for a long time. If they were to discover how these beastmen managed to have companion beasts, this would greatly increase the might of their cavalry. If they were to know how to use soul beasts, then their battle power would also increase greatly. But unfortunately, just as the beastmen said, these two abilities were given to them by the Beast God. With the exception of the beastmen, no other race could use these abilities.

Zhao Hai also knows that, before, some human merchants would purchase soul beasts as well as unique beasts from the beastmen and then bring them back to Human territory to do research on. But unfortunately, most of these beasts would die of illness. Even if its alive, the humans still couldn’t find anything in their research.

Because of this point did Zhao Hai propose to the elder his purchase of their fighting bulls and wild blood cows. This is because he knows the elder will sell, in addition it would eliminate some of the elder’s wariness of him.

As he returned to his tent, Zhao Hai immediately turned on the monitor. The words Beta and the elder has said right after he left gave him relief. He has now found out that the elder’s wariness of him has basically disappeared.

Chapter 284: Seeing West Wonder King

The next morning, Beta went to find Zhao Hai to tell him that everything is ready, ten fighting bulls, ten wild blood cows, 1000 argali, and 600 wool blankets. Beta told Zhao Hai that he can take them away any time.

Zhao Hai went with Beta outside, Beta already loaded the blankets to the carts. The argali, fighting bulls, and wild blood cows are outside the camp. Zhao Hai casually inspected the blankets, they were very good, one of the finest blankets he has ever seen. Just by seeing the blankets, one would see the amazing workmanship of the beastmen.

After Zhao Hai expressed his gratitude, then he made the convoy leave, he commanded the undead to herd the argali, fighting bulls and wild blood cows outside.

Just like before, Zhao Hai let them carry the Ghost Staff, otherwise they wouldn’t have any place to store the beasts.

After everything was done, Zhao Hai returned to his tent. He is still waiting for news as to whether he could meet West Wonder King today, he’s very curious regarding this West Wonder King.

After his convoy has left, the grain that Zhao Hai brought has officially changed ownership. The elder has traded him with products and beasts in exchange for the grain, naturally, the grains are no longer Zhao Hai’s.

Zhao Hai has also witnessed the ability of a big tribe to consume food. It still hasn’t been an hour before the convoy left but the 3 million jin of grain can no longer be seen, they completely vanished, Zhao Hai felt very stunned.

Zhao Hai returned to his tent, he couldn’t see Laura, but he knows that she went outside to trade with other beastmen. Even though Zhao Hai doesn’t have any more grain, he still has fruit wine in his possession. Even though this type of liquor is not very popular with beastmen because they liked milk wine, most beastmen still traded for fruit wine, to be used when entertaining guests.

Vanity is also present within Beastmen, so some live in fairly decent homes, thus they’ll also prepare some fancy wine when a special guest arrives.

Zhao Hai didn’t care about any of these, he’s not planning on leaving his tent today, he’ll stay here in order to await news from Beta. If West Wonder King wants to see him today, and he still needs to find Zhao Hai, it would be somewhat annoying.

Zhao Hai didn’t fear West Wonder King, but he needs to see West Wonder King. He needs to asses what kind of person West Wonder King is so that he could make appropriate plans.

He quietly watched the scenes on the monitor, the beastmen are still busy, the difference compared to a few days before is that there are no longer people observing them, not even one, this all began this morning. This allowed Zhao Hai to confirm his theory that the elder no longer suspects him of being a spy. And this result is what Zhao Hai wants the most.

Zhao Hai is quietly sitting in his tent, he also observed the undead convoy walk away. Because he fears that the convoy would get raided, he got Beta to stick West Wonder King’s flag on his convoy. He believes that in this area, there shouldn’t be anyone who won’t give West Wonder King face.

Beta didn’t say anything, he asked the elder, to which he agreed. After all, Zhao Hai is currently trading them grain at a very cheap price, and very good quality grain at that. If Zhao Hai isn’t eligible to carry West Wonder King’s flag, then all other merchants are even more so.

However, to be sure, Zhao Hai still placed the fighting bulls and wild blood cows inside the space, then he sent them towards the ranch. As the fighting bulls and wild blood cows entered the ranch, Zhao Hai heard an alert, “Bull Variant animal detected, Level 25, mentally unstable, irritable. Improving the animals’ weaknesses… Animal Maturing time, 20 hours, may produce offspring 6 times, produces six calves each time. Consumes three grass per hour. Converting animal to data… Can now be purchased in the shop.”

“Bull Variant animal detected, Level 25, special ability: resilient. Improving the animals capabilities… Animal Maturing time, 18 hours, may produce offspring 8 times, produces six calves each time. Consumes two grass per hour. Converting animal to data… Can now be purchased in the shop.”

“Space’s Pasture has met Level Up requirements, promoted to Level 7. Increased quantity of beasts that can be reared. Current number of beasts the space can breed: 1300. Hopes that host continues to put in more effort.”

Zhao Hai smiled. Good, finally time for a level up. He immediately took out 100 calves and placed them in the space. He turned to Mu’er and said, “Mu’er, I’ll hand this space’s ranch to you, make sure to maintain the number of argalis and bulls.” Mu’er complied with a sound, at this moment, Cai’er informed him that Beta was coming and is soon to arrive at his tent.

Zhao Hai commanded with his mind, he immediately reappeared inside the tent. He walked outside and at this time was seen by Beta who said, “Brother Zhao Hai, come see the elder with me quickly. The elder shall take you to see the prince.”

Zhao Hai nodded and walked with Beta. The West Wonder King’s title, he himself claimed it. But he didn’t dare call himself a royal, he could only claim to be a prince in private. But this prince likes to keep up appearances, like others calling him ‘Your Majesty Prince’. Zhao Hai noticed this point yesterday when he asked  the elder if he can meet with West Wonder King, and the elder himself called West Wonder King ‘prince’.

They quickly arrived outside the elder’s tent, Beta led Zhao Hai inside the tent immediately. The elder saw Zhao Hai and he immediately stood up and said, “Regarding mister’s request, the prince has agreed. Please follow me.”. After that, the elder led him outside.

Zhao Hai is appreciative of the neat way beastmen handles things. Zhao Hai followed the elder towards outside. He froze for a moment, because right outside the tent is a cart pulled by a bull. The cart is very big and also has a carriage on it, obviously meant for them to ride on.

Zhao Hai rarely sees beastmen riding carriages. They generally want to ride on top of their mounts, they think riding on top of a mount is more comfortable than inside a carriage. The elder seems to know what Zhao Hai is thinking, he said: “This elder is now quite old, it’s impossible to stay still at the back of a bull, I can only manage by riding a carriage. Mister please.” Zhao Hai returns the elder’s gesture, then he rode the ox carriage.

The ox carriage is very large, much larger than Laura’s cart, but the inside decorations are obviously inferior, it only has two simple seats on both sides of the carriage, and the above is covered in beast skins, a simple and crude set-up.

After Zhao Hai and the elder had sat down, the ox carriage began to move. When the elder got inside the carriage, he closed his eyes. It is obvious the he does not want to make conversation with Zhao Hai. Since there’s no other way about it, Zhao Hai had to sit quietly inside the carriage.

After about half an hour, the carriage stopped, Zhao Hai who has almost fallen asleep immediately woke up. He opened his eyes and saw a pair of smiling eyes. Zhao Hai cleared his mind, looked at the elder and embarrassingly said, “Hehe, sorry elder, I almost fell asleep.”

The elder didn’t mind it, he smiled and said, “It’s not a big deal, was the road too boring? Let’s continue on, we don’t want to make the prince wait.”

Zhao Hai nodded, and along with the elder, they got off from the carriage.

Zhao Hai went out and gawked, he thought that when they arrived they would be outside West Wonder King’s tent. But now, he was mistaken, after he got out, what he saw was that he was outside some wooden fences, and inside these fences should be West Wonder King’s tent.

This is the first time that Zhao Hai has encountered this situation. There are no fences nor railings outside the beastmen camps. There are no fences outside the camp but instead there are fences surrounding West Wonder King’s tent, it was as if he’s a captive himself.

Of course, West Wonder King doesn’t think that it is so, he just wanted to express that he and humans are different.  However, in Zhao Hai’s eyes, it is like a monkey that trapped himself in a cage, to express that he is different from humans is just ridiculous.

Standing at the front of the fence are two guards, once the guards saw the elder and Zhao Hao go off the carriage, they immediately gave a bow, the elder waved his arm and then led Zhao Hai inside,

While walking, Zhao Hai inspects West Wonder King’s tent. The tent gave Zhao Hai the feeling of magnificence. In the open area outside the tent, two teams of cavalry can be seen patrolling back and forth. The cavalry are wearing leather armor and is equipped with a mace on their hands. You could sense the murderous aura emanating from them, one could see that these men were elites.

West Wonder King’s tent is very white, it’s very clean as well. The roof is gold colored and inserted above it is West Wonder King’s war flag.

Zhao Hai understood that this is the camps’ central tent, very magnificent. While Zhao Hai was observing, the elder actually didn’t stop, he immediately led Zhao Hai towards the entrance.

From the outer gate to the tent entrance is about 100 meters, the two quickly arrived at the entrance where eight guards stood. The guards placed on both sides of the entrance of West Wonder King’s tent stared at Zhao Hai, sizing him up.

Zhao Hai didn’t mind it too much, he just wanted to follow the elder in entering the tent. The elder stopped right at the entrance and told the guard, “Foreign affairs elder Belluk brings the tribe’s human friend Zhao Hai to seek an audience with the prince.”

This is the first time that Zhao Hai has head of the elder’s name, but he felt uncomfortable. This isn’t because he was dissatisfied with Belluk, but instead he became dissatisfied with West Wonder King. West Wonder King’s faction on the cow-headed domain, is at most a medium tribe, which are innumerable inside the prairie. But this fellow not only dubbed himself as king, he also wants his subjects to address him as ‘prince’ or ‘his majesty’. The main point is, his ego is too big, he places himself too highly, completely unlike a beastman. He’s just like those Human nobles, wickedly arrogant.

Zhao Hai didn’t know, but in truth, West Wonder King did this arrangement on purpose. When he sees a human merchant for the first time, he would exhibit an imposing stature before the human gets to meet with him to make them cower.

However he did not think that what he is doing is just deepening Zhao Hai’s dislike for himself. Zhao Hai can even be sure that this West Wonder King isn’t a big deal. Even though his strength still hasn’t reach its max, he still acted as though he is someone grand. If such a person accomplishes something, the result wouldn’t be considered noteworthy, simply not enough. Zhao Hai now understood why the Herculean Bull clan chief decided to support this West Wonder King, it is because this West Wonder King doesn’t have the capability  to threaten the Herculean Bulls.

Chapter 285: The Princesses’ Situation

Zhao Hai entered the tent with Belluk with his head bowed down, using the corner of his eyes he observes everything inside. The ground is covered with a layer of thick carpet endowed with an extremely beautiful design on top, looking very high quality, stepping on it felt like stepping on clouds which is extremely comfortable.

There’s no fire pit inside the tent, but instead there is a big copper brazier about 1 meter in diameter. The brazier appeared very beautiful with its animal carvings. And on top of the brazier is a copper pot exuding the fragrance of milk tea.

At the top of the tent, a source brightness was hung. Zhao Hai stole a glance at it and saw a huge wheel shaped chandelier lamp, these are not oil lamps but is instead magic lamps. Zhao Hai felt very surprised, it seems that West Wonder King has been living comfortably, one must know that the price of a magic lamp is much greater than an oil lamp.

At this time, Belluk bowed, “This one has seen the prince.”

Zhao Hai recovered from his shock and immediately bowed following Belluk, “This one sees West Wonder King.”. Even though he hasn’t seen West Wonder King yet.

A hourse voice replied, “Don’t be so polite, Belluk, Mr.Zhao, please take a seat.”

Zhao Hai started to look up, the first thing he saw was a table, this isn’t a small table but a proper square table, it looked like a writing desk. On the opposite side of the table, a beastman could be seen, this beastman was about three meters high, has a huge Ox-head, a pair of scimitar-like horns, and an unattractive cow face caused by a very long scar, which made him look very fierce.

His body is very sturdy, he looks like a mountain just by sitting there. His body’s muscles are very angular and detailed, comparable to cast iron. Behind him is a huge mace whose head is as thick as Zhao Hai’s body.

The man was not wearing ordinary beastman leather clothes, nor is he wearing human cotton clothes, but instead he wore iron armor, a full set of human made iron armor, which made him look like a terrifying iron monster.

Looking at his appearance makes one think that he’s a battle maniac, a crude and rude man. But Zhao Hai thinks otherwise, the eyes of this West Wonder King is very bright, it gave you a look that seems to penetrate your body and pierce your soul.

Zhao Hai did not think that people who possess these kinds of eyes would be a crude man, this man is surely not a simple character. But Zhao Hai didn’t show any expression, after he expressed his gratitude, he sat down opposite West Wonder King on his table. Elder Belluk sat by his side.

West Wonder King curiously sized up Zhao Hai as he said in a deep voice, “Mr Zhao Hai, welcome to my camp, I must thank you for the grain.”

Zhao Hai smiles and replied, “Your majesty is too polite, we are also in need of your help, not to mention who to thank, I myself must express my gratitude to you, without your tribe buying my grain I may need to wait until next year to find trade again.”

West Wonder King laughed and said, “You humans really have your way with words, mister Zhao doesn’t need to be modest, as long as you bring your grain to the prairie, it’ll surely be instantly sold out.”

If Zhao Hai didn’t notice the look of his eyes before, he would’ve thought that West Wonder King was a hearty person who wouldn’t have machinations in his heart. So now Zhao Hai isn’t affected by the man’s current attitude. He just smiled and replied, “Your majesty is too kind, what I say is certainly true. I consider the cooperation with your majesty as long-term, not just this year, but the next year and the year after that as well. You couldn’t do that with any normal tribe, there no such guarantee. I wonder if I’d be honored to cooperate with your majesty for next year?”

West Wonder King didn’t think that Zhao Hai would quickly get to the point. He looked at Zhao Hai’s eyes and asked, “I wonder how much grain Mister Zhao can provide us next year?”

Zhao Hai thought for a moment then answered, “200 million jin!”

West Wonder King’s face didn’t show surprise, instead in a deep voice he asked, “The price?”

Zhao Hai smiled and replied, “Basically the same as this year, your majesty doesn’t need to worry. Moreover, I could confidently guarantee the grain’s quality.”

West Wonder King looked at Zhao Hai, “Mister, you have to know that 200 million jin of grain is quite a substantial amount for our tribe. If there are any problems with your grain, then my entire tribe may be affected.”

Zhai Hai nodded, “Of course I know about this matter, but your Majesty can be assured of my sincerity in this cooperation. I wont start transporting these 200 million jin of grains during autumn next year, I will instead send the grain in batches starting from the moment grass starts to grow on the prairie up until the start of winter when my carts can no longer traverse the landscape. What does your Majesty think?”

West Wonder King’s eyes turned cold, “Why can you grow grass extensively,  to the point that you can send us food the moment the grass grows?”

Zhao Hai smiles and replied, “Your Majesty, I can only say that my territory has a special climate wherein I can plant grain three quarters of the year. When the prairie’s grass has grown, my first batch of grain would have just matured, after which I’ll send it to your Majesty.”

When West Wonder King heard what Zhao Hai said he was stunned for a moment and then he said, “Aren’t you a resident of Aksu Empire?” What West Wonder King asked makes sense, after all the general climate in the empire only allows planting in one quarter of the year. Only the countries at the front may have two or three seasons of planting.

Zhao Hai shook his head, “I’m not, please be assured your Majesty.”

[N: I think I need to do some re-reading beacause im pretty sure Buda clan is in Aksu empire. Maybe because his territory is quite far from the empire?]

West Wonder King nodded and said, “If mister is confident in his proposal, then we’ll purchase all of your grain, I can guarantee a fair price.”

Zhao Hai smiled, “This one thanks his Majesty, I will assure that his Majesty’s tribe will have a supply of grain. ” West Wonder King nodded,”Well then, I will not keep you here, Belluk, make sure to accommodate Mister Zhao properly.”

Zhao Hai hurriedly replied, “I wont dare make his Majesty worry, I’ll excuse myself.” He then stood up, gave a bow to West Wonder King and then went with Belluk to leave the tent.

On the ox carriage, Belluk looked at Zhao Hai and said, “I hope Mister wouldn’t be offended, there are currently a lot going on in the tribe, the prince really has no time to spare.”

Zhao Hai stared for a moment then smiled, “Elder is too polite, I’m not in the least offended, deciding the cooperation with His Majesty with me is already enough, the elder doesn’t need to worry about me, I’ll take care of my own matters.”

Belluk nodded, then went back to silence. Zhao Hai opened the window and looked outside, suddenly he notices a Herculean Bull soldier, he was handcuffed and fettered. He was pulling a large cart with difficulty and was followed by a Fighting Bull soldier who wielded a whip in his hand.

Upon seeing this scene, Zhao Hai cannot help but he shocked, his complexion changed and immediately understood what was going on. He immediately calmed down his expression then pulled down the curtains.

Luckily Belluk was maintaining his silence with closed eyes, so he did not see Zhao Hai’s actions. Zhao Hai let out a long breath, his heart became overwhelmingly calm, because he knew what that scene just now represented.

If the Herculean Bull’s 2nd and 3rd princesses still held power, the Fighting Bulls would not dare to such a thing to the Herculean Bulls. It appears that the Herculean Bulls in this camp are certain to be the 2nd and 3rd princesses’ retinue, now that the servants are treated this way, it is certain that the 2nd and 3rd princesses aren’t in any better state.

The carriage quickly arrived at Belluk’s tent. Zhao Hai dismounts from the carriage then politely said goodbye to Belluk, then he headed towards his tent because there are many things that he has to consider now. The most important thing is figuring out the 2nd and 3rd princesses’ whereabouts.

At noon, Laura and Meg returned, but although they had a smile on their faces, Zhao Hai noticed that those were somewhat restrained.

When Laura went inside the tent, Zhao Hai immediately turned on the monitor. Seeing that no one was following them, Laura talked, “Brother Hai, we just heard that the 2nd and 3rd princesses were demoted by West Wonder King to slaves, being forced to forage on the prairie.”

Zhao Hai nodded and added, “I thought so, just after I met with West Wonder King, I happen to see a Herculean Bull soldier pulling a cart while being whipped. If there was no incident with the 2nd and 3rd princesses, nobody would dare do such a thing to Herculean Bulls. It looks like West Wonder King is planning on returning to Fighting Bull chieftain’s side.

Laura anxiously replied, “Brother Hai, what do we do now? We must find a way to save the 2nd and 3rd princesses otherwise we wouldn’t have any face left to meet Brother Wales.”

Zhao Hai nodded, “Don’t worry, I have already thought about it,  in a few days when the grain convoy gets out of the cow-headed race’s territory and had the grain loaded up, I will have the Ghost staff brought back by the blood hawk. If our scouting around West Wonder King’s camp goes well and we finally find the 2nd and 3rd princesses, we’ll find a  time to rescue them.”

Laura thought for a moment then she nodded and said, “Presently this is only thing we can do and it’s not like we can do anything else at the moment. We also heard something from the Fighting Bulls, it looks like it came from other Fighting Bulls. It is said that with the recent intervention of a human during the conflict, the Fighting Bull chieftain decided to deport all human from their tribe.”

Zhao Hai paused, then he frowned, “So this is the case, the Fighting Bulls are really good at scheming. With this, not only can they let the humans escape, they can also provide an excuse, this chieftain of the Fighting bull tribe seems to be quite a character, now we don’t really know if they really did expell the humans from their tribe.”

Laura frowned, “It is not yet proven, just a speculation. There is also another rumor that the Fighting Bull chieftain killed the humans who helped him, and also that the Fighting Bulls are ready to attack West Wonder King.”

Zhao Hai nodded, “We don’t have to worry about that now, we need to think of means to rescue the princesses, we can talk about other matters later.”

Chapter 286: Trap

Laura nodded and said, “Good, but when do we rescue the princesses? Do we wait up until we leave?”

Zhao Hai shook his head, “No, if we wait until we leave to rescue the princesses, then West Wonder King would suspect us of rescuing them. As long as we find the 2nd and 3rd princesses, we’ll immediately rescue them, only then would West Wonder King not suspect us.”

Laura heard Zhao Hai’s words and thought that they seemed reasonable, if they rescued the 2nd and 3rd princesses just as they left, then West Wonder King would undoubtedly find fault with them, adding many variables to the current situation. But if they immediately rescue the princesses, West Wonder King wouldn’t be able to find fault with them, even if he has his suspicions.”

Meg looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Young Master, did you see West Wonder King today? How did it go, smooth? What kind of person is he?”

Zhao Hai thinks for a moment then he said, “He looks like a powerful person, if you judge based on his appearance, then you’d think he was a crude man. But if you take note of his eyes, you’ll see that he has a calculating attitude. I went today and talked to him about the issue of our grain business, this should make him trust us.”

Laura nodded and then smiled, “Now West Wonder King would feel proud, I have the inkling that he could not wait for the day that we’d bring him the grain.”

Zhao Hai showed a faint smile, “First we need to stabilize him, have him stay his hand so that Brother Wales can continue on with his plans. And after we rescue the princesses, we’ll snoop around the camp. But from all the rumors going around, it seems that the Fighting Bull tribe isn’t in any better situation, by cooperating with a human they had place themselves in an awkward situation since its a beastman taboo to ask for help with humans, they’ll have to cover it up. If I am the Fighting Bull chieftain, I’ll help the humans escape the prairie, then await for a suitable time for to have them return, as the matter stands, they are on the losing side. This is a big help to brother Wales, it will make his success more possible.”

Laura nodded, “If big brother Wales can counter-attack as soon as possible, then he’ll certainly succeed because nobody would think that he’ll counter-attack immediately.”

Zhao Hai showed a faint smile, he didn’t add any further comments, he looked at Laura and asked, “You have been in contact with the Fighting Bulls these past few days, what do you feel about them?”

Laura thought for a moment, then she said, “I don’t really feel anything, I just think that they are very much unlike Spiel who was easy going, I don’t like them.”

Zhao Hai smiled, “Probably its because they are too practical, you cannot blame them, they often see convoys come so trading has become too common here. In any case, after this we won’t have any interactions with them anymore.”

Laura nodded, then turned her head to the monitor and saw several beastmen being busy, Zhao Hai suddenly sighed, “Look at their busy appearance, it is very difficult to imagine what their response will be when war comes.”

Laura didn’t say a word, none of them have experianced war so they cannot imagine that scene, but they had seen the Giant-Horned Bull tribe’s appearance after Gasol’s attack, and that is only a small tribe. If the big tribe outside encounters the same fate, it would be very difficult to visualize the scene.

Zhao Hai sighed, then the image on the monitor switched to the convoy. The convoy was still on the move without any accidents. Zhao Hai nodded, “Right, I just placed the fighting bulls and wild blood cows on the ranch. It made the ranch rise to level 7 and then I raised 100 cows. The milk wine that we made should be good by now. Want to return to Iron Mountain Fortress and have a taste?”

When Laura heard that the pasture has been upgraded, she became very happy. Then she said, “Brother Hai, the space’s pasture is now level 7, what change do you think will happen when it reaches level 10 ?”

Zhao Hai shook his head, “Who knows? The change that will happen may not be what I want, forget it, any change is good.”

Laura smiles, “I believe that the pasture will keep improving, just like the farm. Also, I didn’t think that the Milk Wine would only take a short time to ferment. To be honest, I cannot seem to get used to the taste of Milk Wine. But our milk might be very tasty, I can’t wait to have a taste the flavor of our milk wine.”

Zhao Hai showed a faint smile, to be honest he also wants have a taste of the wine. Seeing that it is now lunch time, Zhao Hai led Laura and others back to Iron Mountain Fort. He left the camp to Cai’er for monitoring, just in case if  some people come to visit, they’d still have time to come back.

Back at Iron Mountain Fort, the residents have just finished eating their lunch. In general, the lunch provided here at Iron Mountain Fort is very simple. Since they will become busy at the afternoon, lunch would be brief then followed by a short break before they head back to work.

Seeing Zhao Hai suddenly come back, Green became somewhat surprised. Usually Zhao Hai wouldn’t come back for lunch, but fortunately Green prepared a lot of food, he didn’t need to prepare again.

While having lunch, Zhao Hai had Green bring some milk wine, Green got someone bring a pot to Zhao Hai. He then gave each person one cup to taste. The milk wine was very tasty, quite mellow compared to beastman-made wine. It was very fragrant, and coupled with the distillation method, the quality of the milk wine became a lot higher. Laura drank a cup, after which her face reddened.

Zhao hai didn’t drink any more, he only drank a cup then returned to his tent back at the camp, then fell asleep.

In the next three days, Zhao Hai’s life was very calm, sometimes they’d interact with some beastmen. But this time they didn’t just trade things with the beastmen, they also asked them if there are any things that the beastmen specifically wanted, because if possible, he’d bring those to them.

Leaving aside that Zhao Hai trades them with products, when he asked them regarding  things they needed so he can procure them, the beastmen became happy. In reality, these beastmen have many things that they want, but since Zhao Hai mainly trades with food they couldn’t buy anything else, now that Zhao Hai wanted to listen to their requests, they’d be absolutely delighted.

But trouble came afterward, the news that Zhao Hai accepted requests spread throughout West Wonder King’s camp and before long, a bunch of people came in with requests of all the things they needed hoping that Zhao Hai could procure them.

Zhao Hai felt that he made a big mistake, he really shouldn’t have asked for requests. Since the beastmen still had a lot of things to do, Zhao Hai had them return first. He had their requests written down so that he does not need to list them one by one.

Zhao Hai did so because he had a lot of supplies from Casa City, almost all were prepared for this trip to the prairie. So Zhao Hai wanted these supplies to be traded for some argali.

He just underestimated the beastmen’s desire to buy. Since the beastmen cannot buy whatever they wanted on this scarce prairie, their blown out enthusiasm was completely out of Zhao Hai’s expectation.

Zhao Hai finally received all the list of orders, which was enough to compile a few books with. In any case, the grain convoy just reached outside the cow-headed race territory. Zhao Hai can only delay the orders until next shipment to bring in the requests.

These few busy days passed by quickly, Zhao Hai’s grain convoy had finally left cow-headed race’s territory. After they finished loading the grain, Zhao Hai immediately took back his Ghost staff. He then called a blood hawk to seek around West Wonder King’s camp to find Wales’ two sisters.

Now that the beastmen are preparing for winter, the quantity of grass to be foraged by a tribe as large as West Wonder King’s camp reached astronomical figures. Therefore at this time, there were very many foragers out and about, but these foragers were mostly slaves.

Foraging grass for the winter season is very tiring work, you cannot return to the camp for a long time, you work from dawn to dusk, such high intensity work, only after then can you rest. Majority of the large tribes would have slaves do this job, sometimes having a certain quota per slave, if someone cannot meet the required amount, they may even get killed.

Fortunately the blood hawk is quick, and also Zhao Hai believed that the Fighting Bulls would certainly group up all the Herculean Bulls to one place, Zhao Hai is certain to find their specific location.

Laura and the team are also staring at the scene, very careful in looking, fearing that they might miss something. Soon they finally found their target, in reality, it wasn’t that difficult to find them since they are not that far from West Wonder King’s camp, only half-a day’s journey away.

There were more than 100 Herculean Bulls working, both male and female. These people were in handcuffs and fetters. What made Zhao Hai surprised is that they are accompanied by a cavalry of 300 Fighting Bulls, moreover, they were fully-armed.

Zhao Hai didn’t immediately make a move, he observed the Fighting Bull cavalry carefully, as well the the surrounding situation around the Herculean Bulls.

Sure enough, Zhao Hai found something not right with the surroundings. In the herds surrounding the Herculean Bulls, there were a lot of Fighting Bulls working, these were not slaves of the Fighting Bulls but true Fighting Bull clansmen. They also have their mounts and weapons with them. Morover, you could see that they were not working that hard, instead, while working they would sometimes pay attention to the Herculean Bulls’ situation. Counting them up, there were about 5,000 of them.

Zhao Hai immediately understood the situation after seeing this scene. This was a trap set up by the Fighting Bulls, they want to use the 2nd and 3rd princesses as bait. So when the Herculean Bulls come and try to attempt rescue, they would be attacked immediately, catching the Herculean Bulls off-guard.

Seeing this situation Zhao Hai’s expression couldn’t help but sink. Laura with a gloomy face also didn’t speak. Some time after, Meg angrily shouted, “Too shameless! Without the Hercuelan Bulls they wouldn’t even achieve what they are today. But look at what what he did, he unexpectedly set a trap for the Herculean Bull clan. Completely shameless!”

Meg rarely cursed people, but today she madly cursed, you could see how angry she was. Zhao Hai and Laura are also very angry, they really didn’t expect that West Wonder King would be shameless to this point.

Zhao Hai can guess what West Wonder King is thinking, he wants to use this way to show the Fighting Bull tribe that he already drew the line between the Herculean Bulls and himself.

To be honest, after West Wonder King is finished with the Herculean bulls, he wants to hire himself onto the Fighting Bull clan. This point Zhao Hai can understand, after all, West Wonder King is a leader, not only himself, but he also needs to consider his people.

However, the method that West Wonder King used made Zhao Hai very angry to the point of enraging him. He knew from Wales that without the Herculean Bull clan, there wouldn’t be a West Wonder King today, but West Wonder King actually treated the Herculean Bulls this way,  Zhao Hai cannot forgive this action.

Laura didn’t curse, but instead she turned to Zhao Hai, “Brother Hai, what is your judgement?” Laura knows that Zhao Hai isn’t a person to suffer a loss and remain silent, therefore she asked this.

Zhao Hai smiled faintly, “We move this evening, I’ll disptch the undead as well as the hawks. But not to save the 2nd and 3rd princesses but instead make West Wonder King’s 5000 men my subordinates.”

Laura stared, then immadeiately understood what Zhao Hai meant, she frowned and replied, “Is this okay? That is a large battalion of troops, and the camp is very close by.”

Zhao Hai smiles, “Darkness is our domain, we’ll tidy up the surrounding cavalry first then we’ll rescue the 2nd and 3rd princesses after.”

Laura nodded, then said nothing. Like what Zhao Hai said, after darkness, it would truly be their domain. With so many Undead, taking care of these Fighting Bulls should be very easy.

After watching the weather outside, Zhao Hai said with a low voice, “We shall rest first, in a while we’ll begin. We will not wait for the day to be entirely dark, this time we are only here to monitor, it would be best for the Fighting Bulls to see us so they will not have suspicions towards our group.

Laura stared blankly for a moment, then showed a faint smile and said, “Right, we’ll get loud during dinner, we’ll also go out of the tent from time to time, so that no one would doubt us.”

Zhao Hai smiles, “Right, by then we could provide evidence that we’re not the culprit. They wouldn’t think that we have the space, a mysterious existence, with us. I’ll have the bloody hawk hold the Ghost Staff, we’ll poison them first, then we’ll begin.”

Laura didn’t have any further opinion, all those inside the tent hoped that the darkness would come soon.

Chapter 287: Poison!

The sky slowly darkened, because of the preparations for winter, the whole camp had their dinner a bit later than before, sometimes at almost dark. The camp was filled with smokes rising from the tents.

Zhao Hai looked outside and sees beastmen beginning to cook, he could not help but smile, “Let’s get started”, he said. Laura nodded, as per usual, they prepared their dinner in their camp, nothing very out-of-place.

Zhao Hai didn’t come out, through the space’s monitor, he watched the Fighting Bull Cavalry in charge of the Herculean Bulls. The cavalry were currently cooking, one could see that the food was very good, a pot of boiled mutton. Some took out their pouches that were used to hold milk wine.

Zhao Hai showed a faint smile while seeing this scene, which was very suitable for him to use poison. Initially, Zhao Hai planned to have the hawks deliver the poison from the air but after thinking about it, it was very unrealistic. The blood hawks were not aircraft, and even aircraft cannot guarantee that the dropped bomb could hit 100% of the time, let alone the blood hawks by raining poison down.

Since there is no way to use poison with blood hawks, Zhao Hai thought of another ultimate weapon he had inside the space, the blood devouring mosquitoes.

Since the blood devouring mosquitoes have entered the space, Zhao Hai hadn’t used them. This time he had the opportunity to do so, but Zhao Hai didn’t make them bite, instead, he made them deliver poison.

The heads of these mosquitoes were not small, so one or two can secretly infiltrate a camp, and if too many were sent, they would be discovered, so Zhao Hai sent five blood devouring mosquitoes.

These blood devouring mosquitoes gained some improvements from the space so they were not afraid of the space’s poisons. Therefore, Zhao Hai got them to suck up some poison to their bodies, then they dived towards the Fighting Bulls and spat out some poison to the big pot of mutton.

Zhao Hai, after asking Zhao Wen, knew that the mosquitoes possess such an ability. But he didn’t expect that in addition to sucking liquids to their belly, they could also spit it out, they were too overpowered.

Initially, Zhao Hao planned to have them dive towards the pot in a suicidal attack. But it looks like there is no need for it now, the current setup is much better.

Zhao Hai only poisoned the Fighting Bulls that monitored the Herculean Bulls while excluding the Herculean Bulls. He feared that he may injure the 2nd and 3rd princesses, if that happens then he’d have no explanation to give Wales.

While the poison was doing its job, at this time Laura was preparing food outside. Today they also cooked delicious mutton. In the prairie, people didn’t eat mutton daily because they regard Argali as their most important property, so how could the possibly always eat mutton

For herders in the prairie, they would usually eat bamboo rice. Only in special occasions would they cook mutton. Laura also knows this so they usually eat bamboo rice and some pie, they wouldn’t eat mutton regularly.

However, today is a special day therefore Laura prepared mutton. Outside the camp stands a large pot, cooking inside the pot is the mutton, several people are laughing while preparing food.

Of the three, Meg was the one who coked the food. She used to assist Merine prepare food, therefore she’s a very good cook. Laura and Nier cannot cook food, since Laura was a genuine young lady, there would always be someone to prepare for her, and since Nier is always at Laura’s side she also cannot cook.[2]

However the two have not been idle, they followed by Meg’s side laughing and joking being more of a hindrance than help, sending Meg into a flurry.

Zhao Hai sat in the tent, he faintly smiled while looking at the scene of the three women. Zhao Hai felt that he was fortunate that they got along so peacefully, if his backyard were on fire, then it would be a big problem.[3]

Zhao Hai has also been paying attention to the condition of the several camps, seeing that the Fighting Bulls began to eat, Zhao Hai prepared to begin his plan. He selected a far away camp, with a wave of his hand he released some udnead Fighting Bull Cavalry and Jackal Cavalry and had them head towards the camp.

Zhao Hai had to admit that these Fighting Bulls have good physiques. Even after eating the poisoned mutton, they were not affected immediately and were still drinking milk wine. But at the moment, there were people currently charging at them so they immediately equipped their weapons and readied to fight.

However, Zhao Hai’s poison isn’t that easy to deal with. This concoction is made from mixing different kinds of poisons, thus making it very overbearing. At the beginning, the Fighting Bulls didn’t feel anything. Only when they rode their bulls to start fighting did problems arise.

As they readied to fight, naturally their blood flow would speed up thus increasing the rate of absorbing the poison and allowing the poison to reach the heart faster. So as these Fighting Bulls were charging, after a hundred meters, they suddenly felt their body turn weak and their arms numb, at present they can only become accessories stuck at the back of their bulls.

At this time, the Jackal cavalry came. When it comes to harvesting life they are very good. Zhao Hai also immediately stored the undead Fighting Bulls, because the Fighting Bulls would cause much noise when running and may alert the surrounding camps.

The remaining matters became simple, the Jackal Cavalry completely slaughtered all Fighting Bulls. Later, Zhao Hai turned all of them into undead. This camp had 1000 people therefore Zhao Hai gained 1000 troops, after which they headed toward the second camp.

In the first camp, because the Fighting Bulls had just consumed the meat, the poison had yet to affect them. But when Zhao Hai reached the second camp, all the Fighting Bulls there were already poisoned and fell to the ground waiting for the blade to slice them.

Five camps became useless after Zhao Hai dealt with them. After cleaning up the battlefield, Zhao Hai took out all of his fighting type undead. Presently he has six battalions of undead fighters, 5000 of which were West Wonder King’s subordinates.

Zhao Hai let 5000 men of West Wonder King take the lead, followed by 1500 cavalry behind, then they headed towards the place where the Herculean Bulls were located.

The Fighting Bulls that were with the Herculean Bulls were very anxious at first. But after seeing that they were encircled by their own people, they relaxed and even prepared to send greetings.

However, having suddenly appeared here, their clansmen immediately started to charge. And instead of responding to their calls, they were instead met with maces pounded on their heads.

6500 versus 300 who were totally unprepared, one doesn’t need to look to know what the result would be. So the men under West Wonder King that couldn’t react to what is going on immediately got slaughtered clean while the enslaved Herculean Bulls didn’t react. The only looked blankly at all that happened, they really couldn’t wrap their head around what is happening here.

But then suddenly they felt their head go dizzy, afterwards they lost their awareness. Before long, all of the Fighting Bulls vanished along with the Herculean Bulls. On the camp all commodities also vanished. The prairie became peaceful, it became extremely quiet, as if nothing happened.

But because they made a lot of noise while fighting, West Wonder King’s camp naturally heard the commotion since the place is not that far away. So West Wonder King’s camp immediately sent ten thousand cavalry towards where the Herculean Bulls were.

At this time, Zhao Hai seemed to be oblivious to all that was happening. He just ate mutton outside his tent. Midway through their dinner, Meg went out looking for beastmen to trade milk wine, with the reason that their supply of milk wine has run out.

It is normal for many beastmen to have dinner outside their tent, Zhao Hai’s group also had dinner outside several times, especially during the times they were still monitored. During that time, Zhao Hai didn’t return to Iron Mountain Fort nor to the space for dinner and always had their dinner outside so that the observers could always see them.

Later, after the people who monitored them were withdrawn, Zhao Hai still had his dinners outside. To the beastmen, this is nothing strange, everyone had no suspicions at all.

However, this night the camp was not peaceful. In the middle of the night, Zhao Heard a bugle ringing outside. They immediately ran outside the tent in a panicked manner. Currently, the entire camp was boiling with commotion. All Fighting Bull people went out their tents carrying their weapons.

Fortunately, these men didn’t enter Zhao Hai’s tent. But a few Fighting Bull cavalry were patrolling outside their camp, they didn’t know whether they were sent to protect Zhao Hai’s group or monitor them.

Zhao Hai pretended to restlessly walk back and forth in his camp while wearing a very worried face. At this time Beta came, Zhao Hai immediately saw him and moved forward to greet, with a panicked face he asked, “Brother Beta, what happened? Why did you suddenly mobilize troops?”

Beta looked at Zhao Hai and said, “Brother Zhao, I’ll have to inconvenience you, do not leave your camp. Just now we had one team of cavalry suddenly disappear outside when they went to forage some grass. The prince is very angry, we are currently tracing them, do not go out of your camp. We have sent some men to protect you, you’ll be safe inside the camp.”

Zhao Hai pretended to be startled and said, “Good, I’ll definitely refrain from going out. Thank you, brother Beta.” He immediately turned back to his tent and looked at the monitor.

The monitor was guided by a blood hawk carrying the Ghost staff so that the situation around the camp can be seen. Teams of fully grown Fighting Bulls have equipped their weapons and rode their mount before heading out to the prairie, prepared for combat.

* * *

Zhao Wen was the big mosquito Zhao Hai captured way back

After all this time I thought Laura did all the cooking

maybe a chinese idiom, so I just left it as is

Chapter 288: North

Laura looked at the monitor and said to Zhao Hai, “Brother Hai, do you think they’d figure something out?”

Zhao Hai smiled lightly, “Impossible, the most they could see are nothing but hoof prints of some Fighting Bulls and Jackals, remember the way I left the scene, there is nothing left there but grass.”

Laura nodded, then smiled, “What do you think will happen when they see the area? With the sudden disappearance of more than 5,000 people. What speculations would be in their minds?”

Zhao Hai showed a faint smile, “It’s hard to say, from what it looks like, they would be possibly be looking for clues in the surroundings for quite a while. Now that we have nothing else to do, let’s just behave inside the tent.”

Zhao Hai’s action this time was too sudden that West Wonder King hadn’t even thought of them. What he knew presently was that the Herculean Bulls’ area where they worked at was only a half-day’s distance away from his camp. But, in general, if a horse ran very fast, it would be possible to reach the camp in an hour.

But around the camp, there were 5,000 Fighting Bull cavalry. These 5000 Fighting Bull cavalry, when in frontal charge, would surely be able hold wind against 3000 Herculean Bulls.

With such numbers, West Wonder King is confident that even if the strongest Tiger or Lion cavalry on the prairie would attack them, their clan member of 5,000 men could still keep up for an hour, they would have bought enough time for  reinforcements to arrive.

But a faction sending thousands of cavalry to a camp which is only a half-day travel from his camp while beign unnoticed is impossible. Therefore he believed that the Herculean Bulls cannot escape.

However, what he didn’t expect is that in this world a person such as Zhao Hai would exist, one who has the capability to use the power of the Space to completely eliminate his 5,000 cavalry while also departing quietly.

Because he haven’t got any idea that Zhao Hai’s method exists, West Wonder King felt stifled, he didn’t know who he was facing against. For his 5,000 cavalry to simply just vanish is too strange, while leaving no trace at the scene except for some bloodstains. There was almost nothing left worth noting to see.

No trace, except for some tents around which looked like they even hadn’t been disturbed. It looked like they were attacked by a heavenly general, suddenly landing from the sky, trampling his camps flat, then rounded everything up before flying away.

Getting zero leads, everyone from West Wonder King’s camp developed headaches. In the end there was nowhere for West Wonder King to send his troops to. West Wonder King can only go to the Prophets in their tribe.

There were prophets in tribes like West Wonder King’s. At the moment there were currently 5 prophets in West Wonder King’s camp all of which were from the Water Buffalo Tribe.

It is said that in the entire cow-headed race, if one were to be prophets, they were generally of the Water Buffalo clan, because other branches of the cow-headed race cannot produce prophets most of the time. Other races’ prophets couldn’t come to the cow-headed race, this is a beastman tradition. Except truly big warrior clans like the Lion Race and Tiger race, who have prophets of diffferent races, ordinary warrior clans would use their own race’s prophet produced in their branch clans.

This time West Wonder King went to find the prophets for nothing but the prophecy for the future of his camp. He didn’s ask who saved the Herculean Bulls because the prophets weren’t gods, it’s impossible to prophesize about those.

One of West Wonder King’s five prophets was one who became very well-known amongst the beastmen. His name was Blue Jack of the Water Buffalo tribe, he began his debut quite early on in his life. He was best known for having a successful prophecy a few years ago. He prophesized that the beastmen prairie would have a great drought, and indeed, on that year the prairie did have a drought. This made him instantly famous amoungst the entire beastman prairie.

Actually, Beastmen Prophets were not that mysterious. The main thing they use to combat were Beast Soul Tablets, just like how human magicians use their own conduit like staffs. And when prophesizing, among 100 prophecies, they could correctly guess five or six times. Quite a bad rate but the beastmen still believed them regardless, much like how the ancient Chinese believed in fortune-telling.

This time, West Wonder King gathered all the prophets in his tent. He looked at them and said, “Prophets, the situation of this tribe, I believe you already knew more or less about it so I won’t say anything more. What I want to ask of you is to predict the situation of my tribe in the future. If our tribe won’t have a good future, how then should we avoid the disaster, I ask the prophets for help.”

Amongst those gathered, Blue Jack undoubtedly has the highest authority. He took the lead in gining West Wonder King the greetings, “The prince is too polite, sharing the worries of the prince is our duty-bound matter.” Blue Jake wore a cotton robe which looked like a black magician’s gown. He had wrinkles on his face, clearly showing that he’s the opposite of being young. His hand is holding a cane which seems to be made from magic beast bone, white but not pale in color but white like pure jade, very beautiful. Hanging on his neck were skulls, 18 of them, these skulls were not genuine but are instead made of bull horns and is made to be black. Oftentimes he’d trace his hands on them making him look gloomy and grim as if he’s not a beastman but a human black magician instead.

In all honesty, West Wonder King never liked Blue Jack, he thinks that Blue Jack is gloomy. But he had to recognize Blue Jack’s real skill therefore he can only depend on Blue Jack heavily.

As soon as West Wonder King heard Blue Jack’s voice, he nodded and replied, “Very well, then gentlemen please.” He said as he prepared a few items for the several prophets.

Two things were extremely crucial to a prophet’s prophecy. The first is the skull of a magic beast and the second is the blood of the beast. If the prediction is very important, they could even use their own blood.

Presently, five skulls were placed on the ground. These skulls were not of Argali, but the skull of bulls. In a beastman’s view, the higher level the magic beast skull is, the more accurate the prediction would be, so this time West Wonder King presented high quality bull skulls.

Next to the five bull skulls were five bowls of blood, this was also a bull’s blood. The prophets knew that this was prepared for them so they each took one set and then went towards the brazier in West Wonder King’s tent. They put the skull in the brazier before they closed their eyes and started mouthing off incantations,.

These incantations were the type that only beastmen prophets could learn. The prophets believe that this language is used to communicate to the Beast God and receive instructions from him, therefore all prophets must study this language.

Soon, the prophets picked up the the bowls filled with blood then poured the blood onto the skulls.

Afterwards, the prophets took out the skulls inside the brazier and carefully looked at it. After some time, the prophets placed the skills down and then turned towards West Wonder King. West Wonder King looked at the prophets before him and said, “Prophets, tell me, no need to be polite about it.”

The prophets’ expression were quite unattractive, “Prince, from the result of this time’s prophecy, we fear that the situations of your camp is not good.”

Other prophets also told the same thing save for Blue Jack. West Wonder King saw that Jack was not speaking, he quickly asked, “Blue Jack, what is your judgement?”

Blue Jack also shook his head, “Not very good, our West Wonder King camp will encounter a great calamity, but there is a way to resolve it.”

Upon hearing what Blue Jack had said, West Wonder King’s face changed its complexion, he quickly said, “I Invite Prophet Jack to speak clear words.”

Blue Jack said, “From today’s prophecy, if we want to overcome this calamity, there is only one way judging from what can be seen on the skull. Its that there is a means of safety in the north, but as to the specific meaning I do not know. Perhaps to take refuge in the north, or perhaps there is a special person we need to assist in the north.”

West Wonder King knitted the eyebrows on his head, he looked at the prophets one by one, but no other prophet spoke any more words. West Wonder King frowned, he did not understand what this ‘north’ meant.

To say the north, that place is too big, and is isn’t quite possible for them to take refuge in the north. Its impossible for a camp of 100,000 people to go and migrate during winter. Completely impossible to go, but to think of it, there is a special person in the north, because the Fighting Bull clan is in that direction, does this mean that they should take refuge with the Fighting Bull clan?

Actually, this idea of Blue Jack is already on West Wonder King’s mind. He had long wanted to go back to the Fighting Bull clan, therefore it reflected on his current actions. He made the Herculean Bull’s princesses into slaves and he also set up a trap for the other Herculean Bulls who may want to attempt rescue. These actions represent his willingness to side with the Fighting Bull clan.

However, he had long been in opposition with the chieftain of the Fighting Bulls. It could be said that many in the camp has had grudges against the Fighting Bull clan. If he directly said that he wanted to side with the Fighting Bull clan, the people in his camp wouldn’t agree. So he put out many actions to tell the people in the camp that he wanted to side with the clan.

But he could not say this idea plainly since he didn’t have a concrete reason. But now, with Blue Jack’s prophecy, it gave him a good reason to use the prophecy to tell the people that siding with the clan is the decision of the Beast God. This way the voices in opposition would lessen considerably.

But West Wonder King didn’t think that there was another entity in the north other than the Fighting Bull clan, the Herculean Bulls were also in that direction. The Herculean Bulls fled to the Mastiff territory which is in the northern direction as opposed to the Herculean Bull’s main camp.

Perhaps West Wonder King hadn’t thought about this because, in his opinion, the Herculean Bulls are done. They were a completely hopeless tribe who won’t be able to recover, they were simply out of his consideration.

Chapter 289: News and Merchant

Zhao Hai didn’t pay attention to West Wonder King’s tent, but if he did, he would certainly be shocked by the ability of these Beastmen Prophets.

These prophets have unexpectedly prophecized that ‘north’ is salvation. And Zhao Hai understood what this meant, it meant that West Wonder King should support Wales in taking back Herculean Bull’s main camp. In this way, West Wonder King wouldn’t be dealt with en-route, thus he would be absolutely safe.

It was a pity, however, that West Wonder King’s thoughts didn’t coincide with Zhao Hai’s. His brain was now full with the idea of siding with the Fighting Bull chieftain, so how could he possibly thought of giving aid to the Herculean Bull clan.

What Zhao Hai is observing right now were the actions of the Fighting Bull Cavalry. The cavalry, holding torches in their hands, were performing a carpet search all around West Wonder King’s camp. Of course, it was for sure that they wouldn’t find anything.

The entire night had been restless, only when dawn came did the various troops return to the camp. Naturally they didn’t have any leads, this made the entire camp develop a very tense atmosphere.

Naturally, Zhao Hai’s group, who were behaving inside their camp the whole time were forgotten by the beastmen. This did not mean that they were looked down upon by the beastmen, but seeing that Zhao Hai seemed to not be a powerful person, he would naturally be ignored.

Belluk sent someone to check on Zhao Hai, but they only checked for a moment, because at the time of the accident, Zhao Hai’s group were eating in their camp. A lot of beastmen have seen them, therefore it would be impossible for them to be the culprits.

In the next two days, the mood inside the camp isn’t only of anxiety, but also of sadness. They have lost more than 5,000 young and capable men. These Fighting Bulls have their own families and some of them were even living near Zhao Hai’s camp, seeing that their family members were missing, this made their family members sad.

For Zhao Hai, he didn’t regret his actions. For their own sake, he must only do so. There was a saying: Just do, never regret. In Zhao Hai’s mind, there is no good or evil in war, only victory and defeat.

With Zhao Hai being low-key, West Wonder King didn’t have time to take notice of him. He wanted to side with the Fighting Bulls, but it’s clearly not the time for that yet. After preparing for winter, he plans to announce his decision to side with the Fighting Bull chieftain. After all, the Herculean Bulls have just been defeated, if he immediately went forward to rely on the Fighting Bull clan, then it wouldn’t be good for him image.

Just at this time, the sad atmosphere had been diluted a little because of a certain matter. And that certain matter is the arrival of Zhao Hai’s grain convoy.

Zhao Hai’s grain convoy came at a very timely moment since the camp’s atmosphere is very bad. With the convoy’s arrival, the sad atmosphere surrounding the camp have been cleared, the people’s live seem to become a bit calmer.

Unfortunately, because of the recent incident, there was no way for the Fighting Bulls to collect plants and magic beasts. Zhao Hai can only trade with Argali, this time Zhao Hai did not want wool products, he wanted to exchange the whole shipment with 1,500 heads of Argali.

At the same time, in front of the beastmen, Zhao Hai handed a stack of papers to the undead[1]. The beastmen couldn’t help but to be excited because they knew what those stacks of paper were, those were the requests of things that they made Zhao Hai purchase.

After the grain convoy left, Zhao Hai had managed to restore the beastman camp to calmness. People were foraging grass, you could also hear occasional laughter in the surroundings.

This made Zhao Hai very surprised. He looked at the beastman camp and then turned to Laura, “Laura why are they laughing? They just lost 5,000 people recently. Don’t they feel sad?”

Laura looked at these beastmen, she sighed and said, “Perhaps they got used to it. I heard that in the beastman prairie, wars are very common. They do it to compete for slaves, compete for territory, compete for women, they will have wars. You can say that there are wars everyday in the beastmen prairie. You can see that idea from the defeat of the Herculean Bulls, it had caused quite the sensation among the cow-headed race. But can you see whether or not the other beastman races were affected? No, because for the beastmen, that kind of situation happens very often.”

Zhao Hai sighed and then stayed silent, he turned to go back inside the tent also followed by Meg[2]. In the tent Zhao Hai turned to Laura and said, “I think that Brother Wales will soon find his fellow clansmen, we need to prepare grain for their consumption. Right, how many requests from this camp can we meet?”

Zhao Hai promised the beastmen of this camp to help them buy some things. There were some requests which were similar, so Zhao Hai made Laura help with the statistics of the orders and then look if they have enough from what they brought from Casa City.”

Laura had known how to do all of these calculations mentally since she used to do this before, so naturally it would come familiar and easy. Therefore she smiled and replied, “It would be enough, but I do not think that we should give the items to them in one go. This may cause suspicions, from what I see, how about we give them a tenth of the total quantity? This would not only help ship items easily, it would also consume less space in the grain convoy.” Zhao Hai nodded to show his consent.

Zhao Hai didn’t idle about, he immediately sent a letter to Wales that the princesses were rescued and that his people were now saved so Wales would not worry. He also added the matter about West Wonder King preparing a trap, to make Wales completely lose trust in West Wonder King.

After completing all of these, Zhao Hai patiently waited for Wales’ reply. He must determine Wales’ condition and determine if Wales needed aid for anything.

Wales’ reply quickly arrived, along with the letter, there were also six space bags brought. This time, besides grain, there were several things that Wales urgently needed, at the same time Wales also told Zhao Hai about the situation with the Mastiff tribe.

This time, the Herculean Bulls have suffered such a huge defeat. To understand, the Herculean Bulls used to have a number of more than one million clansmen and their troops have reached three hundred thousand. Now the Herculean Bulls have fled, their numbers have been reduced to half a million clansmen, but they still have troops of over two hundred thousand.

This is because during the Fighting Bull’s attack on the Herculean Bulls, the Herculean Bulls didn’t have a central command to coordinate them therefore they were quickly defeated. And in the process of being routed, those younger can run faster while the old and weak could not catch up.

Now these half million people came for refuge inside the Mastiff tribe, fortunately, there would be Herculean Bulls joining the group from time to time. Now, even though the Herculean Bulls have suffered such a defeat, they still have kept their fighting strength, they still have the ability to fight it out.

After Wales returned to the Herculean Bulls, he immediately took over the position of chieftain without question. He also took out Gasol’s weapon and told the tribe that he had already executed Gasol on charges of treason against the tribe.

But most important thing is that he brought grain with him. These life-saving grains stabilized the will of the people. One could say that these grains were crucial to him being able to take the position of chieftain.

At the same time, Wales also told Zhao Hai about the news that Zhao Hai’s magic peach juice and life water fully healed their tribe’s Supreme elder. Not only did it heal his wound, it also pushed him towards a breakthrough and also having to the brink of another breakthrough towards the next level. If he were able to breakthrough successfully, his strength would undoubtedly soar.

Naturally, this breakthrough didn’t mean that he would level up from 9th to 10th rank, that would be impossible. The 9th rank is divided into nine layers, the elder used to be 9th rank 3rd layer. And after this, he may possibly become 9th rank 5th layer, about two consecutive breakthroughs, which in the 9th rank is considered to be a miracle.

Zhao Hai didn’t think that the magic peach juice as well as the life water would have this effect, this made him very surprised. But with this breakthrough, Wales can now arrange a plan for his counter attack.

Zhao Hai quickly prepared all of Wales’ needs and delivered those to him. This time he used 5 space bags to store grain while the remaining bag was used to store some living materials.

Busy day, Zhao Hai’s convoy have just arrived for the third time in West Wonder King’s camp. This time, in addition to food, they also brought a lot of the items requested by the Fighting Bulls. Because of this, Zhao Hai’s standing inside West Wonder King’s camp improved by a lot, he had become one of the most popular here.

Due of this popularity, Zhao Hai had managed to get some news about the Fighting Bull clan. He is specifically concerned about news regarding West Wonder King and the Fighting Bull chieftain. West Wonder King already exhibited his motive to hire himself to the Fighting Bull chieftain, but he didn’t explicitly say so, he has not sent someone to contact the Fighting Bull clan, hence in the camp, some sensed fear, they don’t know what their future holds.

It was this sense of fear that the people at West Wonder King’s camp made sure to pay special attention to the Fighting Bull chieftain. They were afraid of being attacked by the Fighting Bull chieftain.

But they also know that it would also be unlikely, because at this time, they need to forage for grass in order to prepare for winter. The Fighting Bull chieftain also needs to forage, moreover, he needs to forage for many more people.

In addition, winter is not generally a time where beastmen dispatch troops. Amongst the beastmen, aside a few races, few would choose to dispatch troops in the winter. However the sense of fear still exists, therefore inside the camp, plenty of rumors are in circulation regarding the Fighting Bull chieftain, both genuine and fake, it was very hard to tell them apart.

However, Zhao hai had reached two conclusions from looking at these genuine and fake rumors. First, the Fighting Bulls reduced all remaining Herculean Bulls into slaves, a total number reaching an astonishing three hundred thousand. Second, the human who cooperated with the Fighting Bulls was already not in the Fighting bull clan. Regarding this human’s whereabouts there were two opinions. First, the human was really expelled by the Fighting bulls, and the second is that the human was killed by the Fighting Bull chieftain, Zhao Hai is partial towards the first opinion.

No matter which opinion it is, it became very clear that currently, the Fighting Bull clan did not have any helpers. If there were gonna be helpers inside the Fighting Bull clan, the success rate of Wales’ counter-attack would drop.

Zhao Hai immediately told Wales about the information he had obtained, he hoped that Wales would attack as soon as possible. Due to it being winter, if they were to attack during this season, their time would be tight because war preparation isn’t simple.

Although rumors were flying everywhere in West Wonder King’s camp, overall, the general mood is positive. Especially because Zhao Hai had sent them grain, it made the camp’s winter food sufficient, although they lost 5,000 people, people still wore smiles on their faces.

Now Zhao Hai had stayed inside West Wonder King’s camp for about 20 days, in ten days he would have to leave. At this moment another convoy arrived at West Wonder King’s camp.

This convoy already had established a cooperation with West Wonder King, this time they did not deliver grain to West Wonder King but instead they delivered living materials.

Different from Zhao Hai’s amateurish mercantilism, these merchants who delivered commodity goods were genuine traders. Even though true merchants wouldn’t be eager to trade during the winter, they still would like to trade grain. But delivering grain during this time isn’t wise, they would be raided too easily, and going back would be similarly unsafe, moreover, big tribes would prepare grain in the two months following winter therefore transporting grain to the prairie this time is a pretty huge risk, and beastmen would surely find reasons to undercut the price.

So during these times, prairie merchants would bring with them living materials. These were items essential to living in the prairie, therefore these products’ prices would never be undercut. For the small tribes, however, these things were not as attractive as grain,

The people of the caravan didn’t think that inside West Wonder King’s camp there would be another merchant group, but this group unexpectedly focused on trading grain.

The head merchant of the convoy had tried contacting Zhao Hai twice, but Zhao Hai seems to not like coming in contact with them. He did not criticize Zhao Hai, however, because through his connections in West Wonder King’s camp, he understood who Zhao Hai was.

The merchant was startled when he heard of the facts, he did not think that Zhao Hai had managed to supply more than ten million jin of grain to West Wonder King. This number, for a merchant, is not a small number, this fact made him more careful of Zhao Hai.

Zhao Hai was also very concerned about this merchant. The merchant said that he is an Aksu Empire citizen, named Bell, but he is not a Purcell Duchy citizen. He said he arrived to beastmen prairie through Ikisa Family territory.

Regarding the Ikisa Family, Laura had some knowledge about them. This is a family in the west of Purcell Duchy, its neighbor. Moreover, their territory also neighbored the beastman prairie, which became another passage for humans to smuggle goods towards the prairie.

And this Bell, is the Iksa family’s most famed grain and commodity merchant. But Laura didn’t know that this Bell was in cooperation with West Wonder King.

* * *

I am in the assumption here that the undead were in their “not undead look” form.

Meg the eternal background character. One mention per two chapters.

Chapter 290: One of Us

Bell appearing here was unexpected, Laura had cooperated with him before but not too deep, they didn’t get to see face to face, they only knew each other’s names.

The reason why Laura didn’t get too deep with their cooperation was because Bell didn’t hold a good reputation.

According to the rumors, Laura judged that Bell and Thompson were the same type person. They would resort to all means in order to achieve their goals, even though unethical. This mindset let Thompson transform the Markey family into a famous merchant family. Also, by using various means, Bell also made himself the largest grain and commodity trader in the Iksa Family territory.

Because of Bell’s style, Laura felt repulsed. Therefore there weren’t much cooperation between the two of them.

Zhao Hai was sitting in the tent while looking at the picture on the monitor. Currently the picture showed Bell’s image. Bell’s location isn’t far away from where Zhao Hai stayed, in a similar tent prepared by West Wonder King which were prepared for the use of human merchants.

After he heard about Bell’s character, Zhao Hai felt that this Bell was a formidable man, therefore he paid special attention to Bell.

He wanted to know the other people accompanying Bell, and there were a lot of them. Bell himself is mediocre, only a 6th rank warrior, but in his entourage he had two 8th rank warriors, a 7th rank black magician, five 5th rank warriors, twenty 6th rank warriors, and 500 fifth rank and below personnel.

Such group, their strength isn’t something to be looked down at. If they were to fight on the surface, then they would be a lot stronger than Zhao Hai.

However, Zhao Hai didn’t worry too much that Bell would find trouble with him because Bell wouldn’t dare do it. They were in the beastman prairie, they would have to obey beastmen rules, if they were to cause trouble, it would be equal to slapping the beastmen on the face, and they will not like it.

Zhao Hai knew that he is not in a low position in the hearts of these beastmen. He sold them grain at low prices. He also bought them items, and he didn’t charge too much. All these beastmen felt good about Zhao Hai, so if Bell dares to cause trouble with Zhao Hai, then it’d be the end for Bell.

However, since Bell still hadn’t done anything, Zhao Hai could only act amicably. But looking at Bell’s fat face, Zhao Hai felt uncomfortable, he had thought of an expression for a person with a kind face but a cruel heart, a smiling tiger. In Zhao Hai’s eyes, Bell was a smiling tiger.

Because of this, Zhao Hai shifted his attention to Bell as there doesn’t seem to be any movements from West Wonder King. Zhao Hai is spying at Bell, he wants to know what measures he could prepare to cope with this man.

With his fourth batch of grain arriving at the camp soon, Zhao Hai fears that Bell would make a move then.

On the monitor, Bell was sitting still inside his tent. In his hand is a cup of fruit wine, and in front of him unexpectedly were fruits. One must know that in the prairie, it is very difficult to acquire them. Zhao Hai looked at the fruits and noticed that they were frozen, it looked like Bell didn’t have any spatial equipment with him.

In front of Bell sat a person, Laura and Zhao Hai had not seen this person before. His appearance is that of a subordinate, he looked to be over 30 years old, but his face has the color of frost and wind, seemingly like a bachelor.

Zhao Hai turned his head towards Laura, “Laura, do you recognize this person?”

Laura shook her head and said, “I don’t, maybe its an undead that Bell raised.”

Then, they heard Bell speak, “How’s the probing?”

The man said to Bell, “It’s okay, there’s nothing odd with Zhao Hai and Laura. Their names don’t seem to be fake. The food they sold to the beastmen was haven rice, and they only sold it at half the normal price.”

Tasting the wine in his glass, Bell said, “A completely careless and wasteful use of nature’s gifts, if this haven rice were sold on the mainland, then they wouldn’t sell for cheap, what a pity. Radiant Church, those bastards and Southern King that buffoon, they deserve to fall off their horse and die.”

The man then followed, “Currently the Aksu Empire is still tracing the origin of Zhao Hai, but its a mess and they can’t figure anything out . But it is certain that Zhao Hai came from a large aristocratic family and in his hand were space equipments, and that he is also a very strong black magician, other than those there aren’t any leads.”[1]

Bell nodded, “This is normal, we can see from Zhao Hai’s actions that he does not want others to take notice of him. But sometimes he does things that can only make other people pay turn their heads to him. How do you say it, low-key but arrogant. To be honest, I’m very like this Zhao Hai. Unfortunately my reputation is not good, otherwise I might have accomplished more right now. Right, what message did the league want to transmit?”

The servant suddenly smiled, “The league only transmitted a few words, three words, ‘One of Us’.”

Bell became surprised for a moment then he laughed, “I knew those old fogies of the league won’t give up on Zhao Hai, one who is this powerful. In addition he is someone the Radiant Church wouldn’t certainly let off. We can certainly pull him closer to the alliance, good, ‘One of Us’, perhaps,  Haha, I must chat with him for cooperation.”

The servant looked at Bell and said, “Will he believe you?”

Bell showed a faint smile and said, “I have this.” He took out a small badge, it was a League of Black Mages’ identification medallion.

Zhao Hai and Laura who saw this were shocked. They had not thought that Bell, this successful merchant, was unexpectedly a member of the League of Black Mages, this fact surprised Zhao Hai.

Zhao Hai turned his head towards Laura, then he showed a faint smile, “The league’s range of power really isn’t to be underestimated, for a successful merchant like Bell to be a member of the league, really surprising.”

Laura smiled, “Yes, what a coincidence, we should go see him, since he is in the league, let’s just ask him for news about the Fighting Bull clan.”

Zhao Hai smiled, then he stood up, “Come, let us go meet him.” He said as he walked out, Laura, Meg and Nier followed hastily.

Even in his dreams, Bell would not think that all of what he said would be heard by Zhao Hai. Before he made his move, Zhao Hai beat him to it.

While Bell was discussing with his subordinate about when to see Zhao Hai, suddenly a voice came from the entrance of his tent, “Master, Mister Zhao Hai along with Miss Laura, Miss Meg, and Miss Nier, have come to see you.”

Bell became surprised for a moment, he turned to his subordinate and asked, “They came first, what do you think?”

The man shook his head, “I’m unable to guess, even master wouldn’t know.” Bell nodded then he said, “Invite them in quickly.” The servant on the entrance complied then turned to invite the visitors in.

Bell stood up , ready to meet Zhao Hai. The tent’s entrance was opened, Zhao Hai and his group came in, Bell immediately smiled and greeted, “For Mister Zhao Hai to come suddenly, it really gave me a scare.”

Zhao Hai smiled as he replied, “May Mister excuse my disturbance of your rest,  I apologize.” He said as he gave Bell a simple salute.

Bell quickly responded, “Mister is too polite, I am very honored, Mister please sit down.” After Zhao Hai finished sitting down, a servant came and poured him a cup of wine, then they took out a bowl of fruit and place them on the table in front of Zhao Hai.

Zhao Hai showed a faint smile, he turned his head and looked at the two servants by the entrance, he then turned to Bell and said, “Mister Bell, I have somewhat of an important matter to discuss with you so can you please invite them to leave.” Zhao Hai gestured towards the two servants by the entrance.

Bell stared blankly as he looked at Zhao Hai, then he nodded, he signalled towards the two servants, the servants bowed then drew back.

Seeing that the servants were now away, Zhao Hai turned his head to Bell and said, “This time I came to find mister bell to inquire about something.” After he finished talking, a League of Black Mages’ medallion appeared on his hand.

Bell didn’t think that Zhao hai would show his badge to him, he stared for a moment then looked at Zhao Hai before he laughed, “Mister is really bad, you already knew about my identity.” He also took out his badge, the two people stared at each other and laughed.

Some time after the two persons have calmed down, Bell looked at Zhao Hai and said, “I really didn’t think that you could know of my identity so quickly, what do you want to know?”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly, “I wanted to know for how long have you cooperated with West Wonder King? And if whether you have any other cooperation with others?”

Bell became surprised for a moment, he looked at Zhao Hai puzzled, “Why do you ask? Mister Zhao Hai, do you have matters to take care of?”

Zhao Hai nodded, and replied, “Mister Bell, I’ll be honest with you, presently I am in an alliance with the Herculean Bull’s chieftain, the tribe’s seventh prince Wales is my Beheading Oath Brother. The reason that I’m moving about in the prairie is to gather information for Brother Wales with regards to the Fighting Bull clan. But you also know that it’s my first time in the prairie, therefore I am lacking with regards to information here, thus I wanted to ask you for help this aspect.”

Bell looked at Zhao Hai, the information Zhao Hai told him really gave him a shock. He didn’t know of a beastman performing a Beheading Blood Oath with a human. But Zhao Hai has unexpectedly managed to do it in his first year in the prairie, this is too astonishing.

* * *

Note here that our MC uses his name Zhao Hai for his dark magician persona. His name in this world is Adam Buda. This is the reason why people are having a hard time finding out about his background.

Chapter 291: Inside Information

Bell looked at Zhao Hai, “Mister Zhao Hai, are you sure you aren’t joking? Are you really Wales’ Beheading Blood Oath brother?”

Zhao Hai nodded, “Therefore I need to know information about the Fighting Bull chieftain, to make brother Wales’ counterattack against the Fighting Bull clan more successful.”

Bell stood up, and walked back and forth twice while muttering, “Good good, this is heaven’s will, this must be god’s will.”

Zhao Hai puzzlingly looked at the excited face of Bell, he didn’t know what elated Bell. It took a while before Bell managed to calm himself down. He turned towards Zhao Hai who still wore a puzzled expression, he couldn’t help but laugh then he said, “Mister Zhao Hao, you really are a lucky star, out League of Black Magician’s big lucky star.”

This made Zhao Hai even more puzzled, he looked at Bell, “What is going on Mister Bell? Do you care explain it to me?”

Bell looked at Zhao Hai’s face, he showed a faint smile and then sat down. Red drunk with wine, Bell let out a long breath and then said, “Mister Zhao Hai, because you just joined the League, there are a few things you know about what is going on in the inside. In fact, the Hercules Bull’s matter this time is in fact a contest between the League of Black Magicians and the Radiant Church, a contest on another level.”

Zhao Hai stared, then he looked at Bell and said, “What you mean is that the human expert who helped the Fighting Bulls was from the Radiant Church?”

Bell nodded, “Yes, that person was from the Radiant Church. In fact, the Radiant Church had long wanted to extend their claws towards the beastman prairie. They have tried controlling the tribes using business, but the beastmen have always believed in fellow beastmen, the Church didn’t succeed on several occasions.

After this matter was made known to our League of Black Magicians, we naturally needed to act on it. If we allowed the Church’s control to reach the beastmen, then our difficulties would increase in the future, so we kept an open eye on their actions with the beastmen. After learning that the Church wanted to cooperate with the Fighting Bulls,  we tried to destroy their plan several times but we haven’t succeeded. Finally, they managed to draw in the Fighting Bull chieftain to their side. The League wanted to ally with the Herculean Bulls, but their clan chieftain is a stickler for tradition, he didn’t want human help, thus we have not succeeded yet.”

Bell looked at Zhao Hai, “The next thing we know, they actually sent a 9th rank warrior to aid the Fighting Bulls, helping the Fighting Bulls to expel the Herculean bulls in one go, becoming the Cow-headed race’s royal clan. You can say that this was their first success in invading the prairie, moreover there was nothing we can do about it. Now that you became Wales’ beheading oath brother, you can help him openly, standing behind you will be the League of Black Magicians. Even if the Radiant Church were to send a 9th rank expert, you do not need to fear, the League will send a 9th rank expert to protect you.”

Zhao Hai stared blankly for a moment, he didn’t think that the fight between the Church and the League would reach to this point. But he still shook his head, “No, it would be best if the League refrain from participating. You already know that the beastmen have been rivals with the humans for many years, and they are not simpletons. The cow-headed race can only count as a medium rank race in the prairie, so those truly big warring races wouldn’t care about their conflict. But if those warring races were to know that humans have tried to control beastmen, then no matter which organization it is, they would suffer the wrath of the beastmen, and it may lead to a war. Being in the forefront of the war isn’t in our League’s best interest, moreover I am also preparing to use this information to take care of the Radiant Church personnel, therefore the League can opt not to participate.”

Bell was stunned, then he looked at Zhao Hai and nodded, “Good, let’s do it according to you advice, it seems the rumor that you have a grudge with the Radiant Church is real.”

Zhao Hai showed a faint smile, then he waved his hand, an undead wearing a white magic robe appeared in front of him, he smiled towards Bell, “This is a Church’s White-Robed Bishop, he is now my servant.”. The Bishop was Lindsey Becker, this guy was infamous in the League of Black Magicians and his father was a red-robed Archbishop, Zhao Hai took him out to show Bell that he indeed has a hatred towards the Radiant Church.

Bells also knows Lindsey Becker, so when Zhao Hai introduced him, Bell was shocked. Disbelief was plastered on his face, “How did you do it? Didn’t they say that Light Magicians can’t be turned into Advanced Undead?”

Zhao Hai smiled faintly, he waved and Becker disappeared, he replied, “My Magic Staff can do black magic variations, hehe.”

Bell did not comment any further, he knows that each Mage had their own secrets so he didn’t prod any further, he just nodded and said,”I didn’t expect you to be more ruthless than the average Black Mage, killing a white bishop immediately.”

Zhao Hai smiled, “Not the same, at that time there were five others. Five Radiant Bishops attacked along with 18 Radiant Cavalry, but they were extinguished by me in the end. Mister Maru was also there. Right, let’s not talk about this anymore, tell me some information about the Fighting Bulls that you know of.”

Bell nodded, with a serious voice he replied, “The Fighting Bull clan has long been preparing for their confrontation with the Herculean Bulls, but with their attack against the Herculean Bulls, their losses were certainly not small. They originally had a total clan number of 800 thousand, with available military strength of 250 thousand, and if you include their slaves, their forces would reach about 400 thousand. The Hercules Bulls is a large tribe numbering about a million people, their available strength is 300 thousand and if we also include their slaves, it will reach at about 500 thousand. But the Herculean Bulls didn’t think that the Fighting Bulls will move on them, moreover on their 9th level expert. Their defeat had dampened their morale, adding on to Gasol’s effort to replace his father as chieftain by killing him, and also his plot of killing his brother, this made the wills of the Herculean Bulls unsteady. When the Fighting Bulls attacked, Gasol was absent, the Herculean Bulls didn’t have a complete line of command, therefore they were quickly routed, but they also made the Fighting Bulls lose about 50 thousand personnel. Now, the forces of the Fighting Bulls only amount to 200 thousand, adding the slave soldiers it would number to about 300 thousand but this time they didn’t have a human expert to help them anymore since they were being pursued by 9th rank Beastmen experts.”

Zhao Hai nodded, “So this means that the current Fighting Bull troops is only about 300 thousand, and 100 thousand of these are slave soldiers, this is good news.”

“When will Wales’ counterattack be ready?”, Bell asked Zhao Hai.

Zhao Hai shook his head and replied, “It’s still not known, this time the Herculean Bulls have suffered a great loss, this winter will be very sad. I am only responsible for gathering information for Brother Wales, he also has his own worries. And Brother Wales is very similar to his father, a very traditional man, he still has reservations regarding asking humans for help.”

Bell did not doubt Zhao Hai’s words, he nodded “I also thought so, otherwise the old Herculean Bull patriarch won’t pass his seat to Wales, not even considering Gasol from the very beginning. Right, when will you return to human territory? Maybe we can cooperate at that time.”

Zhao Hai looked at Bell, he smiled bitterly and said, “Mister Bell are you serious? You must know my current situation with the Aksu Empire? It’s what everyone is shouting about these days, if those people were to know that you were cooperating with me, there will be no advantages for you. You’ll also become a target for the Radiant Church as well as Southern King if this information were to be known. I think that you being able to keep your current identity is much more advantageous for the League.

Bell nodded to what Zhao Hai said, “You’re right, but there are a lot of good things in your hand, if you gave it to me, I can make a lot of money with it.”

Zhao Hai stiffly smiled, “I also know that I hold a lot of good things, but because of these things, I was chased around in the Aksu Empire. You don’t want to be like me. Right, we can do another type of business, this business is absolutely good.”

Bell stared, he looked puzzled at Zhao Hai and asked, “What business?”

Zhao Hai smiled slightly, “Milk wine, do you want to sell milk wine to Humans? I know that milk wine couldn’t be preserved for a long time but my milk wine is different. My milk wine can be preserved for a long time and it wouldn’t affect its taste, I think there would be people willing to try it.”

Bell stared, to be honest, although he went to the prairie many times, he still was not used to the taste of milk wine because the absurd smell of mutton. And the flavor isn’t something that any ordinary human could bear. He did not understand why Zhao Hai spoke of his milk wine with an appearance of infatuation, was this person a beastman?

Zhao Hai looked at Bell’s appearance, he smiled faintly and said, “You need to taste my milk wine to understand. Right, should we not celebrate our meeting as fellow members of the league? Why don’t you go roast some argali? I’ll take care of the milk wine.

Seeing Zhao Hai’s appearance, Bell suddenly laughed. He felt Zhao Hai to be a very interesting person compared to the other members of the league. He immediately beckoned towards the servant by his side, “Cassie, go kill an argali to roast. Also, ask the captain to come, today we’ll be drinking nicely.”

Cassie complied, then he turned around to arrange the roast. Zhao Hai smiled and said, “Then I should go and prepare some vegetables and milk wine, we’ll see each other at the camp.” Bell nodded, then Zhao Hai led Laura and Meg as they returned to their tent.

Chapter 292: A Sense about Living

Zhao Hai and Laura returned to their tent but did not immediately head back out. Laura looked curiously at Zhao Hai, “Brother Hai, you did not mention to Bell that Brother Wales would counter attack immediately, are you afraid that he’ll spread the news?”

Zhao Hai nodded, “Although Bell is also a member of the league, we can’t not hold a little bit of precaution. It’s better to be more careful, in any case, so that Brother Wales’ counterattack this time would be successful. This time, Brother Wales’s attack hinges on the element of surprise. If we let others know when he will counterattack, the plan may fail, so we should tell nobody about this matter.”

Laura nodded, to be honest, if Bell were not a member of the League of Black Mages, they wouldn’t even make a contact with him, after all, Bell’s reputation is really bad.

Meg turned to Zhao Hai, “I think Mister Bell is a good man, he told us some secret information. Why is young master still on guard against him?”

Zhao Hai looked at Meg and the innocent Nier with a wry smile, Laura also shook her head. Meg and Nier were the kind of people who wouldn’t make any further assumptions. To them, if a person treated them well, then the person must be good. With this mindset, if nobody protects them then they would most likely be swindled and become bankrupt.

Zhao Hai cannot bear to look at their eyes any further, he said “Bell is a good person, and he is also a fellow member of the League of Black Magicians so he should not be against us. But with the current situation, the less people who knew the better, anyway you must remember this saying, ‘Never harbor the intent to victimize others; but never let your guard down against being victimized.'[1]

They nodded earnestly, but looking at their faces, Zhao Hai had the impulse to hit a wall, looking at them, its really uncertain if they will really remember.

Zhao Hai and Laura looked at each other, they cannot help but shake their heads and focus on preparing things they needed to eat. They did not believe that Meg and Nier would be able to hurt someone in this life.

The things that they need to prepare aren’t that many, as long as they have milk wine and some vegetables then they would be fine. Zhao Hai didn’t bring out many vegetables, only ones that were easy to preserve, he didn’t want the beastmen to be jealous of his space.

In only a few minutes, the four people were ready to go out of their tent. Outside the tent the bonfire was already going on, the argali already roasted. This made Zhao Hai admire the technique of Bell’s subordinate in handling food.

In his hand, Zhao Hai was holding the sheepskin knife given to him by Spier. Even though what Mendez gave him was much more gorgeous, Zhao Hai still liked using the one Spier gifted him. Maybe it’s because he felt Spier’s sincerity in handing him the knife, while the knife Mendez gave him was too magnificent, and not suitable for use, perhaps only for collection.

Bell was waiting for Zhao Hai, as though he was waiting for a treat. Glasses, plates, and all the things they needed for the meal were prepared ,only Zhao Hai was missing.

Zhao Hai didn’t act too polite, he put out several pots of milk wine, you must know that these big pots were used by beastmen to hold their milk wine. Each pot can hold up to 5 jin, Zhao Hai brought six pots this time.

As Zhao Hai brought out the wine, Beta also arrived, he did not come empty-handed. He held a big basin in his arms, which actually turned out to be beef.

Bell immediately sat down along with the other two. After they have sat down, Meg and Nier immediately went forth and poured them some wine. As the wine was poured down, Beta and Bell could feel the difference in this wine, this wine’s fragrant aroma is too imposing.

What’s most important, is that the liquid is very clear as though it doesn’t have any point of impurity, it pretty much looked like water. However, the fragrance and mellowness of the milk in the liquor greeted the nostrils, making one unable to stop smelling.

At this time, Cassie had cut up the beef that was brought by Beta, but Bell and Beta didn’t notice the beef at all, their eyes were stuck staring ant the wine glass in front of them.

Bell took a deep breath, then he looked towards Zhao Hai and asked, “Mister Zhao, is this you milk wine?”

Zhao Hai smiled and nodded, he replied, “Try it, see how my milk wine compares so Brother Beta’s. Brother Beta, you also taste, but I have to warn you that this wine strongly burns.

Beta didn’t know what it meant by being polite, so he immediately downed the entire glass. Then Zhao Hai looked at his appearance as though he was watching an entertaining show, a show on a screen called the face, with the performer being Beta, as the performance proceeded, Beta’s face turned red in a flash.

This cannot be blamed on Beta, he was not used to drinking liquor with a high degree of alcohol. Although Zhao Hai’s liquor only underwent simple distillation, the degree went up by almost 30 proof. The milk wine that the beastmen drank before can only be considered a simple alcoholic drink, it didn’t have that high of a degree.

Looking at Beta’s situation, Bell was surprised and also became a bit cautious. He raised the cup and took a little sip, the mellow wine fragrance along with its milky flavor became sandwiched in his mouth, the taste was really exquisite.

Bell closed his eyes, and just felt the fragrant taste of the wine. Although the wine also had a milky flavor, it wasn’t any bit smelly and the taste wasn’t uncomfortable at all but was rather mellow making the wine a bit more rich, this was the first time that Bell has come to drink this type of wine .

Beta was breathing heavily at this time, he was already unable to wait and he poured himself another glass of wine, he did not even have the time to praise the first glass before he drunk the second glass. His face became even more red, as if they were bleeding.

Zhao Hai saw Beta beginning to get his third glass, he quickly said, “Brother Beta, no rush, we may not even taste the beef that you’ve brought, you wouldn’t want yourself to be drunk do you?”

Beta responded, he gave back his glass full to the brim with liquor, then he said to Zhao Hai, “Right, Brother Zhao come taste the beef that I brought, this was just boiled with some unique spices from our prairie, taste it quickly.”

Seeing Beta this way, Bell and Zhao Hai couldn’t help but laugh, then they tasted the beef that he brought. It was very fragrant, and the flavor is really unique and can only be found in the prairie, humans had no way of replicating this flavor.

Zhao Hai was curious about the spices that Beta mentioned, he turned to Beta and said, “Brother Beta, can you give me some of your spices? It’ll be much better if they were alive.”

Beta knew that Zhao Hai wanted to collect plants, but he didn’t think that he would collect these kinds of plants also, after he heard Zhao Hai, he immediately replied, “Very well, Brother Zhao, this is not a problem, tomorrow I will find some spices and have them sent to you alive, but I have a request, you have to send me a few pots of your milk wine.”

Zhao Hai laughed, “No problem, brother, even if you didn’t give me some of those spices I would’ve still given you a few pots of milk wine.” he said while laughing. Bell also laughed with Zhao Hao, Bell liked Zhao Hai more and more now, at the same time he also understood why in such a short time, Zhao Hai managed to make the entire West Wonder King camp like him so much.

Bell didn’t know that the two flags that Zhao Hai had were friendship flags, nobody could blame him because most people who did business in the beastmen prairie did not understand what friendship flags were or have even heard it since they could not win the beastmen’s trust, thus they weren’t given friendship flags.

But even so, looking at the way the beastmen act towards Zhao Hai, the beastmen seem to be showing a different side, they seem to like interacting with Zhao Hai more. Them interacting with Zhao Hai and them interacting with Bell, it’s exactly two different things.

At the beginning, Bell didn’t understand what it was, but now when he saw Zhao Hai, he understood, he understood why those beastmen like to make contact with Zhao Hai, it was because of respect.

Although Bell didn’t want it known, but he had to admit that he had always looked down on the beastmen. He despised them, who only know how to herd sheep and had very unpleasant sheep smell. He thought that these beastmen were some uncouth boorish fellows, that they were completely different.

When he comes in contact with the beastmen, he was polite and merry, which was enough. But he had to recognize that he was less respectful and is a bit more arrogant towards them. Therefore this made it very difficult for him to become a true friend to the beastmen.

Bell cannot help but sigh, he can now understand why Zhao Hai became Wales’ Beheading Blood Oath brother, it was because Zhao Hai held a respect for him.

This meal eaten by several people was very merry, not only because of Zhao Hai’s wine, but also because of Bell’s fruits, Zhao Hai’s vegetables, Bell’s beef, and Cassie’s roast argali.

After eating, many beastmen who were familiar with Zhao Hai came and joined them, Zhao Hai was busy making Laura take out more milk wine to drink with everyone. More than a dozen beastmen became drunk in the camp. It didn’t mean that they had drunk a huge amount of liquor, on the contrary, they did not drink too much but instead drank too fast, therefore they made themselves intoxicated.”

Zhao Hai didn’t drink too much since he was very experienced with high degree alcohol. One cannot drink too much of this type of liquor, drinking too fast will also make you drunk. But to Zhao Hai, this milk wine was not the high degree alcohol that he was used to, compared to a high degree alcohol back on Earth, this milk wine felt too light.”

All the people who came to the camp were happily drinking. For Bell, this was the first time he experienced beastmen being intimate with him[2], he really admires Zhao Hai now.

Bell was also happily drinking, in the end he needed to be lifted by Cassie back to his tent, but Bell didn’t say anything, he was the first one keeling over, drunk.

When the other people in the camp were gone, Zhao Hai also returned to their tent. Zhao Hai didn’t drink too much today, so he was very awake, he did not need to drink life water to heal his hangover.

Laura looked at Zhao Hai and smiled, “It seems that the milk wine deal with Bell is finalized.”

Zhao Hai slightly smiled, “It looks like there would be no problems. Moreover, I think our milk wine sales in West Wonder King’s camp would also skyrocket, a pity that West Wonder King wouldn’t exist for too long.”

Laura stayed silent, she didn’t know what to say, if Wales’ counterattack against the Fighting Bulls were to succeed, he certainly wouldn’t let West Wonder King off easily. When that time comes, West Wonder King’s camp would be embroiled in the flames of war.

Zhao Hai looked at Laura’s appearance, he knew what she was thinking, he sighed and said, “There’s no other way, forget it, give me a piece of paper, I have to write the information we gathered today and send it to brother Wales to make him prepare earlier. I want the information regarding the Radiant Church to be among these, this would be a very important weapon for him, he can use this information to invite other beastmen races for help, they’d certainly agree to give aid.”

Laura nodded and replied, “I think that this thing was already been known by those large warring races in the prairie. The strength of those races couldn’t be underestimated, but why they just turned a blind eye towards the Herculean Bulls, is beyond me.”

Zhao Hai laughed and said, “Not necessarily, these warring races aren’t gods, they cannot know everything. Although the Herculean Bulls are fairly famous among the beastmen, they are still a small group, they cannot necessarily be able to attract the attention of those big warring races.”

Laura nodded, “I certainly hope that is the case. I always had the feeling that something was going on between the beastmen and humans recently, and it’s not good”

Zhao Hai sighed and said, “No matter what we do, we only need to ensure the safety of out territory. I heard a saying, if everything is left to the world, then poverty is the only good. What it means is, we need to help others when we have the power but if you have no power, just let yourself not be bad and be an honest person. We can only count as poor people now. If there is really something big going on in the continent, then we can only do our best to help others.”

Laura nodded, she also thought that these words were reasonable, their current status on the main continent was very sensitive, especially inside the Aksu Empire. Zhao Hai and Laura’s status is likened to that of an old street mouse, being chased and hunted around. At this time, even if they wanted to help others, they were unable to, it would not bode well if they were to expose their secret, as their troubles would become greater.

Laura sighed and said, “If the beastmen would really make a move, their only goal could only be the Aksu empire because they share borders. They wouldn’t cross the ocean to attack the Rosen Empire, that would be unrealistic. If the beastmen were to really wage war with the humans, then what do we do? Do we still provide grain to the beastmen? But in that case, wouldn’t it be unfair for the humans?”

Zhao Hai had a headache thinking about this, he touched his forehead and after some time sighed, “Let’s not think about this anymore. Right now there still hasn’t been a war. And if it breaks out, Wales is still my sworn brother. To be honest, I don’t hold much favor towards the human race, naturally this refers to those at the higher positions. Human commoners are just the same as beastmen commoners. I do not hope for war, but we can only do what we can. These matters are out of our control, we can only act as observers, quietly watching, offering help where help is needed. This is what we can do at most.”

* * *

proverb is Hài rén zhī xīn bù kě yǒu, Fáng rén zhī xīn bùkě wú.  Source

( ͡° ͜ʖ ͡°)

Chapter 293: Milk Wine Partnership

Zhao Hai never thought of himself as a saint, he was just an ordinary man who can be a bit selfish. He didn’t think of becoming a hero nor did he want to become a saint, he just wanted his life to be a little bit more comfortable, and also make his followers’ life more comfortable.

Laura also knows that this was Zhao Hai’s ideals, she didn’t think that Zhao Hao was wrong. After all, who wouldn’t want want to make his family’s life more comfortable, isn’t that a man’s responsibility? If you don’t help your family, but you’re trying to help other people, then you are not a saint but a hypocrite, and neither are you a good husband.

Laura nodded, “Now we can only wait until something happens. Then we decide what to do. I hope the result wouldn’t be too bad.”

At this time, Meg had brought the pen and paper. Zhao Hai started to write Wales’ letter. The information he got today was very important, he wanted to tell Wales immediately.

After writing the letter and having the blood hawk send it, Zhao Hai also rested, after all it was already late. What they didn’t know, when Bell came back to his tent, he was already sober.

Pretending to be drunk was a basic merchant’s skill, so Bell with his long years of experience would naturally be very skillful in this aspect.

How could a merchant possibly be unable to handle alcohol? Although Zhao Hai’s milk wine had a high alcohol content, Bell quickly adapted to it after having a small sip. He then pretended to be drunk so that he could return to his tent.

After returning to his tent, Bell immediately drank a few glasses of cold water to make himself feel better, the he ate a few fruits, only then did his mind completely sober up.

Cassie was standing next to him, he looked at Bell and said, “Master, Zhao Hai was quite reserved when speaking to you, you asked him about his matters but he didn’t respond, why did you still give him a lot of information?”

Bell shook his head and replied, “Zhao Hai not trusting me is completely normal. I can be sure that if I weren’t a member of the league then he’d never even meet me, perhaps he’ll even deal with me. He is not the friendly kind, moreover he has astonishing power. Currently, in the whole of Aksu Empire, aside from a few people, almost all nobles wanted to deal with Zhao Hai, making Zhao Hai and Laura give up their business for many years, this hatred is impossible to be erased. I can say that right now, Zhao Hai won’t just trust anybody. Him meeting and speaking with me is already good enough. The current matter is very favorable to the alliance, I did not tell him this, moreover he also had not told me his secret, the matter that stumped the league would be solved by him. This time, the Radiant Church’s men in the prairie would certainly suffer a few big losses.”

Cassie was not opposed to what Bell said, he knows that Bell was right, Zhao Hai wouldn’t let go of the chance to attack the Radiant Church, his enmity with the church was very big.

Bell calmed his mood, he turned his head to Cassie, “Did you drink Zhao Hai’s milk wine? What do you think?”

Cassie’s eyes lit up, “Money!”

Bell became amused by Cassie’s expression, he laughed and said, “You say it well, money, a lot of money, hahaha, I believe this wine is a huge business opportunity. Zhao Hai must’ve given me face as a fellow league member, otherwise he wouldn’t have given me such a good deal. The taste of the wine is too fragrant, looking at what those beastmen’s expression, it seemed that they haven’t drunk such good milk wine is their entire life, they haven’t expected that milk wine could taste so good.”

Cassie flapped his lips, to be honest, that milk wine was the best liquor he had drank. Though he was not used to the taste of alcohol, that milk wine’s taste made him unable to stop.

Bell looked at Cassie’s appearance and smiled faintly, “Do to not think about it too much, take a good rest, tomorrow we’ll talk to Zhao Hai about this milk wine partnership.”

Cassie nodded, he prepared Bell’s bed then retreated outside the tent. Casey is the absolute subordinate of Bell, he knows all of Bell’s matters. In fact, they grew up together, this is why he calls Bell master, as well as being able to talk casually with Bell if there are no other persons nearby.

The next morning, Bell wasn’t able to find Zhao Hai to discuss the matter with the milk wine because the camp suddenly became lively, and there’s no other reason for this atmosphere other than Zhao Hai’s convoy arriving for the fourth time in West Wonder King’s camp.

Bell didn’t think much of it when he saw the big row of grain carts, when he delivered grain to West Wonder King before, his convoy was a lot bigger than this one. But he didn’t not expect the beastmen to be more enthusiastic to Zhao Hai.

When Zhao Hai transports to West Wonder King’s camp, he didn’t need to arrange for his people to unload the grain. These beastmen would willingly do the work, before long, all the grain had been snatched up.

With the grain gone, Zhao Hai immediately had his team head towards the outside of the camp where the Argali were herded, ready to be taken away.

Bell also saw Zhao Hai’s convoy and noticed the undead which made him envious. He hired a lot of people for his convoys, and all of them needed to be paid with money, unlike Zhao Hai, who had no other men on his convoy other than undead. There was no need to be told that Zhao Hai didn’t need to spend a single cent for wages, as well as money for meals.

Zhao Hai reducing the price of grain, Bell didn’t mind. The beastmen lack food too much, and Zhao Hai’s grain quantity is merely a spray compared to the entire prairie. Additionally, he also knew that Zhao Hai was selling grain in order to gather information, thus Bell didn’t mind it too much.

To be honest, after drinking Zhao Hai’s milk wine, Bell almost wanted to give up his grain business in the prairie. This was because trading grain the the prairie was a very huge risk, very hard. But the milk wine was a very high quality good just in the continent alone, doing such business one wouldn’t worry about money not coming in droves, therefore Bell is preparing to make trading milk liquor his main business now.

However, after the grain convoy left, Beta came. This led Bell’s plan to approach Zhao Hai delayed once again, which made Bell very helpless.

Beta went and delivered the spices to Zhao Hai, he brought a lot of spices this time, with only a couple of them being seen at Spier’s camp, and the others Zhao Hai hadn’t seen before. Unfortunately, when he threw these spices to the space, the space gave a prompt saying that the level of these plants were too low and therefore is not enough to upgrade its level, this made Zhao Hai quite depressed.

However, he still gave Beta some milk wine since in any case, Beta treated him well. He wanted to pay Beta back as a friend, so he gave Beta 50 jin of wine.

After Beta was sent away, Bell came to Zhao Hai immediately. He was afraid that other people will come and delay his plans yet again. Seeing Bell’s behavior, Zhao Hai couldn’t help the urge to laugh,

They sat down inside the tent, Laura gave the two of them some milk tea. Bell smiled at Zhao Hai and said, “Brother Zhao, I thought that you had already familiarized with the lifestyle of the prairie, drinking their drink but instead you’re drinking milk tea.”

Zhao Hai smiled and replied, “I really like the taste of milk tea, and I’m unable to stomach the beastmen’s milk tea. Thus, I made my own, come taste.”

Bell smiled, then he tasted Zhao Hai’s milk tea, its taste was very good. He thought that this couldn’t be sheep’s milk, but a never before seen Magic Beast’s milk, the flavor is very mellow, very good to drink.”

After putting down the cup, Bell laughed and said, “I won’t be polite to you, I came here today to discuss to you about the matter with the milk wine, how much milk wine can you provide me?”

Zhao Hai smiled, “Calculating the current production progress, I can provide about 1,000 jin every month, although its quite small, it’s the current limit.

Bell smiled and said, “This is already a lot, this number was above my expectations. I’ll have you know that I already have the equipment and route for selling your high-quality milk wine, so for how much would you want to sell it?

Zhao Hai smiled, “What do you think? I don’t know the prices of alcohol that well.”

Bell replied, “I think one bottle can be sold for three gold coins, a jin of wine per bottle, what do you think?”

Zhao Hai replied with a faint smile, “Right, going by your calculation, how about I sell you the wine for two gold for one jin, while you sell it at three gold?

Bell stared for a moment, “Godo, let’s do it, to be honest I feel that I got the wine for cheap, to be able to gain a gold coin per bottle is quite good. Right, how do you want to deliver the goods?”

Zhao Hai smiled, “We don’t need to rush about this I think, if we do, I won’t have time to return to human lands. We’ll begin our business at the beginning of spring, when the time comes I’ll tell you where to pick up the goods, what do you think?”

Bell knitted his eyebrows, he thinks that the beginning of spring is quite a long time, but he also knew that Zhao Hai was in the prairie to collect information for Wales, so he didn’t say anything, he just nodded and replied, “Ok, let’s do that, I’ll wait for your news. I’ll get ready to head back tomorrow, when the time comes it’ll be easier if you look for me at the Iksa territory.”

Zhao Hai smiled lightly, “I’d also like to express my gratitude for the information you provided. Right, I have a small request, can you help me with a small matter, a simple mercenary task? The task is to collect rare plants and magic beasts, the more the better, all needs to be alive, I’ll pay handsomely.”

These days Bell has been made aware of this habit of Zhao Hai, he just nodded his head, “No problem, don’t worry.” After that, Bell said goodbye, then Zhao Hai escorted him out of the tent.

Chapter 294: Leaving West Wonder King’s Camp

Seeing Bell leave, Laura turned to Zhao Hai and said, “Brother Hai, we can produce more than 1,000 jin of milk wine every month, why do we only sell 1,000 jin?”

Zhao Hai showed a faint smile, “Good things should be in low supply to be valuable, if we control the supply then it would never become cheap. Right now, our 1,000 jin is still a small number when being sold to something like the Iksa territory. But there is still an adjustment time for the people since we had just introduced the milk wine to the market, in the future when there would be more demand, we shall increase our supply then.”

Laura was also a merchant, so he understood what Zhao Hai is saying. She smiled and didn’t say anything else, then she immediately frowned, “Then how do we deal with supplying Bell? We have no transfer point in Iksa territory.”

Zhao Hai shook his head, “Even if we have a delivery point in the territory, it still couldn’t be used because the people on the continent would think we have some sort of special means to make milk wine. Our supply point for Bell should be in the prairie since nobody would find out due to milk wine being common here. They will only think that we bought it from the beastmen to resell.”

Laura understood, but she still couldn’t help but worry, “There is a great deal of risk having trade with the beastmen, especially in the prairie. But if we suddenly appear in this huge prairie, nobody would notice. Then there probably won’t be any more trouble.”

Zhao Hai nodded, but he still said, “There’s no need to worry about this right now. We’ll go to the border where the Iksa territory and the Prairie meets, we’ll decide where to place our supply point then.”

Laura agreed, she had not been to the Iksa territory before and was not familiar with the situation there. However, another reason she agreed with Zhao Hai’s words was that if they want to sell milk wine, it would indeed be better to do so in the prairie so that no one would have any suspicions.

Although Bell told them that the Radiant Church had some influence in the prairie, the Radiant Church’s influence was too small to cover the entirety of it. Even the large warring beastmen races couldn’t possible monitor the entire place.

Today had been a peaceful day, in fact, it has been quite tranquil these past few days in West Wonder King’s camp. Even though they lost 5,000 clansmen, they couldn’t even find any traces of them so they eventually let the matter go.

The camp was very calm, after all, winter was approaching. People had many things to do in preparation. There was no time to be distracted. Zhao Hai had no more information to collect since he already got all he needed, so he had nothing to do but idle about in the past few days. Now he was only waiting for the last convoy to arrive before leaving the camp.

The next day, Bell left West Wonder King’s camp. As was said before, winter was already fast approaching and the winter in the prairie is very terrible. Not to mention the winds and blizzards, there would also be devil wolves wandering about.

The demon wolves can also be categorized as one of the disasters in the prairie. In the winter, because these magic beasts would find it hard to get food, many small magic wolf packs will join forces and attack beastmen tribes. Due to this, there were a lot of beastmen tribes who were eliminated in the winter.

It was precisely because of those that humans would return to their territory during the winter. When the spring of next year comes, there would be flocks of humans returning to the prairie, this process had become like a tidal movement every year.

In the following days, Zhao Hai’s life was very calm. From time to time, Beta would come find him sporting a reddened face, it seemed that he was drunk with wine. This made Zhao Hai a bit regretful, he did not think that because of his liquor, Beta would turninto a drunkard.

However, like the first time, Zhao Hai still gave some wine to Beta, after all, they were both friends. And even if Zhao Hai didn’t give any wine to him, Beta was already an alcoholic, sending or not sending wouldn’t make any difference.[1]

Soon, six days had passed and Zhao Hai’s convoy arrived at the camp for the last time. Before the convoy arrived, Zhao Hai already had all his things packed up. When the convoy came, Zhao Hai immediately said his farewells to Belluk and left the camp.

But before leaving, Zhao Hai gave Beta another 50 jins of milk wine. Beta was very happy, but this time he did not dare get so drunk. He decided to keep the wine and wouldn’t use them all up before Zhao Hai returns to the prairie. But what a pity, he would never imagine that the next time him and Zhao Hai would see each other, they would be enemies.

After Zhao Hai left West Wonder King’s camp, he followed his previous route and walked towards the Pig-headed race’s domain. Zhao Hai didn’t want to play any tricks inside the Cow-headed race’s territory because if he suddenly disappeared, people would find it odd.

Zhao Hai immediately sent Wales a letter after leaving the camp telling him that he was already out of West Wonder King’s camp and would soon come to find him.

Then they hurriedly headed to the Pig-headed race’s domain, but not too anxiously, they rushed but at a controllable rate to avoid suspicion. Five days after leaving West Wonder King’s camp, they managed to enter the Pig-headed race’s territory.

Upon arriving at the Pig-headed race’s domain, Zhao Hai walked a bit further before he was certain that he wasn’t followed by another person. Then he went into the space and gave the Ghost staff to a blood hawk to head towards the Mastiff clan.

* * *

Wales’ recent days had not been well, although there was the grain that Zhao Hai provided to get through difficult times, the grain was not sufficient enough. This gave the people in the tribe a pessimistic mood, everyone seemed to think that their situation wouldn’t turn for the better.

Although Wales was trying to find ways to change the situation, there hasn’t been a solution found. Even if he got grain everyday from Zhao Hai, the space bag had a limited size, there would be no way to send food at huge quantities for his people. Every time food was delivered to the camp, it’ll be devoured instantly, making people worry about their next meal which further adds to the pessimism.

Right now, Wales really wanted Zhao Hai to just appear in front of him. Although he already received a letter from Zhao Hai five days ago that he was coming, five days had already passed and Zhao Hai hadn’t arrived yet. Currently, Wales felt that every day seemed to be as long as a year.

He knew that the best time to counterattack would be right now. Because currently the Fighting Bulls are lacking in troops, their human helpers were away, and now he received information from Zhao Hai that the human helpers were from the Radiant Church, which was good news since he can use this information to get aid from other beastmen.

Although these facts made it clear that there was definite reason for success against the Fighting Bulls, if his men’s morale is not high, then all of these might as well be empty talk. After all, he may invite other race’s experts to deal with the Fighting Bulls but he could not invite other’s troops. Otherwise, they may face resistance when passing by other Cow-headed tribe’s area.

Having said that, Wales also had his own pride, he hopes that what the Herculean Bulls had lost, they themselves would be the ones to reclaim or otherwise the Herculean Bulls couldn’t hold the title of being the Royal Clan of the Cow-headed race.

* * *

Currently, Wales was sitting inside his tent, Yale and Mendez were sitting right next to him. There was also another man sitting inside the tent. The man looked old, his face wrinkled, but his body looked very strong, had eyes that showed wisdom, and an aura of a lord.

This person was a Herculean Bulls’ elder, Kony. He was a friend of Wales’ father, the two grew up together so they were as close as brothers. It could be said that Wales and his group grew up while looking up to him, he was also an 8th rank expert and is very loyal and devoted to Wales’ father. He was also one of the reasons why Gasol couldn’t snatch the seat of chieftain after having killed his father.

Moreover, this elder Kony is quite well-known in the tribe as a brave warrior, for the Herculean Bulls to have this much military prowess and fame, he contributed greatly through his achievements.

However, there was also a small issue regarding this man. Like Wales’ father, elder Kony never did have any trust towards humans, he did not make contact with humans, he did not cooperate with humans, more so wanting to ask for help from a human.

Wales suddenly said to Mendez, “Sixth Brother, didn’t Little Hai deliver his letter a few days ago? Why hasn’t he arrived yet?”

Mendez replied, “Five days, forget it, don’t worry, Little Hai will surely arrive.”

Kony knit his eyebrows and said, “Little Seven, why do you always mention that human, do we not have any other means? To me, since winter still isn’t in full bloom, why not go towards the Feline race’s territory and pillage some grains, not only would we have food, we can also develop a good relationship with the Mastiffs.”

Wales cannot bear with Kony’s suggestions. Although Kony was very powerful, he was a military man through and through, and this time he wants to go raid the Feline race. If the Herculean bulls were to cause trouble for the Felines, then the Felines may be pushed to ally with the Fighting Bulls, which would create more trouble.

If the Feline race were to side with the Fighting Bulls and suddenly attack them, they would be finished. Therefore, Wales had never thought of attacking the opposite party, he can only wait for Zhao Hai to arrive. As long as Zhao Hai comes and brought some grain, the morale of his troops would be stabilized, then they could prepare for the counterattack.

Yale sighed and said, “Kony, please talk less nonsense, if we go and attack the Felines, wouldn’t that create more trouble? Our main concern now is to stabilize the morale of our men, then counterattack now that the injuries of our Supreme elder has been cured. Moreover, the Mastiffs has agreed to help us, while the Fighting Bulls currently don’t have any helpers, now is the best time to counterattack, attacking the Feline race now would only worsen our position.”[2]

At this time, the sounds of running footsteps could be heard outside, then Wales’ guard entered with an excited face and said,” Chieftain, young master Zhao Hai has arrived.”

* * *

O, rly?

Yale was that prophet guy that was with Wales.

Chapter 295: Revenge! Revenge!

When Wales heard the guard, he immediately stood up and rushed towards the guard named Bogut, “Are you sure?”

Bogut excitedly replied, “Yes, the caravan is not far away from here, come immediately.”

Wales laughed and turned to run outside the tent, Yale and Mendez also followed while Bogut also ran behind them. Inside the tent, only Kony was left, gazing at the empty area.

Kony saw Wales’ excited expression, he looked at the now empty tent then muttered, “Looking too excited, let’s go see what’s so remarkable about it.” He slowly stood up and headed outside the tent.

As he arrived outside, Wales had already ridden his mount and rushed towards the plains. The sound of hooves rumbling alerted the entire camp. The Herculean Bulls were horrified, they thought that the enemies had already come and attack them. Many people clutched their weapons and went with Wales.

Kony became shocked at the situation at the camp. Of course he knew why Wales immediately rushed out of the camp, but he didn’t imagine that the people’s response would be this intense. This time he grasped the clan’s current situation, he now knew that his perception of his clansmen was wrong.

Kony couldn’t help but be stunned, then he what Yale said. In the entire Herculean Bull camp, only Yale could move him, since Yale and himself were of the same generation and the two of them were friends. In addition, Yale had always been smart, so Kony would almost always listen to Yale, because of this, Kony wouldn’t object to Yale’s words.

And Kony wasn’t a completely coarse fellow, otherwise he wouldn’t attain his current position. Currently, he realized that the state of the clan is far from what it was before. The young clan members were as if rabbits that were being hunted, easily getting frightened by the sound of arrows, this made Kony angry.

In Kony’s mind, the Herculean Bulls shouldn’t be afraid of anyone, they should be the bravest warriors in the entire prairie. No matter what kind of enemy they face, they should be courageous enough to charge into battle. No matter how many times they were defeated, they should still charge head on at the next confrontation. Looking at it now, these young Herculean Bulls fell short of his requirements.

Wales did not have the means to change this right now, he had long been aware of this fact, but did not have any solutions. Currently he was leading Bogut and the others away from the camp. At this moment, he saw a beastman friendship flag from afar and below the flag was a carriage followed by a long caravan of carts.

Wales laughed and patted his mount, the mount moved faster and soon arrived next to Zhao Hai’s carriage. Zhao Hai was standing outside his carriage at this time, watching Wales approach.

Wales jumped down from his mount, he laughed, opened his arms and hugged Zhao Hai, “My goodness, you really made me wait.”

Zhao Hai also laughed and said, “You really cannot blame me, but brother, if you don’t let go now I’ll actually be killed by you.”

Wales laughed, then he put Zhao Hai down on the ground, he turned around and glanced at the grain carts behind him, he looked at Zhao Hai, “Why did you use carts to transport grain?”

Zhao Hai smiled, “Don’t you think that this effect is better? Let your people see the grain, we have quite a few.”

Wales laughed and patted Zhao Hai’s shoulder forcefully. He knew that Zhao Hai did so to help his men recover their morale.

At this time, Mendez and Yale had also arrived, and they both walked towards Zhao Hai and laughed, leaving the people following them stunned, unable to understand what was happening.

Wales also noticed that behind Zhao Hai’s grain carts were about ten thousand argali, these argali were from Zhao Hai’s trades with West Wonder King. Zhao Hai knew that when regards to beastmen, if they did not have any argali, then it would be akin to a human having no land, it’ll make them restless. Therefore he took these argali out and planned to give them to Wales.

Wales didn’t need to say anything, he led Zhao Hai towards the camp. Although there were many argali in their camp, compared to the the tribe’s hundreds of thousands of people, their argali were still too few, this made the Herculean Bulls feel unease.

However, the grain that Zhao Hai brought this time would give relief to the Herculean Bulls. After arriving at the camp, the people of the Herculean Bull camp were very surprised as grain cart after grain cart were being unloaded until a pile of grain appeared in the camp. Looking at the huge pile of food, the people from the Herculean Bull camp became shocked silly, some even knelt down and started praying to the Beast God.

And standing at the side was Kony staring blankly at all of these, he now finally understood why Wales was filled with the thought of Zhao Hai arriving, it was because of this.

Konly looked at Zhao Hai, he really cannot see how this thin and small human could have such ability.

After unloading about 100 million jin of grain, Zhao Hai stopped. Wales patted Zhao Hai’s shoulder and then jumped on top of the grain pile, he looked around his clansmen and spoke loudly, “My people, this year has been a disaster for our Herculean Bull tribe. Our late chieftain was killed. We were even driven out of our homes by the traitorous Fighting Bulls. Many people thought that our Herculean Bull tribe was finished, that we are already defeated, but I would not say that the Herculean Bulls are finished. We Herculean Bulls were just taking a nap, but a thief just stole our belongings. We the Herculean Bulls, with the help of a friend, shall reclaim all that belonged to us!”

The people below looked blankly at Wales, and then towards the piles of grain, their hearts lit up with fire. Just as what Wales had said, when they were defeated by the Fighting Bulls, they felt as though the sky had collapsed, they felt that the Herculean Bulls were finished. Overnight, they lost all their grain, and all their argali, they thought that they wouldn’t have hope, that their future was bleak, they all seemed to became nobodies.

Wales looked at this clansmen. He knew that his words had an effect, so he went on, “I want to tell everyone the good news that our Supreme elder didn’t just recover from his injuries, but he also achieved a breakthrough. And he’s going to teach those Fighting Bulls a lesson!”

The Herculean Bulls burst into cheers, if the grain stabilized their hearts, the fact about their Supreme elder gave their hearts a shock of revival. Their grey future seemed to light up with hope.

Wales waved his hand, the people began to calm down. Wales continued, “The shameless Fighting Bulls didn’t actually defeat us with their own hands, they cannot defeat us with their own strength so they asked humans for help. Moreover, they did not just invite an ordinary human expert, this human is actually from the Radiant Church. All of you know that this Radiant Church had always wanted to control and enslave all the beastmen in the prairie. For the Fighting Bulls to be working for them, this is a betrayal to all beastmen, absolutely unforgivable! But we will not ask others for help, this is our Herculean Bull tribe’s own matter, so we shall take revenge with our own hands! Revenge!”

All the Herculean Bulls were shouting, “Revenge! Revenge!”

Wales went on, “My clansmen, this human is Zhao Hai, my Beheading Blood Oath brother. He is a human merchant as well as a formidable mage. He has grain and is willing to support us in our path of vengeance. Some time ago, he gathered information for as at West Wonder King’s camp and now he has arrived here carrying an innumerable amount of grain. Now that we have food, we shall fill our stomachs, we shall eat till we are full so that we can have the strength to fight. I order, that starting today, all of you shall sharpen your axes, prepare to go back and fight for revenge and claim back our territory. Claim everything that belonged to us, Claim back our clansmen!”

More and more beastmen gathered and loudly shouted, “Claim back our camp! Claim back our camp!”

Wales loudly said, “My clansmen, go get some food, eat till you are full, we have a war to fight!” He waved his hand, the guards immediately distributed grain to their clansmen.

Currently there were 500 thousand clansmen in the Herculean Bull camp, but Zhao Hai brought more than 100 million jin of grain, this means that each clansman can get 200 jin each, but some of these beastmen have families to feed to they would be given a few hundred more jin. But to them, this quantity of grain is already a lot. Even before their plight, it would be impossible for a person to be allocated 200 jin during winter season.

While they were distributing the grain, Wales led Zhao Hai to his tent. After they entered the tent, Wales laughed, Mendez laughed, and a smile was plastered on Yale’s face. Zhao Hai became quite puzzled, he did not know why they were laughing.

At this time, Kony was looking and Zhao Hai and Laura’s group. He had not thought that they could bring so much food with them, looking onto Wales’ words, he now understood what Wales meant. He believed that the Herculean Bulls now had a good chance to restore their past glory, even if they were led to battle at this very moment, the people would certainly agree.

Morale is a thing that can’t be seen nor can it be touched, but this thing can actually decide the result of a war. If the army doesn’t have morale, even if they were trained well, it would be impossible for them do defeat a crowd of enraged peasants equipped with crude weapons, this is what morale can do.

Before, what the Herculean Bulls lack the most is morale, but now they have recovered it back. The current morale driven Herculean Bull army would even dare to charge a same number of Lion or Tiger race warriors, not to mention a small Fighting Bull tribe.

After some time, Wales stopped. He turned to Zhao Hai, he smiled widely and said, “Brother you came just in time, now we can plan for the counterattack immediately.”

Zhao Hai showed a faint smile, “It’s not too late, Big Brother did you manage to find help? When do you plan to begin?”

Wales thought for a moment then replied, “We need to be quick now that morale is recovering. If the morale dissipates, then it would be too troublesome. I think we should contact the Mastiffs, immediately invite their experts to make sure they arrive fast.”

Zhao Hai nodded and said, “I don’t have any problems on my side, leave your army’s food supply to me. Right, Big Brother, do you want to prepare some gifts for the Mastiffs this time? When I’m not here, I’m unable to prepare various things. Now that I came, you can tell me what you need, I’ll deliver them to you.”

Wales patted Zhao Hai’s shoulder, “Brother, because of the Mastiffs my clansmen had fortunately able to live. The gave us some grains and argali, otherwise would be unable to reunite with me, how would you consider this matter?”

Zhao Hai thought for a moment then he said, “I have a lot of grain on hand, but if we were to give all of it to them, then your days will be bad. Brother, how about this, we’ll give them milk wine, vegetables, fruit oil in addition to some grain as a gift, what do you think?”

Wales stared blankly, the vegetables and fruit oil he understood, but milk wine is something that beastmen always produced, did Zhao Hai plan to give that as a gift?

Looking at Wales’ appearance, Zhao Hai understood what he was thinking, he smiled and handed over a pot of milk wine, “Brother Wales, taste it, this is your brother’s milk wine.”

Although shocked, Wales smiled and took the jug, “What’s the matter? Why did you start brewing milk? You want to be a beastman?” While talking, he poured some wine on a cup.

While the wine was being poured out of the jug, the people in the tent involuntarily sucked some air into their noses, it was because the smell of the wine was too fragrant, a brand new kind of smell.

Wales couldn’t control himself, he took the cup and drained it dry. But he didn’t think that this wine would be so strong, he choked and began to cough immediately. Zhao Hai was there smiling, Laura was at the side laughing, they already expected this kind of result.

After quite some time, Wales eventually stopped coughing. He gave a complicated look at the wine pot in his hand, he looked at Zhao Hai and asked, “Little Hai, this is milk wine? Why doesn’t it have any color? And why is it so fragrant? How did you make it?”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “This I cannot tell you brother, this wine is my lifeblood product. Brother, how was it? Is it qualified to be a gift?”

Wales actually shook his head and said, “Brother, do not gift this, instead why don’t you just give it to me? I cannot bear seeing other people take away this wine.”

Zhao Hai laughed loudly.

Chapter 296: Semi-Warring Clan

On the yellow and withered plains, an enormous convoy was moving forward. The convoy consists of about 2000 carriages, about a thousand were large carriages used by the beastmen, while the remaining thousand were human carriages.

Escorting the convoy was a team of ten thousand Herculean Bull cavalry. At the front was a human carriage, inserted on both sides of the carriage were two friendship flags, one from the Big bellied Pig tribe, while the other is from the Giant horned Bull tribe.

Around the carriage was a group of Herculean Bulls, the cotton robes worn by these bulls were not ordinary showing their exceptional status.

Zhao Hai was sitting inside the carriage, he looked towards Wales and said, “Big Brother, can you drink moderately? If you drink all the wine, we won’t have any left to gift.”

At the moment, Wales was holding a leather pouch in his hand while having a mouthful of wine on his mouth. Watching this made Zhao Hai helpless, since the time he gave Wales some milk wine up until now, Wales almost never stopped drinking. He was always carrying a leather pouch filled with the wine around, Zhao Hai was helpless.

Wales glared at Zhao Hai and said, “You had such good wine but you never let me drink? hmpf, and you still want to gift it to others, I haven’t drunk enough yet.”

Wales laughed, Laura laughed and Yale who was riding his mount also laughed. They knew that Wales was just joking, but Zhao Hai’s wine was really good, it even made Yale who was not an alcoholic a bit greedy for this wine.

Zhao Hai shook his head and said to Wales, “Brother, is it fine that there’s only sixth brother to manage the camp?”

Wales showed a faint smile, “It’s fine, Sixth brother is very good at logistics, don’t worry, he’ll be fine.”

Zhao Hai nodded and then he said, “Also, we’re moving at wintertime, it would be better to prepare liquor. Winter is too cold no matter if you are a person or a magic beast. Before battle, it would be best to drink liquor to avoid being cold.”

The light on Wales’ eyes changed, “Don’t worry, I have arranged this as well. These are desperate times for our tribe, I had all argali killed and be turned to rations, I also made a prohibition on alcohol consumption, controlling the amount of Milk Wine being drank. We only wait for the start of the battle. If this time we cannot claim our camp back, then the Herculean Bulls might as well vanish from the prairie.”

Wale’s words held a trace of resolution, just as he said, the Herculean Bulls are preparing to go all out this time. Right now that their tribes’ strength is dwindling, moreover they had lost their home in this war. if they cannot reclaim their territory back, then the Herculean Bulls will not have any more chances to rise back.

Zhao Hai thought that Wales had gone a bit mad, but this madness was what the Herculean Bulls need right now, he sighed, “Aside from second and third sister, how’s the situation with eldest sister and fourth sister?”

Wales nodded and said, “Dead, they said the Fighting Bull chieftain ordered their execution. Not only them, the Fighting Bulls also executed all their servants. The old and weak were captured and turned into slaves. This time I will make sure to have all Fighting Bull clansmen killed.”

Zhao Hai didn’t say anything, he knew that for the beastmen, killing was very common. He replied, “Brother, when dealing with West Wonder King, is it really necessary to do so?”

Wales froze for a moment, then he nodded, “West Wonder King’s people can be spared, but West Wonder King himself must die. Little Hai, you must promise me that you will turn all the dead Fighting Bulls into undead, make them slaves.”

Zhao Hai forcefully smiled, “Big Brother, that is several hundred thousand people, do you really want to do it?”

Wales nodded, and fiercely said, “If we don’t do that, it’ll be difficult to quell the hatred in my heart. Brother, you must promise me.”

Zhao Hai was helpless, he said, “Brother, wouldn’t I profit much from this? After giving me all those people, my combat strength would increase, of course I’d be happy to help.”

Wales didn’t say anything, he thought that Zhao Hai was just comforting him. He had some basic understanding of Black Mages, he knows that if a Black Mage controls too many undead, they’d have some difficulties. A common Black Mage that can command several hundred undead is already a very good feat. For him to request Zhao Hai to control several hundred thousand undead is actually a little excessive.

What he didn’t know was that Zhao Hai was not a true Black Mage. For Zhao Hai, controlling that much undead isn’t much of a trouble, it was just like what Zhao Hai said, the additional undead would be a great help for increasing his strength.

Wales has now completely regarded Zhao Hai like his own biological brother, even more than his own brother. In any case, his biological brother didn’t achieve such high contributions such as Zhao Hai.

Wales had an idea, if they won against the Fighting Bulls this time, in addition to turning the Fighting Bulls as slaves for Zhao Hai, he is also prepared to give Zhao Hai several hundred thousand argali.

However, he didn’t say it out loud, it was only an idea. But he believed that Yale and Mendez wouldn’t disagree, because without Zhao Hai, there would be no longer any Herculean Bulls today.

* * *

This time, they were planning to give some gifts to the Mastiffs. Zhao Hai initially didn’t want to come, but Wales forced him to go because he felt that it would be advantageous for Zhao Hao to be acquainted with the Mastiffs. The two could also do trades with each other, which would not only benefit Zhao Hai, but it would also benefit the Mastiffs.

The convoy slowly progressed, the Mastiff’s main camp isn’t too far away. The Mastiffs set a certain area close-by for the Herculean Bulls to live in, as well as to protect them. This made Wales very touched.

For the Herculean Bulls, the people that helped them in their present situation were true friends. This time’s disaster could be said to be a test. You could find who your real friends were during this time, differentiate friends from wolves.

It would take two days to travel from the Herculean Bull’s camp to the Mastiff’s camp. Wales didn’t hurry but proceeded slowly.

Before Zhao Hai arrived, Wales already informed the Mastiffs about the matter with the Radiant Church and the Fighting Bulls. Among the beastmen, the Mastiffs held a higher status than the Herculean Bulls, so when Wales told the news to the Mastiffs, the Mastiffs would pass the news on to the Lion and Tiger tribes, for a war clan to know about this matter, it would mean that there would be a huge purge that will happen in the prairie.

It could be said that for the beastmen, the most loathsome human organization would be the Radiant Church. They always suppress the beastmen, they talk to the beastmen as though they are inferior, and they also had many wars with the beastmen due to repeatedly provoking the inhabitants of the prairie.

What’s most important was that they had tried to control beastmen tribes before, thus making tribes experience internal strife. This made all the beastmen full of hatred for the Radiant Church.

When Wales received the news from Zhao Hai, that the Fighting Bulls were working with the Radiant Church, he knew that as long as the information becomes known, the Fighting Bulls would be finished.

Wales believed that when the Lion and Tiger tribes received the message from the Mastiffs, they would act and thus will help Wales reclaim their place.

However, Wales didn’t want to rely on the powers of the Warring clans to retrieve his position as the Royal Family. Because if that happens, the prestige of the Cow-headed race would plummet, which would make his rule on the entire race difficult in the future.

* * *

At night they pitched their tent in the plains. Wales did not make a huge fuss, he just ate some food and took a rest, he wants to save his energy, so all enjoyment would be put on hold.

Wales, for the sake of the war preparations, put strict measures on everything. Even on this trip, he only brought basic foods, there were no argali brought. Wales wanted the argali to be turned to war rations.

The next day after they woke up, they can already see the foraging teams of the Mastiffs. Beastmen foraging can be seen everywhere on the prairie. They need to prepare for winter, thus you can see them foraging for grass everywhere, not just clansmen, but there were also many slaves working.

You can say that this was the busiest time of the year for the prairie. The Mastiffs can also spot Wales’ group, one can see the fondness of the Mastiffs of the Bulls, many Mastiffs ran over to greet Wales.

This was also the first time that Zhao Hai saw the Mastiffs. The Mastiff clansmen were big, about 2.5 meters tall maximum. Although they were short compared to the Herculean Bulls, they weren’t that short in general, their bodies were sturdy, with a giant Mastiff head. On their faces and necks was a layer of fur, this made them look like mighty lions.

Their voices were deep, but it had an remarkable power of penetration that made people feel the strength on their voices, very domineering.

In fact, on the entire prairie, the Mastiff tribe is very well known. Even the large Wolf, Tiger, Bear, and Lion tribes wouldn’t carelessly provoke the Mastiffs. They are very strong, a number Mastiffs could hold wind against the same number of Lions, if against the Tigers, they would be slightly disadvantaged, if against the Wolves, they’d certainly win, if against the Bears, the Bears would also be defeated. Such prowess made the Mastiffs quite famous in the prairie.

However, the Mastiffs had so many clans in their race, and their strengths were not well, therefore the Mastiff can only rank a bit lower as a tribe. For the people in the beastmen prairie, the Mastiffs can be considered as a warring clan, but they can only hold onto half of this claim because of their unique situation, thus they could only be classified as a Semi-Warring clan, and only the Mastiffs hold this classification.[1]

* * *

I think this refers to dogs having numerous breeds. So, in a way, the weak breeds sort of dilute the overall power of the race.

Chapter 298: If We Won’t Succeed, Then We’ll Die With Honor

After the group went out of the tent, Buffon immediately spoke and laughed, “Wales, you ungrateful brat, you had such good liquor but you only took it out and gifted it to father. Although father likes to drink, he just doesn’t drink any ordinary wine. For him to say that the wine is good, it certainly wouldn’t be bad. Did little Hai really make it?”

Wales smiled and replied, “Of course he did, what do you think. Hehe, I remember someone saying that me giving uncle milk wine is a joke? How about not drinking for now?”

Buffon immediately played the fool, “Someone did? Who said it?” With his appearance, in addition to his huge dog head, nobody could really tell if he was joking or not.

Wales and the group laughed, then they immediately arranged for some wine to be delivered to Buzeer. They sent a large bag, about 50 jin of wine, after which they headed towards the area next to Buzeer’s. There were already several fires built, along with argali being roasted.

Zhao Hai can tell that Wales was very popular with the Mastiffs as they would greet him with smiles on their faces. Wales would also greet those people and would crack jokes from time to time.

And these Mastiffs, when regards to their fifth prince Buffon, didn’t have any attitude of reverence, as they would often tease Buffon. Zhao Hai could see that the Mastiffs liked Buffon, you can say that Buffon is very popular with his clansmen.

Several people arrived at the campfire, immediately a few drunkards encircled the fire. Obviously, they were freeloading, but Buffon didn’t catch them, he ridiculed a few of them, making some go home and get a few snacks.

The drunkards didn’t say anything, they ran back home and soon they came back with some beastmen specialties such as milk skin, cheese and so on.

Wales, however, had a large amount of vegetables brought out by Zhao Hai. This made the beastmen wide-eyed, one must know that vegetables were very rare in the prairie.

It was at this time that the argali had finished roasting, the milk wine that Zhao Hai brought started to be poured. The result didn’t even needed to wait for the mutton to be eaten up, the vegetables that Zhao Hai brought were obliterated, there were many drunks sprawled under the table, they have drank the wine too quickly, they have became drunk.

But what surprised Zhao Hai the most was Buffon, this guy was like a bottomless barrel. During his first drink, his face still had a hint of red, even his tongue had stretched out, but after a few cups he acutally recovered. Cup after cup of liquor went to his stomach, Zhao Hai went speechless.

Moreover, this guy didn’t even eat mutton, he seemed to become a herbivore, he plugged his mouth with vegetables enough for Wales to reprimand him. But he didn’t listen, he just went on his own way.

Zhao Hai was somewhat envious of Buffon. By this time, Zhao Hai already had a general view of the Mastiffs. They were the most simple type of beastman, they like the strong, they display their happiness and anger outwardly, they stick to their own way of doing things, never caring for other’s criticism. Such race is worth a merit.

The feast made Zhao Hai very happy because the Mastiffs were very accommodating. When Zhao Hai finished eating, they went to the tent prepared for them. The tent had a fire pit inside, they can come in and rest anytime.

With this heartfelt arrangement of the Mastiffs, Zhao Hai and Laura were very thankful, but they still went to the space to rest. This time, in order to help Wales, Zhao Hai’s supplies had been reduced significantly. There weren’t many argali left in his space, moreover, he also brought out a lot of grain, vegetables and fruit oil. Fortunately these products were produced by the space, otherwise he’d be helpless.

Now that things have gotten to this point, Zhao Hai couldn’t retreat. His investment was not small, if Wales were to fail, his losses would be massive.

However, Zhao Hai didn’t think about these anymore, all he wanted right now was to help Wales get his revenge. Zhao Hai didn’t know that the Beheading Blood Oath had slowly influenced him, but this effect isn’t any disadvantageous to Zhao Hai.

* * *

The next morning, after breakfast, Wales went to see Buzeer, Zhao Hai didn’t go with him. He knew that the reason Wales wanted to meet the chieftain this time was to discuss the matter of his counterattack.

This time’s meeting of Wales and Buzeer can be said to have a huge impact for the future of the Herculean Bulls. If the Mastiffs were to help, Wales would have a seventy percent chance of success, otherwise he’d only have fifty percent.

Of course, Wales wouldn’t ask for troops from Buzeer, instead, he wanted to request the deployment of the Mastiff’s 9th rank expert as help. This was what Wales and Buzeer had agreed on before, Wales was asking whether Buzeer could comply.

Whether it were humans or beastmen, the deployment of 9th rank experts were not a small matter. So even if Wales had a good relationship with Buzeer, the latter wouldn’t dare say that he had full assurance.

Zhao Hai and Yale sat quietly inside Wales’ tent, they were waiting for the final news. As long as the Mastiffs agreed, the only thing left is to plan for the attack.

Shortly before noon, Wales finally came back, as soon as his face entered the tent and saw Zhao Hai, he laughed, “They agreed, Uncle Buzeer agreed, their 9th rank elder also agreed. Little Hai, thank you, if you hadn’t brought in the information, I’m afraid their elder wouldn’t agree.

Zhao Hai and Yale cheered, they jumped, they knew that the only thing left is to grasp victory.

Seeing the group being happy, Buffon said, “This is a happy occasion, right? We should drink a few cups!”

The group turned around, they didn’t know when Buffon arrived in front of their tent. He grinned at them, Wales rushed out and grabbed Buffon, he laughed and said, “Drinking two cups isn’t enough, me must drink two pots!”

Buffon laughed as well, he did not fare well the previous evening, he had to be lifted to his tent. But he was really happy, because the wine was too tasty.

After a moment, Wales finally calmed down. He looked at Buffon, “Thank you, Buffon. I know you’ve done a lot of work this time, thank you.”

Buffon chuckled, “This is actually also in consideration for our Mastiff tribe, just think what would happen if you Herculean Bulls were to be replaced by the Fighting Bulls as the royal clan of the Cow-headed race. The Fighting Bulls had no connections nor relations to us. It would not be good for us to make them the royal clan of the Cow-headed race, thus we’ll certainly support you.”

Wales smiled faintly, of course he knew that Buffon was only saying this to comfort him. Regardless of who the royal clan of the Cow-headed race were, it wouldn’t actually matter to the Mastiffs. If you were to compare the overall strengths of the two races, the Mastiffs were many folds stronger than the Cows.

* * *

After taking care of this matter, Wales did not spend too long at the camp. The next day, they immediately set out early to return, this time they hurriedly traveled and at that night they arrived at the Herculean Bull camp.

Upon arriving, Wales immediately busied himself on planning for the counterattack. They also had more argali killed and made into rations.

Although Zhao Hai can follow them and provide grain at any time, it was impossible for beastmen to be unable to eat meat, especially during war, so they still prepared rations.

But this time, the way they prepared rations were not the same as before. Before when they prepared their rations, they would have the mutton air-dried, then it would be boiled during consumption. This time they didn’t air-dry their meat as they just did not have the time to do so. After they had the argali killed, they immediately boiled their meat, then gave them to Zhao Hai. Zhao Hai was a huge mobile warehouse, if they didn’t make use of him, then they’d be fools.

At the same time, Zhao Hai gave Ares[1] orders to make more milk wine. He is even prepared to use his fruit wine supply if Wales were to lack milk wine, it isn’t good to run out of wine.

For the beastmen, not being able to drink during winter is the same as taking their lives. And another reason Wales did such a large scale slaughter of argali to turn in rations is also to use their skin as supplies for warmth. The winter in Beastman Prairie is too cold, and this time, they didn’t have any other materials, Zhao Hai also had ran out of materials. So the only solution is to kill the argali and use their sheepskin to keep warm.

Zhao Hai did not oppose their decision. The beastmen had their own way of living. He cannot intrude upon their ways. Zhao Hai can only help Wales with the means he already had.

Zhao Hai actually thought of having Wales enter his space then transport them to an area not far from the Fighting Bulls and release them there. The Fighting Bulls certainly wouldn’t expect such sudden attack.

However, he gave up on this idea, he knew it wouldn’t work because his secret would be completely exposed. He’ll certainly be the target of all major forces on the continent, then he couldn’t show his face on the continent for the rest of his life.

Green didn’t oppose Zhao Hai’s decision to help Wales. This is because they thought that the prairie could become another escape route for them.

Currently in the Aksu Empire, they didn’t dare show themselves too much. And if one day other people would discover the situation of the Black Wastelands, they must find another place to settle down.[2]

Although there was the Carrion Swamp’s Flower City, it was a dead end. If they go there, they would have to live there for the entirety of their lives. And if Zhao Hai were to die, they certainly wouldn’t have any way of getting out. They could only wait for their deaths there, so that place was not the best place of retreat.

But in the Beastman Prairie is different, the relationship between humans and beastmen were generally not good. Even if Zhao Hai made a huge sin in human territory, the beastmen here can still accept him.

However, the beastmen were also not so dull. You must be accepted by the beastmen first to be able to settle here. Now that Zhao Hai is helping Wales, his integration to the prairie had already started. As long as he becomes an inseparable brother to Wales, the other beastmen would definitely accept him, thus providing Zhao Hai another burrow to escape to.

For one thing, in business terms, Zhao Hai was currently investing. If he were to succeed, he’s have returns of a hundredfold or even a thousandfold. If he were to fail, he’d only lose some resources that the space can just replace given some time. Looking at this, why wouldn’t he support Wales?

After obtaining Green’s approval, Zhao Hai can go all out in helping, other than making Wales aware of his space. As long as he has the ability to help Wales, Zhao Hai wouldn’t be stingy.

* * *

During this time, the Herculean Bulls’ camp was very busy. This time they are putting all of their manpower into preparing for their all out counterattack. If they were to fail this time, then the Herculean Bulls would vanish from the Beastman Prairie.

Zhao Hai looked at the people busying themselves in the camp. He can feel the resolve and vigor in the bodies of these people, even if they fail, then they’d have died for an honorable cause. Many times have Zhao Hai heard these words, but only few can only achieve it. But this time, Zhao Hai is convinced that the Herculean Bulls would achieve it. They have no other escape routes to come back to, they already killed all of their argali, effectively cutting off all paths to retreat.

Argali for the beastmen is equivalent to land for humans or a shop for merchants. But this time, the Herculean Bulls had killed all argali, just like a farmer selling off his own land. If they do not succeed, they’d have no possessions left in this world, they could only become slaves, or even just die.

Zhao Hai knew that such group is to be feared. In China there was a saying, ‘An army burning with righteous indignation is bound to win'[3]. Now, these warriors of the Herculean Bulls have become underdogs, they have lost their homeland which they have settled in for generations, they have lost their family members, lost their own pride, they had almost lost all hope. Now they place all of their strengths towards a single matter, which was revenge! Claim back all that belonged to them, or otherwise die!

Laura had also noted the actions of the Herculean Bulls. She did not say anything, she only followed Meg and helped whenever she could. In any case, they had already thrown in their lot with Wales, if they cannot help Wales win this war, then they could just get out of the prairie.

Half a month after Wales returned from the Mastiff camp, the prairie’s winter came. Overnight, the prairie plunged into winter with its piercing cold wind, the grass turned yellow in one night. This is also the first time Zhao Hai encountered the fierce prairie winter.

Laura didn’t dare exit their tent, it was too cold. Laura felt that as soon as they go out, they would immediately freeze to death.

However, Wales’ reaction was just normal. They immediately donned their winter clothes, it seemed like the winter had no effect on them.

* * *

That pleb from the large horned bull clan.

I think this refers to the fact that they managed to make the wastelands fertile again bit by bit.

āi bīng bì shèng

Chapter 299: Snowstorm

Seeing the tribe ready, Zhao Hai knew that the time for attack was coming. His heart was a little agitated, this will be the first time that he’ll witness a battle between several hundred thousand people, he cannot help but be excited.

Zhao Hai was also preparing, since he knew that the time for revenge is not far. While they were busy in their tent, the tent curtain was suddenly lifted, then Wales came in. The action caused a cold breeze to come in, Laura couldn’t help but shrink her head into her coat.

Wales saw Laura’s appearance, he laughed and said, “Laura, you have to get used to the temperature soon you know, because the coldest time of winter hasn’t arrived yet.”

Laura’s face paled, she shook her head and replied, “I’m afraid I cannot get used to it. If the coldest time came, I think I’ll just freeze to death.”

Wales cannot help but laugh, he turned to Zhao Hai and said, “Brother Zhao, come with me, the Supreme Elder wishes to see you.”

Zhao Hai stared blankly, he didn’t think that the Herculean Bulls’ Supreme Elder would want to see him. The Supreme Elder is a 9th rank expert, people on that power level cannot be met just casually.

Zhao Hai immediately responded, he nodded and replied, “Okay, then let’s go, I don’t want the elder to wait long.” Wales nodded, then walked outside with Zhao Hai.

Although Zhao Hai’s physique isn’t that good, he was not afraid of the cold. This may be related to the previous him who lived at the northern part of China. The winters in Northern China were also very cold, Zhao Hai was already used to this temperature.

They quickly arrived at Wales’ tent. Wales was not polite, he immediately raised the curtain and entered together with Zhao Hai.

Mendez and Yale were sitting inside the tent. However, they both look solemn, as though they were of the younger generation. Zhao Hai also noticed an additional person inside the tent.

Inside the tent sat an old man, plainly dressed, with a tall and mighty body. He looked extremely majestic sitting there as firm as a mountain. Although the old man’s eyes were closed, Zhao Hai felt that every movement inside the tent couldn’t escape the notice of this old man.

When they entered the tent, Wales was very careful, his footsteps were very formal as he slowly arrived at the side of the old man and said with a soft voice, “Elder, Zhao Hai has come.”

Zhao Hai went forward and performed a gesture toward the old man, “Zhao Hai has met the Supreme Elder.”

The old man slowly opened his eyes, he sized up Zhao Hai then faintly smiled, “Get up young man, I express my gratitude for giving me medicine.”

Zhao Hai hurriedly replied, “The elder is too polite, it was this Zhao Hai’s honor to be of help.”

The old man smiled at Zhao Hai, “You and Wales are blood oath brothers, therefore you are also part of the Herculean Bulls. I won’t be polite to you, young man, take note of this, since you are a member of our clan, remember that us Herculean Bulls have our own pride, and we’d rather die than let go of this pride. In order for the Herculean Bull flag to not fall into dust, you have to guard it with your life, can you do that?”

Zhao Hai stared blankly, he didn’t know where the old man was going with this, but he still replied with a serious tone, “I can, I can do it.”

The old man nodded, the turned and gave Wales a look. Wales bowed towards the elder, then went to the side and took out an already prepared war flag and placed it on Zhao Hai’s hands, “Zhao Hai, this War Flag is the Cow-headed Race’s King Flag, it’s a War Flag that can only be used by members of the Cow-headed Race’s Royal Clan, namely the Chieftain and the Crown Prince. Starting today, you are our Herculean Bull’s Crown Prince.”

Zhao Hai became stunned, he had not thought that when Wales went to fetch him today, he would be given a war flag, and a King’s flag at that. This King’s flag didn’t only represent the approval of the Herculean Bulls, but similarly, it also represented a special status in the Prairie, which was the status of being the Herculean Bull’s Crown Prince.

And in this special time, this King’s flag represents a huge responsibility for the upcoming counterattack of the Herculean Bulls. Giving Zhao Hai this War Flag represents their confidence in him and their success.

Zhao Hai received the War Flag solemnly, he looked at Wales and said, “Be relieved Brother, rest assured knowing that I won’t shame the Herculean Bulls.”

Wales patted Zhao Hai’s shoulder, “Little Hai, I wanted to wait after we have recaptured everything before handing you this War Flag. However, the Supreme Elder believed that such arrangement would be unfair to you. Your contribution to the Herculean Bull tribe had been astronomical, we can even say that the counterattack’s merit belongs to you. So we gave this War Flag to you before the battle to let you know that the Herculean Bulls recognize your efforts, so you must treasure this flag.”

Zhao Hai nodded seriously then said, “Don’t worry brother, I’ll treasure this flag as if its my own life.”

At this time, the Supreme Elder talked, “Good, make sure to remember your own words Little Hai, we will move after the first wave of snow, prepare yourself well.” After which he flashed and disappeared.

* * *

After setting the day for the attack, Wales immediately sent a letter to notify the Mastiffs, then they quietly waited.

The weather on the prairie changes constantly, but the beastmen had lived on this place for many years, so they had their own means of forecasting the weather. On the day Zhao Hai received the King’s War Flag, Wales also told Zhao Hai that an elder from the tribe had predicted that the first batch of snow to arrive in ten days would be the biggest snowstorm that had been seen for the past 10 years.

Zhao Hai didn’t know how strong a snowstorm never before seen in ten years is, but he knows that this will bring no small inconvenience to their attack. However, on the other hand, it is also advantageous because nobody would also think that someone would march into war during this kind of weather.

Ten days was not that long, but to people who were waiting, these ten days seemed like ten years. For this war, the Herculean Bulls had bet their all. While waiting, they’d go sharpen their axes and take care of their mounts. Also at this time, Wales had prohibited his clansmen from drinking liquor, no one was allowed to drink.

Not allowing beastmen to drink during winter is like taking their lives. But the Herculean Bulls didn’t oppose this time and just accepted the order. Since they couldn’t drink, they could only exercise in this cold weather, some even went outside and practice their martial skills there.

This is also the first time that Zhao Hai saw the beastman’s soul techniques. When using their soul techniques, a projection of a beast would appear and slowly merge with their body and after which their strengths would increase. Looking at this, Zhao Hai suddenly had a chill, he felt that the process looks very much like being possessed by a soul, giving him a feeling of gloom.

* * *

To everyone’s disappointment, after ten days had passed and the sky was overcast, snow didn’t fall down, making Wales anxious.

At this time, the forecasting elder went to see Wales, he told Wales that the weather had undergone some changes. This time they wouldn’t encounter a snowstorm that can only be seen once every ten years, but on that can only be seen once in fifty years. It would be best for the camp to group up immediately, otherwise their tents would be blown away by the snowstorm.

Although the elder’s previous forecast didn’t hit right on the spot, Wales still decided to trust the elder. He made his clansmen group up the tents, then reinforce them, as well as building a few more additional tents to have their mounts stay in.

This time the elder’s predictions were not wrong. While they were reinforcing their tents, large swathes of snow came blowing down like flying knives.

Fortunately, the Herculean Bulls were known for their strength. After deploying all of their manpower, they managed to finish their reinforcements despite the buffeting snow. They had also grouped up all of their tents, making the place much warmer.

Naturally, Wales’ and Zhao Hai’s tent were at the very center of the camp so that they couldn’t be directly affected by the cold, they were even warmer than before.

When the snowstorm came, Zhao Hai and Laura came to know how fierce a once in fifty year snowstorm actually was, for a straight 10 days, day and night it fiercely stormed. The Herculean Bulls had to send people out to clear the snow on top of the tents, they had to be tied by a rope while working because otherwise they’d be swept up by the fierce storm and die.

Laura looked at the busy beastmen and sighed, “In the face of such a storm, the power of men is truly very weak.”

Its true, in front of such a snowstorm, the power of men was really insignificant. Even  the well-known strength of the Herculean Bulls can only bow down to the power of nature, nature’s might is really great.

After ten days, the sky finally cleared and the sun finally came out. Although it was still very cold in the prairie, the fearful snowstorm had finally passed, the entire camp couldn’t help but cheer.

Laura also couldn’t help but cheer, this was a contest between man and nature, and fortunately, man had managed to win. But this also came with a price, seeing the final tally, there were 123 Herculean Bulls[1] who froze to death. Although the number was small compared to the full five hundred thousand population, it was still very sad.

Although the snowstorm had already passed, Wales couldn’t charge immediately because the area around the tents were filled with snow that was even higher than the tents. They first need to clear out the snow before they could move.

But despite this, the camp still exploded with enthusiasm and soon the snow had been cleared enough for them to pass through.

* * *

When you can’t be arsed to think of a number XD

Chapter 300: Difficulty Hurrying Along

A large group walked slowly on the endless, snow-covered prairie. Looking at the scene, it was like they were lice walking on a bald person’s head.

At this time, there was nobody else on the plains. Prairie winter was terrible; cold winds, snowstorms, and wolf packs are the most fearful things currently on the prairie.

Beastmen rarely leave their camps during winter, even more so a group of them. The group numbered about five hundred thousand beastmen. Although the snowy lands were full of perils, the group didn’t stop moving along.

If you look at it closely, these group of beastmen were not only the young and strong, there were also many elderly, children, and women present, it was like an entire tribe was moving.

The group was precisely the Herculean Bull tribe. On this expedition, not only did the young and strong go, everybody went.

There was a saying in the prairie, ‘Beastmen were long lasting’, so long as they are still breathing, they’re still dangerous. This fully explained the fighting strength of the Beastmen, some elderly beastmen were sometimes more difficult to deal with than the younger ones, this was because although their strength wasn’t as great as before, they still had experience that the young ones didn’t have.

The Herculean Bull women were also cannot be dealt with easily. Although they did not study beastmen soul techniques, they were still Herculean Bulls in the end with their innate divine strength. A fully mature female Herculean Bull would have strength comparable to a human 4th rank warrior, this made the Herculean Bulls quite fearsome among the beastmen.

The Herculean Bulls had to choice but go all out, currently, there were no child too young nor an elder too old, all of them would be unable to escape the Fighting Bulls, they can only become slaves. Under this circumstance, Wales decided to have everyone march together and fight it out with the entire clan, otherwise the clan would rather die.

Zhao Hai followed the group, but he was inside his carriage instead of riding a mount outside like other people. Their carriage was covered with thick sheepskin since Laura couldn’t handle the cold.

In fact, while inside the carriage and behind shut doors, Zhao Hai and the group went inside the space, so they didn’t suffer much. Meg immediately went to the villa’s kitchen to heat up some tea and brought it in the living room.

Laura drank her cup of hot tea, making her feel better. Laura put her cup down and sighed, “Being inside the space is good, I think I’ll freeze to death outside.”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “Is it too freezing cold? I feel pretty fine, not really feeling anything.”

Laura looked at Zhao Hai, “Brother Hai, didn’t you always live in the imperial capital? You should be like me who can’t handle the cold, but why aren’t you a least bit affected?”

Zhao Hai faintly smiled, “You forget, I’m a mage, so I’m quite resistant to cold, hehe.”

In fact, this is only but one reason why Zhao Hai can take cold compared to Laura. But Laura was already convinced of this reason, she nodded “That’s good, I’m afraid of you becoming sick, it’ll be quite troublesome.”

Zhao Hai smiled and replied, “Don’t worry, my body is very healthy now that I drink life liquid everyday, if I were to get sick, I’m afraid all other people could only be worse.”

While Zhao Hai and the others were chatting and laughing inside the space, Wales and the others outside weren’t faring very well. Their bodies were fully wrapped with sheepskin, even their mounts were covered. On their hands were alcohol bags, the necks of the bags were exposed and if the beastmen were to feel too cold, they would chug some liquor into their stomachs to raise their body temperature, so that they could feel a little bit better.

Marching during winter was a great trial for beastmen, it required endurance and the nerves to survive the task. Fortunately Wales had prepared heavily beforehand, otherwise all of them would be long dead.

In complete contrast to the prairie’s cold weather, Iron Mountain Fort’s weather was far from cold, the people were even wearing unpadded clothes. Since it was currently winter in the prairie, Zhao Hai went to Iron Mountain fort. Compared to the prairie, Iron Mountain Fort was completely different, the grass was green here, as though the two places were from two different worlds.

Zhao Hai knew why the weather in Iron Mountain Fort was such. Firstly, because it was surrounded by the Iron Mountains, winter still hadn’t arrived here. Secondly, its because Cai’er managed to maintain the temperature, therefore place was still relatively warm.

Since Iron Mountain Fort was fine, Zhao Hai didn’t worry about it anymore, and instead focused his mind on the prairie helping Wales.

After a day’s journey, night came, Wales had everyone stop, make their shelters, and prepare for resting. They didn’t worry about dinner since they already had steaming hot mutton to eat.

This was also Zhao Hai’s idea, he told Wales to cook the mutton then Zhao Hai would store them while still warm. As long as the food was stored inside the space, it would retain its properties when taken out again.

Upon hearing what Zhao Hai said, Wales immediately changed the way they prepared rations. After they boiled the mutton, they immediately gave it to Zhao Hai. In this matter, when the time for eating came, they’ll have hot and delicious mutton which, in this winter weather, made the people happy.

After constructing their tents, Zhao Hai immediately went to give everyone their food. He was quite busy, imagine catering for five hundred thousand people, its not an easy task.

However, Zhao Hai didn’t complain since he knew that these beastmen just marched the whole day while being cold and hungry. Because of this, Zhao Hai didn’t make them leave their tents and instead he just delivered the food himself.[1]

Now that they were going for battle, the clan was not separated according to their families, but instead they were divided by gender. Each tent would have 20 people each and had separate tents for men and women.

In order to avoid accidents, there were no fires inside the tents, so they had to sleep on their sheepskins. But after eating the warm mutton and drinking the hot soup, they felt much better.

When Zhao Hai was sending mutton and soup to the people, he also had the mounts be given their fodder. This was also prepared by Wales before and had Zhao Hai store them in the space.[2]

The Herculean Bulls had developed an extreme fondness for Zhao Hao, before they went to battle, they already experienced this treatment. They knew that if Zhao Hai was present, the logistical problems was solved.

While all of these was happening, Wales was right beside Zhao Hai. He often asked his clansmen how they were. Such actions moved his clansmen, you can say that Wales had already captured the hearts of all his clansmen.

* * *

Because they had to hurry during the daytime, they could only have two meals each day, one in the morning and one in the night. They used almost all the time during daytime to travel, almost nobody had time so dismount.

This method of hurrying along, which was very taxing for anyone, made Zhao Hai view the tenacity of the beastmen.

* * *

After given the Herculean Bulls their meals, Zhao Hai and the group gathered inside Wales’ tent since they still hadn’t eaten. They ate the same as the other Herculean Bulls, mutton and soup.

Wales drank some soup and let out a long breath, “Little Hai, we are very happy ah. To be so relaxed before the battle.”

Kony smiled and said, “It it isn’t only that, even before, when we go to battles during summertime it isn’t as comfortable as this time.”

But at this time, Yale knit his eyebrows as he said, “Currently our issue is that the time for travels are just too small. In the morning we collect our tents, and at the evening we set them up, thus there wouldn’t be enough time for travelling. Now adding the occasional snowfalls, the distance that we would travel is too short.”

Wales put down his bowl and also frowned, he had no solution for this matter. In the summer, they can afford to not pitch their tents, just lie down using their sheepskin on the grass at nights. But in the winter it won’t work since one would freeze to death.

Zhao Hai looked at Wales’ expression and said, “Brother, how about this, tomorrow don’t worry about deconstructing the tents, just proceed along. I’ll go fetch the tents and store them on my space, and at night I’ll just take it out, what do you think?”

Wales replied, “How would you dismantle the tent?”

Zhao Hai faintly smiled, “They don’t need to be demolished, I’ll just store them as they were, isn’t that fine?” In fact, Zhao Hai’s tent was already pitched inside the space, so when the time for resting arrived, he’ll just take it out while Wales would still pitch his.

But now that it seems that pitching and unpitching a tent was a waste of time, so Zhao Hai decided to store them as a whole.

Wales was surprised, “Can you store them all?”

Zhao Hai shook his head, “I’m not sure, if we can store them then that’ll be best so we can save a lot of time. We still need to try.”

Wales nodded, “Very well, let’s try that, that would be the best, then we would have more time to move along.”

Mendez said, “According to our present progress, we should arrive at the old camp in about half a month or so. Little Hai, have you sent some blood hawks to monitor the Fighting Bulls that are in the old camp?”

Zhao Hai nodded, “Be relieved, Sixth Brother, they were still there at this time, it’s seems that they didn’t leave the camp for the winter.”

Wales’ eyes lit up with a cold gaze, “That is good, a chance of revenge is finally here!”

* * *

Now that’s just impossible, how long would it take?!

They didn’t know about the space, per se. They only know that Zhao Hai had space items.

Chapter 301: Captives

Zhao Hai was sitting inside a tent drinking some mutton soup and eating some mutton. This time, they weren’t hurrying along anymore since they just arrived at an area not far away from Herculean Bull’s old camp.

Wales drunk an entire bowl of soup and ate a piece of mutton, after feeling nourished he turned to Zhao Hai and asked, “Little Hai, are you sure that the Fighting Bulls didn’t see us?”

Zhao Hai nodded, “Don’t worry brother, the Fighting Bulls had not come out of the camp after all this time, so it’ll be impossible for them to spot us. But brother needs to prepare your heart, the Fighting Bulls hadn’t treated you clansmen properly.” Zhao Hai stopped talking at this point.

Wales looked at Zhao Hai, “Little Hai, what’s it like there?”

Zhao Hai sighed, “They didn’t provide any tents for your clansmen, they also didn’t give them some padded clothing, and they were only fed once every few days . Of the three hundred thousand captured Herculean Bulls, two hundred thousand remain.”

Wales’ eyes almost fell from their sockets, he stared blankly, one could see veins bulging on his head. Zhao Hai hurriedly added, “Big Brother, don’t be angry, we can save your people soon.”

Wales took deep breaths and closed his eyes, it took a while for him to calm down. He turned to Zhao Hai, “Right, we can take revenge soon. Brother Hai, I want to thank you. Because of you all of these became possible.”

Zhao Hai smiled and said, “Big Brother is too polite, I’m the Herculean Bull’s Crown Prince, isn’t this what I should be doing? Brother, currently, the clansmen are grouped together, the elderly are placed at the outer parts while the women and children are in the middle, warming each other up by talking a walk from time to time. However, there were no Fighting Bulls monitoring them, so I can go there ahead and supply them some food, if there are weapons, I could also deliver it to them so that when we launch our attack, they may be able to help out.”

Wales shook his head, “We can give them food, but not weapons. They suffered for a long time, their bodies have long since grew weak. If we let them fight, they may just die in vain.”

At this time, Mendez interjected while shaking his head, “Brother Seven, I agree with Little Hai’s words. We should give them weapons, not only can they provide help in killing the enemy, they could also use the weapons as a means of self defense. If we are battling, what if the Fighting Bulls were to send some people to kill them? Thus we should provide them weapons.”

Yale also nodded, “I also agree that we should give them weapons, but we can’t give them weapons that are too large, hatchets would be good, as they are not too conspicuous. Right, Wales did the Supreme Elder say when we’ll begin?”

Wales replied with a serious tone, “The day after tomorrow. We cannot wait for too long, the earlier the better.”

Yale nodded and said, “At night?”

Wales nodded, “Yes, a surprise attack at night.”

Yale asked again, “Did the Mastiff elder arrive? How many are there?”

Wales said, “They arrived, two came. I actually didn’t hope that the Mastiffs would send their three elders, but sending two is certainly a surprise.”

Yale added, “Good, let everyone take a rest tomorrow and prepare for the attack the day after tomorrow.” They want to attack the Fighting Bulls with the element of surprise. So while they were moving, they were very careful to not come across any other tribes along the way, minimizing the advantages that the Fighting Bulls could acquire.

What they’re planning was the right thing to do, but moving around with five hundred thousand people while remaining undetected was challenging. Fortunately, beastmen tend to remain inside their camps during winter, so Zhao Hai lent Wales some hawks to survey the area ahead to spot some tents and then avoided those areas.

This aid, along with his previous deeds, were taken by all the Herculean Bulls at heart. Now they were convinced that without Zhao Hai, their counterattack wouldn’t be possible. This opportunity was given to them by Zhao Hai, thus the Herculean Bulls have been very respectful to him.

In the current Herculean Bull clan, even though Zhao Hai wasn’t a beastman, his position wasn’t any lower than elder Kony. Now, every time Zhao delivered them food, no matter old or young, they would give Zhao Hai their salutes, as a sign of their innermost gratitude.

At this point, Zhao Hai told Wales, “Big Brother, it would be better if you send a clan representative with me. Otherwise, since the other clansmen do not know of me, they may make a fuss, and the Fighting Bulls might be alerted.”

Wales knew that Zhao Hai was about to give his captured clansmen some food. He nodded and replied, “Right, Uncle Kony, please go together with Little Hai. I’ll have the hatchets prepared right now.”

Kony didn’t oppose, he nodded and replied, “Good, when it comes to familiarity with the other clansmen, I’m at the advantage so it’s right that I come.”

At this time, Mendez exited the tent to fetch the hatchets. He got a few of them, enough for a person to wield one each. Although these hatchets weren’t large, in the hand of the Herculean Bulls they would be equally terrifying.

Before long, all of the hatchets were collected and placed in the middle of the camp. Zhao Hai looked at Wales and said, “Well, Brother, I’ll go now.” After having said that, the middle of the camp was immediately covered in a black fog taking Zhao Hai and Kony along. When the black fog disappeared, the two also vanished from the camp.

When the two appeared, they were already not far from the Fighting Bulls encampment, it was a huge camp. To be honest, this was actually the Herculean Bull’s old camp, but now it was acquired by the Fighting Bulls.

Kony can finally see the situation outside now that they were so close from the camp. Kony’s eyes gave of a bit of light but Zhao Hai didn’t comment on it. They were again wrapped by the black fog and reappeared right beside a ragged group. These people wore expressionless faces and were moving constantly. They were bundled together with almost having no gap between them.

This time, Zhao Hai used Earth Magic to elevate the place that they were in. Now they were able to see the whole group of Herculean Bull captives.

The Herculean Bull captives didn’t have anything to warm themselves up. So in order to survive the freezing winter, they crowded together to share warmth and kept moving around like a group of penguins. The person outside would be switched from time to time by someone from the inside so that nobody would freeze to death quickly.

Although their methods did work, not everyone could survive the freezing cold and snowstorms. Of the three hundred thousand captives, only less than two hundred thousand remain.

Many of those who died were the elderly, in order to save the Herculean Bull children, they placed the children in the middle of the group and stood outside to block off the cold winds. If the Fighting Bulls were to send some food, the children would be the first to eat. Because of the cold and hunger, many people died as a consequence.

When Kony saw his clansmen, he grit his teeth almost to the point of crushing them. Then he patted the side of a clansman’s face since they didn’t manage to notice him, and with his old voice he said, “Carrik, Carrik, I’m Kony, can you still recognize me?”

The Herculean Bull woke up and started to turn his eyes. He glanced at Kony and seemed to not see him. He closed his eyes again before he opened them up quickly, as though in disbelief, the clansman looked around and then said with a lowered voice, “Elder, why are you here? Were you also caught?”

Due to the small commotion, the surrounding people came to notice the new arrivals. But since all were elderly Herculean Bulls, some of them knew that Kony was able to escape and was thus surprised to see him here. However, since they were experienced, they didn’t make any loud noises and seemed to continue on with what they’re doing while engulfing Kony and Zhao Hai towards the middle of the group.

Kony looked at Carrik and shook his head, his eyes were tearful, “This old man has made you suffer, but your suffering will soon be over. The Seventh Prince Wales has managed to return to the clan and became the new chieftain. He took us back here to seek vengeance, you only need to wait for two days. In two days, we will attack the Fighting Bull clan. This is the chieftain’s Beheading Blood Oath Brother and also our tribes Crown Prince Zhao Hai. He is also a formidable magician and today he brought us here to deliver you food and weapons. You only need to endure for two more days.”

Carrik looked excitedly at Kony, his tears were flowing down. It was a very difficult time for them, they were waiting for this day and it finally arrived.

At this time, the sky had already turned dark, and the Fighting Bull camp was very quiet, they seemed to have gone to bed. In such a weather, even Polar Bears and Giant Tigers who loved fighting would stay inside their camp to rest.[1]

They didn’t fear that the Herculean Bulls would escape. In such a weather, if the Herculean Bulls were to try to escape without any warm clothes, then they would definitely freeze in the prairie. Thus they didn’t send anyone to monitor the captives, but only sent someone look out for their argali and grain.

Fortunately, Carrik and the others were veterans who had fought many battles. Although they were old and captured, they immediately calmed down, which was a skill they had acquired. Thus, the group resumed their tranquility after only a few moments as though there weren’t anything new happening.

Kony looked at their calmness and then turned his head to Carrik, “Pass on the information that we have come back, so that they do not make a ruckus, act as though nothing’s going on”

Carrik nodded, immediately conveyed the message to the people around and pass it on. The message was simple, Elder Kony has returned, the other clansmen has returned.

This information spread like a ripple as though a pebble had disturbed the pond. The message spread and then Zhao Hai also began giving out mutton and mutton soup. He didn’t give them much, only half a jin of lamb as well as a bowl of soup.

They did not dare speak too loudly, afraid that the Fighting Bulls might hear. Currently, Carrik didn’t go with the other clansmen, but followed Kony and Zhao Hai at the side to help the clansmen.

Zhao Hai started with the elderly first, some of these elderly were almost beyond saving, they need food the most.

Carrik also came to know Zhao Hai’s magic, he saw that in Zhao Hai’s hand a bowl of hot soup and some warm mutton would suddenly appear. When he looked at Zhao Hai, he seemed to see the Beast God.

Zhao Hai didn’t give their weapons immediately, he was afraid of being found out by the Fighting Bulls. He only gave them some food. Then, in between the cover of Carrik and the others, they headed towards the center of the group where the women and children were and gave them some food.

Zhao Hai found out that giving food this time was more difficult. Back at the main camp, he only needed to send food to each tent, but this time he needed to deliver them one by one to the hands of the people.

Zhao Hai was busy until dawn. Although it was winter, Zhao Hai and Kony were sweating. When the morning came, all of the people had already drank hot soup and ate warm mutton. Kony then told Carrik about their means of transfer and then vanished from the group with Zhao Hai.

Although Carrik still had to endure the cold winds here, they now have a burning hope in their hearts. If winter comes, can spring be far behind?[2]

When Zhao Hai and Kony returned to the main camp, Wales still had not rested and had been waiting for them. Looking at their unsightly complexion, Wales decided to walk to them instead.

Zhao Hai was already tired and didn’t have the energy to say a few words, he just waved his hand and went to the side to lie down. Kony fared better than Zhao Hai since he had a beastman’s stamina, and also he didn’t personally hand out the food one by one to the clansmen back then. Kony nodded at Wales and said, “The food has been given, but Little Hai didn’t give them the weapons in fear of it being discovered. He decided to give the weapons tomorrow as we gave the evening meal, I also agreed with this.”

Wales nodded and asked, “How were the clansmen?”

Kony replied, “There were less than two hundred thousand people left. Calculating the combat potential with the elderly and the women, they would amount to one hundred and fifty thousand which is still a formidable force. The rest have died of freezing or starvation and is now lying down on the prairie.”

Wales, angrily snorted, “Fighting Bulls, I’ll certainly make you into slaves for generations.”

At this time the sound of snoring could be heard. Wales turned to look at where it came from, but realized that it was just Zhao Hai, tired and has fallen asleep.

* * *

[1] I just want to state that if an animal’s name is capitalized, then its referring to the beastman version of that animal.

[2] If winter is approaching and everything is dying, then there is a spring season ahead.

Chapter 302: Time for Revenge

Wales looked at Zhao Hai sleeping soundly, he sighed and turned to Mendez, “Sixth Brother, please return Little Hai to his tent, have Laura take care of him. Don’t disturb him today.”

Mendez asked, “But what about breakfast?”

Wales sighed and said, “Just tell everyone to endure it today. Little Hai is too tired, these days he’s the busiest person out of all of us.”

Mendez didn’t say anymore, he picked Zhao Hai up and went outside, soon he arrived at Zhao Hai’s tent and had Laura receive Zhao Hai.

Laura looked at Zhao Hai’s state and thought that he was injured. She put Zhao Hai on the ground hastily and then whispered with a low voice, “Cai’er, Cai’er, quickly come out.”

Cai’er’s form appeared, Laura immediately asked, “Cai’er, what’s all this about? What happened to Elder Brother Hai?”

Cai’er looked at Zhao Hai and said, “He’s alright, just resting. He only needs to drink water from the space to get well.” After saying this, a small vine appeared in front of Zhao Hai’s mouth, it reached towards the mouth’s opening and then water from the space smoothly rolled off the vine into Zhao Hai’s mouth.

After drinking a mouthful, Zhao Hai opened his eyes. He saw Laura and couldn’t help but be surprised, he touched his head and asked, “I fell asleep?”

Laura’s heart ached when looking at Zhao Hai, she looked at him and said, “Brother Hai, why do you try so hard? You need to be careful, we don’t know what we’d do if you get sick.”

Zhao Hai faintly smiled, “I’m alright, its nothing, I’ll only be busy for another two days. In a moment, we’ll go give them breakfast. You did not see those who were captured by the Fighting Bulls, of the three hundred thousand, a hundred thousand died. Now only less than two hundred thousand Herculean Bull captives were left, they were all dressed in unpadded clothes while having little to no food and drink. Those Fighting Bulls were too vicious.”

While speaking of this, Zhao Hai’s complexion was bad. He saw the slaves on West Wonder King’s camp as well as various slaves all throughout the prairie, but this was the first time he saw that slaves were treated like this. It was obvious that the people involved wanted the Herculean Bulls to die out completely.

This was the first time that Laura has heard of this incident since Zhao Hai never told them before. Now that she heard this information, she couldn’t help but look shocked at Zhao Hai.

Laura had also seen beastmen slaves, she also saw Human slaves in the past, but the way the Fighting Bulls treated their slaves was a first for Laura.

Although the humans did not treat their slaves that well, they didn’t make their slaves die at will. After all, the slaves were also their property, and nobody is willing to just throw away their properties.

The beastmen slaves were actually treated better compared to human slaves, therefore Laura didn’t expect the Fighting Bulls to treat the Herculean Bull captives this way, they were too cruel.

Zhao Hai sighed, “I now wholeheartedly support Brother Wales’s revenge, the Fighting Bulls were really too much. Forget it, let’s not talk about this anymore. I still have to serve breakfast, I’ll take a rest after then.”

Laura nodded, this was the first time that she experienced the brutality of wars in the prairie, a defeated tribe would have zero dignity left, they may even get exterminated.

* * *

Wales didn’t think that Zhao Hai would go out to serve breakfast. After breakfast, everyone returned to their tents, Wales told Zhao Hai, “Little Hai, why didn’t you rest for a little more? You didn’t need to hurry along, not being able to eat breakfast isn’t a big deal.”

Zhao Hai just faintly smiled. “Well, I can rest later, the group still needs to get full, its no big deal, no need to say anything more. Right, I’ll go sleep now, don’t look for me today.”

Wales nodded, Zhao Hai then returned to his tent. Wales looked at Zhao Hai’s departing back and muttered to himself, “Feel relieved Little Hai, Elder Brother will make sure to succeed.”

* * *

When the sky was turning dark, Zhao Hai went out of the space, he had already rested well. But what Zhao Hai didn’t know was, while he was sleeping, the whole camp was very quiet.

In the evening, Zhao Hai gave the clansmen their dinner then went to the captives along with Kony. He gave out food as well as weapons to the captured Herculean Bulls. This was in preparation for tomorrow, where the attack would commence in the evening.

Zhao Hai and Kony told them the news of the attack tomorrow evening, advising them to get away from the camp before that time.

The night passed as the food was distributed, then Zhao Hai returned to the camp and gave the other group their breakfast, after which he rested.[1]

What Kony didn’t know, was that when Zhao Hai gave food to the captives, he also included some life liquid to the soup given, this would help the recoveries of these people.

Because they needed to act tonight, instead of giving the food then, the clansmen were given an extra portion of mutton while they stayed and waited for the evening so that they wouldn’t get hungry.

During daytime, the camp was quiet, they wanted Zhao Hai to have a proper rest. They were also afraid of making loud noises since it could alert the Fighting Bulls, fortunately, there were no reactions from the Fighting Bulls.

Perhaps in the entire prairie, only crazed people like the Herculean Bulls would take revenge at this time, nobody else would wage war in such terrible weather.

As the sky was slowly turning dark, the people at the Herculean Bull camp began to act. They stood quietly outside along with their mounts. Everyone was calmly watching Wales standing in the middle.

Wales looked at the moon up above the sky, after a few moments he turned to look at his clansmen, “My people, the time for revenge has come.” After saying that, he dismounted from his mount and slowly walked towards the Herculean Bull’ sold camp.

All the other Herculean Bulls also dismounted from their mounts. They remained silent, they didn’t move too fast, afraid of making noise and alerting the Fighting Bulls. But in their eyes was a fierce gaze, they tightly clutched their own weapons as they bit their teeth together. The expression on their faces were indifferent, like sold rocks.

Zhao Hai and Laura were sitting inside Xenomorph’s body, Yale was also inside and although table inside had tea, Yale didn’t have the thought to drink right now. He had been paying attention to the camp’s situation.[2]

The Herculean Bulls were also familiar with the camp’s surrounding terrain. They know every nook and cranny here because for thousands of years, they had resided here, they were born here, and would die here. But they never thought that one day they would be driven out from this place, and needed to fight to take it back.

The army very slowly approached the Fighting Bull encampment because of the snow on the ground, they also managed to sneak up because of this. Wales was at the front, followed by the young warriors of the clan then the elders, the women, and finally the children.

Zhao Hai’s undead army was also beside the group and was commanded by him alone as Wales couldn’t command the undead.

As the camp was getting closer and closer, Wales movements became even more careful. Just about 500 meter away from the camp, Wales suddenly issued a warcry and rode his mount, then he rushed towards the camp. The others also rode their mounts and followed Wales on his charge.

They held their axes on one hand and a lit torch in the other. When they charged towards the camp, the place they chose to charge through was right at the center, where a huge tent was erected. One must know that the when it comes to understanding this camp, the Herculean Bulls were much more adept that the Fighting Bulls.

The Fighting Bulls were obviously alarmed, and the whole camp fell into panic. The Fighting Bulls didn’t imagine that the Herculean Bulls would do their counterattack at this time. One must know that the Herculean Bull camp was just captured about two months ago, and the Fighting Bulls also pillaged the Herculean Bulls of all their commodities. They were thinking that the Herculean Bulls would be too preoccupied of surviving the winter and didn’t think of their counterattack. This made the Fighting Bulls lower their guard, which gave Wales a huge advantage.

Wales’, however, was very ready for this attack, they had brought rope, a flare, and their weapon. Two Herculean Bulls would collapse the tent by pulling it with ropes, and as the inhabitants ran out, what waited for them were axes.

In the entire camp, flames were rising from all directions. The scene almost resembled the day of Judgement. Zhao Hai didn’t participate in the attack, he was at the side observing. He knew that at this time, Wales’ wouldn’t want him to intervene, their enemies must only be dealt with by themselves.

At this time, there were two roars that can be heard inside the camp. Zhao Hai’s face changed since he can hear that this roar can only be made by 9th rank experts.

This time, not far from the camp came a loud roar which was made by a 9th rank expert, a flare went up and Zhao Hai saw two bodies flying from the camp, one was a tall and large figure while the other one was noticeably smaller.

The former was the 9th rank expert of the Fighting Bull clan, while the latter was obviously a human 9th rank expert. Zhao Hai didn’t expect that the Human expert actually didn’t leave the Fighting Bull camp. It seems like there were errors from the information he got from Bell.

However, Zhao Hai didn’t worry much since in addition to the Herculean Bull’s 9th rank Supreme Elder, they had also invited two 9th rank experts from the Mastiffs to help them deal with the Fighting Bulls.

A 3 versus 2, this scenario was very advantageous for the Herculean Bulls.

* * *

[1] Fukin hell, the sheer number. Just imagine, Jesus only fed five thousand.

[2] Big croc thing